<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<metadata>
    <owner>videl</owner>
    <noteworthy>
        <case name="Godiva Hair" min="6" max="6">
            <description>Videl removed her bra but positioned her twin tails to cover her nipples</description>
            <trigger tag="stripped">
                <state img="stripped.png">Okay fine, get it out of your systems. Anyone who looks longer than 5 seconds is going to get 5 minutes worth of pain! Not like you can see much anyway... Heh.</state>
                <state img="stripped.png">Twin tails for the win! Hmph, and he told me I should cut my hair short...</state>
                <state img="stripped.png">This doesn't mean anything, okay? I don't know the meaning of the word defeat! This is totally in accordance with the rules by the way.</state>
                <state img="stripped.png">They're just breasts, so what? Every girl has them... speaking of which, go look at theirs!</state>
                <state img="stripped.png">So what do you think of my back up plan? You've always gotta keep a trick up your sleeve in a fight, and poker is no different!</state>
                <state img="stripped.png">Come on, did you realy think it would be that easy?</state>
                <state img="stripped.png">I guess I'm a pretty big tease aren't I? You're going to have to fight me for awhile longer now.</state>
                <state img="stripped.png">You guys didn't look while I took my bra off right? This kind of takes time and a bit of precision you know.</state>
                <state img="stripped.png">So, do you like them? What's that? You can't see them? Oh that's too bad...</state>
            </trigger>
        </case>
        <case name="Squirter" min="9" max="9">
            <description>Videl squirted significantly when cumming</description>
            <trigger tag="finished_masturbating">
                <state img="finished.png">Oh no, you're all staring at me... I made a mess, didn't I?</state>
                <state img="finished.png">I don't even know what to think right now...</state>
                <state img="finished.png">Ah... S-so can I put my clothes back on now? You know what, forget it.</state>
                <state img="finished.png">After that I guess I might as well just stay naked...</state>
                <state img="angry.png">I can't believe you guys saw that...</state>
                <state img="sad.png">It's everywhere, isn't it?</state>
                <state img="flying.png">Maybe I shouldn't have been flying if that was going to happen...</state>
                <state img="interested.png">Finally over... this has been a weird day...</state>
            </trigger>
        </case>
    </noteworthy>
    <hidden />
    <responses />
    <notes />
    <labels />
    <prefixes />
    <nextId>0</nextId>
    <markers />
</metadata>
