<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<collectibles>
    <collectible id="nugi_panties" img="opponents/nugi-chan/collectible_nugi-chan_panties.png" thumbnail="opponents/nugi-chan/collectible_nugi-chan_panties.png">
        <title>Nugi-chan's Panties</title>
        <subtitle>Simple black panties from a maid cosplayer</subtitle>
        <text>In an attempt to be gracious in defeat, Nugi-chan let you keep her panties after the game. When you received them, they were warm with her body heat, and she promised to warm them back up for you if you can beat her again.</text>
        <unlock>Win a game against Nugi-chan.</unlock>
        <hide-details>true</hide-details>
    </collectible>
    <collectible id="nugi_mahjong" img="opponents/nugi-chan/collectible_nugi-chan_majong_tile.png" thumbnail="opponents/nugi-chan/collectible_nugi-chan_majong_tile_icon.png">
        <title>Mahjong Tile + Little Nugi (2")</title>
        <subtitle>Strip Mahjong, anyone?</subtitle>
        <text>Nugi-chan is an expert at stripping games, but she knows when she's been bested. She challenges you to a game of Strip Mahjong at the Inventory next time, handing you this little tile as a keepsake. 

Being a digital mascot, she's also made a copy of herself as a thumb-sized chibi to sit on the tile and stay with you. The chibi is fully voiced and articulated. When you take it home, it alternates between treating you sweetly and berating you for not paying more attention to it.</text>
        <unlock>Win 5 games against Nugi-chan and a full table.</unlock>
        <hide-details>true</hide-details>
        <counter>5</counter>
    </collectible>
    <collectible id="nugi_condom" img="opponents/nugi-chan/collectible_nugi-chan_condom.png" thumbnail="opponents/nugi-chan/collectible_nugi-chan_condom_icon.png">
        <title>Condom + Little Nugi (8")</title>
        <subtitle>It's dangerous to go alone! Take this.</subtitle>
        <text>Nugi-chan is concerned that playing with all of these perverted opponents might have long term consequences, especially if you're participating in epilogues without protection. She gives you this condom with a wink. 

Also winking is the little eight inch copy of herself that Nugi-chan lends you. Little Nugi is like a walking, talking anime figure. Big Nugi tells you that Little Nugi is going to watch over you to make sure you don't get into any trouble, but the devious look that Little Nugi has makes you unsure of that.</text>
        <unlock>Help Nugi-chan beat 10 characters tagged as "perverted".</unlock>
        <hide-details>true</hide-details>
        <counter>10</counter>
    </collectible>
    <collectible id="nugi_drinks" img="opponents/nugi-chan/collectible_drinks.png" thumbnail="opponents/nugi-chan/collectible_drinks.png">
        <title>Assorted Cocktails</title>
        <subtitle>On the house!</subtitle>
        <text>Nugi-chan's day or night brightens when she's waitressing and she sees you arrive. She knows your favorite drink by heart, and she's always giving you way more of her time than she's meant to give to any one customer. For a beautiful moment, she forgets she's a waitress or a mascot; she's just a person who enjoys spending time in your company.

She's waiting for you to ask her to have drinks after work. When that night comes, she'll accept in a heartbeat.</text>
        <unlock>Win 3 games against Nugi-chan in her Swimsuit Server outfit.</unlock>
        <hide-details>true</hide-details>
        <counter>3</counter>
    </collectible>
</collectibles>
