<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>

<!--This file was machine generated using the Character Editor v6.7.6 at 6:50:04 PM on July 30, 2022. Do not edit this file directly unless you know what you're doing.-->
<opponent>
    <version>v6.7.6</version>
    <first>Dorothy</first>
    <last>Haze</last>
    <label>Dorothy</label>
    <gender>female</gender>
    <size>small</size>
    <timer>23</timer>
    <intelligence>average</intelligence>



    <wardrobe>
        <clothing name="panties" generic="underwear" position="lower" type="important" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="bra" generic="bra" position="upper" type="important" />
        <clothing name="shirt" generic="shirt" position="upper" type="major" />
        <clothing name="skirt" generic="skirt" position="lower" type="major" />
        <clothing name="shoes" generic="shoes" position="feet" type="minor" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="ribbon" generic="ribbon" position="upper" type="extra" />
    </wardrobe>

    <poses>
        <pose id="2-stripping">
            <sprite id="skirt" z="1" src="d-skirt.png" x="-25" y="641" />
            <sprite id="stripping-" src="2-stripping-.png" x="0" y="0" />
            <directive type="animation" id="skirt" ease="smooth" interpolation="linear">
                <keyframe time="0" x="-25" y="641" />
                <keyframe time="0.5" x="-17" y="645" />
                <keyframe time="1.25" x="11" y="675" />
                <keyframe time="1.5" x="-1" y="781" />
                <keyframe time="1.75" x="11" y="962" />
                <keyframe time="2" x="-23" y="1191" />
            </directive>
            <directive type="animation" id="skirt" delay="0.5" ease="smooth" interpolation="linear">
                <keyframe time="0" scalex="1.16" scaley="0.61" />
                <keyframe time="0.75" scalex="1.17" scaley="0.76" />
                <keyframe time="1" scalex="1.28" />
                <keyframe time="1.25" scaley="0.62" />
            </directive>
            <directive type="animation" id="skirt" delay="0.5" ease="bounce" interpolation="linear">
                <keyframe time="0" rotation="-3" />
                <keyframe time="0.5" rotation="10" />
                <keyframe time="0.75" rotation="-2" />
                <keyframe time="1" rotation="7" />
                <keyframe time="1.25" rotation="-9" />
                <keyframe time="1.5" rotation="6" />
            </directive>
            <directive type="animation" id="stripping-" ease="linear" interpolation="none">
                <keyframe time="0" src="2-stripping-.png" />
                <keyframe time="1.25" src="2-stripping+.png" />
            </directive>
            <directive type="animation" id="stripping-" delay="0.5" ease="smooth" interpolation="linear">
                <keyframe time="0" rotation="5" />
                <keyframe time="0.5" rotation="-2" />
                <keyframe time="1" rotation="3" />
                <keyframe time="1.5" rotation="1" />
            </directive>
        </pose>
    </poses>

    <behaviour>
        <trigger id="selected">
            <case stage="0" id="1">
                <test expr="~player~" value="Daddy" />
                <state img="#-glee.png">Oh-oh! &lt;i&gt;Wow!&lt;/i&gt; Is Daddy here to play with his little girl? What kind of &lt;i&gt;game&lt;/i&gt; are we going to play?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="3">
                <test expr="~player~" value="Mister" />
                <state img="#-services.png">Mister? Well... if you don't want to tell me your name, I'll have to call you that all night... Mister? Are you trying to get some services from me?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="5">
                <test expr="~player~" value="Stud" />
                <state img="#-sugar.png">Well, &lt;i&gt;damn&lt;/i&gt;. Who brought out the &lt;i&gt;cake&lt;/i&gt; tonight?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="6">
                <test expr="~player~" value="Honey" />
                <state img="#-l-lewd.png">Just so you know, it's going to get &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; confusing to call you "Honey," honey. If you want to see me get all criss-crossed apple-sauced, keep it up, though...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="16">
                <test expr="~player~" value="Big Brother" />
                <state img="#-services.png">Big brother... you know in a game like this, if you aren't careful, you might...? See your little sister do something &lt;i&gt;lewd.&lt;/i&gt; Or show &lt;i&gt;her&lt;/i&gt; something &lt;i&gt;very&lt;/i&gt; lewd...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="17">
                <test expr="~player~" value="Onii" />
                <state img="#-services.png">Onii-chan... you know in a game like this, if you aren't careful, you might...? See your little sister do something &lt;i&gt;lewd.&lt;/i&gt; Or show &lt;i&gt;her&lt;/i&gt; something &lt;i&gt;very&lt;/i&gt; lewd...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="18">
                <test expr="~player~" value="Onee" />
                <state img="#-services.png">Sis... you know in a game like this, if you aren't careful, you might...? Give your little sister the wrong idea...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="19">
                <test expr="~player~" value="Big Sister" />
                <state img="#-services.png">Sis... you know in a game like this, if you aren't careful, you might...? Give your little sister the wrong idea...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="20">
                <test expr="~player~" value="Bitch" />
                <state img="#-whocares.png">Oh, you're here? Jeez. If I wanted to take care of a dirty little bitch like you, hun, I wouldn't have needed to come here. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="21">
                <test expr="~player~" value="Mistress" />
                <state img="#-services.png">Mistress... I am eager to please... whatever you desire, I am yours to use as you please... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="23">
                <test expr="~player~" value="Chad" />
                <state img="#-l-lewd.png">A-Ah! I can't believe I'm playing with Chad Thundercock himself! W-what's a little robot girl to do in the face of such masculinity! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="24">
                <test expr="~player~" value="Stacey" />
                <state img="#-l-lewd.png">Oh &lt;i&gt;wow&lt;/i&gt;! It's &lt;i&gt;Stacey!&lt;/i&gt; The girl everyone aspires to be, or to do! H-how can I ever hope to get her attention? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="25">
                <test expr="~player~" value="Stacey" />
                <state img="#-services.png">&lt;i&gt;Senpai...?&lt;/i&gt; I &lt;i&gt;knew&lt;/i&gt; I'd track you to a filthy place like this. Don't you know DFC72's can place tracking nanomachines? Now, stop this foolishness. Come back to my embrace... or else.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="26">
                <test expr="~player~" value="Bitch" />
                <state img="#-whocares.png">On your knees, then, bitch. I don't have time to spare the energy to bother being nice to you. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="27">
                <test expr="~player~" value="Bitch" />
                <state img="#-easy.png">Oh...? &lt;i&gt;This&lt;/i&gt; one's fun. Are you here to watch someone else show me the business? By business, I mean how to actually cum? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="28">
                <test expr="~player~" value="Darling" />
                <state img="#-services.png">&lt;i&gt;Darling?&lt;/i&gt; Oh... is this what you wanted for your birthday? The least I can do is tell you how much you mean to me...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="29">
                <test expr="~player~" value="Teacher" />
                <state img="#-coquettish.png">Oh! Professor! I wasn't sure how to do these problems. Could you show me how to do it right? I &lt;i&gt;just&lt;/i&gt; want to be a &lt;i&gt;good student&lt;/i&gt; and do a &lt;i&gt;good job.&lt;/i&gt; </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="30">
                <test expr="~player~" value="Master" />
                <state img="#-services.png">Master... I am eager to please... whatever you desire, I am yours to use as you please... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-chatter.png">Well hey, honey, good to see you. </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">Strip Poker... You know, if you're trying to cheap out on just paying me... Not a bad idea. </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">We all pay in one way or another. Show me a good time, and I might show &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; a &lt;i&gt;good time.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="22" hidden="1">
                <test expr="~player~" value="???" />
                <state img="#-easy.png">Well, well, if it isn't ~player~ from back home. Finally grown up enough to play a game of strip poker? Maybe you've been crushing on me all these years... haha!  </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_start">
            <case stage="0" id="2">
                <test expr="~player~" value="Daddy" />
                <state img="#-sugar.png">...If you're going to be a &lt;i&gt;naughty&lt;/i&gt; Daddy tonight, don't be too rough with my moneymakers, honey. But just for legal reasons, you know I'm an adult. I know I'm an adult. So, let's get back to it, &lt;i&gt;Daddy.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="4">
                <test expr="~player~" value="Mister" />
                <state img="#-sugar.png">I'm just screwing with you, honey. But if you want to roleplay, you're paying for the night, so pick a name and let lil' ol' me get you what you're here for, okay?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-easy.png">All this effort to see  &lt;i&gt;me&lt;/i&gt; naked? You know, you could just pay for me like an adult, ~player~. </state>
                <state img="#-easy.png">I'd use a dynamic entrance, but this body's a loaner.</state>
                <state img="#-glee.png">&lt;i&gt;Hooray!&lt;/i&gt; Time to get real lewd!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="swap_cards">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-whocares.png">...~Cards.text~.</state>
                <state img="#-whocares.png">Does anyone really pay attention to these lines? </state>
                <state img="#-whocares.png">~Cards.text~.</state>
                <state img="#-whocares.png">I'm not terrible at poker, you know. </state>
                <state img="#-whocares.png">Swear on whatever deity is out there, if you complain this part of the game is repetitive...</state>
                <state img="#-whocares.png">Yeah, ~cards.text~. </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="good_hand">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-easy.png" oneShotId="19">If you haven't figured it out, the name you start the game with &lt;i&gt;is&lt;/i&gt; a quick way to determine what I say to you, ~player~. </state>
                <state img="#-easy.png">Not bad! All those rounds have paid off. </state>
                <state img="#-chatter.png">Aw... I was &lt;i&gt;so&lt;/i&gt; ready to lose. </state>
                <state img="#-chatter.png">I'm &lt;i&gt;always&lt;/i&gt; okay. But i'm &lt;i&gt;especially&lt;/i&gt; okay here. </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">You know what it's like to have a human libido in a body that's only going to simulate being tired?</state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">Who's going to be up this time? Don't worry, honey. I've seen it all at this point. </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="okay_hand">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-sugar.png">So, what's it going to take for one of you to order me a drink, anyway? </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">Don't you know it's polite to let a young lady have her first sip of champagne? If we're playing strip poker, may as well, right?</state>
                <state img="#-services.png">Oh... this hand is &lt;i&gt;so&lt;/i&gt; hard to read... what am I to do? </state>
                <state img="#-services.png">...You aren't going to make someone like me lose, are you? </state>
                <state img="#-whocares.png">Eh... so-so hand. Wouldn't you rather hear about something more interesting than this? </state>
                <state img="#-whocares.png">...I'm going to need a lot more karmotrine to get through the little things, here. </state>
                <state img="#-chatter.png">So... how'd everyone else do? &lt;i&gt;How. Not&lt;/i&gt; what.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="bad_hand">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-easy.png">Well, looks like you're about to see something good.</state>
                <state img="#-easy.png">Even if I lose, the attention's on me, right? Hard co complain.</state>
                <state img="#-easy.png">I'm not obsessed with attention, but it's not a terrible thing to be seen, right?</state>
                <state img="#-easy.png">Well, well. It looks like you're all about to see &lt;i&gt;something&lt;/i&gt; good.</state>
                <state img="#-easy.png">...Hm. If I win here, it makes the rest of you look pretty bad at this. </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="hand">
            <case stage="0" id="56" totalRounds="0" priority="201">
                <condition count="4" gender="male" role="opp" />
                <state img="#-adjust.png">I don't think this'll get to sex... but if all four of you want a turn, let me warm up a bit. Just don't stand there like a little bitch when your buddy's blowing his load in me. </state>
                <state img="#-adjust.png">So, someone's thinking about a gangbang? Is this going to actually happen, or are you going to have trouble getting it up around that many cocks? I'm game either way, honey. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="8" oneShotId="1" priority="200">
                <state img="#-sugar.png">I'm sure you've got quite a few questions. I'm not &lt;i&gt;fully&lt;/i&gt; on the clock, so let's chat! </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">You probably have a lot of things you'd rather know about me than about what cards I'm holding, right? You didn't pick me for my INCREDIBLE CARD-PLAYING APTITUDE, right?</state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">Since we're all just chatting, I'm sure you curious about more than my cards, right? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="7">
                <state img="#-chatter.png" oneShotId="1" marker="dorothy_lilim">Backstory and exposition time! I'm not a "robot" in the conventional sense. I'm a Lilim, which makes me an AI with human consciousness. And basically a human body, down to &lt;i&gt;allll&lt;/i&gt; the important bits. </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png" oneShotId="2" marker="dorothy_sexwork">Backstory and exposition time! I &lt;i&gt;am&lt;/i&gt; a sex worker, and my "normal" body wasn't one they'd let me in at the door with. So, I made a few upgrades, but same ol' Dorothy Haze in here! </state>
                <state img="#-iukuk.png" oneShotId="3" marker="dorothy_glitchcity" font-size="small">Backstory and exposition time... I'm from a place called Glitch City. Typical cyberpunk cityscape. Uplifted dogs running around, the economy is more important than humanity, high tech stuff used for greed, yada yada.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="9" priority="0">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="dorothy_sexwork" />
                <state img="#-glee.png" oneShotId="52">My best clients are the type that just want to have fun with me. You know, like they missed out on something, and just want to catch up? Or there's something innocent missing in their lives, I guess. </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png" oneShotId="53" font-size="small">The regular Johns are the best, you know. I know them, they know me, and... we don't really have to debate what we're doing. They're people that know what they want, and have the sense to get it from me. </state>
                <state img="#-iukuk.png" oneShotId="54">A lot of people ask "why not be a kindergarten teacher if you're good at dealing with children?" &lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;Do I strike you as an idealist?&lt;/i&gt; It's nice... but gotta make some money first, honey. </state>
                <state img="#-chatter.png" oneShotId="16">My origin story's nothing too exciting. I lucked out with a cute frame, and an open mind. And who doesn't like money? A lot of johns cry after. So it's easy to charge extra and make sure they're okay, you know?</state>
                <state img="#-chatter.png" oneShotId="17">The Inventory's &lt;i&gt;the place&lt;/i&gt; to be. Even if I can't do my &lt;i&gt;usual&lt;/i&gt; routine here, I'm sure you're not playing with me to learn about the economics of sex work, are you, honey?</state>
                <state img="#-iukuk.png" oneShotId="18">I don't do non-consentual or violent stuff. Even if I'm a Lilim, I only take myself apart for maintainance. </state>
                <state img="#-easy.png" oneShotId="20" weight="1.01">I do keep an updated price list, you know. If you ever want something private... I'll talk about it at the end of the game. </state>
                <state img="#-iukuk.png" oneShotId="89">Just so you know, I never do work for free. It's a principle that's kept me, my clients, and everyone else honest. Maybe someday, when I settle down, but that's a long, long time away. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="10" priority="0">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="dorothy_lilim" />
                <state img="#-sugar.png" oneShotId="4">The difference between a robot and a Lilim is pretty obvious, don't you think? I've got free will. Robots don't. </state>
                <state img="#-services.png" oneShotId="5">AI, like me, even if I'm in one body... usually... have to have some human quirks engineered into them. I don't like onions, and dogs sort of freak me out, even if there's not sense for it. </state>
                <state img="#-chatter.png" oneShotId="6">Lilim can swap our bodies on occasion. This is just kind of a temporary proxy. I'm going back to my "normal" one after this. But maybe not &lt;i&gt;immediately&lt;/i&gt; after. </state>
                <state img="#-iukuk.png" oneShotId="7">I can take myself apart to make sure it's all working okay. I can even operate my body remotely, if my head's off. But I'd rather &lt;i&gt;give head&lt;/i&gt; than split myself up for a client. </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png" oneShotId="8">Lilim do pretty much what you'd expect them to. Normal human things. With a bit more durability. </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png" oneShotId="9">If you're wondering why people would make Lilim with human personalities... Why not? Companionship, or just playing God... Eh. I'm not the philosophizing type, but it's fun, and I'm glad to be alive. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="11" priority="0">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="dorothy_glitchcity" />
                <state img="#-chatter.png" oneShotId="34" font-size="small">Glitch City's economy is based. &lt;br&gt;Okay, screencaps done, but it's based on a pretty open economy. Progress abounds... but you really want to know? Open economy, few regulations... kind of a nice, shitty place. Where Lilim girls sell themselves for money. </state>
                <state img="#-iukuk.png" oneShotId="35">Some people in Glitch believe that God is an iterative process... you know, like God comes out of the machine given enough time. </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png" oneShotId="36">Everyone's gotta have a social life in the city. If you can find one between your job and rent, and all that. </state>
                <state img="#-glee.png" oneShotId="37">So many different types of professions in Glitch City... some are easy, some are hard, but a lot of them just... well, I wasn't lying when I said it's hard out here. </state>
                <state img="#-iukuk.png" oneShotId="38">Human prostitution's still a thing where I'm from. But Lilim have a &lt;i&gt;way&lt;/i&gt; easier time of it. So the demand, price, and... &lt;i&gt;specificity&lt;/i&gt; varies a lot. </state>
                <state img="#-chatter.png" oneShotId="39">Lilim are a pretty common sight in Glitch... but I'm not really sure how many people have seen us naked. Be honest, ~player~, if you didn't wonder, you wouldn't pick me, right?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-easy.png">Watch and learn, folks. </state>
                <state img="#-easy.png">You know I'm here to have fun too, right? Watch this. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-blow.png">Enjoy the view, honey, </state>
                <state img="#-blow.png">Since you're going to be looking up my skirt anyway, why don't I save you the messing around?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-coquettish.png">Since you saw my panties earlier, do you really need me to take off my skirt...</state>
                <state img="#-coquettish.png">Aw... but you've already looked at my cute underwear... maybe I should take them off from under my skirt?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-sugar.png">Hope you're having a good time already. I know I am. </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">I'd &lt;i&gt;never&lt;/i&gt; tell you to keep your shirt on, so I won't keep mine on, either. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-coquettish.png">You're welcome to compliment me. I know these are as cute as the rest of me...</state>
                <state img="#-coquettish.png">D-do you think I'm beautiful? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-easy.png">So... if you liked my tits... I hope you'll like this next part too~ </state>
                <state img="#-easy.png">Hm... I know my upstairs is nice and cute, but what about down? </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripping">
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">Ah, you know, it's hard to not &lt;i&gt;try&lt;/i&gt; to mess with you people. If you're really into it, I definitely don't mean it badly! </state>
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">I'm aware of how I look, but flattery's always nice! And if I'm messing with you or making you check your values a bit, hey, honey, I'm into it. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">I know, I know, I do this a lot. I'm not here to show off... much. But I'm a professional. And I promise to give you your money's worth. </state>
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">You know, sex starts &lt;i&gt;way&lt;/i&gt; before anything goes into anything else. You have to make the undressing fun too. But more than that, you have to build trust with your clients, and that means being faithful to what they're paying you for. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">In my line of work, I usually wear something pretty simple and sexy... lacy panties, a nice black bra...</state>
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">I like stuff that makes me feel sexy, and if I'm not sure who doesn't like a nice set of black lacy stuff. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="custom:#-stripping">Presentation is the difference between seduction and... uh... not. </state>
                <state img="custom:#-stripping">Professionalism, presentation, and pussy. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">It's kind of funny. You'd think with all the engineering that goes into making a body like mine, I wouldn't really &lt;i&gt;need&lt;/i&gt; a bra...</state>
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">Before you ask, I'm plenty perky and don't need a bra... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">I think it'd be pretty cheap to take my panties off and not make it worth your while... </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripped">
            <case stage="5">
                <condition filter="uses_camera" />
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">&lt;i&gt;*Sigh.*&lt;/i&gt; You can take a picture, but you better make it worth my while after this.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">You know, I'm not here to kid around, either. If you're squeamish about my line of work, you might want to go outside for a bit and pick someone else. </state>
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">I do want to say that this is the last chance. I'm plenty cute and I know I'm adorable... but if you're expecting something nice and vanilla, oh, honey, you're in the wrong place.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-easy.png">But, you know, all things considered, I've got other sets when someone hires me for roleplay. </state>
                <state img="#-easy.png">I have a lot of other sets for when I'm doing roleplay, though. But for general day stuff, things like this what you just saw are pretty much the gold... black... standard. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">Oh, and just so you know, it feels just like a "human" girl's, except it's not going to get pregnant or have any types of unpleasantness. </state>
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">From experience... mind feels just like a human's, you know. Except you can cum in it as much as you like... or put your tongue in without anything unexpected, honey~</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">But I'd be missing out on all kinds of cute stuff! Plus, authenticity is key. The robophiliacs are fun, sometimes, but I'm a bit more than a sex machine. Though, I guess I am pretty good at it. </state>
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">A girl's gotta dress for her job, though. Even if it means getting &lt;i&gt;undressed.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">No pictures, please, a girl's gotta keep &lt;i&gt;some&lt;/i&gt; tools of her trade, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">...And &lt;i&gt;I'm&lt;/i&gt; worth every single cent, honey. </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_strip">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-chatter.png">Time to get to the first half of the name of the game we all know and love. </state>
                <state img="#-chatter.png">What are you expecting from me? To blush? Take it off, ~name~. </state>
                <state img="#-glee.png">&lt;i&gt;Hoo-rah and celebrations&lt;/i&gt;, get to it, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-glee.png">Huzzah, and back to the part of the game where I get to watch, you get to wonder, and I can verify nothing else, honey~</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-chatter.png">I'd complain, but you do usually want to get your clothes off before you get off. Unless you're into that, in which case, boy do I got a deal for you!</state>
                <state img="#-easy.png">Oooh... show us some skin, honey. Or whatever passes for it, iin your case. </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">Stare all you like, ~name~. Just means more time I get to stand like this. </state>
                <state img="#-services.png">Oh... ~Name~... won't you &lt;i&gt;pretty please&lt;/i&gt; take off something nice for me? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6">
                <state img="#-easy.png">Hubba hubba, ~name~, whatcha got for me? </state>
                <state img="#-services.png">But I'm &lt;i&gt;so&lt;/i&gt; small, you could cover me with something nice and big... or hot and sticky, honey~</state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">So, you going to stare, or give me something to stare back at, honey?</state>
                <state img="#-glee.png">Thank fuck!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-blow.png">Honey, show me the good stuff, okay?</state>
                <state img="#-easy.png">Say, is this free advertising? Maybe you want to &lt;i&gt;play&lt;/i&gt; a bit more than to &lt;i&gt;watch&lt;/i&gt;, ~name~. </state>
                <state img="#-easy.png">Take a good look, ~name~. I know I'm going to. </state>
                <state img="#-blow.png">...Come on, honey. Help a girl out. </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_strip">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-chatter.png">Come on, honey, give us a show!</state>
                <state img="#-glee.png">I'd say you're making us work for it, but usually I'd be doing all kinds of things right now. </state>
                <state img="#-easy.png">Take! It! Off! </state>
                <state img="#-easy.png">You don't have to be a professional to be an excellent amateur at getting naked, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-sugar.png">Like what you see, ~name~? Happy to say it back to you after you strip. </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">I know people say that Lilim girls are "built different," but you really just need to show we're not that different, okay, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">Just ease yourself into it, ~name~. That's what they all say, anyway. </state>
                <state img="#-glee.png">Come on and join me! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6">
                <state img="#-easy.png">I'm here all ~background.time~, honey! Get comfy. </state>
                <state img="#-easy.png">I always charge for my services, but since I've already gotten paid, you may as well take a good, long look. But also, join me. </state>
                <state img="#-services.png">Oh... ~name~... you're getting me &lt;i&gt;so&lt;/i&gt; turned on...</state>
                <state img="#-services.png">Girls are fine too, obviously... but maybe you need a bit more incentive?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-chatter.png">If you've never tried a girl before... well, you could say I'm a &lt;i&gt;great&lt;/i&gt; starter option!</state>
                <state img="#-chatter.png">I'd say don't give it away for free, but it's your body, ~name~. </state>
                <state img="#-blow.png">I could blow you a kiss, or something else, ~name~. </state>
                <state img="#-blow.png">Well, honey? Showing off the goods or being a good girl? </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="tie">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-glee.png">&lt;i&gt;Ding ding ding&lt;/i&gt;! So rare, may as well turn this into a gangbang! </state>
                <state img="#-glee.png">&lt;i&gt;Ding ding ding&lt;/i&gt;! Looks like someone could use a &lt;i&gt;dong dong dong&lt;/i&gt;!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-blow.png">C'mon, honey, show us like you mean it. </state>
                <state img="#-chatter.png">I'm firmly of the opinion that there's no bad male chests. Each one has something unique to offer. </state>
                <state img="#-easy.png">Whether you've got finely engineered abs or a big old gut, the feel when it's pressing down on top of you... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-whocares.png">Let's hope my tits are a little smaller than yours, huh, ~name~? </state>
                <state img="#-services.png">What we we going to do with you, ~name~? </state>
                <state img="#-easy.png">Heyyy~ Time to see your chest, huh? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6">
                <state img="#-adjust.png">I'm watching, I'm watching. Just... gussying up. Not the 'ussy you really expected, huh? </state>
                <state img="#-blow.png">Come on, honey. We're ready for you. </state>
                <state img="#-blow.png">Don't keep me waiting, honey. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-services.png">~Name~... You're going to look handsome no matter what. But... I do want to look. </state>
                <state img="#-services.png">Instead of pretending... how about you just show me more of yourself, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-services.png">I might have fantasized about you... want to make it a little more real?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-easy.png">I can't say I'm surprised, with the ~clothing~ you had on... but you're nice to look at, and since you're not paying me, you know I'm being honest! </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">That's the kind of chest you pour shots down and lick up. Or maybe if you made a mess, I'd clean something else off it. </state>
                <state img="#-coquettish.png">W-wow... I'm not lying when I say I wouldn't mind lying under &lt;i&gt;~name~.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-glee.png">Ah, holy shit! You &lt;i&gt;are&lt;/i&gt; hot! </state>
                <state img="#-glee.png">Fun stuff ahead. You can go ahead and &lt;i&gt;stuff some fun, too&lt;/i&gt; if you know what I mean. </state>
                <state img="#-blow.png">Mmf... Anyone going to give ~name~ a feel? Can I? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6">
                <state img="#-services.png">...What's a girl like me to do besides get all wet thinking about how good you might feel, ~name~...</state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">Hey, ~name~, are you a Lilim? Because &lt;i&gt;damn&lt;/i&gt; that chest looks built to spec. </state>
                <state img="#-services.png">Is your chest hard or soft? Well... one way to find out, huh?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-blow.png">Now &lt;i&gt;that's&lt;/i&gt; the kind of chest you don't mind licking sweat off of. </state>
                <state img="#-blow.png">Using my mouth to talk to you seems like a waste.</state>
                <state img="#-blow.png">&lt;i&gt;Whew.&lt;/i&gt; Making a girl want to violate her principles is &lt;i&gt;very naughty, ~name~.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-coquettish.png">You're already going to... </state>
                <state img="#-coquettish.png">O-Oh... What are you going to be showing us...? </state>
                <state img="#-coquettish.png">~Name~... what's that thing in your pants, Mr. ~name~? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-services.png">The second best part of the game... the first is what you end up doing with your...</state>
                <state img="#-services.png">Am I turning you on, ~name~? </state>
                <state img="#-services.png">Oh... let's see your &lt;i&gt;big, thick...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-sugar.png">Here we go! </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">There!&lt;br&gt;We!&lt;br&gt;Go!</state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">Fuck yes! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-blow.png">Kept me waiting long enough.</state>
                <state img="#-blow.png">Oh, honey, keep a girl waiting and she'll have to get started herself. </state>
                <state img="#-blow.png">Honey, my fingers do a pretty good job... but show me something a little more... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6">
                <state img="#-services.png">Oh, ~name~... Won't you take it out for me?</state>
                <state img="#-services.png">~Name~... you're not going to just let that wonderful member of yours hang there, swaying? </state>
                <state img="#-services.png">Mmf. &lt;i&gt;Finally.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_small_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-blow.png">Aw, honey. I'm kidding around. And take it from me, the small ones are just as good. </state>
                <state img="#-blow.png">Oof-- Brave of you, ~name~. But &lt;i&gt;trust me&lt;/i&gt;, girls like me like the smaller ones. &lt;i&gt;Way easier&lt;/i&gt; to do all kinds of lewd things. </state>
                <state img="#-blow.png">As much as I'm having fun messing with people, I'm not joking when I say I'd totally blow you. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-coquettish.png">Wow... Your cock's sized just right for me. You could fuck me all night long and I'd be perfectly calibrated for it.</state>
                <state img="#-coquettish.png">Hm! I guess we have to make that disappear into somewhere nice and tight, ~name~... </state>
                <state img="#-coquettish.png">Oh &lt;i&gt;wow&lt;/i&gt;... it's so perfect! You could ram it in pretty much any one of my holes until you came without any problems...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6">
                <state img="#-sugar.png">Don't worry, ~name~. I discount regulars, and that looks like one that'll keep you coming... back... again and again...</state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">Guys hung like you seem to have something to prove. Not that &lt;i&gt;I&lt;/i&gt; mind a good time.</state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">It's so &lt;i&gt;cute&lt;/i&gt;, ~name~. I bet it'd still look that way if you were pinning me to a wall and giving it to me. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-easy.png">If I call it cute, maybe you can show me how decidedly &lt;i&gt;not&lt;/i&gt; cute you can be, ~name~...?</state>
                <state img="#-easy.png">Oh... good boy... why don't you just watch me, and then I can tell you all the filthy things I can do with that. </state>
                <state img="#-easy.png">If you can last the few minutes I'll give you head, you can slide that nice and raw, wherever you'd like, ~name~. </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_medium_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-easy.png">Did that actually turn you on, ~name~? Aren't you a special kind of pervert.</state>
                <state img="#-easy.png">You know I'm just screwing around, right? If you want me to do that kind of thing for you... well, you know the drill. </state>
                <state img="#-easy.png">Aww, are you getting hard off of that little comment? Do innocent robot girls flick your switch, ~name~? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-sugar.png">Well look at &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; beautiful instrument. Maybe you can use it to penetration test my access ports? </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">It's a shame that cock's so pretty. I won't be seeing much of it when it's buried to the balls in me. </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">Nurture</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6">
                <state img="#-chatter.png">Since you're here, you're looking for some fun, right? Good thing I'm fun-sized~ </state>
                <state img="#-whocares.png">Huh... you're not that client from the other night, are you? I guess the only way to find out would be to see how you react to my tongue wrapping around your head... </state>
                <state img="#-chatter.png">It &lt;i&gt;sure is nice&lt;/i&gt;... but I want to find out how well you can use it... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-services.png">...You could just jam that down my throat. Lilim don't need a gag reflex... or to breathe that often... </state>
                <state img="#-services.png">Honey... I think I need an inspection... could you make sure my pussy is well-lubed with your cum? </state>
                <state img="#-services.png">I can't help myself, ~name~. So maybe you should help yourself to &lt;i&gt;me&lt;/i&gt;?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_large_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-sugar.png">Hel-&lt;i&gt;lo&lt;/i&gt; there, sailor. </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">It'll fit, you know. &lt;i&gt;Somewhere&lt;/i&gt;. </state>
                <state img="#-whocares.png">It's a nice dick, but you know size isn't everything. If it were, I'd be pretty bad at my job. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-oya.png" oneShotId="65">Aw, fuck. Look at that hog. That salami splitter. That sausage that can savage me. </state>
                <state img="#-oya.png">...Sorry, where were we, again? </state>
                <state img="#-oya.png">...Ahahha... Yeah... That's a great dick. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6">
                <state img="#-oya.png">Who doesn't love big dick... but if I charged by the inch...</state>
                <state img="#-oya.png">...I &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; hope you're going to be at least gentle with that. I recover pretty well, but if you smash the back over and over, I'll charge extra for repairs... </state>
                <state img="#-oya.png">...Hahhhah... Y-yeah... Nothing's broken me yet, but holy fuck... That'd stretch me out... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-sugar.png">I could stroke your ego... or... </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">I'm sure you're used to girls that get a little concerned about your size. That's why you should consider a woman who can take it all the way to the back, all night long. </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">If this were Glitch City, you'd get taken down for packing that much heat. I could stand to do some civic duty myself... </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-glee.png">Give 'em a little jiggle, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-glee.png">Boobs! Where function follows form, and the function is to make your day better!</state>
                <state img="#-glee.png">Who doesn't love a nice pair of titties? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-chatter.png">Ready for some flattery, ~name~? </state>
                <state img="#-chatter.png">I can't say I'm surprised, but I have a sixth sense for titties. </state>
                <state img="#-chatter.png">Just do you know, ~name~, girls are totally fine by me. And by that, I mean &lt;i&gt;you're&lt;/i&gt; totally fine. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6">
                <state img="#-services.png">~Name~...</state>
                <state img="#-chatter.png">Whether you lick them, squeeze them, or motorboat the shit out of them, all titites are good titties! </state>
                <state img="#-chatter.png">Hey, I'm built to look the way I am. Let's see what you've got under there, ~name~. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-glee.png">I happen to have a ton of other skills, ~name~. But I think my profession's probably the most helpful in getting me at those wonderful...</state>
                <state img="#-glee.png">Your breasts look woefully under Dorothy'd. </state>
                <state img="#-glee.png">Not going to lie: I'm totally thinking of the lewd things I can do to you, ~name~. </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_small_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-chatter.png">Technically, if you do a fourier transform--which I know, by the way, as a Lilim--small ones give you the biggest chest/body ratio!</state>
                <state img="#-chatter.png">&lt;i&gt;Super cute&lt;/i&gt;! </state>
                <state img="#-adjust.png" oneShotId="66">It's not about the size of the boobs on the girl, it's about the amount of fight in the size... wait, shit. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6">
                <state img="#-sugar.png">I bet you could borrow my bra. Or I could make you moan like I do. </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">They say familiarity breeds contempt, ~name~. But how about we get you to dislike me a whole lot when I make you cum your fucking brains out? </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">I've never met a guy who &lt;i&gt;actually&lt;/i&gt; didn't like the smaller ones. And even if I'm not a guy, gotta say I like the way you look, ~name~. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-sugar.png">Aw, honey, they're perfect. For my hands, my mouth... or whatever it is you're into. </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">Having tried smaller breasts and bigger ones, that whole thing about them being more sensitive just isn't true. But if you want them to get nice and sensitive, I have a few things I can do for you.. .</state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">Thanks, honey~ &lt;i&gt;Loving&lt;/i&gt; your whole... &lt;i&gt;unf--&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_medium_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-sugar.png">So... what's going to do it for you, ~name~? Some friendly motorboating?</state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">Gorgeous! </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">Not that you should consider a career like mine, but I wouldn't mind you taking on my services, honey. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6">
                <state img="#-blow.png">I bet you get this a lot, but I think your tits would look a lot better with my face between them, honey~ </state>
                <state img="#-blow.png">Aw, honey... save some beauty for the rest of us. </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">I'm a sex worker, not a fortune teller, but I can tell a lot about someone with my hands. Mind if I give you a reading? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-coquettish.png">...Mmf. Just &lt;i&gt;a little&lt;/i&gt; groping? </state>
                <state img="#-coquettish.png">Oh fuck... ~name~... </state>
                <state img="#-coquettish.png">...Wow. That little bounce when your ~clothing~ came off... expertly done, ~name~.  </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_large_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-easy.png">I won't claim I'm a good masseuse, but if I were to use my mouth, I think I'd do a pretty good job taking off some of your tension. </state>
                <state img="#-easy.png">Mind if I rest my head there? Or my mouth?</state>
                <state img="#-easy.png">You probably get all the attention you want, and then some. So...  I'll compliment how brave you are for playing this game. As an amateur, anyway. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6">
                <state img="#-sugar.png">Some girls get all the luck. That "oppai loli" look was all the rage not that long ago... so just getting a feel for it. Or you, if you'd let me~ </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">Well, hey, honey, and I thought &lt;i&gt;I&lt;/i&gt; was packing some ballistics away. </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">Seriously, let me know if you want a back massage later. I can massage those enormous boobs of yours too, but that's extra. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-services.png">That looks like a nice way to end, or start, an evening... </state>
                <state img="#-services.png">Oh, honey... you're just getting me wound up. </state>
                <state img="#-services.png">...The big ones &lt;i&gt;do&lt;/i&gt; give you more to play with... but quality matters too. You're lucky you got both, ~name~. </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-sugar.png">You can always be proud of your body. After all, it's what houses pretty much all of you that makes you who you are. &lt;br&gt;But you can be especially proud of those &lt;i&gt;divine&lt;/i&gt; titties, ~name~. </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">Nice curvature, lickable nipples... those are some good boobs. Nice, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-coquettish.png">They really do complete your figure, you know. </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-glee.png">From where most people sprang forth and long to return! </state>
                <state img="#-glee.png">No matter if you're shaved, synthetic, suppurating or otherwise, I've yet to meet a kitty I didn't want to pet! </state>
                <state img="#-blow.png">And to think, I haven't even shown you my panties. Are you some kind of dirty lil' exhibitionist? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-coquettish.png">O-oh! Miss ~name~... A-are you about to show us your naughty... tight... wet... little... </state>
                <state img="#-coquettish.png">Miss ~name~! Won't you tell me why what you're about to show us is called a pussy? Do you want me to pet it all night long? </state>
                <state img="#-coquettish.png">Miss ~name~? What does it mean when someone says they want to cream all over your pussy? Wouldn't a kitty prefer to drink the cream? What about you? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6">
                <state img="#-services.png">Honey... you've already come this far... maybe you might want to make some new bad choices with me? </state>
                <state img="#-services.png">Want me to show you &lt;i&gt;my&lt;/i&gt; vibrate function, honey? </state>
                <state img="#-services.png">Oh, honey... don't keep me waiting... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-chatter.png">I can flirt a bit, but you know what I'll say, right?</state>
                <state img="#-chatter.png">If you want, I've been &lt;i&gt;dying&lt;/i&gt; to try out some roleplay where &lt;i&gt;I'm&lt;/i&gt; the teacher. First step! Take out your materials! </state>
                <state img="#-chatter.png">Do you like it when I call you a good girl, or... maybe a &lt;i&gt;naughty,&lt;/i&gt; little... </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-adjust.png">Not to seem disinterested. Just making sure everything in me's ready for if you wanted to... spend some time to get to know each other. </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png" font-size="small">I bet a lot of girls realize something about themselves when they see you for the first time. For instance, I know I want to bury my face between those thighs until &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; learn that not all of us need to be paid to act like a naughty whore. </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">As someone with an android body, I can tell good construction when I see it. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-whocares.png" oneShotId="70">Well, well, well. If it isn't an excuse for me to make a joke about eating you out. Wait, fuck, I should've just made the joke. </state>
                <state img="#-blow.png">Did that do it for you, honey? Don't worry. We're all having fun, huh?</state>
                <state img="#-easy.png">If &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; got you wet, I've got &lt;i&gt;great&lt;/i&gt; news for you, ~name~. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6">
                <state img="#-blow.png">I'm not exactly &lt;i&gt;high class&lt;/i&gt;, but I know great art when I see it. </state>
                <state img="#-adjust.png">...Aw. How'm I supposed to keep a business going with girls like you showing off for free, ~name~? You're too fucking hot. </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">I've heard of getting hot under the collar, but my mind's just burning major RAM thinking of how I'd like to... well, ram myself up in your business. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-coquettish.png">Dang, girl. If you're not wet already, tell me how to... make corrections, please, honey?</state>
                <state img="#-glee.png">That's one for the memories. But why settle for one when we could go for two... or three... or six... or just sex. </state>
                <state img="#-glee.png">Ah... ~Name~, I don't even care that it's prettier than mine. I'm super jealous, and all I can think about is letting you climb on top and fuck my brains out. </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_lost">
            <case stage="0-6" id="57">
                <condition role="target" character="cagliostro" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-sugar.png" marker="doro01">Hey there, honey. If you're trying to act &lt;i&gt;cutesy&lt;/i&gt;, you want some tips? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="123">
                <condition role="target" character="sucrose" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-glee.png" marker="doro01">Ah! Your name's &lt;i&gt;actually&lt;/i&gt; Sucrose? You're the sweetest girl here, you know? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="85">
                <condition role="target" character="mari_setogaya" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-chatter.png" marker="doro01">Mari, I've gotta know: Is the barely-legal promiscuous high schooler thing a work, or is that who you really are?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="64">
                <condition role="target" character="toph" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-easy.png" marker="doro01">Well &lt;i&gt;hey there,&lt;/i&gt; cutie! You're the reason we've got these nifty dots on the cards, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="80">
                <condition role="target" character="rouge" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-coquettish.png" marker="doro01">Ms. Rouge, do you think I'll be as pretty as you, someday?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="91">
                <condition role="target" character="ahri" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-coquettish.png" marker="doro01">Ms. Ahri, have you heard  of &lt;i&gt;"oyakodon"&lt;/i&gt;...?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="116">
                <condition role="target" character="meia" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-sugar.png" marker="doro01">Hey, honey. You've done good for yourself, huh?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="74">
                <condition role="target" character="9s" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-services.png" marker="doro01">Oooh... Mr. Mysterious. C'mon, you gotta have a name besides your serial number.. .</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="113">
                <condition role="target" character="nanoko-chan" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-easy.png" marker="doro01">Well, hey there, honey. Don't be nervous. You're with a professional! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="60">
                <condition role="target" character="cagliostro" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-adjust.png" marker="doro11">So... this body's a loaner, and I can upload my mind wherever. How's that work for you? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="67">
                <condition role="target" character="toph" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-chatter.png" marker="doro11">Sorry, Toph, it's always super fascinating to me to find out what gets people going, especially if they're built a little different. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="70">
                <condition role="target" character="toph" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-chatter.png" marker="doro21">I've experimented with some mods that make me invisible to cameras. I don't think it'd work on you. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="75">
                <condition role="target" character="9s" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-whocares.png" marker="doro11">That drone of yours... your "Pod," I can't say I've seen one like it. What kind of tech is it running? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="78">
                <condition role="target" character="9s" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-whocares.png" marker="doro21">So, if you're not going to pick a name, I'm calling you Oscar. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="83">
                <condition role="target" character="rouge" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-glee.png" marker="doro11">I don't think I've ever met a jewel thief, before. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="88">
                <condition role="target" character="mari_setogaya" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-whocares.png" marker="doro11">I'm calling bullshit. I'm a sex worker and even &lt;i&gt;I&lt;/i&gt; can't subsist on cum alone. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="94">
                <condition role="target" character="ahri" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-sugar.png" marker="doro11">I bet people go &lt;i&gt;crazy&lt;/i&gt; for those tails. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="97">
                <condition role="target" character="kumatora" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-easy.png" marker="doro01">Hey, honey. You look like the type of girl with some experience &lt;i&gt;waitressing.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="100">
                <condition role="target" character="kumatora" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-whocares.png" marker="doro11">Kumatora, sorry if you got the wrong idea earlier. If you really were just waitressing. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="120">
                <condition role="target" character="noelle" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-adjust.png" marker="doro01">...So, when you say 'maid'... Is that your niche, Noelle?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="104">
                <condition role="target" character="rosa" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-chatter.png" marker="doro11">Wow, are you some kind of big movie star? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="107">
                <condition role="target" character="rosa" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-chatter.png" marker="doro11">Have you ever thought about it, though? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="110">
                <condition role="target" character="rosa" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-services.png" marker="doro21">...So, if you're not starring in movies, how do you feel about hiring me for a one-night-only role? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="119">
                <condition role="target" character="meia" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-coquettish.png" marker="doro02">Before this game, you've &lt;i&gt;seriously&lt;/i&gt; never seen a dick? Holy shit! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="126">
                <condition role="target" character="sucrose" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-chatter.png" marker="doro11">You know, if you're trying to get over some anxiety, you can always hire a professional, sweetie. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" hidden="1">
                <condition role="target" character="natsuki" />
                <state>What they say to an opponent who has lost a round. This is considered in conjunction with the more specific (male/female) must strip/masturbate cases</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" hidden="1">
                <condition role="target" character="senko" />
                <state>What they say to an opponent who has lost a round. This is considered in conjunction with the more specific (male/female) must strip/masturbate cases</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" hidden="1">
                <condition role="target" character="nagisa" />
                <state>What they say to an opponent who has lost a round. This is considered in conjunction with the more specific (male/female) must strip/masturbate cases</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" hidden="1">
                <condition role="target" character="mari" />
                <state>tips and tricks</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" hidden="1">
                <condition role="target" character="kora" />
                <state>What they say to an opponent who has lost a round. This is considered in conjunction with the more specific (male/female) must strip/masturbate cases</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" hidden="1">
                <condition role="target" character="jim" />
                <state>aged out </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" hidden="1">
                <condition role="target" character="trixie" />
                <state>tips and tricks</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" hidden="1">
                <condition role="target" character="mikan" />
                <state>tips and tricks</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_stripping">
            <case stage="0-6" id="58">
                <condition role="target" character="cagliostro" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-adjust.png" marker="doro02">Roleplay is fun. I get paid a lot to do it. But you know, to a professional, you're laying it on a little thick. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="61">
                <condition role="target" character="cagliostro" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-chatter.png" marker="doro13">Hey, you do you, honey. I'm okay with pretty much whatever. But I'll go back to my usual frame tomorrow morning. I just go this one to get in here in the first place. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="63">
                <condition role="target" character="cagliostro" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-whocares.png" marker="doro23">&lt;i&gt;*Sigh.*&lt;/i&gt; Leave it to an amateur to drop character. You're here to get laid, at least stick to it if you want to get your stuff stuck. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="65">
                <condition role="target" character="toph" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-glee.png" marker="doro02">Don't worry, I do a &lt;i&gt;lot&lt;/i&gt; of things by feel too. Texture in any career is &lt;i&gt;so&lt;/i&gt; important. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="68">
                <condition role="target" character="toph" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-adjust.png" marker="doro12">You're blind, I'm a sex worker. Can you really blame me for-- Anyway, do you like it when people speak to you in a naughty voice?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="71">
                <condition role="target" character="toph" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-whocares.png" marker="doro22">Huh. That probably doesn't make a whole lot of sense to you... basically, magic that makes me invisible to getting painted...? I guess. You're smart but it's kind of a weird concept... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="79">
                <condition role="target" character="9s" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-sugar.png" marker="doro22">'Cause you're being a dick, &lt;i&gt;Oscar.&lt;/i&gt; And if you want to act like a wiener, I'm calling you one. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="81">
                <condition role="target" character="rouge" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-sugar.png" marker="doro02">If I wanted to make you squirm, there's some other approaches I could employ. But I know a woman comfortable in her sin when I see one. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="84">
                <condition role="target" character="rouge" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-whocares.png" marker="doro12">I'm pretty skilled at playing with jewels, in one manner of speaking, though. What about you? You look like you're here for a good time. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="86">
                <condition role="target" character="mari_setogaya" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-iukuk.png" marker="doro02">No no, I can respect it either way, but I think that niche is a lot more common, so it's less lucrative. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="89">
                <condition role="target" character="mari_setogaya" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-coquettish.png" marker="doro12">Wow... really? I can't tell if that's amazing or horrible. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="92">
                <condition role="target" character="ahri" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-services.png" marker="doro02">It's where someone takes a mother and daughter to bed at the same time... and since you're so pretty... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="95">
                <condition role="target" character="ahri" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-iukuk.png" marker="doro12">I've thought about getting some extensions to cater to the fetishists, but... a little too pricy for what they're willing to pay and my current niche isn't half bad. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="98">
                <condition role="target" character="kumatora" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-iukuk.png" marker="doro02">Hey, I stand in solidarity with you. A girl's gotta make ends me. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="105">
                <condition role="target" character="rosa" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-easy.png" marker="doro02">You're seriously pretty enough for it. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="108">
                <condition role="target" character="rosa" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-easy.png" marker="doro12">You know... &lt;i&gt;adult films?&lt;/i&gt; </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="111">
                <condition role="target" character="rosa" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-chatter.png" marker="doro22">I'm trying to put the moves on you, but I do have a business to keep running. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="114">
                <condition role="target" character="nanoko-chan" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-sugar.png" marker="doro02">Also a lot of other people. It's just a game. If you're not &lt;i&gt;trying&lt;/i&gt; to get laid, that's fine. But I'd say I'm pretty good at it. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="117">
                <condition role="target" character="meia" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-iukuk.png" marker="doro02">Meia, you know what I do for a living. I can tell you had a pretty rough few years there, too. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="121">
                <condition role="target" character="noelle" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-chatter.png" marker="doro02">You pull it off really well! You've got the whole caring demeanor thing down! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="124">
                <condition role="target" character="sucrose" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-chatter.png" marker="doro02">You're &lt;i&gt;adorable&lt;/i&gt;. You're cute... but still dressed sexy. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2" id="31">
                <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="extra" />
                <state img="#-whocares.png">I'd say the small stuff isn't that important, but I'm pretty small myself... easily tossed around... </state>
                <state img="#-chatter.png">Nice ~clothing~. </state>
                <state img="#-easy.png">Take your time, ~name~. It all comes off eventually! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4" id="32">
                <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="extra" />
                <state img="#-iukuk.png">Sometimes, my regulars give me their accessories, too. I've got a whole drawer of them, but if they're nice, I can let them show me off a bit. </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">So, is this one of those stylistic choices, or are you trying to pad your layers? Speaking of &lt;i&gt;padding&lt;/i&gt;-- I'd &lt;i&gt;never!&lt;/i&gt; It's bad business! </state>
                <state img="#-services.png">I was hoping I'd get to see more of you, ~name~... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6" id="35">
                <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="extra" />
                <state img="#-whocares.png">I've done the ribbon-wrap thing on occasion. Just saying.</state>
                <state img="#-whocares.png">It's not the size that matters, but what it's covering, you know. </state>
                <state img="#-glee.png">What kind of kinky stuff can you do with that...? I already know the answer, but feel free to get creative!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2" id="34">
                <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="minor" />
                <state img="#-glee.png">There's only so many "jack it" jokes I can make. But that list is a &lt;i&gt;long&lt;/i&gt; one! </state>
                <state img="#-iukuk.png">I'm into whatever, but it's always a bit more fun when someone's picked me for me, you know?</state>
                <state img="#-easy.png">Oh honey, I'm having a great time. </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">I could use a drink. What about you, ~name~? Or did you have something else you wanted to put in my mouth? </state>
                <state img="#-services.png">Y-you know, if you hurry up, ~name~... you'll see what a Lilim looks like when she's turned on... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4" id="36">
                <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="minor" />
                <state img="#-iukuk.png">If you want me to get into some other kind of outfit after this, I can, but doesn't that skip the appeal of how I'm normally dressed?</state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">Like I said, this body's a loaner. I'll get back to my &lt;i&gt;other&lt;/i&gt; one after this, if that's really what you're after. </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">This is a fun little game, huh? I still think I'd rather get taken out to dinner or a movie before we get down to it... but this is interesting. </state>
                <state img="#-easy.png" oneShotId="28">Hey... ~target.ifMale(Mr.|Ms.)~ ~name~... you wanna buy my underwear after this? Pfft... I'm not joking, but don't freak out! </state>
                <state img="#-glee.png">Things on the internet have 99.99% uptime! I wish I could say the same about my clients! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6" id="33">
                <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="minor" />
                <state img="#-services.png">Oh, honey... not bad... </state>
                <state img="#-services.png">Aww... you look like you're struggling, ~name~. Need some help? </state>
                <state img="#-chatter.png">I'd offer to buy you a drink if you take it off in a weird way, ~name~, but where would I keep my cash right now?</state>
                <state img="#-chatter.png">Do you get really excited with an amazing entrance and catchphrase? I can think of a &lt;i&gt;few&lt;/i&gt; amazing entrances. </state>
                <state img="#-easy.png">Aww, don't give up now, ~name~~</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2" id="51">
                <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="major" />
                <state img="#-chatter.png">Normally it's me that undresses first. This is almost worth considering a career change for!</state>
                <state img="#-easy.png">Show me what you got. </state>
                <state img="#-easy.png">If you &lt;i&gt;can&lt;/i&gt; show me something I've never seen before, I'll buy you a drink! </state>
                <state img="#-chatter.png">I hope you wore cute underwear. </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">Be honest. You kinda want to show off, don't you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4" id="49">
                <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="major" />
                <state img="#-easy.png">Well~ Between the two of us, we're getting quite a few looks, huh, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-easy.png">Now we're getting somewhere. And I think I know where that is...</state>
                <state img="#-easy.png">Don't be shy, ~name~. It won't save you. </state>
                <state img="#-chatter.png">As someone who gets paid to take her clothes off, keep your day job. </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">If that counts as big stuff, you could wear me pretty easily, ~name~. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6" id="50">
                <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="major" />
                <state img="#-chatter.png">They say you can tell a lot about a person when they're down to their underwear. Not as much as when they're naked. </state>
                <state img="#-iukuk.png">As much as I love lewd jokes, I'm not about to start saying I should pay you anything, you know? Professionalism. </state>
                <state img="#-easy.png">It's almost a shame I'm not here to bang you.</state>
                <state img="#-easy.png">Finally, now I get to stare back. And if you claim I'm putting words in your mouth, I think there's something else I could put there instead! </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">You're not really going to stop there, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8" id="37">
                <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="extra" />
                <state img="#-easy.png">Even a small drink can pack a big punch. Just lay on the karmotrine, ~name~. </state>
                <state img="#-coquettish.png">If you're not going to use that to gag me... </state>
                <state img="#-easy.png">I'm not going to get upset over it, but my mind's elsewhere. And I think you know where. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8" id="39">
                <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="minor" />
                <state img="#-chatter.png" oneShotId="55">They say that lying's the most fun a girl can have without taking off her clothes, but they've clearly never met you. </state>
                <state img="#-chatter.png">Mmf... I'm feeling generous, ~name~. Anything you want to see? </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">That moment when you can see someone's expression change from a &lt;i&gt;little&lt;/i&gt; bit of worry to &lt;i&gt;lust&lt;/i&gt;... That really does it for me. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8" id="48">
                <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="major" />
                <state img="#-sugar.png">If I told you that you had a hot body, would you rail me until you sweat enough to cool off? </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">It's almost worse to be that close to being naked... and not able to even pretend not to touch yourself. </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">I'd &lt;i&gt;love&lt;/i&gt; to help you out of that, but... I'm a little busy over here. Maybe you should help me first, ~name~. </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_stripped">
            <case stage="0-6" id="59">
                <condition role="target" character="cagliostro" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-coquettish.png" marker="doro03">Aww, whatever could you mean? Referring to yourself in the third person just makes you sound like a silly-billy. If you really want to sound cute, ma'am, don't you think you could shift your posture a bit? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="62">
                <condition role="target" character="cagliostro" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-iukuk.png" marker="doro13">Pretty amazing technology if that body's all biology. Be yourself, whatever that self looks like, but not everyone can afford that kind of thing, you know. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="66">
                <condition role="target" character="toph" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-sugar.png" marker="doro03">...But I wonder if you own anything &lt;i&gt;else&lt;/i&gt; that's got some comfy bumps. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="69">
                <condition role="target" character="toph" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-coquettish.png" marker="doro13">Wow... What kinds of details can you &lt;i&gt;see&lt;/i&gt;? Even my tech's not built for that... That sounds hot as fuck. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="72">
                <condition role="target" character="toph" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-blow.png" marker="doro23">Honey, I guess I'm just asking what I can do to get you nice and wound up. Maybe I'm already doing that for you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="73">
                <condition role="target" character="cagliostro" stage="7" />
                <state img="#-chatter.png" marker="doro67">Well, fuck me with an overcharged vibrator-- Cagliostro's gotten the cute and totally fuckable look down. But you'd be the one doing the fucking, huh? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="76">
                <condition role="target" character="9s" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-coquettish.png" marker="doro23">No nipples? Boy, you're missing out on some of the best configurations out there...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="77">
                <condition role="target" character="9s" stage="6" />
                <state img="#-blow.png" marker="doro53">You look like you've never had that &lt;i&gt;equipment&lt;/i&gt; good and serviced, Oscar. Why don't you leave &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; to an &lt;i&gt;expert&lt;/i&gt;? On the house. And my tits, when you're done. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="82">
                <condition role="target" character="rouge" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-blow.png" marker="doro03">Honey, I didn't misspeak. But with a rack and some makeup like that, can you really blame me? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="87">
                <condition role="target" character="mari_setogaya" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-easy.png" marker="doro03">A girl's gotta work, honey. If you're always giving it up for free, you're not going to get where you want. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="90">
                <condition role="target" character="mari_setogaya" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-sugar.png" marker="doro13">On the plus side, if you're not looking for something longer term, it's easy cash, &lt;i&gt;and&lt;/i&gt; you get fed, if you want my professional opinion, honey. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="93">
                <condition role="target" character="ahri" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-glee.png" marker="doro03">I was wondering if I could go ahead and call you "mommy" for tonight! It'd get people really wired! Including me. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="96">
                <condition role="target" character="ahri" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-adjust.png" marker="doro13">If I put on a black wig, though, I think there's a whole other set of clientele I could get at, though...  Or maybe you'd look good in red...? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="99">
                <condition role="target" character="kumatora" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-blow.png" marker="doro03">Personally, though, I'd rather spend some time later tonight meeting &lt;i&gt;your&lt;/i&gt; ends. How about it, honey?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="106">
                <condition role="target" character="rosa" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-adjust.png" marker="doro03">From one working girl to another, though, make sure you get the part you want, and not &lt;i&gt;parts&lt;/i&gt; you don't. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="109">
                <condition role="target" character="rosa" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-glee.png" marker="doro13">Maybe that's something you save for a more personal encounter, I guess. Not that you'd make a career out of it, but if you want any advice to make &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; look good on camera, I'm your girl. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="112">
                <condition role="target" character="rosa" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-coquettish.png" marker="doro23">If you take me out to dinner first, though, I'd &lt;i&gt; make sure&lt;/i&gt; to end up between those gorgeous thighs of yours. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="115">
                <condition role="target" character="nanoko-chan" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-glee.png" marker="doro03">Happy to help you out, Nanoko-chan, you remind me of a good friend of mine, so you better take me up on it. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="118">
                <condition role="target" character="meia" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-chatter.png" marker="doro03">If nobody's ever told you they're proud of you for that... well, that's free. Have some fun tonight, though. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="122">
                <condition role="target" character="noelle" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-whocares.png" marker="doro03">...If you're an actual maid, how do you have time to do knight stuff? Lotsa girls work to put themselves through school and such, so why would being a knight... huh. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="125">
                <condition role="target" character="sucrose" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-chatter.png" marker="doro03">You're &lt;i&gt;adorable&lt;/i&gt;. You're cute... but still dressed sexy. I think we're going to get along great, sugar! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="127">
                <condition role="target" character="sucrose" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-glee.png" marker="doro23">My signal jammers are shaped like cat ears, too! You know lots of people are into that kind of stuff? Why are you embarrassed? Tons of people would want to fuck you, you know. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2" id="43">
                <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="extra" />
                <state img="#-sugar.png">If I ever get a bit annoying, you can always shove that in my mouth, you know. Your call what &lt;i&gt;it&lt;/i&gt; is, honey. </state>
                <state img="#-glee.png">This is so exciting! </state>
                <state img="#-easy.png">That looked easy, ~name~. But it's not the only easy thing here, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4" id="45">
                <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="extra" />
                <state img="#-easy.png">I could talk, but like I've said, there's other things you'd prefer me to use my mouth for, right, honey?</state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">Looking a little better without that, ~name~. </state>
                <state img="#-easy.png">What can little ol' me do to inspire you to go a bit &lt;i&gt;bigger&lt;/i&gt; and &lt;i&gt;harder&lt;/i&gt; next time? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6" id="42">
                <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="extra" />
                <state img="#-sugar.png">It's a good thing I'm not charging by the minute, huh? </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">Don't be shy, ~name~, or I'll really have to &lt;i&gt;make&lt;/i&gt; you shy. </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">Good boy, ~name~. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2" id="41">
                <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="minor" />
                <state img="#-glee.png">When you see as much as I do, you learn to appreciate all the little things. But I'm seeing big opportunities ahead, to! </state>
                <state img="#-glee.png">As much fun as kidding around is, tonight's a &lt;i&gt;little&lt;/i&gt; different, huh? </state>
                <state img="#-easy.png">If you think I'm gratiuitous now, just wait until people start policing you for playing with me! </state>
                <state img="#-glee.png">Heck yes, hell yeah, and all the other firey places people like to threaten me with! </state>
                <state img="#-services.png">Oh... not bad, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4" id="47">
                <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="minor" />
                <state img="#-glee.png">Aww... ~name~! Is that expression for me, honey? </state>
                <state img="#-easy.png" oneShotId="33">So... I have some open slots tomorrow, if you're interested it. &lt;br&gt;Got some tonight, too-- What, you thought I wouldn't go there? Speaking of going there--</state>
                <state img="#-whocares.png">Ah! So &lt;i&gt;that's&lt;/i&gt; what you were doing. With that thingy. You were wearing. That I was watching. Sorry, I kinda spaced out there. </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">You were holding out on us, ~name~. If you want me to hold &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt;, you can just ask~ </state>
                <state img="#-whocares.png">Huh. I'm glad you're getting more undressed. You'd be surprised what people are into. I mean, I'm not, I think everyone's got something beautiful about them. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6" id="44">
                <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="minor" />
                <state img="#-whocares.png">Huh. You know, I don't &lt;i&gt;actually&lt;/i&gt; masturbate that often. I'm usually getting fucked. Hm. Is that like, if you're always going out to restaurants, it's not the same to just cook at home? </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">...Yup! You'll do just fine later. </state>
                <state img="#-glee.png">Just because I'm paid for my job doesn't mean I don't enjoy it. Good to see more of you?</state>
                <state img="#-whocares.png">It's kind of funny. I don't think I've played a game like this that often, unless it's during roleplay... hm... </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">So, how about I buy you a drink in a bit? I'd say it's my treat, but we all know I'm delightful. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2" id="52">
                <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="major" />
                <state img="#-services.png">Oh. Well, hel-lo there...</state>
                <state img="#-services.png">...Why'd you hide something like &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; from us, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">I could see you as a regular of mine, ~name~. </state>
                <state img="#-easy.png">Lovely.</state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">If you're trying to make &lt;i&gt;me&lt;/i&gt;  blush, that's a good start, but if you want a good finish, you'd keep going. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4" id="53">
                <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="major" />
                <state img="#-whocares.png">It's kind of funny that people think this kind of game would devolve into a big gangbang. ~Name~'s attractive, but are we all going to go to town on ~target.ifMale(him|her)~? I guess we could. </state>
                <state img="#-glee.png">Holy tits. Looking &lt;i&gt;hot&lt;/i&gt; over there, honey!</state>
                <state img="#-whocares.png">Huh... I'd ask you to do that again, but you look nice like this, too.</state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">I'd say I'd head back to my bunk, but we both know that's not what we want. </state>
                <state img="#-services.png">Mmf... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6" id="54">
                <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="major" />
                <state img="#-glee.png">Let's get it going, ~name~. I know &lt;i&gt;you're&lt;/i&gt; going already, so help the rest of us out! </state>
                <state img="#-blow.png">Wow.. .would you like at &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt;, ~name~? </state>
                <state img="#-whocares.png">It's not a conflict of interest for me to enjoy myself. But I can't start fucking for free. </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">Curiosity killed the cat... but I can think of a few other things you could do to &lt;i&gt;my&lt;/i&gt; little kitty. </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">So, what's &lt;i&gt;your&lt;/i&gt; particular persuasion, ~name~? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8" id="40">
                <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="major" />
                <state img="#-adjust.png">Damn, honey... don't go stealing the show. </state>
                <state img="#-adjust.png">Sorry, everyone, I just got distracted by ~name~. </state>
                <state img="#-services.png">Mmf... ~name~... you gonna show us what's under there...?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8" id="55">
                <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="major" />
                <state img="#-easy.png">Just because I'm an AI in a body doesn't mean the other AIs don't have a lot to say. It's a whole new definintion of cyberprotection out there, ~name~! </state>
                <state img="#-easy.png">I may look like this, but I've got a &lt;i&gt;lot&lt;/i&gt; of practice in all kinds of things. </state>
                <state img="#-whocares.png">There's only really a few things I'd consider totally off limits. So, if you're creative, let's get talking. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8" id="46" hidden="1">
                <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="extra" />
                <state img="#-chatter.png">I'm not joking, you know. </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">If you're trying to tease me, keep it up. See where it gets both of us. </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">I like a ~target.ifMale(man|woman)~ with skills. Cards, or otherwise. But let's see how &lt;i&gt;lucky&lt;/i&gt; you're going to &lt;i&gt;get&lt;/i&gt;. </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0-8" id="101">
                <condition filter="gay" role="target" />
                <state img="#-adjust.png">Don't worry, ~name~. I'm a sex worker, not blind. I'm not going to hit on you. </state>
                <state img="#-adjust.png">I don't need gaydar installed to know not to flirt with you now, ~name~. Have a great time. </state>
                <state img="#-adjust.png">&lt;i&gt;*Sigh.*&lt;/i&gt; Have fun, ~name~. I'm not really equipped to do what you're about to be thinking of. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-services.png">Oh, honey, done playing already?</state>
                <state img="#-services.png">You're not trying to protect me, &lt;i&gt;are you?&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-services.png">I like a man that lasts a little longer, you know... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-chatter.png">Why don't you &lt;i&gt;show&lt;/i&gt; me &lt;i&gt;just&lt;/i&gt; how cute you think my panties are? </state>
                <state img="#-chatter.png">Enjoy the view, ~name~. </state>
                <state img="#-chatter.png">Just because I'm not putitng on a show for you &lt;i&gt;yet&lt;/i&gt; doesn't mean you can't look. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6">
                <state img="#-services.png">Oh honey... don't make a mess all over the ground when you have so many other options to shoot into. </state>
                <state img="#-services.png">My hands would just glide up and down you... or anywhere you'd like, ~name~... if you hadn't just lost. </state>
                <state img="#-services.png">Poor boy, having to rely on your hand instead of perfectly sliding raw into me...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-chatter.png">Hey, honey, people pay a lot of money to see me like this. But for you, you can enjoy the view for free, just this once. </state>
                <state img="#-chatter.png">We're about one slip away from you ending up inside me. Don't get the wrong idea. But do get ideas. </state>
                <state img="#-chatter.png">Not that I don't have a lot of vivid memories to draw on... but I'm always happy to make more. </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8" id="102">
                <condition filter="gay" role="target" />
                <state img="#-easy.png">I wouldn't mind us doing a &lt;i&gt;different&lt;/i&gt; kind of tag team if you want to send anyone &lt;i&gt;my&lt;/i&gt; way.</state>
                <state img="#-easy.png">But if you ever feel like experimenting... I'll let you do the first time for free, cutie. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-blow.png">Touching's not free... good thing my mouth is good for speaking, too, hm? </state>
                <state img="#-blow.png">If you finish fast enough, you'll be up for another round, won't you, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-blow.png">Honey, you can blow your load &lt;i&gt;anywhere you want&lt;/i&gt;, but only after my clothes are off, okay? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-blow.png">Take it all in now, ~name~. You never know if &lt;i&gt;I'll be taking it all in&lt;/i&gt; later. </state>
                <state img="#-blow.png">I've got enough self respect to just appreciate being looked at. </state>
                <state img="#-blow.png">Don't worry honey. There's  &lt;i&gt;always&lt;/i&gt; more Dorothy to see. Either in this game... or later. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6">
                <state img="#-sugar.png">C'mon, honey... you don't get to see this everyday. </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">Oh, honey. I'm not stopping there, you know. I've got you for at least the next 30 seconds, do I? </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">Just because I'm a master conductor doesn't mean I don't like an amateur performance. To extend the analogy, I also like having multiple instruments in my composition.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-coquettish.png">...You'd like that, wouldn't you? I would, you know. </state>
                <state img="#-coquettish.png">...That cock looks amazing right now. </state>
                <state img="#-coquettish.png">...You know, if you bought me a soda or something... we could work out a deal anyway... </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8" id="103">
                <condition filter="gay" role="target" />
                <state img="#-adjust.png" oneShotId="77">So... what kinda stuff on guys gets you going? </state>
                <state img="#-adjust.png" oneShotId="78">I always wanted to know what the difference between giving it to a guy and a girl is. Obviously in the butt, otherwise you have no basis for comparison. </state>
                <state img="#-adjust.png" oneShotId="79">Hm... You know, it's kind of soothing watching a guy with absolutely no interest in you. You get to see human nature at work, basically. </state>
                <state img="#-adjust.png">...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-pantyshot.png">You're really missing out, ~name~. I bet your balls will be empty &lt;i&gt;way&lt;/i&gt; before I'm ready to let you take me raw~</state>
                <state img="#-pantyshot.png">Just think of what I'm hiding under &lt;i&gt;here&lt;/i&gt;, boy. </state>
                <state img="#-pantyshot.png">Oh... Honey, do you need me to give you a nice view so you can cum?</state>
                <state img="#-glee.png">Cum! Cum! Cum! Cum! Blow your load! Cum! Cum! Cum! Cum! Fire it all in any hole!</state>
                <state img="#-services.png">Mmm... You don't have to wear a rubber with Lilim girls, honey~</state>
                <state img="#-services.png">You know, I offer a good discount if you buy me a drink first... think of all the naughty things you could do with me when I'm good and tipsy...</state>
                <state img="#-blow.png">Mmmf. I bet a pair of soft lips would feel better than those big, strong hands, ~name~...</state>
                <state img="#-coquettish.png">S-So, Mr. ~name~... What &lt;i&gt;are&lt;/i&gt; you into? Do you like girls like me? </state>
                <state img="#-easy.png">Honey, don't hold back. Recovery time is way more important than endurance~</state>
                <state img="#-whocares.png" oneShotId="91">You can cum anywhere you like... but I'd rather not pay for dry cleaning, so that's usually a little extra. But I guess if it's going to the laundry anyway, I may as well have as many people cum as I can, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-blow.png">If you're getting this riled up with my underwear, honey, just imagine my hips up and down your cock... just a thin bit of fabric between you and plunging that cock into me.. .</state>
                <state img="#-easy.png">So... are you open to feedback, ~name~? Or maybe you'd like to open my mouth up to feed me something else?</state>
                <state img="#-services.png">Oh, honey... I'd love to just ride you until you shoot your load all the way to the back...</state>
                <state img="#-coquettish.png">Mr. ~name~? Do you want to take advantage of my &lt;i&gt;extra flexible joints?&lt;/i&gt; Really &lt;i&gt;bend me&lt;/i&gt; and give it to me?</state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">A shame you don't have a nice, tight hole to shoot your load into, honey.</state>
                <state img="#-blow.png">Oh, honey... </state>
                <state img="#-easy.png">I don't say this to anyone, ~name~... but you're the type of man who seems to know what he wants. Let's chat after this. It can be a &lt;i&gt;short&lt;/i&gt; conversation, &lt;i&gt;or&lt;/i&gt; a long, hard one. </state>
                <state img="#-services.png">Oh, honey... Don't you want to just bend me over the nearest surface and ram my holes until you're satisfied? If I act like a little brat, is that going to make you want it even better?</state>
                <state img="#-services.png">Are you imagining how it'd feel to fuck me, ~name~? To just lay me back and hear me moaning your name as you bury your cock into either of my holes? Or maybe you just want to spray your cum all over my cute little face?</state>
                <state img="#-blow.png">Protein and sugar are pretty good fuels for my internal boiler, ~name~. And I'm feeling &lt;i&gt;tired~&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6">
                <state img="#-coquettish.png">As nice as your cock is... you'll probably make me feel so &lt;i&gt;tiny&lt;/i&gt; under your hands. Won't you make me feel loved, and cum inside, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-chatter.png">Damn, ~name~. Is this really doing it for you? Do you like the idea of me sucking your cock until you blow all over my face... your cum dripping down my chin onto my tits...</state>
                <state img="#-services.png">...Honey, what's it going to take for me to get over there and milk you dry?</state>
                <state img="#-adjust.png">So... where &lt;i&gt;do&lt;/i&gt; you want to cum for me? Maybe you want everyone to see how you've made me into your dirty little whore by covering my face or tits? Or maybe you just want to creampie me?</state>
                <state img="#-chatter.png" oneShotId="93">Just saying, if you're &lt;i&gt;curious&lt;/i&gt;... Anal's half off if you can cum inside my pussy within 15 minutes. Consider it my "Killed the Cat" special. </state>
                <state img="#-services.png">Honey... how much longer can you hold out...? I'm &lt;i&gt;so&lt;/i&gt; close to finger-fucking myself for you. </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">You know what to do with yourself... but now, so do I, ~name~...</state>
                <state img="#-easy.png">You can be honest, ~name~... you &lt;i&gt;like&lt;/i&gt; the way I look, huh? </state>
                <state img="#-coquettish.png">&lt;i&gt;W-wow...&lt;/i&gt; It... takes a bit for me to... You're getting me wet over here, ~name~. </state>
                <state img="#-services.png">Honey... that load better be for me. But I'll get it out of you however I can. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-chatter.png">...Feeling your cum squirt all over my hand as I stroke you to a finish...</state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">...My tiny, cute little tits softly stroking your cock up and down as my tongue works her magic on your head...</state>
                <state img="#-chatter.png">One of the &lt;i&gt;many&lt;/i&gt; nice things about Lilim girls is that our feet are nice and soft... if you're into that. And even if you're not, don't you like the idea of trying to aim for my pussy while you can see my face? </state>
                <state img="#-easy.png">Your cum could shoot right here, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-services.png">Fuck... ~Name~... Don't stop... Just... think of fucking me so good... my tight cunt wrapped around you, each thrust against my soft thighs bringing you closer and closer to marking me as yours for the night... </state>
                <state img="#-chatter.png">...Hah... Do you want everyone here to see your cum drip out of my holes? </state>
                <state img="#-glee.png" oneShotId="96">Are you the type of man that wants to be rough? To push me forward and mount my asshole like you own it, and just fuck your way into my memories until you empty your balls into to ass while I wail into the pillow? </state>
                <state img="#-chatter.png">You don't have to pull out, you know... but maybe you want me to walk around in your cum? Maybe answer the door for a delivery boy... maybe invite him in so you can use me like a tight little tool?</state>
                <state img="#-services.png">...I give &lt;i&gt;great&lt;/i&gt; head, if you can't afford to fuck me like the little whore I am. </state>
                <state img="#-glee.png">Just grab my legs and mating press me. It might not work the first time, so... I won't stop you if you want to see how many loads you can get into me... Actually, it's kind of a fun challenge! </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-sugar.png">I see that was almost as good for me as it was for you. Ha! </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">Don't you feel better? </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">In my expert opinion, you look like you got what you &lt;i&gt;came&lt;/i&gt; for. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-coquettish.png">Oh... someone's been a bit backed up, hm? </state>
                <state img="#-blow.png">You can say it was for me, if you want, honey. </state>
                <state img="#-glee.png">I see I haven't lost my touch. Without even touching! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6">
                <state img="#-easy.png">That's a good boy. </state>
                <state img="#-easy.png">Even if it was free, glad to see you got your money's worth. </state>
                <state img="#-blow.png">Maybe that'll be on or in me. Next time. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-easy.png">That really did it for you, huh? Well... close. </state>
                <state img="#-easy.png">What were you aiming for, anyway? If it was right here, you missed, honey. </state>
                <state img="#-easy.png">~Name~... Impressive showing. I'll be thinking of that... for a while. </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-chatter.png">Don't worry your pretty little head, ~name~. </state>
                <state img="#-chatter.png">So... I'm guessing the maid outfit really does it for you.</state>
                <state img="#-chatter.png">I've met plenty of guys who can rush to the end, if they want me to mock them a bit. but never a girl who was so quick to it. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-blow.png">So, time for me to blow your mind. I think I've got a few ways to do it. </state>
                <state img="#-blow.png">While you're down there, maybe you might think of putting your mouth to work, too? </state>
                <state img="#-blow.png">Hat's off, ~name~. Panties too, and soon to be...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6">
                <state img="#-sugar.png">As far as losing a game goes, this is a pretty bad punishment, right? </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">I've got a theory, ~name~. Do you think girls that are trying really hard to act all innocent have the naughtiest fantasies? </state>
                <state img="#-glee.png">If anyone tells you an opinion you don't like, now you &lt;i&gt;can&lt;/i&gt; show them where to shove it. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-chatter.png">You know... even if you've never tried a woman before... spaghetti's straight too until you get it good and wet. </state>
                <state img="#-chatter.png">Take your time. I don't mind going again later, honey~ </state>
                <state img="#-chatter.png">Imitation is the sincerest form of flattery. But feeling someone clench as they're coming is plenty sincere. Maybe I need to be taught some manners, ~name~...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-glee.png">But if you &lt;i&gt;want&lt;/i&gt; anything from me, you're welcome to request, and I can price accordingly. </state>
                <state img="#-glee.png">Oh, if you ask &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; nicely, I'll talk dirty to you. Just kidding, that's happening anyway. </state>
                <state img="#-glee.png">Aww... I don't usually get to do this while I'm fully dressed. This'll be fun, ~name~! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-services.png">I'm not too many layers from that myself. Make it look good enough and I'll join you. </state>
                <state img="#-services.png">Good girl, ~name~... just relax and let your fingers do the talking. </state>
                <state img="#-services.png">Oh... honey... you looked like you need that &lt;i&gt;so&lt;/i&gt; bad.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6">
                <state img="#-sugar.png">Say my name when you cum, and you get a discount, by the way. The louder you yell, the easier it'll be to actually afford the real thing~ </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">Just sink into yourself. Literally &lt;i&gt;and&lt;/i&gt;as a euphemism! </state>
                <state img="#-chatter.png">I shouldn't have to tell you twice to take a good look, but you're welcome to throw some flattery &lt;i&gt;my&lt;/i&gt; way, too. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-easy.png">It's not a competition. But if you're into it... </state>
                <state img="#-coquettish.png">And if you happen to look my way... t-that's pretty great too, huh, ~name~? </state>
                <state img="#-easy.png">It's rude to overcharge a Lilim girl, but I can handle a &lt;i&gt;lot&lt;/i&gt; of stimulation...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-easy.png">You look like you're enjoying yourself, ~name~. Hard not to! </state>
                <state img="#-pantyshot.png">If you like girls, you can enjoy this view, too, ~name~... </state>
                <state img="#-services.png">Oh... honey... you really needed that, huh? </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">You're a lot more aggressive with yourself than I expected, ~name~. </state>
                <state img="#-blow.png">You know, one of the advantages of my tongue is that I can actually screen for all kinds of things. As long as you don't mind me going down on you. </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">With all the work you're doing, this hardly seems fair, ~name~. </state>
                <state img="#-services.png">Was that moan for me, ~name~? </state>
                <state img="#-easy.png">Are you imagining just laying there, naked, and me taking care of you until you're done?</state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">If you &lt;i&gt;aren't&lt;/i&gt; imagining my soft lips at the nape of your neck, kissing my way along the edge of your jaw... are you now?</state>
                <state img="#-blow.png">"Oh, &lt;i&gt;fuck&lt;/i&gt;. ~name~! You're gonna-- h-hahh... you're making me cum!" &lt;br&gt;...That could be you, ~name~...!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-blow.png">Honey, I do plenty of work with women, if you're interested. </state>
                <state img="#-glee.png">Oh! This is so fun! It's like you're just there, waiting for me! </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">Honey... if you... yeah, just like that. </state>
                <state img="#-chatter.png">If nobody's told you you're beautiful, ~name~, there you go. </state>
                <state img="#-services.png">My tongue's jealous of your fingers, ~name~... </state>
                <state img="#-services.png">Mmf... The mess we could make... </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">What you want, not waht you need</state>
                <state img="#-glee.png">You look like the type of girl who masturbates at a strip poker game. Because you are, and that &lt;i&gt;basically&lt;/i&gt; means it's my duty to make sure we're both safe!</state>
                <state img="#-glee.png">Are you going to do... &lt;i&gt;Oh!&lt;/i&gt; Nice work, honey! Looking great! Sounding better.</state>
                <state img="#-services.png">Don't keep me waiting all night, honey... I want to see your legs shake and you clamp nice and tight around...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8" id="132">
                <state img="#-adjust.png">Hey, I'm kind of tired, but I promise I'll get some more lines to girls getting off soon, okay?</state>
                <state img="#-adjust.png">Whew, the next couple things I'll say are kind of rough, but I'll try and add a bit more here tomorrow. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8" id="130">
                <state img="#-blow.png">Honey, I do plenty of work with women, if you're interested. </state>
                <state img="#-glee.png">Oh! This is so fun! It's like you're just there, waiting for me! </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">Honey... if you... yeah, just like that. </state>
                <state img="#-chatter.png">If nobody's told you you're beautiful, ~name~, there you go. </state>
                <state img="#-services.png">My tongue's jealous of your fingers, ~name~... </state>
                <state img="#-services.png">Mmf... The mess we could make... </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">What you want, not waht you need</state>
                <state img="#-glee.png">You look like the type of girl who masturbates at a strip poker game. Because you are, and that &lt;i&gt;basically&lt;/i&gt; means it's my duty to make sure we're both safe!</state>
                <state img="#-glee.png">Are you going to do... &lt;i&gt;Oh!&lt;/i&gt; Nice work, honey! Looking great! Sounding better.</state>
                <state img="#-services.png">Don't keep me waiting all night, honey... I want to see your legs shake and you clamp nice and tight around...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8" id="131">
                <state img="#-easy.png">You look like you're enjoying yourself, ~name~. Hard not to! </state>
                <state>If you like girls, you can enjoy this view, too, ~name~... </state>
                <state img="#-services.png">Oh... honey... you really needed that, huh? </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">You're a lot more aggressive with yourself than I expected, ~name~. </state>
                <state img="#-blow.png">You know, one of the advantages of my tongue is that I can actually screen for all kinds of things. As long as you don't mind me going down on you. </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">With all the work you're doing, this hardly seems fair, ~name~. </state>
                <state img="#-services.png">Was that moan for me, ~name~? </state>
                <state img="#-easy.png">Are you imagining just laying there, naked, and me taking care of you until you're done?</state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">If you &lt;i&gt;aren't&lt;/i&gt; imagining my soft lips at the nape of your neck, kissing my way along the edge of your jaw... are you now?</state>
                <state img="#-blow.png">"Oh, &lt;i&gt;fuck&lt;/i&gt;. ~name~! You're gonna-- h-hahh... you're making me cum!" &lt;br&gt;...That could be you, ~name~...!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6" hidden="1">
                <state>Services</state>
                <state>Kidding around</state>
                <state>Nurture</state>
                <state>DYNAMIC</state>
                <state>Lilim Non-Human</state>
                <state>Anyone got a drink?</state>
                <state>What you want, not waht you need</state>
                <state>No sins here, honey</state>
                <state>Sweet as a sugar rush</state>
                <state>Limits are for squares</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8" hidden="1">
                <state>Services</state>
                <state>Kidding around</state>
                <state>Nurture</state>
                <state>DYNAMIC</state>
                <state>Lilim Non-Human</state>
                <state>Anyone got a drink?</state>
                <state>What you want, not waht you need</state>
                <state>No sins here, honey</state>
                <state>Sweet as a sugar rush</state>
                <state>Limits are for squares</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-sugar.png">You know, if you ever need another one like that, I &lt;i&gt;might&lt;/i&gt; have gotten a good record in my brainbox about it. </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">I liked the way your legs twitched at the end. </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">Be honest, you practiced, huh?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-easy.png">Thanks for getting them warmed up. Mind if I warm you up, later?</state>
                <state img="#-easy.png">Are we going to see more of you? I wouldn't mind a repeat...</state>
                <state img="#-services.png">Come again soon?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6">
                <state img="#-services.png">Don't you think it's rude to make that kind of mess? If only you had someone you could get to clean it up~</state>
                <state img="#-chatter.png">I'm gonna be real with you, ~name~. I don't have anything clever to say. I just want to make you cum. Again. &lt;br&gt;And again.&lt;br&gt;And again. </state>
                <state img="#-chatter.png">Now &lt;i&gt;that's&lt;/i&gt; the look of someone who needed to let go. Fortunately, we can help you get plenty of grip, too! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-services.png">...Fuuuuuuuck... </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">Hot damn, ~name~. You could make a career out of that. Not that you should, but &lt;i&gt;damn&lt;/i&gt;!</state>
                <state img="#-services.png">Done already? I could get another go in here with you, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate_first">
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-glee.png">Nice! Probably almost got you on that. Or not, do you really care? Don't report me to management or I'll publically shame you. </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate">
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-services.png">So... now's the time you get to not just &lt;i&gt;wonder&lt;/i&gt; about what it'd feel like to violate every hole in my body regardless of its original purpose, but maybe see me do it! </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="start_masturbating">
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-coquettish.png">You've got me so &lt;i&gt;vulnerable and exposed&lt;/i&gt;... What am I going to have to do for you, ~player~? &lt;i&gt;Pfft...&lt;/i&gt; Have fun watching~</state>
                <state img="#-coquettish.png">You can enjoy the view, even if I'm &lt;i&gt;exploring and exposing&lt;/i&gt; every single hole in my body, ~player~~</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="masturbating">
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-oya.png">Make my buffer overflow!</state>
                <state img="#-oya.png">Escalate user privileges! </state>
                <state img="#-easy.png">Put a backdoor in me-- or just fuck my tight little asshole, either's fine~</state>
                <state img="#-blow.png">Ah...</state>
                <state img="#-chatter.png">Oh, honey... you can be honest about how badly you want to fuck my tight, tiny little body until a human girl'd be sore. And I'd just be ready to keep going... and going... </state>
                <state img="#-iukuk.png">This is nice, but I usually just prefer to get laid than to just... &lt;i&gt;perform&lt;/i&gt;. </state>
                <state img="#-coquettish.png">Mmmf... I just... really, &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; need it. I feel so hot inside... c-can I show you?</state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png" oneShotId="98">Have you ever watched a girl finger herself while eating a girl out and a gentleman pounds her sweet ass? Would you like to? </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">Honey... part of the show is to just enjoy it. And I'm &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; enjoying it. </state>
                <state img="#-whocares.png" oneShotId="99">People get so bent out of shape... "Did she cum?" Like, that's nice, but you can enjoy pizza even if it's bad pizza, right? As long as you're happy, I'm happy. </state>
                <state img="#-services.png">...I've got a craving for pussy. 69'ing is &lt;i&gt;nice&lt;/i&gt;, but... making a girl question her contact to the bed sheets by making her cum from your tongue...</state>
                <state img="#-services.png">Cum for me... however you want...</state>
                <state img="#-whocares.png">It's actually kind of hard to just come up with things to say whne you're not actually getting railed. Give me a minute, and I'll cater to your fetishes in time. </state>
                <state img="#-coquettish.png">If I said I've been a bad girl, would you spank my skin pink? Hearing me moan and yelp with each slap... of your hands... or maybe... </state>
                <state img="#-oya.png">H-haha...</state>
                <state img="#-oya.png">...F-fuck...</state>
                <state img="#-services.png">...Why the fuck &lt;i&gt;wouldn't&lt;/i&gt; you finish inside me? I can't get pregnant and I'm not a host to anything that'd otherwise dissaude you from doing so. </state>
                <state img="#-services.png">Show me more... I wanna see...</state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">D-don't... hold back for me... I can handle it...</state>
                <state img="#-chatter.png">I'm not the right kind of fucked yet... </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="heavy_masturbating">
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-services.png">Oh... honey... don't stop... just like that... I'll be good for you, just don't stop...</state>
                <state img="#-services.png">I could take all of you... if you wanted...</state>
                <state img="#-coquettish.png">~Player~... you wanted me here, didn't you?</state>
                <state img="#-coquettish.png">Oh... I'm gonna cum... </state>
                <state img="#-blow.png">Oh &lt;i&gt;fuck...&lt;/i&gt; you're gonna make me cream...</state>
                <state img="#-blow.png">Just laying there and having every inch of my body taken care of by any number of implements and bodyparts...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finishing_masturbating">
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">Oh... &lt;i&gt;FUCK.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">C-come for me, honey...!</state>
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">Oh, oh, oh-- Honey, I'm-- I'm--</state>
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">F-fuck... D-don't stop I'm gonna, you're making me... &lt;i&gt;ah!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-adjust.png">Whew. Give a girl a second. </state>
                <state img="#-adjust.png">I might be Lilim, but I need a few minutes to cooldown...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="after_masturbating">
            <case stage="8" id="129">
                <state img="#-adjust.png">So... how many times does a girl gotta cum to get someone to buy her a drink?</state>
                <state img="#-chatter.png">That was &lt;i&gt;sooo&lt;/i&gt; fun! I bet it'll be even better to learn about all the interesting people here. </state>
                <state img="#-blow.png">So... anyone got anything new I can cater to?</state>
                <state img="#-coquettish.png">Oh... you don't think less of me, because of my profession, do you...?</state>
                <state img="#-easy.png">See? No mess, no stress. And &lt;i&gt;definitely&lt;/i&gt; never ever any duress. </state>
                <state img="#-glee.png">I hope you all liked that as much as I did! Love your job and you never get to work a day in your life. But &lt;i&gt;like&lt;/i&gt; your job and you don't suffer existential ennui! </state>
                <state img="#-iukuk.png">I'm kinda surprised. I like that you're all really respectful, but no offers yet? </state>
                <state img="#-l-lewd.png" oneShotId="108" marker="other_jobs">S-sorry! Just... thinking of some of the other jobs I've done, if you're curious...</state>
                <state img="#-oya.png">...Kinda... want to go again, honestly?</state>
                <state img="#-services.png">Mmf... I know I'm just waiting... but I'm still enjoying the view...</state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">So, if you liked &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt;, I think there's a lot more you could get into. In this case, &lt;i&gt;I'm&lt;/i&gt; a lot more. If you're shy, that's fine... but it'll be a little extra to meet me backstage~ </state>
                <state img="#-whocares.png">So, is &lt;i&gt;this&lt;/i&gt; doing it for someone? Watching a girl sit in post-coital bliss with herself...? It's fine if so, I just need to know how to build rates for it. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="128" hidden="1">
                <state oneShotId="90">x</state>
                <state img="#-chatter.png"></state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_victory">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-pantyshot.png">Aww... the least I can do is give you a last look at my panties... but maybe you'll play a better game next time .</state>
                <state img="#-pantyshot.png">You know I'm not &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; some inexperienced girl, right? Give me a better game next time, honey. Unless you &lt;i&gt;like&lt;/i&gt; losing, you little perverts.</state>
                <state img="#-pantyshot.png">Aw, come on, honey... don't you wanna see more?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-adjust.png">Ah... damn it. I'm wet and not even going to get off... &lt;i&gt;*Sigh*.&lt;/i&gt; I'll offer a discount if anyone wants to go again. </state>
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">Ooo... Some of you were listening! You've definitely left &lt;i&gt;me&lt;/i&gt; wanting more. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6">
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">I can't say I'm too surprised. But if you want to see me &lt;i&gt;at work&lt;/i&gt;... Just call my number, honey. </state>
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">I'm always up to go down, you know. Maybe you should pick me again, honey~</state>
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">You were all &lt;i&gt;great&lt;/i&gt; to play with. But are you great at other things, too? Why don't you show me in another game? </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_defeat">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-services.png">Aw... We're already done? We can go again if someone likes...</state>
                <state img="#-services.png">Mmf... Kind of a short job. ...I don't mind fitting in another game. Or other things. </state>
                <state img="#-sugar.png">Good game... I'm still up for a few more rounds, if you're all interested! </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="global">
            <case stage="0-2" hidden="1">
                <state>Services</state>
                <state>Kidding around</state>
                <state>Nurture</state>
                <state>DYNAMIC</state>
                <state>Lilim Non-Human</state>
                <state>Anyone got a drink?</state>
                <state>What you want, not waht you need</state>
                <state>No sins here, honey</state>
                <state>Sweet as a sugar rush</state>
                <state>Limits are for squares</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4" hidden="1">
                <state>Services</state>
                <state>Kidding around</state>
                <state>Nurture</state>
                <state>DYNAMIC</state>
                <state>Lilim Non-Human</state>
                <state>Anyone got a drink?</state>
                <state>What you want, not waht you need</state>
                <state>No sins here, honey</state>
                <state>Sweet as a sugar rush</state>
                <state>Limits are for squares</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6" hidden="1">
                <state>Services</state>
                <state>Kidding around</state>
                <state>Nurture</state>
                <state>DYNAMIC</state>
                <state>Lilim Non-Human</state>
                <state>Anyone got a drink?</state>
                <state>What you want, not waht you need</state>
                <state>No sins here, honey</state>
                <state>Sweet as a sugar rush</state>
                <state>Limits are for squares</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8" hidden="1">
                <state>Services</state>
                <state>Kidding around</state>
                <state>Nurture</state>
                <state>DYNAMIC</state>
                <state>Lilim Non-Human</state>
                <state>Anyone got a drink?</state>
                <state>What you want, not waht you need</state>
                <state>No sins here, honey</state>
                <state>Sweet as a sugar rush</state>
                <state>Limits are for squares</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

    </behaviour>
</opponent>
