<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>

<!--This file was machine generated using the Character Editor v6.7.9 at 5:11:02 PM on November 07, 2022. Do not edit this file directly unless you know what you're doing.-->
<opponent>
    <version>v6.7.9</version>
    <first>Dwight</first>
    <last>Fairfield</last>
    <label>Dwight</label>
    <gender>male</gender>
    <size>medium</size>
    <timer>21</timer>
    <intelligence>average</intelligence>

    <intelligence stage="1">average</intelligence>

    <intelligence stage="2">average</intelligence>

    <intelligence stage="3">average</intelligence>

    <intelligence stage="4">average</intelligence>

    <intelligence stage="5">good</intelligence>

    <intelligence stage="6">bad</intelligence>

    <intelligence stage="7">bad</intelligence>

    <nicknames>
        <nickname for="susie">Legion</nickname>
    </nicknames>


    <wardrobe>
        <clothing name="boxers" generic="underwear" position="lower" type="important" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="pants" generic="pants" position="lower" type="major" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="shirt" generic="shirt" position="upper" type="major" />
        <clothing name="shoes" generic="shoes" position="feet" type="minor" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="belt" generic="belt" position="waist" type="extra" />
        <clothing name="tie" generic="tie" position="neck" type="extra" />
        <clothing name="bracelets" generic="jewelry" position="arms" type="extra" plural="true" />
    </wardrobe>


    <behaviour>
        <trigger id="selected">
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~player~" value="Entity" />
                <state img="#-stern.png">Hahaha. &lt;i&gt;Very&lt;/i&gt; funny, ~player.ifMale(sir|miss)~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~player~" value="Lazar" />
                <state img="#-sad.png">W-Wha...? Why would you call yourself that? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-fidgeting2.png">F-Finally, I can relax for a bit... Oh! I'm Dwight, by the way.</state>
                <state img="#-content.png">Uh, Dwight Fairfield. That's my name, I mean. So... nice to meet you, ~player~.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_selected">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="meg" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Oh, um... Hello, Meg. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="susie" />
                <state img="#-scared.png">T-The Legion! Oh my god, I left my flashlight at the campfire. W-What do I do!?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_start">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition count="3-" filter="dead_by_daylight" role="opp" />
                <condition count="0" filter="villain" role="opp" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">Survivors poker night, then? I'm happy to play with you all, if that's what you'd like!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Survivor poker night, huh? Sure thing, I'd be happy to join you guys!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-happy.png">No hooks in sight! Of course I'll join you, ~player~. Uh, if that's okay.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Thanks for having me! I don't get to go out much, you know? {small}Hahaha...{!reset}</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="swap_cards">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <test expr="~cards~" value="0" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">Oh, wow! No new cards needed here!</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I won't need any new cards, t-thanks though.</state>
                <state img="#-content.png">I don't need to swap any cards, thanks.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <test expr="~cards~" value="1" />
                <state img="#-content.png">I think I'll just need one changed.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Just one should do it...</state>
                <state img="#-fidgeting.png">Uh, I think I'll only switch out this one...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-fidgeting.png">Um, I'll be good with just ~cards.text~ new cards.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Can I swap ~cards.text~ of these...?</state>
                <state img="#-content.png">~Cards.text~... Yeah, ~cards.text~ should be fine.</state>
                <state img="#-startled.png">Uh... Oh! Sorry, just ~cards.text~ new cards.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-nervous.png">P-Please give me ~cards.text~ new cards...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I'm really banking on these ~cards.text~ new cards...</state>
                <state img="#-fidgeting.png">Oh, god. Just ~cards.text~ should be fine, right?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">T-These ~cards.text~ will be much better! I-I'm sure of it!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-content.png">Just ~cards.text~ new cards, please.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Uh, ~cards.text~ new cards should do it.</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">I think ~cards.text~ will be just fine...</state>
                <state img="#-fidgeting.png">~Cards.text~ new cards, if that's okay...</state>
                <state img="#-fidgeting2.png">~Cards.text~ new ones, I think.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="good_hand">
            <case stage="3-5">
                <state img="#-horny.png" oneShotId="1" marker="boysnight">Oh! Maybe we could have a guys night back at the campfire and play this with one another! I know Ace has a deck of cards.</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">I'm getting better at meeting new people, if you can believe it. It's a leader's job to greet and explain everything to anyone new.</state>
                <state img="#-fidgeting.png">I hope I haven't been complaining too much to you. I don't get to just... talk. Usually I'm busy hiding in a locker.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Campfires are super homely, aren't they? They really melt away your stress.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Looking good, Dwight.</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">The plus of being a pizza boy was the free meal with each shift. PizzaWhat! is pretty damn good.</state>
                <state img="#-stern.png">My buddy told me to "let my heart out of the locker". What does that mean? Was he trying to make fun of me for being single?</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Claudette's taught me a bunch about botany and flowers. Now I know not to eat poison ivy!</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">The other trial, Meg looped the killer for like... four gens. Hahaha! He was so pissed! &lt;br&gt;Uh, did any of that make sense?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">All survivors have something great in them, really. Even the ones that are mean to me, like Yun-Jin.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-sad.png">We don't really &lt;i&gt;need&lt;/i&gt; to eat in the Fog... But I-I miss it so much! I want pizza, pancakes, cookies... I want junk food!</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">Brave and unyielding... that's what a leader &lt;i&gt;should&lt;/i&gt; be... Like Jake. I've never met someone as capable as him, or as stubborn. </state>
                <state img="#-fidgeting.png">There's this older guy, Ace. He's insanely lucky, especially with gambling. Really, I should have asked him for advice before this.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Are you sure these are my cards? They look too good to be mine.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Oh, do they play music here? I'd love to go dancing! I-I'm no good, but it's really fun...</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Alright!</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">It's been, what... six years since I've been able to eat pizza? Isn't that depressing?</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">I &lt;i&gt;hate&lt;/i&gt; being called into trials. But, sometimes, we do really good. It's worth it to piss off a killer.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I sure could go for some microwaved fish... The terrible smell is worth it, I swear.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Looking good.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Hey! I did something right!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Poker's just luck, huh? Is there any point in being proud when I didn't do anything?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Is dating even viable in the fog? She lives off our emotions... could love be one of them? {small}Or lust?{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I can't overstate how great it is to be out of the fog! E-Even if I'll have to go back...</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Even a guy like me got invited to strip poker. Take that, high school bullies!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">That's a relief...</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">H-Hey! Maybe some of Ace's luck &lt;i&gt;did&lt;/i&gt; rub off on me! </state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">You're making it hard for me to focus on my cards, ~player~...</state>
                <state img="#-startled.png">D-Don't stare, I get nervous under pressure. Or, that sounds bad... I don't! I'm a good leader, I swear!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Oh, lucky break! &lt;i&gt;Phew!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-content.png">Don't be mad at me, but I think I'll survive a little longer.</state>
                <state img="#-idle.png">Well, I am a &lt;i&gt;survivor&lt;/i&gt; after all. Get it? &lt;br&gt;{small}Did that even make sense?{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Is Futurama still running? I loved that show. Well, before being taken and all...</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">It's nice to feel an emotion other than terror, even for a bit.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="okay_hand">
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-idle.png">Once, I dreamed about a galaxy made of cotton candy... It was amazing. Uh, until Leatherface showed up and sawed me in half.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I wonder how many emails are in my inbox now... </state>
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">Urgh, can I get something more definitive?</state>
                <state img="#-startled.png">&lt;i&gt;Yawn...&lt;/i&gt; Oh, sorry. I'm not bored, I swear! I could just use some rest...</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I believe there'll be a day-- m-maybe tomorrow - where all the survivors are freed. It'll happen, I'm gonna make sure of it.</state>
                <state img="#-content.png">This'll probably be good enough.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I'll survive just fine, see?</state>
                <state img="#-fidgeting.png">Sure could go for some french fries right now...</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Oh! Could I get something to eat here? Do they take bloodpoints?</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">Sadly, I can't seem to remember any of the cocky one-liners Ash likes to say. Otherwise, I'd look super badass!</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">Ouch! I think I stepped on something... Oh, I didn't alert anyone with that yelp, did I?</state>
                <state img="#-stern.png">The Entity sure loves to pick on me. "Here's that crummy elf outfit you hate so much, Merry Christmas". Give me a break!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Actually, did you know the cop in the original &lt;i&gt;Scream&lt;/i&gt; movies was also named Dwight? Except he didn't... end up dying to Ghostface. {small}Uh, like I do, a lot...{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I keep rambling to you all, so I'm sorry about that. Uh, yeah. That's all I had to say.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Wanna see a card trick? I used to perform them at birthday parties! </state>
                <state img="#-fidgeting2.png">It's a little funny, some of the survivors seem to go out of their way just for me to praise them. I know I'm the leader, but my opinion isn't &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; important.</state>
                <state img="#-stern.png">Listen, I don't like country music. But in the fog, it's our only choice. Times are desperate, you know?</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">Aw, it's boring. Just like me.</state>
                <state img="#-fidgeting2.png">"Professional" clothes can cost so much. It's kinda stupid... I need this job to have money, how am I supposed to afford a $30 tie before starting?</state>
                <state img="#-fidgeting.png">My back is &lt;i&gt;killing&lt;/i&gt; me.. Did I sleep on it wrong? Or is it the fact I sleep on a wooden log?</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">I can't really hold my liquor, but I could really go for a drink right now. As long as it isn't moonshine, though.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Whenever I get too nervous, something sweet always calms me down. Chocolate, pastries, pudding... It's all great!</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">I once got stuck on the subway. I-I was too scared to ask anyone for directions, so I just sat there in this goofy orange cap. Humiliating, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-startled.png">Huh!? What was that noise...?</state>
                <state img="#-idle.png">What a boring set of cards...</state>
                <state img="#-idle.png">Hm? Oh, sorry, are you waiting for me to say something? Uh...</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">Meg's got these two braids in her hair, she says it helps her with running. Don't tell her I said this, but half the time &lt;i&gt;I'm&lt;/i&gt; the one braiding her hair for her.</state>
                <state img="#-fidgeting.png">Being a leader means more than instructions in a trial. I have to worry about morale, chores, offerings... It can get to be a lot.</state>
                <state img="#-idle.png" font-size="small">Would it be weird to tell David about this?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I'm definitely a cat person, even if I walked dogs one summer. Cats always seem to love me, and they're so soft!</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Sometimes my words come out all weird. Even through all those customer service jobs, I can barely talk.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">♫&lt;i&gt;It isn't true, I am not the ghost... Without a soul...&lt;/i&gt; Hm hmm hm~♫ </state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Sometimes I dream that I'm back at my office job, but I'm in my underwear and hiding in a locker. What could it mean?</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Sometimes just thinking about relaxing at home and eating pizza is enough to get me through the day... Well, I'll have to escape first to get back home, but still!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="bad_hand">
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-startled.png">I can't let my guard down. Who knows if someone is hiding around that corner...?</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">It'll be aldwight. &lt;br&gt;{small}Get it?{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">Typical for me...</state>
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">Rgh... Screw me!</state>
                <state img="#-content.png">I wonder if Ghostface and I could ever be friends. We both love classic horror movies, and... Actually, scratch that, he's a jerk no matter what.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">It's weird having my heart beat so fast for reasons &lt;i&gt;other&lt;/i&gt; than a killer nearby.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Oh, see... I can... I can try and do a card trick with these... Oh, I think I just creased that one. Sorry.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Are you a french fries with ranch, or a french fries with ketchup ~player.ifMale(guy|girl)~, ~player~? It can say a lot about a person, you know.</state>
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">The Entity's Realm sucks, don't get me wrong, but it's better than High School. </state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">One thing I'd tell my younger self? Head up, little guy! It doesn't get better, {b}it gets worse.{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Gotta stop talking about food... I'm not a glutton, or anything. It's just so comforting to eat something sweet...</state>
                <state img="#-fidgeting.png">I wasn't invited as a &lt;i&gt;joke&lt;/i&gt;, right, ~player~? Cause I usually don't get invited to anything... Especially things where I strip naked.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">I've stepped in bear traps, I can survive some bad cards.</state>
                <state img="#-startled.png">It's so nice here. No screaming, or... I guess someone &lt;i&gt;could&lt;/i&gt; scream in pleasure, or something. Was that weird to say?</state>
                <state img="#-fidgeting2.png">I was a dog walker one summer. There was this big dog named Treasure. God, she'd drag me on the pavement for as long as she felt.</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">A-Are you mad at me? Sorry, ~player~. I'm really sorry...</state>
                <state img="#-scared.png">Gah! I think I just saw a spider! Is She trying to spy on me?</state>
                <state img="#-fidgeting.png">Come on, I need to relax more. Mellow out, have some fun... {small}Deep breaths, like Claudette taught me.{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-stern.png">No matter how bad your life gets, &lt;i&gt;never&lt;/i&gt; work as a mall elf. I wanted to burn that entire outfit, as well as those stupid plastic ears.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">I'm man enough to admit it... When I was in high school, I was &lt;i&gt;obsessed&lt;/i&gt; with Nine Inch Nails. I had all their CDs...</state>
                <state img="#-idle.png">I don't get out much. Besides all those stupid realms filled with hooks, I mean.</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">I couldn't go a day without coffee back at my office job. Now look at me! I haven't had any in six years.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Y-You know, you're looking at Phil's Petrol's MVP. Nobody could... stand there... and pump gas, uh, like I could!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-5">
                <state img="#-nervous.png">When I was a pizza boy, they'd send me down all these shady alleys and freaky backroads... &lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;"30 minutes or it's free, Dwight! Move your ass!"&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">Everyone keeps telling me to be more confident in myself, but it just isn't that simple. Though, the praise is nice to hear.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Leadership is exhausting... I was just an office drone, it's not like I'm super smart or anything, either.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Oh, what a bunch of shit... Can I have a redo?</state>
                <state img="#-frustrated.png" font-size="small">Fuck...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">My hair used to be a bit longer, but like this it's so much easier to maintain, you know?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I've been trying to look in the bright side lately. Like, this one time after I got mugged I saw this big rainbow in the sky. It had me smiling the whole time I limped home!</state>
                <state img="#-startled.png">One time a guy flirted with me by saying he wanted to display my head on a shelf. W-What the hell is that supposed to mean? At least he found me handsome... </state>
                <state img="#-startled.png">I hope all these bad stories don't freak you out, ~player~. It's not karma or anything! I think I'm just unlucky.</state>
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">Shit, I bit my fingers too much... I think my pointer is bleeding. None of you feed on blood, right?</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Sorry if I seem on edge, I just can't get used to relaxing. If I do, then I'll let my guard down and hold everyone back.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">I remember my Dad making me try out for all these sports in high school. Of course, the jocks were pissed! Man, they'd leave me in a locker for the whole game.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I hope I'm not making anyone feel bad... I'm just really nervous by nature, I can't help it!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="hand">
            <case stage="0-7 9" id="16" totalRounds="0">
                <condition role="other" character="anatoly" stage="0" sayingMarker="introductions" />
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Oh my god-- She's so cute! I don't get to see many animals aside from crows... So this is a real treat for me!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="19">
                <condition role="other" character="ignatz" stage="4" sayingMarker="paintingoffer" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png">N-No thank you... Um, sorry. I appreciate it, but, uh... I don't think I'm worth wasting paint on.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9" id="18">
                <condition role="other" character="anatoly" sayingMarker="illiterate" />
                <state img="#-idle.png">(&lt;i&gt;...There's no way this guy is really illiterate.&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="other" character="jason" />
                <state img="#-stern.png">Since when did Jason wear skinny jeans and a camisole? Have you seen the films?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" oneShotId="8">
                <test expr="~background~" value="holiday lodge" />
                <state img="#-scared.png">O-Oh god! This is just like &lt;i&gt;Black Christmas&lt;/i&gt;... N-Nobody answer that phone, got it!?</state>
                <state img="#-scared.png">Gah! I-It's the perfect setup for &lt;i&gt;Black Christmas&lt;/i&gt;... Nobody answer the phone, and maybe Billy will leave us alone?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" oneShotId="9">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="british" />
                <state img="#-conversational.png">&lt;i&gt;"A'ight, wots all 'is den? Couple a' shite cards!"&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br&gt;Hahahaha! F-Funny, right? Right...? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-6" oneShotId="4">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="boysnight" />
                <state img="#-sad.png">Or... M-Maybe not. "Hey guys, want to play strip poker?" Yeah, Dwight, real smooth... {small}Idiot.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" oneShotId="10">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="david2" />
                <state img="#-horny.png">Uh, make sure David doesn't know I told you all that. He'd get all mad that I broke his "fighter persona". Heheheh!</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Uh, don't tell David I said all that. He'd get all mad that I "ruined his fighter persona". Hehehe!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="1" oneShotId="1">
                <state img="#-bashful.png" marker="pizzatoppings">Oh, you know my &lt;i&gt;favorite&lt;/i&gt; ice breaker? Asking what people like on their pizza! I'm a mushroom and pepperoni guy myself, but any pizza is good pizza!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="3" oneShotId="2" priority="0">
                <state img="#-fidgeting.png" marker="nervoushabits">I really need to stop chewing on my nails, b-but I just can't help it. I get so nervous sometimes. Does anyone else have any nervous habits, or am I crazy? Heh...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7" id="23">
                <state img="#-ass.png" marker="bigass">J-Just... checking the surroundings. &lt;br&gt;(&lt;i&gt;Is anyone looking...? Everyone seems to say my butt is my best asset...&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="14">
                <state img="#-sad.png">(&lt;i&gt;Man... I can't believe I'm having this hard of a time just talking. I'm so confident in trials, why can't I handle a simple conversation?&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip">
            <case stage="1-6">
                <condition role="self" consecutiveLosses="3" />
                <condition role="other" character="susie" />
                <state img="#-startled.png">I have to calm down... But my heart won't stop racing with her nearby! T-This isn't fair...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-6">
                <condition count="3-" filter="dead_by_daylight" role="other" var="survivor" />
                <condition count="0" filter="villain" role="other" />
                <state img="#-startled.png" oneShotId="5">Hey... Come on guys, aren't we friends? What about all the toolboxes I gifted you, ~survivor~?</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png" oneShotId="6">Sucks that I lost, but it's great that you guys won! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" oneShotId="11" priority="10">
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="entity">I should probably tell you about this "Entity" thing... That way I don't sound crazy when I talk about it.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="entity">Before I get ahead of myself, I should probably talk about the Entity. I don't wanna confuse anyone if I start talking about it.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_winning">
            <case stage="1-3">
                <state img="#-conversational.png">No big deal, I doubt I'll stay in the lead much longer.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Oh, m-me? Well, okay...</state>
                <state img="#-idle.png">You don't have to pretend to be interested, it'll just be something small.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">What can I do to stay in the lead? Come on, Dwight...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">O-Oh, alright! Uh, if you insist... {small}Or, well, you aren't insisting anything. It's just the rules of the game and all that-- Okay, I'll shut up now.{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Um, I'll stay positive. I lost-- but that's o-okay! I just have to show you all my... {small}uh...{!reset} N-No big deal at all!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-startled.png">Yeah, you all are probably mad at me anyways... I-I'll get right to stripping, then.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">S-Sure, I'll get to it... Uh, sorry about being in the lead, and all that.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">M-Me? Alrighty... I'll get right to it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-6" hidden="1">
                <condition role="other" character="susie" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">Still doing better than Legion, that's all that matters. Hahaha! {small}Please don't hurt me.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_normal">
            <case stage="1-3">
                <state img="#-fidgeting.png">Yeah, I'll get to it, then.</state>
                <state img="#-fidgeting2.png">It's no big deal.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Try not to die of boredom. I don't think I have anything interesting to remove...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Am I up again? A-Alright... I'll try and make this quick for you all.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-conversational.png">I don't mind losing again. Uh, if anything, these boxers are feeling a bit tight.</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">Uh, that's fine... D-Don't make fun of me though, okay?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Heheh... I-I guess I lost again.</state>
                <state img="#-idle.png">I lost again?</state>
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">Should've seen it coming...</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">It feels so nice to lose here! The stakes are so low... Nobody is going to stab me! That's so nice!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_losing">
            <case stage="1-3">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Every game needs a loser, it's only natural I fill that role!</state>
                <state img="#-content.png">I'm pretty sure I'll live without my smaller stuff. I just hope it doesn't get lost.</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">Uh, it's no worries. Losing comes natural to me, anyways.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Losing here is so &lt;i&gt;nice&lt;/i&gt;! There's no meat hooks, and I get to get out of these office clothes!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">O-Okay! {small}Man up, Dwight. You can do this...{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Ah... I-I guess my best wasn't enough. Just, keep your snickering to yourself, okay?</state>
                <state img="#-stern.png">Of course I would do this bad... Who would expect anything else from me?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Y-Yeah, I know I lost... Um, just give me a second, okay?</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">This is kinda embarrassing...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-6" hidden="1">
                <condition role="other" character="susie" />
                <state img="#-stern.png">D-Don't get a big head or anything, Legion. Unlike your &lt;i&gt;leader&lt;/i&gt;, I don't have a tantrum over every loss.</state>
                <state img="#-startled.png">Um... Is she staring at me? W-Would you tell me, ~player~? I can't focus on my cards with her there...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripping">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="entity" />
                <state img="#-stripping-.png" marker="entity2">The Entity... it's almost like a god. It feeds on me and my friends as survivors, watching us get chased around in Its realm by killers.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-stripping-.png" marker="friends">Before being taken by The Fog, I don't think I had really &lt;i&gt;any&lt;/i&gt; friends. Just a bunch of s-shitty jobs and bad coworkers.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping+.png" marker="cheerleading">There has to be some new ways to raise the morale of other survivors. How about I dress as a cheerleader and shout for everyone?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-stripping+.png" marker="david1">When David first arrived at the fire, he scared the shit out of me. All muscle and anger. That's the kinda guy who wouldn't listen to a dweeby leader like me.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping-.png" marker="david1">When David first arrived at the fire, I expected him to deck me in the face or something... A guy like that wouldn't take any orders from a dweeb like me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">This thing is so ratty now. I got it secondhand to begin with... Can you believe how expensive ties are?</state>
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">The Entity has a weird way of getting you into its realm. I got taken after passing out drunk in front of my boss. Guess I had to be humiliated one last time.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">I guess I could tell you all about generators and exit gates. But, to be honest, I'd rather not think about those right now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4" id="10">
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">I'm a guy, so I &lt;i&gt;know&lt;/i&gt; showing my chest shouldn't be a big deal... {small}I mean, David barely knows what a shirt is.{!reset} Just, ugh... Sorry.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">I know, I know... It isn't a big deal since I'm a guy. But it's hard for me, okay?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-stripping-.png" font-size="small">Shit, I think the fly got stuck... Come on, Dwight. Get it together!</state>
                <state img="#-stripping+.png" font-size="small">This is kinda exciting... Even though I doubt anyone is interested in me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">Y-Yeah, sorry... </state>
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">Don't expect anything great. If anything, you should look at someone else.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">This line shouldn't be playing. Send a bug report if it is.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripped">
            <case stage="7" oneShotId="5">
                <condition role="other" character="susie" />
                <state img="#-stern.png">Y-You're gonna tell all your killer friends about this, aren't you? J-Just to embarrass me. Well, I don't care! Stare all you want, m-monster!</state>
                <state img="#-stern.png">I-I bet you'll tell all your killer friends about this, huh? W-Well, I don't care! Stare all you like, y-you... monster!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="friends" />
                <state img="#-conversational.png">But being the &lt;i&gt;leader&lt;/i&gt; in there... Well, I, uh, don't think I'm the best pick for leader. {small}Maybe Meg is a better choice.{!reset} There're so many people I can call my friends, now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="entity2" />
                <state img="#-stripped.png">Not to get all depressing, h-haha! Sorry, too much, right? Uh... Yeah. Anyways! I took off my watch and all that...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="cheerleading" />
                <state img="#-horny.png">...That was a joke. You were supposed to laugh.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="david1" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="david2">But at his core-- he's just a big softie! We got real close. We both like The Clash, pizza, and hate Michael Myers!</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png" marker="david2">But really, he's a great guy! Who knew we had so much in common? Sometimes, we'll sing Clash songs together...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="british">Oh! Wait, wanna hear my impression of my friend David? He says it's funny!</state>
                <state img="#-content.png">I really could go for a beer. I know I shouldn't... I'll probably embarrass myself and get all drunk. But, uh, still.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-nervous.png">P-Please don't stare at me so much, it makes me anxious.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">I'm really n-nothing special. You don't need to stare so much.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-stripped.png">Sorry, I know I don't look very good. No abs, just... flab.</state>
                <state img="#-stripped.png">Whatever insult you're thinking, I-I've already been called it-- so don't bother.</state>
                <state img="#-stripped.png">Oof... Uh, I'm sorry. I'm a bit shy about my stomach. Uh, I don't want to bring the mood down, though...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Well, uh... Now you know what underwear I wear. Pretty cool, huh?</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">M-My underwear is kinda boring, isn't it? Or... uh. Not like I need anything crazy, it's not like anyone sees them. {small}Should I shut up now?{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-startled.png">This shouldn't be playing!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-nervous.png">This line shouldn't be playing.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-nervous.png">This line shouldn't be playing.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_strip">
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="12">
                <condition role="target" character="leon" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-horny.png" marker="leon_ms0">Uh, Leon, not to bug you but... Last trial, you left me on the hook. Um, i-it's no big deal or anything! But, maybe next time...</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" marker="leon_ms0">Um, not to bug you, Leon... But, last trial you kinda left me on the hook for a while. I-It's no big deal, or anything! But, um, maybe...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="28" oneShotId="18">
                <condition role="target" character="leon" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="leon_ms1">You did most of your work by yourself, didn't you? I can't imagine actually &lt;i&gt;fighting&lt;/i&gt; The Nemesis, especially all alone.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-sad.png">Sorry... I hope you aren't too mad at me, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Oh, wow! I won at something!</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Ace would be so proud of my poker skills...</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">Winning always feels nice. No complaints on seeing ~name~ strip, either.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">You did your best, ~name~. Be proud of that fact! Uh-- Unless you weren't doing your best. In which case, nevermind.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Sorry that you lost-- Unless you were trying to lose. Uh, if you were-- Congrats! Great work, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Well... Uh, we're eagerly awaiting, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-startled.png">It's always nice to get some eye candy-- Uh... If that's alright to say!</state>
                <state img="#-startled.png">You aren't gonna deck me for winning, right, ~name~? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7 9">
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Um, you're doing better than me, at least. </state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Shit... ~Name~ lost, and my heart won't stop pounding.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Uh... Are you having fun, at least?</state>
                <state img="#-idle.png">(&lt;i&gt;Man, I'd kill for a slice of pizza right now.&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-idle.png">Oh, this rules.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Well, you take your loss in stride. Nothing can bring you down, huh, ~name~?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-mast1.png">You came here to be looked at, right? T-That's the point of playing?</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I don't... I don't want to be creepy. Is it too awkward to ask if I can watch?</state>
                <state img="#-mast2.png">I'll try not to make this weird. Unless you, uh, like that. Or something.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">If I say something too weird, you'd tell me. Right, ~name~? Bro code, and all that...</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Hey... Thanks, ~name~. </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_strip">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="jason" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-content.png">Are you one of those girls who dresses up as "sexy" versions of things? Jason's kinda a strange choice. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" oneShotId="20">
                <condition role="target" character="mari_setogaya" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-frustrated.png" marker="maris_ms0">So you're like... a friendly succubus? I can trust you?</state>
                <state img="#-frustrated.png" marker="maris_ms0">So you're a friendly succubus, right? You won't hurt anyone?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Hopefully you don't think less of me for... uh... Not losing.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Well, it's not like you're out of the whole game or anything. That's good, right?</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I'm rooting for you!</state>
                <state img="#-content.png">Bad cards never killed anyone. </state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">If you do bad now, you're more likely to do better later on! Isn't that what gamblers tell themselves?</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Aren't girls clothes way more expensive than guys? W-What if you lose something?</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">Sorry you lost...</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Uh, it's cool that I won and all... But I feel kinda bad seeing ~name~ take the fall.</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">I-I'm not that good with words and advice. Sorry, ~name~. Unless you need instructions on fixing a generator, I'm kinda useless.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">D-Don't give up-- Hang in there, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Need a pep talk, ~name~?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7 9">
                <state img="#-fidgeting.png">Uh... Hopefully you aren't mad. </state>
                <state img="#-content.png">Don't worry, you're alright, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">I think I'm getting more nervous than you, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-idle.png">...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Ah... This is kinda cool. </state>
                <state img="#-startled.png">(&lt;i&gt;Why is it so hard for me to talk to girls!?&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">You've been really sweet this whole time, ~name~. Is there any way I could repay you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-sad.png">Sorry, sorry! I feel like such a freak!</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">I-It's not that I'm happy you lost, ~name~. It's just-- Um...</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">You can ignore me, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-fidgeting.png">Um... You're really pretty, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-mast1.png">If you don't want me to look, you can just tell me-- okay?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" hidden="1">
                <condition role="target" character="susie" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-startled.png">~Player~! Y-You need to be careful... The Legion are ruthless, you can't trust this shy girl act!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="14" hidden="1">
                <condition role="target" character="susie" stage="6" />
                <state img="#-scared.png">H-Hey!! I saw that, you know! Just because you lost again doesn't mean you need to take it out on me!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="15" hidden="1">
                <condition role="target" character="susie" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-stern.png">There's no way you're &lt;i&gt;actually&lt;/i&gt; some shy and meek girl. Don't you know what you do to me and my friends?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" hidden="1">
                <condition role="target" character="susie" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">I'm not sorry for what I said. I hope you lose one of those stupid shoes while we're here, too.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" hidden="1">
                <condition role="target" character="susie" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-scared.png">God... I'm getting too bold. I-I can't be like this to a killer! She's gonna rip me to shreds as soon as she can! Why did I try and step up for myself!?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" hidden="1">
                <condition role="target" character="susie" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I can't believe you brought a knife! J-Just what are you scheming? Did the Entity bring you here after me or something?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="tie">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Huh? What happened? Did I screw up or something?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-content.png">Don't be afraid to take your time.</state>
                <state img="#-idle.png">Yep. ~clothing.ifPlural(Those|That)~ sure ~clothing.ifPlural(are|is)~ ~clothing.a~ ~clothing~.</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">Don't worry too much about your ~clothing~. Uh, what's important is having fun!</state>
                <state img="#-fidgeting2.png">I guess I can take this time to adjust my own clothes.</state>
                <state img="#-fidgeting.png">I always forget how many guys accessorize. You know, even Leatherface wears a bracelet.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6">
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I'm not mad or anything, j-just a bit embarrassed.</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">So ~clothing.ifPlural(are|is)~ your ~clothing~ something important to you, or is it just for fashion?</state>
                <state img="#-fidgeting.png">I was never that fashionable. So, props to you for understanding it better than I ever could.</state>
                <state img="#-idle.png">Oh. Just your ~clothing~,</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7 9">
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Are you trying to make fun of me?</state>
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">I promise I'm not upset. B-But... really, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-stern.png">C-Come on... I'm literally standing right next to you, naked.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">Really, ~name~? If I didn't know any better, I'd think you were teasing me on purpose.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I guess I could just use my imagination.</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">Mm... Whatever.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Feeling a little better, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">Progress is progress, that's all that matters.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">(&lt;i&gt;What's that thing Ash said? Man, I have to be desperate if I really am thinking of reusing a pickup line from &lt;/i&gt;Ash.)</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">I can't believe I'm blushing over ~clothing.a~ ~clothing~...</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">All good now, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">I always find accessories to be kinda annoying, unless they have some practical use.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6">
                <state img="#-nervous.png">What are you staring at &lt;i&gt;me&lt;/i&gt; for?</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">Kinda was hoping for something bigger. Er-- Hopefully that isn't weird to admit.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I mean... I showed up with my own accessories too.</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">We can move on now.</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">It's the little things that make an outfit come together! {small}Not that I know anything about fashion.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7 9">
                <state img="#-sad.png">Kinda dragging it out...</state>
                <state img="#-content.png">It's not very time efficient, but it's fine.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">~Name~! </state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Can't I convince you to take a littleeee but more off next time? Pretty please?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-mast1.png">It would've been nice to have some extra help...</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">I-It's fine! I wasn't looking forward to it or anything...</state>
                <state img="#-stern.png">Well, I'll just look somewhere else, then. Happy?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I tried going to a speed dating thing, once. I sat on my rose and got a thorn stuck in my butt.</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">T-Take your time! We aren't going anywhere, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">You're s-- Uh! I mean &lt;i&gt;your ~clothing~&lt;/i&gt;  is, um, super pretty!</state>
                <state img="#-fidgeting.png">I can't believe how hard my heart is pounding. It's just ~clothing.ifPlural(some|~clothing.a~)~ ~clothing~.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Knock knock... {small}Okay, now someone can say "Who's there?", and then I can say something clever about her ~clothing~.{!reset} Oh. We're moving on.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6">
                <state img="#-sad.png">I wish I had my iPod in my pocket when I was taken, then I could listen to something while we played. Definitely would keep me energized.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">~clothing.ifPlural(They're|It's)~ r-real pretty, huh? I wonder where you bought it.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">You really are fashionable, ~name~. I'm kinda embarrassed I came dressed like this...</state>
                <state img="#-fidgeting.png">Most of the girls I knew just bought everything from Hollister. If you didn't, you'd probably get made fun of until you did.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7 9">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">I didn't think it was possible to feel &lt;i&gt;more&lt;/i&gt; naked, but I do.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">You're really embarrassing me...</state>
                <state img="#-fidgeting.png">Y-Yeah... Just take your time, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-sad.png">Is that what you chose? Oh...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">A-Are you trying to be cruel to me, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-mast1.png">No worries.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="0-7" id="4">
                <condition role="target" character="ms.fortune" stage="3" sayingMarker="Fortune_Strip_2C" />
                <state img="#-idle.png">The scariest thing is how little this phases me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-conversational.png">Be careful not to lose that, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Even without your ~clothing~, your style really shines through!</state>
                <state img="#-fidgeting.png">I used to wear a bunch of accessories from my mall's Hot Topic. Uh, luckily, I grew out of that phase.</state>
                <state img="#-fidgeting2.png">Oh... Sorry, I think I started daydreaming.</state>
                <state img="#-content.png">Are girls into guys who also accessorize? I always assumed they weren't.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6">
                <state img="#-nervous.png">(&lt;i&gt;Why is this making me feel so insecure all of a sudden?&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I'm not very good at talking to girls... And I can't really think of anything interesting to say about ~clothing.a~ ~clothing~.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Every little bit is progress!</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Flirting is left to the hot guys, right? Nobody wants a nerd to hit on them.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7 9">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Would you consider something a little more bold next time? {small}P-Pretty please?{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">It's my fault for expecting something bigger.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">What did you take off again? I think I missed it, sorry...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Hm... Sometimes, the smaller things are sexier than the big pieces. </state>
                <state img="#-mast2.png">Ah... S-So you took off your ~clothing~?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Your ~clothing~? Good choice!</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">We're getting there, aren't we?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Definitely bigger than choosing like... a bracelet. Still, not too overwhelming. Nice.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Is ~name~ trying to use some super smart strategy here? Maybe I should too.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">We're definitely moving faster now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6">
                <state img="#-horny.png">I didn't realize poker could be so exciting!</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">You're getting me all flustered... Could it be on purpose?</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">When you go all slow and intimate like that, you can make anything sexy.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7 9">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">A-Are you getting a little bit bolder, ~name~? I appreciate that.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">You sure know what you're doing...</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Only so many pieces left.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">You seem like you know what you're doing, ~name~. T-Taking it all slow like that...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-mast2.png">That's it... Good job.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Yeah... L-Let's pick up the pace. </state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">(&lt;i&gt;No way I can say that to his face.&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_minor">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Yeah... I liked your ~clothing~, you know. It looked, uh, really good on you.</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">Ow... I think I have a headache coming on... Oh! Sorry, your ~clothing~.</state>
                <state img="#-fidgeting2.png">All my clothes just appear by the campfire. The Entity sure loves to dress us up.</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">Do you feel more comfortable without your ~clothing~? Sometimes clothes can feel so suffocating.</state>
                <state img="#-fidgeting.png" font-size="small">~Name~ takes off his ~clothing~, and I'm already a sweaty mess.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6">
                <state img="#-conversational.png">That's fine with me.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">I'm a patient guy, so don't feel pressured to take off more, okay?</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I-I'll keep my mouth shut. {small}I doubt a compliment from me means anything.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7 9">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">You pull off your ~clothing~ so well, ~name~! Style comes so natural to you...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">I can't get too ahead of myself... M-Maybe it'd be better if I looked away.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">I'm happy I get to play with you, ~name~. {small}Hopefully the feeling is mutual...{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Uh, if I can say this... Y-You're real handsome, ~clothing~ or not...</state>
                <state img="#-mast2.png">That's really nice...</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">Y-Your ~clothing~, huh? {small}Cute...{!reset}</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-horny.png">T-That's a good choice. Your ~clothing~.</state>
                <state img="#-startled.png">Ow--! I think I just bit my tongue...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Have you done anything like this before, ~name~? Or-- Was that kinda rude to ask? It's just... You, uh, strip good. {small}I'll shut up now.{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">What ~clothing.ifPlural(cute ~clothing~|~clothing.a~ cute ~clothing~)~! You're real stylish, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I'm, uh, lucky to be playing with you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Is this exciting for you too, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">You can probably move faster without your ~clothing~ anyways. Then, if we get ambushed, you'll be able to escape super easy!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I've always wanted to learn how to sew... It's so much cheaper than buying into fast fashion.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7 9">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">~clothing.ifPlural(~Clothing~|~Clothing.a~ ~clothing~)~... Of course! What a smart strategy...</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">T-That's a good choice. {small}Uh, maybe something a little bolder next time, though?{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-fidgeting.png">Why are you looking over here, ~player~? ~Name~ is the one taking off her ~clothing~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-mast2.png">Mhm... Yeah, good choice.</state>
                <state img="#-mast1.png">(&lt;i&gt;It'd be creepy to stare, Dwight.&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_minor">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-fidgeting2.png">Does anyone have a cloth? There's this big smudge on my glasses...</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">Claudette is like... my best friend back at the campfire. She has the cutest fashion sense, too. Maybe I can tell her about your ~clothing~? </state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Any guy can appreciate a pretty girl taking off her ~clothing~.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Yeah, nothing wrong with going slow and steady.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Mhm. You're doing good!</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">It gets my approval as leader.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Clothing gets a bit stuffy sometimes, you know? Do you feel any better now, ~name~?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7 9">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Y-Yeah... Feeling very naked, right now.</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Oh! I think I just got chills... </state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">If I'm annoying you, can you let me know? I'm not very good at this stuff...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-nervous.png">(&lt;i&gt;No girl wants a nerd to hit on them, Dwight. Keep that to yourself.&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">N-Nice...</state>
                <state img="#-mast2.png">H-How kind of you, ~name~...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_major">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-startled.png">R-Really? Your ~clothing~?</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Huh... I guess I'm not as unlucky as I thought...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">That's a big step, ~name~. Do you need any help from me?</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Sorry! Sorry... I-I don't mean to stare so intensely.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">(&lt;i&gt;Did my stomach just growl? That's so humiliating...&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">You sure know how to fluster a guy, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7 9">
                <state img="#-horny.png">It's hard for me to take my eyes off you, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Ohh... My face is burning up!</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">I, uh, like this choice. It's good.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">I hope my glasses don't fog up, I'd really like to see this.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Y-You're the best, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-mast2.png">Man, I'd do anything for you...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">I appreciate it, ~name~. Is there anything you'd want in return?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_major">
            <case stage="0-7 9" id="17">
                <condition role="target" character="anatoly" stage="5" sayingMarker="paskaleaves" />
                <state img="#-conversational.png">It'll be okay! We... uh... We can just follow her scratch marks, right? Yeah!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="21">
                <condition role="target" character="steve" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-idle.png">I guess we both are pretty hairy...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-idle.png" font-size="small">I think I forgot to blink.</state>
                <state img="#-fidgeting.png">Fuck, it's been so long since I got to see &lt;i&gt;anything&lt;/i&gt; like this...</state>
                <state img="#-fidgeting.png">D-Do we really have to move on so soon? </state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Um, I hope you're okay with my staring, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">You're living proof that there are things better than pizza, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">(&lt;i&gt;I've got no idea if ~name~ likes guys... I'm being really bold acting the way I am, huh?&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7 9">
                <state img="#-horny.png">You're like... uh, r-really handsome. Good job.</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">Uh, ~name~... Would you want to get some drinks sometime? Y-You can say no, I'd understand.</state>
                <state img="#-startled.png">My hair isn't a mess, is it? I-I look presentable, right!?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Yeah, just like that...</state>
                <state img="#-mast2.png">The view is really appreciated, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-heavy2.png">&lt;i&gt;Oh!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-mast2.png">Man, that's a lot of skin.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_major">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-conversational.png">~Name~ could be a model, really. </state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">I could get used to winning, especially if the reward is like this.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">It feels good to win for once.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">You uh... Seem to know what you're doing, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I hope this isn't too weird for you.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Y-Your ~clothing~? That's a really good choice!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-mast2.png">Ah... ~name~...</state>
                <state img="#-fidgeting.png">D-Don't look at me like that!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7 9">
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Victory is sweet, but also really awkward.</state>
                <state img="#-idle.png">She's taking off her ~clothing~...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_major">
            <case stage="0-9" id="11">
                <condition role="target" character="mari_setogaya" stage="4" sayingMarker="Mari_wings_reveal" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I hope it doesn't offend you... But I'm gonna keep m-my distance, Mari. I don't know if you want to eat me alive or not.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-conversational.png">L-Looking good, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Moving along...</state>
                <state img="#-content.png">That seems like it was important. You're positive you're okay without your ~clothing~, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Definitely an interesting way to meet new people, isn't it?</state>
                <state img="#-fidgeting.png">Don't leave it on the floor! What if someone steps on it?</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">There's a real classic appeal to a woman's ~clothing~.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">I can't buy you a drink, but I could give you a really good medkit. W-Would you want that, ~name~?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7 9">
                <state img="#-horny.png">It's worth each loss to be able to see ~name~ like this.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I never had much luck with girls {small}or guys, really{!reset}. T-This isn't totally new, or anything-- but it takes some getting used to.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I've never been good with words... But ~name~, you're, uh. Very pretty.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-mast1.png">Before you know it, you'll be on the floor like I am.</state>
                <state img="#-mast2.png">(&lt;i&gt;If name caught me staring, she'd probably step on me or something... That thought really shouldn't turn me on.&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I definitely appreciate it.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-horny.png">It's nothing new to me, really. But it's normal to get kinda excited for.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">It's not uncommon for most of the guys at the campfire to take their shirts off. And I mean... who am I to complain about that?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Uh, no need to be shy. It's not just about muscle -- all chests are good chests, right?</state>
                <state img="#-startled.png">I-I'd been thinking about you and your chest, ~name~-- Shit, that sounds creepy.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7 9">
                <state img="#-horny.png">S-Stay strong, Dwight. Will yourself to stay down.</state>
                <state img="#-fidgeting.png">I-I'm much too excited. I can't help but bite my nails...</state>
                <state img="#-stern.png">It's only fair! You got to see mine, right?</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">It's a good thing we're here and not in a trial, or something. No way I'd be able to focus with ~name~ shirtless.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-horny.png">I was already interested in looking you, ~name~. This makes it even more worth it.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">My hero!</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">You must look &lt;i&gt;amazing&lt;/i&gt; under that, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">It's like all my dreams are coming true... This has to be some trick, right? Hahaha!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-7 9" id="20">
                <condition role="target" character="steve" />
                <state img="#-sad.png" marker="steve_chestreveal">I've always wanted some chest hair... I guess it wasn't meant to be. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="22">
                <condition role="target" character="steve" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" marker="steve_chestreveal">(&lt;i&gt;I can't say that... Who could ever respect a leader who admits something so lewd?&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition filter="muscular" role="target" />
                <state img="#-idle.png" oneShotId="2">D-Dude... Your pecs are the things of dreams.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png" oneShotId="3">You must really take care of yourself, huh? C-Cool... that's cool.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png" oneShotId="4">Were you looking forward to taking that off, just to show off all your muscles? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition filter="chubby" role="target" />
                <state img="#-bashful.png">You look so soft... a-and your chest is like... perfect for resting your head on.</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">The perfect kinda guy to snuggle up with in front of the campfire.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">You look perfect, ~name~. I-I'm really lucky to be here.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">You sure know how to stay in shape, huh?</state>
                <state img="#-idle.png" font-size="small">I think seeing it fried my brain.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Man, I think my hands are shaking. Do you usually have this effect on people, ~name~?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7 9">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">It's practically perfect for resting your head on...</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">M-Mine barely compares. That's a &lt;i&gt;real&lt;/i&gt; man's chest.</state>
                <state img="#-idle.png">(&lt;i&gt;Man do I wanna touch him... His skin is probably so soft.&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-mast2.png">(&lt;i&gt;I wonder how mad he'd be if I licked from his stomach to his pecs...&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Fuck, that's good.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Totally stunning...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-horny.png">We're definitely moving fast now, aren't we? Not that I'm complaining!</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">The build up is the best part, really.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">S-So now we all see your...?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Better than all the bloodpoints in the world.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7 9">
                <state img="#-stern.png">I'm not gonna make some joke about you being "dead hard", so don't expect one.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Give me a second to calm my heart down, o-okay?</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" font-size="small">Mm.... Heheheh...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-idle.png">You're gonna show us, ~name~? R-Really...?</state>
                <state img="#-mast2.png">Man, I don't deserve this.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">You know exactly what I need, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Remind me to show my thanks to you later.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_small_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Oh! Well, that's no big deal, then.</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">Hey... It's fine! All that matters is how you use it, right?</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">I'm sure you could still make the girl of your dreams happy, ~name~. O-Or guy!</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">Uh, you don't need to be so shy about it. It's not like you have much control on how big it is, anyways.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7 9">
                <state img="#-conversational.png">It's, uh, cute! People love cute guys, too. {small}...Does that make you feel better?{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">Some guys care way too much about this. ~Name~, stand proud! You're cute and that's what's important here!</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">Small doesn't have to mean bad, you know? It's perfect.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-horny.png">I'm sure you know what you're doing with it, huh? Mm... I'd like to see that.</state>
                <state img="#-mast2.png">I'd take anything at this point.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">It's kinda small, huh? Oh! T-That wasn't meant to be an insult, sorry! It's... it's really cute, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_medium_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-content.png">Good. It... uh. It's good.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">I-I mentioned I'm into guys, right? Hahaha...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">See... If I knew any good one liners, I'd say them now. Though you'd probably just find them dorky...</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">You already had my interest, ~name~. Though I appreciate the sight, heheh...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7 9">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Any way I can see you for a bit after this game?</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">Looks like you'll be on the floor soon, huh, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">(&lt;i&gt;Do they sell lube here, or something? I'd kill to have ~name~ in me.&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-horny.png">It looks perfect for the job. </state>
                <state img="#-fidgeting.png">W-Whatever it is you want, I swear I'll do it!</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">D-Did it just twitch? {small}Cute...{!reset}</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_large_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-7" id="5">
                <condition role="target" character="takatoshi" />
                <state img="#-conversational.png">H-Hey, it isn't something to be embarrassed about, Takatoshi!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" oneShotId="6">
                <condition filter="huge_penis" role="target" />
                <state img="#-startled.png">O-Okay! That's too big, now I'm freaked out!</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">T-That's too much! Geez, it freaks me out more than anything!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-idle.png">...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Hey, are you trying to make me blush or something? Cause it's working!</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">You can't blame me for being starstruck... </state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">Brings me back to the locker room. All those mean, muscly jocks...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7 9">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Y-You're trying to fluster me, aren't you, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">S-Sorry! Sorry... I don't mean to stare at it, but it's just... Damn.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">It'd be a bit of a challenge... but the reward would be worth it.</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">W-Who ordered the extra sausage pizza? {small}Jesus, that was awful.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Oh, &lt;i&gt;w-woah&lt;/i&gt;... </state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Not too big for me, I promise I could take you.</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Oh &lt;i&gt;man&lt;/i&gt;! You really aren't messing around, huh?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-fidgeting.png">Boobs... Boobs are good.</state>
                <state img="#-content.png">Uh, do girls find magic tricks dorky, still? I might still remember one... It's when you-- Oh, who cares.</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">Uh, if you'd rather I just look away, I won't be mad. </state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">You're real bold, ~name~. It's s-sexy.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7 9">
                <state img="#-conversational.png">Much more important than a guy's chest, right?</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">M-My face is getting all hot... </state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">I hope my glasses don't fog up, then I'll miss ~name~ taking off her ~clothing~...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-mast2.png">It's &lt;i&gt;so&lt;/i&gt; worth getting out of my comfort zone, especially if I get to see people like ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">You've made me the happiest guy on Earth,~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-mast2.png">Oh... I-I don't know if I can handle that...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_small_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">There's no way people &lt;i&gt;actually&lt;/i&gt; don't like small chests. E-Especially when the girl is as cute as ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">(&lt;i&gt;I think &lt;/i&gt;my&lt;i&gt; chest is bigger than hers.&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Uh, I think you look great, ~name~! I doubt that means much to you-- but, uh, yeah!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7 9">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Oh... You're too cute like that!</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">(&lt;i&gt;I wonder if they're more delicate at that size.&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-idle.png">S-Small boobs are great. Some guys are too picky, in my opinion.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-mast2.png">No complaints here.</state>
                <state img="#-fidgeting.png">I-I'm not used to good things. ~Name~... you're not hiding anything, right?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_medium_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-idle.png">No matter what happens, one thing rings true... Boobs are great.</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">I-I already knew you were pretty, this just further proves my point.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">I-It's not like this is totally new to me, or anything. It's just been a while, you know?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">It's gonna be a bit hard focusing on my cards after this...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7 9">
                <state img="#-idle.png">My mind is blanking. I think I can't do anything but stare.</state>
                <state img="#-startled.png">S-Sorry! I hope my staring isn't too much for you! Um, I can look somewhere else.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">A g-great size! Or, well... All sizes are great, you know?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-mast2.png">Great... ~Name~, you're great...</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">(&lt;i&gt;Keep that thought to yourself, Dwight.&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_large_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Is it harder to run with such a large chest? It's a really good thing you don't need to worry about trials.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I think big boobs are a trait of slasher victims... Be careful, okay?</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">I-I don't even know what to say-- You have to know how hot you are already, so do I need to repeat it?</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Somehow, they make me feel safe.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7 9">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">(&lt;i&gt;Just resting my head on them would be more than enough.&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Just the sight is enough to make my hands start shaking.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Isn't this the type of thing every guy dreams about?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-horny.png">T-They bounced a little while you were taking off your ~clothing~. Uh, if anyone else noticed.</state>
                <state img="#-mast2.png">They'd probably fit in the palm of my hand &lt;i&gt;r-really well&lt;/i&gt;... Damn.</state>
                <state img="#-mast1.png">Keep your mouth shut, Dwight. Don't humiliate yourself.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-9" id="12">
                <condition role="target" character="sannytess" sayingMarker="COCK" />
                <state img="#-idle.png">Well that's unexpected.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-fidgeting.png">I-I can't get too distracted! I need to make sure we really are alone...</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I, uh, am looking forward to seeing more of you.</state>
                <state img="#-fidgeting.png">I've seen hell... And now, ~name~ is gonna show me heaven.</state>
                <state img="#-scared.png">ACK!  Oh-- Sorry. I thought... I think there was a bug on me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7 9">
                <state img="#-fidgeting.png">I-If you want me to look away, just let me know, okay?</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">I-- Uh... Heh.</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Oh, this is like, a r-really big deal, isn't it? Maybe I should wipe my glasses off, first...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-idle.png">...</state>
                <state img="#-mast2.png">I wonder if the guys back at the campfire would be jealous... </state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">No way I'm &lt;i&gt;this&lt;/i&gt; lucky.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Your figure is l-like, hypnotic to look at. </state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">The way your stomach dips down... It's really cute.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Well, t-there you are! Um, how do you feel?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7 9">
                <state img="#-horny.png">T-This is crazy. I mean-- Like, in a good way! Uh, or maybe I'm making it a bigger deal than it is?</state>
                <state img="#-fidgeting.png">I'll just... look away.</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">We're matching, i-if you think about it!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-mast2.png">You can yank me by the hair whenever you want, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-mast1.png">(&lt;i&gt;Is she wet? ...Is that self centered to wonder? I mean, I doubt it's cause of me, but...&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-mast2.png" font-size="small">Ah-- There's nothing more blissful than the feeling of thighs around your neck...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_lost">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="meg" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Meg, are you okay? I-It's just... you aren't acting like yourself...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="steve" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="steve_ms0">Heheh... Of course you'd be here, Steve. It seems like your kinda place.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="steve" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-conversational.png" marker="steve_ms1">I'm glad you're here, you know? You're always so energetic-- It's so nice to see.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="steve" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png" marker="steve_ms2">Oh! Actually, while you're here... I wanted to ask for some hair advice?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="yuno_uno" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-conversational.png" marker="yuno_ms0">I'd offer to play some Uno with you, but it'll probably get boring with how bad I am... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="yuno_uno" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-content.png" marker="yuno_ms1">You're from New York, right? I can't imagine living there-- Everything is so expensive...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition filter="dead_by_daylight" role="target" />
                <condition count="0" filter="villain" role="target" />
                <state img="#-content.png" oneShotId="10">No worries on losing, right? Think about why you lost, and apply that to the next round. You're doing great!</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png" oneShotId="11">Hey, it's fine, ~name~. Loss is inevitable, yeah? Either way, I think you're doing great!</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png" oneShotId="9">Stay focused and move forwards. But most importantly, have fun, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png" oneShotId="12">Definitely not the time for a pep talk, is it? Hahaha...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" hidden="1">
                <condition role="target" character="susie" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-sad.png">Um... I'm sorry for yelling at you earlier. I-It's just... I'm kinda tired of being slaughtered. I didn't mean to be so aggressive... </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_stripping">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="yuno_uno" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-bashful.png" marker="yuno_s0">Though I could teach you some of the tricks I know... Like, how to make cards disappear, or that whole "Is this your card?" schtick.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="19">
                <condition role="target" character="yuno_uno" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-bashful.png" marker="yuno_s1">But, uh... Is New York pizza really the best kind? Be brutally honest here!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="mari_setogaya" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" marker="maris_s0">Sorry, I know that was rude to ask -- I can't be too careful, though. For all I know, you could be on &lt;i&gt;Her&lt;/i&gt; side.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" hidden="1">
                <condition role="target" character="susie" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">Do you know how hard it is to be a leader in hell? Probably not, since you just listen to your stupid friend. It's so hard to keep all those people happy.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_stripped">
            <case stage="0-9" id="24" oneShotId="17">
                <condition status="exposed" role="target" />
                <condition count="1" status="exposed" />
                <test expr="~target.biggestlead~" cmp="&gt;=" value="3" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png">What's wrong, ~name~? You're really losing your focus... Is something bugging you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" hidden="1">
                <condition role="target" character="susie" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png">So without your mask... You really are just a normal girl. That's freaky. I-I think you should keep the mask on.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" hidden="1">
                <condition role="target" character="susie" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-stern.png">After a lifetime of misery, I have to become some teenager's toy. &lt;br&gt;{b}I &lt;i&gt;hate&lt;/i&gt; you, Susie.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-surprised.png">~Name~? Oh, I'm shocked he's losing before me...</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Take it in stride, ~name~! Y-You're handsome, you can own this!</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">Ah, well... I-I was really rooting for you, I swear. I'll enjoy the view, though.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7 9">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">It's probably a bit presumptuous to say you can look at me. I won't be offended if you look somewhere else, heh.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Uh, be sure to enjoy yourself and all that...</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">I don't think I can watch. I-It might rile me up too much, haha...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-mast1.png">T-The both of us are gonna...?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I've been waiting for this, you know.</state>
                <state img="#-mast2.png">I hope you don't mind me being like this...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-conversational.png">Uh, yeah. Get comfortable.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Let me know if you need any help, yeah?</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Oh, h-he's really starting, huh? Not that I'm complaining, I mean.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7 9">
                <state img="#-conversational.png">Show me what you've got, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">Don't worry about proving yourself or anything, just enjoy it, yeah?</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Nothing strange about watching ~name~, right? It's the point of the game, after all...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-idle.png">~Name~?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Uh... Thanks, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">No complaints here!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_masturbating">
            <case stage="7 9">
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Hopefully I don't gross you out.</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">(&lt;i&gt;Should I try and show off for ~name~? Maybe he'd like if I turned around...&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">(&lt;i&gt;He's kinda loud.&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">You're making my knees all weak. Do you always have this affect one people, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-stern.png">Don't slow down, ~name~. Come on!</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">I'm really enjoying our time together, you know?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-mast1.png">A-Am I helping at all?</state>
                <state img="#-mast2.png">You do it in your own way... Even if the movements are similar.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">You know what you're doing, huh? So you're comfortable taking the lead?</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">I-I'm not clever enough to say it sexily, so I'll just say you're hot.</state>
                <state img="#-mast2.png">You caught my eye t-the second we started, you know?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">It's a little hard to focus.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Really, this is good practice for not getting distracted during a trial.</state>
                <state img="#-startled.png">Sorry! I didn't mean to make eye contact...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">No need to make this a big deal, right?</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Shockingly, not the first time I've seen something like this. {small}Heh.{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-fidgeting.png">Can't lose my focus. You understand, right, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Looks like you know what you're doing.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">That face you made was really cute...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-startled.png">G-Gah!  Oh, it startled me...</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">Need a second to catch your breath?</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Y-You're giving me some ideas, you know.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7 9">
                <state img="#-horny.png">How many seconds until you're no longer exhausted, ~name~? {small}Maybe then... round two?{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">That's a sight I can never get enough of.</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">&lt;i&gt;Sigh...&lt;/i&gt; It's been way too long.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Oh... T-That looked like a lot, huh?</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">I don't think I can get enough of you, ~name~. </state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Was it as good for you as it was for me?</state>
                <state img="#-mast2.png">(&lt;i&gt;Shit... if only it was inside.&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="susie" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="susie_lost">Make sure to tell your leader that you lost to &lt;i&gt;Dwight&lt;/i&gt; of all people.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-horny.png">No big deal, right? Only weird if we make it weird, and all that...</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">No worries! Uh, take your time, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-startled.png">I swear I'll look away, okay?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7 9">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">T-There's plenty of other good looking people to look at, so hopefully you enjoy yourself!</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">It's been &lt;i&gt;forever&lt;/i&gt; since I got to see anything like this...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Man, you've made me the luckiest guy. You know that, ~name~? Heh...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Sorry it's, uh, with me next to you.</state>
                <state img="#-mast2.png">It's pretty relaxing to just let go for a bit...</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Just have fun with it, ~name~. No need to prove anything, you know?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-nervous.png">She's really starting, huh?</state>
                <state img="#-fidgeting.png">Come on, come on... Gotta stay focused on the task at hand.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">You're getting my face all hot, ~name~...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">It's probably for the better, right? It sucks to have no release.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7 9">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Sit down on the ~background.surface~ and get comfortable, right?</state>
                <state img="#-content.png">Um, I meant to say sorry. Since you, uh, lost, and all that.</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">Nothing's more attractive than confidence, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-mast2.png">(&lt;i&gt;She's already wet...&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-mast2.png">Ugh... I-I can't go too fast...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Is that how it's done?</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">~Name~'s a bit louder than I expected.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Uh. Is everyone having fun? Heh.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">I mean... Everyone does it, so it's not like it's weird.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">How easy is it to throw a game of poker?</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I'm so glad to be here!</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">That place you keep pressing against... I-Is it extra sensitive?</state>
                <state img="#-fidgeting.png">Y-You can just tell me to shut up, if you want... The commentary is probably more distracting than anything.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7 9">
                <state img="#-idle.png">(&lt;i&gt;...No way she just looked at me.&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-idle.png">It's pretty hard to look away.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I know the sight isn't just for me, but I appreciate it.</state>
                <state img="#-idle.png">It's crazy how good you are with your fingers...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">(&lt;i&gt;Do girls like guys with big butts, or do they just think it's weird?&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Just like that, I'm under your thumb.</state>
                <state img="#-fidgeting.png">(&lt;i&gt;Don't talk about that, Dwight. You'll kill the mood.&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-mast2.png">You're, uh, real good with your fingers.</state>
                <state img="#-mast1.png">Hope you don't think any less of me...</state>
                <state img="#-mast2.png">If you need anything, let me know. It's a leader's job to make sure everyone's happy.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Just the noises are enough to make me sweat.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">(&lt;i&gt;At this rate, I'll be wetter than she is.&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-mast1.png">Definitely a new experience for me. I don't know about you, though.</state>
                <state img="#-mast1.png">(&lt;i&gt;Would a girl ever eat a guy's ass? Probably not, right? Yeah.&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-horny.png">The type of sight that leaves you starstruck.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">You really do make the cutest faces...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">...I'll remember that for later, heh.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7 9">
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Oh, a-are you okay?</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">Great work, ~name~. Take some time to rest, okay? </state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">L-Looks like you had fun. That's all you can ask for, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-mast2.png">B-Be there soon...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Ah-- T-That was great.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate_first">
            <case stage="7">
                <condition filter="dead_by_daylight" role="other" var="survivor" />
                <condition count="0" filter="villain" role="other" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">A true leader should set by example, r-right? I don't mind going first if it means ~survivor~ still has a chance of winning. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <condition count="2-" status="decent" role="other" />
                <state img="#-stern.png">R-Really? Was this some plan to make fun of me, or what?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">M-Me first? But what if I mess up? Or, well, that was a stupid question. I'll just get to it.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate">
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">M-Me? Well, alright... {small}I've kinda been looking forward to t-this, anyway...{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <condition role="other" />
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Hopefully this isn't too weird for you guys...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="start_masturbating">
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-starting.png">Y-Yeah, I'll get started then... Uh, just don't stare so much, okay?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="masturbating">
            <case stage="8" oneShotId="13">
                <condition role="self" timeInStage="0" />
                <state img="#-mast1.png">I'll just... Take a second to settle down and get comfortable. {small}This sorta hurts my knees.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-mast2.png">Nobody's treated me with such kindness before, I almost started crying.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png" font-size="small">C-Come on, I'm nothing special. Why do you work so hard for my approval?</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">A-Ah...! {small}Oh, that noise was kinda embarrassing...{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-startled.png">At least I don't have to worry about &lt;i&gt;it&lt;/i&gt; watching me, r-right?</state>
                <state img="#-mast2.png">Come on... I don't need to worry anymore, just focus on feeling good.</state>
                <state img="#-mast1.png">Leaders need some time to unwind too.</state>
                <state img="#-scared.png">Augh! Why the hell did I think of Lazar for a second!? What the fuck, brain?</state>
                <state img="#-mast2.png">I-I need this...</state>
                <state img="#-fidgeting.png">My heart is &lt;i&gt;pounding&lt;/i&gt;... I really hope it isn't due to a killer nearby.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Uh, yeah. Up and down, up and down. All that stuff.</state>
                <state img="#-mast2.png">It's not like I can't do this at the campfire. But I get so nervous in the woods, it's kinda hard to get into it.</state>
                <state img="#-stern.png">Did I hear someone snicker?</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I don't wanna finish too early... Geez, how sensitive am I?</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Hey, why are you trying to lock eyes with me, ~player~?</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">What, like what you see? {small}Probably not.{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">I'm sick of being anxious... I just wanna have fun.</state>
                <state img="#-content.png">Brings me back to my days of retail hell. Sometimes, the only way to release stress was to get home and do this.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="heavy_masturbating">
            <case stage="8" oneShotId="16">
                <condition role="self" timeInStage="0" />
                <state img="#-mast2.png">(&lt;i&gt;I don't have lube... But I could tease myself... w-with my fingers?&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-heavy1.png">Y-Yeah... Right there...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy1.png">C-Come on, bastard. Go faster...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy2.png">A-A bit too busy to fix my glasses...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy3.png">Just do what you want, man...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy1.png">Fuck!</state>
                <state img="#-heavy3.png">Mhm... T-That's the spot.</state>
                <state img="#-heavy1.png">A-A little hard to commentate right now!</state>
                <state img="#-heavy2.png">Just what I needed...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy1.png">(&lt;i&gt;D-Don't think of anyone in particular. God knows I won't be able to look them in the eye...&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finishing_masturbating">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-finishing.png">&lt;i&gt;R-Right there!&lt;/i&gt; Oh-- G-Gah!</state>
                <state img="#-finishing.png">&lt;i&gt;A-Ah...!&lt;/i&gt; W-Woah!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="9" oneShotId="3">
                <state img="#-finished.png" marker="fell">I... I fell over. </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="after_masturbating">
            <case stage="9" oneShotId="7" priority="100">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="fell" />
                <state img="#-standingup.png">I'll just... steady my legs and stand up again. Up and at 'em, Dwight.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9" oneShotId="15">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="humiliated" />
                <state img="#-bashful.png">No... Actually, it's okay. I don't need to freak out. Whew... it felt good, that's all I need to think about.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-conversational.png">I'll listen to Meg and be proud of myself for once! I-It felt good, and I'm totally not embarrassed of anything I said aloud...!</state>
                <state img="#-content.png">Don't look so disappointed... What, did you expect me to scream when I came? </state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" oneShotId="17" marker="humiliated">I can't believe I did all of that in front of you all... I even... w-with my fingers--!</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">(&lt;i&gt;I had to have been making the ugliest faces.&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">Soo... ~Player~, are you here often?</state>
                <state img="#-fidgeting.png">Good thing I found my glasses so fast. I'd rather not crawl around naked on the floor.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I'm okay spectating. I'm a bit tired, anyways.</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">I can't believe I'm out of breath over something as simple as that... </state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">Thanks for dealing with me, everyone. Uh, I appreciate it.</state>
                <state img="#-content.png">Is everyone doing okay?</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">I'm glad I stood up, otherwise my foot would've fallen asleep, heh.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I'm good, I'm good! Don't worry about me, okay?</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">Kinda nice to feel my heart pounding and know I'm not in danger. I can't get used to it, though...</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">I won't bother trying to make small talk, it'll just be awkward. I mean, you all just watched me stick my fingers up my--</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Maybe I should sit down? Or, I'd rather not sit on the ~background.surface~ naked... Seems uncomfortable.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Hey... Doing that wasn't too weird, was it? I know it's part of the rules and all, but still...</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Mmm... Pizza.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">My brains kinda mushy now, so don't expect some like... r-really smart comments.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_victory">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="other" character="susie" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">I-I won...? Hahaha! T-Take that, Legion! Survivors never give up.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6">
                <state img="#-horny.png">I guess I won! Uh, thanks for inviting me-- and if you wanna see me again, let me know? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-sad.png">B-But, losing looked so nice! Oh...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-startled.png">There's no way I'm &lt;i&gt;this&lt;/i&gt; lucky. Something bad is gonna happen... L-Like a piano falling on my head.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Uh. Has anyone seen my watch? I think I lost it. Or... nevermind, you all seem a bit tired.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-4">
                <state img="#-horny.png">The one time losing seems like the better option, I win. Sounds about right, hahaha...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_defeat">
            <case stage="9">
                <condition role="winner" character="susie" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Mm... T-This doesn't count as a win for killers, okay? Survivors will always prevail!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <condition role="winner" character="meg" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">Nice job, Meg! Who knew you were a poker master?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9" id="25">
                <condition status="lost_all" role="target" />
                <test expr="~self.place~" value="2" />
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">&lt;i&gt;So&lt;/i&gt; close! One round was really all it took...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9" id="26">
                <test expr="~self.place~" value="2" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">Second place, huh? You know... I'm proud of myself for doing that good. Good game, ~name~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-happy.png">If only losing a trial felt this nice. Great job, ~name~!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

    </behaviour>
</opponent>
