<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<collectibles>
    <collectible id="health_pop" img="opponents/aella/health_pop.png" thumbnail="opponents/aella/health_pop.png">
        <title>Health Pop</title>
        <subtitle>A healing item created by Aella's alchemist friend, William.</subtitle>
        <text>Aella is used to enemies dropping items upon defeat, so she thought for her defeat, she should leave something with the victor.

She didn't have much with her to give beyond a Health Pop, a tastey treat that recovers HP.</text>
        <unlock>Win a match against Aella.</unlock>
        <hide-details>true</hide-details>
        <counter>1</counter>
    </collectible>
    <collectible id="sword_of_kings" img="opponents/aella/sword_of_kings.png" thumbnail="opponents/aella/sword_of_kings.png">
        <title>Sword of Kings</title>
        <subtitle>Aella dropped a present. Inside, there was a Sword of Kings. ~player~ takes it.</subtitle>
        <text>Aella is used to enemies dropping items upon defeat, so she thought for her defeat, she should leave something with the victor.

Sometimes, enemies drop really rare items upon defeat, with the chance being some obscure number. This is one of those items, but Aella can't equip it herself, so she gave it to you instead.

 While the name might make it sound pretty special, it's really just an ordinary sword. The name totally oversells it. Its attack power is decent, but otherwise, there's nothing special about it.

 It's actually a rather bad sword, since it's pretty heavy due to the decorative cross section. Aella isn't really sure why she hung on to this item, but it's likely that she just didn't want to give this to her teammate who CAN use swords, Niccolo. He's really insufferable, so she tries to interact with him as little as possible. 

If you don't like swords, you can probably sell it, but not for a whole lot. Probably the equivalent of $12 in fantasy gold currency. It's weird how the sell price doesn't add up to just how rare this item is, but maybe the sword is only rare because it sucked and no one ever bought one?</text>
        <unlock>128 chance of dropping upon defeating Aella.</unlock>
        <hidden>true</hidden>
        <hide-details>true</hide-details>
        <counter>1</counter>
    </collectible>
</collectibles>
