<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<metadata>
    <owner>monique</owner>
    <noteworthy />
    <hidden />
    <responses>
        <response id="2" opponent="joey" opponentId="26" />
        <response id="3" opponent="joey" opponentId="27" />
        <response id="4" opponent="joey" opponentId="32" />
    </responses>
    <notes />
    <labels>
        <label id="1" label="Error" folder="" sort="0" />
    </labels>
    <prefixes />
    <nextId>4</nextId>
    <markers>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Stripping0-1">Monique strips her gloves in a normal fashion.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Stripping0-2">Monique strips her gloves using her mouth.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Stripping0-3">Monique strips her gloves backwards, from fingers to wrists</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Stripping1-1">Monique strips her hat in a normal fashion.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Stripping1-2">Monique strips her hat with a butterfly underneath.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Stripping1-3">Monique strips her hat by allowing it to fly off somehow.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Stripping2-1">Monique strips her boots in a normal fashion.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Stripping2-2">Monique strips her boots without using her hands.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Stripping2-3">Monique strips her boots by kicking them off.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Stripping3-1">Monique strips her shirt in a normal fashion.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Stripping3-2">Monique strips her shirt using a vanishing trick.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Stripping3-3">Monique strips her shirt by ripping it off.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Stripping4-1">Monique strips her bra in a normal fashion.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Stripping4-2">Monique strips her bra from behind a white sheet.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Stripping4-3">Monique strips her bra by somehow misplacing it in her pocket.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Stripping5-1">Monique strips her socks in a normal fashion.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Stripping5-2">Monique strips her socks without using her hands.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Stripping5-3">Monique strips her socks by washing off the paint.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Stripping6-1">Monique strips her panties in a normal fashion.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Stripping6-2">Monique strips her panties through her skirt somehow.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Stripping6-3">Monique strips her panties by pulling on a scarf tied to a scarf tied to a scarf that was tied to them.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Stripping7-1">Monique strips her skirt in a normal fashion.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Stripping7-2">Monique strips her skirt by slingshotting it off of her body.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Stripping7-3">Monique strips her skirt by allowing it to fade away.</marker>
    </markers>
    <recipes />
</metadata>
