<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<collectibles>
    <collectible id="Wanted Poster" img="opponents/nami/x-poster.jpg" thumbnail="opponents/nami/x-poster.jpg">
        <title>Nami's Wanted Poster</title>
        <subtitle>DEAD OR ALIVE</subtitle>
        <text>Nami's second wanted poster. She was tricked into posing for the photo (and not for the first time), though she still likes how she looks in it.</text>
        <unlock>Play a game with Nami until she loses.</unlock>
        <hide-details>true</hide-details>
    </collectible>
    <collectible id="Happiness Punch!" img="opponents/nami/collectible01.png" thumbnail="opponents/nami/thumbnail01.png">
        <title>Happiness Punch!</title>
        <subtitle>Her deadliest attack.</subtitle>
        <text>Nami's strongest attack, forever captured in a photograph for your delight.</text>
        <unlock>Win a game against Nami starting with 4 or less clothing items.</unlock>
    </collectible>
    <collectible id="Straw Hat" img="opponents/nami/collectible02.png" thumbnail="opponents/nami/thumbnail02.png">
        <title>Straw Hat</title>
        <subtitle>Luffy's treasure</subtitle>
        <text>He left it with Nami while he's playing around with Usopp and Chopper.</text>
        <unlock>Play a game with Nami until she loses. (Nostalgia costume).</unlock>
    </collectible>
    <collectible id="Ice cream" img="opponents/nami/collectible03.png" thumbnail="opponents/nami/thumbnail03.png">
        <title>Ice cream</title>
        <subtitle>For the girls</subtitle>
        <text>While the Nami and Robin are hanging out, Sanji made ice cream. Extra portions only for them.</text>
        <unlock>Win a game against Nami as a female player.</unlock>
    </collectible>
    <collectible id="Memento" status="testing" img="opponents/nami/collectible04.png" thumbnail="opponents/nami/thumbnail04.png">
        <title>Memento of a lustful moment</title>
        <subtitle>Something to remember her by</subtitle>
        <text>"T-Take a picture of me...! Right now...!" Nami said, between moans, while you two were having sex for the third time today. As soon as the game ended,  you and Nami went to a hotel room to continue what you had started. She had alreaady taken her clothes off before the door was closed.
So, per her request, you snapped a picture of her in this blissful moment, her body glistening with sweat while she moans with pleasure.
"This way you'll always remember me, no matter how far away I am. I want you to use this when you feel like you miss me..."
She also took a picture of you, for her own use.</text>
        <unlock>Finish a game with Nami in New Game Plus. (hint: New Game Plus activates inmediately after watching her epilogue)</unlock>
    </collectible>
</collectibles>
