<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<collectibles>
    <collectible id="Wanted Poster" status="online" img="opponents/nami/x-poster.jpg" thumbnail="opponents/nami/x-poster.jpg">
        <title>Nami's Wanted Poster</title>
        <subtitle>DEAD OR ALIVE</subtitle>
        <text>Nami's second wanted poster. She was tricked into posing for the photo (and not for the first time), though she still likes how she looks in it.</text>
        <unlock>Play a game with Nami until she loses.</unlock>
        <hide-details>true</hide-details>
    </collectible>
    <collectible id="Happiness Punch!" status="online" img="opponents/nami/collectible01.png" thumbnail="opponents/nami/thumbnail01.png">
        <title>Happiness Punch!</title>
        <subtitle>Her deadliest attack.</subtitle>
        <text>Nami's strongest attack, forever captured in a photograph for your delight.</text>
        <unlock>Win a game against Nami starting with 4 or less clothing items.</unlock>
    </collectible>
    <collectible id="Straw Hat" status="offline" img="opponents/nami/collectible02.png" thumbnail="opponents/nami/thumbnail02.png">
        <title>Straw Hat</title>
        <subtitle>Luffy's treasure</subtitle>
        <text>He left it with Nami while he's playing around with Usopp and Chopper.</text>
        <unlock>Play a game with Nami until she loses. (Nostalgia costume).</unlock>
        <hidden>true</hidden>
    </collectible>
    <collectible id="Ice cream" status="online" img="opponents/nami/collectible03.png" thumbnail="opponents/nami/thumbnail03.png">
        <title>Ice cream</title>
        <subtitle>For the girls</subtitle>
        <text>While the Nami and Robin are hanging out, Sanji made ice cream. Extra portions only for them.</text>
        <unlock>Win a game against Nami without being attracted to her.</unlock>
    </collectible>
    <collectible id="Memento" img="opponents/nami/collectible04.png" thumbnail="opponents/nami/thumbnail04.png">
        <title>Memento of a lustful moment</title>
        <subtitle>Something to remember her by</subtitle>
        <text>"T-Take a picture of me...! Right now...!" Nami said, between moans, while you two were having sex for the third time today. As soon as the game ended,  you and Nami went to a hotel room to continue what you had started. She had already taken her clothes off before the door was closed.
So, per her request, you snapped a picture of her in this blissful moment, her body glistening with sweat while she moans with pleasure.
"This way you'll always remember me, no matter how far away I am. I want you to use this when you feel like you miss me..."
She also took a picture of you, for her own use.</text>
        <unlock>Finish a game with Nami in New Game Plus. (hint: New Game Plus activates immediately after watching her epilogue)</unlock>
    </collectible>
    <collectible id="Sexy Poster" status="online" img="opponents/nami/collectible05.png" thumbnail="opponents/nami/thumbnail05.png">
        <title>Nami's Other Poster</title>
        <subtitle>VERY LIMITED EDITION</subtitle>
        <text>She'd kick your ass if she finds out you hanged this somewhere.</text>
        <unlock>Comply to Nami's seduction attempts, and see one of her three sexy poses after getting her naked. (Not available in New Game Plus)</unlock>
    </collectible>
    <collectible id="Bath time" status="online" img="opponents/nami/collectible06.png" thumbnail="opponents/nami/thumbnail06.png">
        <title>Bath time</title>
        <subtitle>...and girl time</subtitle>
        <text>Taking a bath with her friends after her recent insightful sexual experience, Nami has a hard time not looking at them in a new way.
After getting out of the bath, Nami tries not to stare at Robin's body while Carrot hugs her from behind.</text>
        <unlock>Play a game with Nami until she loses after trying to seduce you as a female player. (hint: Play as a female with the bisexual/lesbian tag)</unlock>
    </collectible>
    <collectible id="log_pose" status="online" img="opponents/nami/collectible07.png" thumbnail="opponents/nami/collectible07.png">
        <title>Log Pose</title>
        <subtitle>A navigator's essential tool</subtitle>
        <text>A device similar to a compass for navigating through the second half of the Grand Line, known as the New World. Each one of the three needles records the magnetism of a nearby island. The more the needle moves, the more unstable the magnetic field of that island is, and therefore the more dangerous.

Wear this to have a 100% chance of seeing one of Nami's special poses once she's naked.</text>
        <unlock>Win a game against Nami and another One Piece character</unlock>
        <wearable>true</wearable>
        <clothing name="Log Pose" generic="jewelry" position="other" type="extra" img="opponents/nami/collectible07.png" />
    </collectible>
    <collectible id="top" status="online" img="opponents/nami/collectible08.png" thumbnail="opponents/nami/collectible08.png">
        <title>Nami's top</title>
        <subtitle>It's big...</subtitle>
        <text>It feels like it's gonna come loose at any second, yet it never does.</text>
        <unlock>Finish a game in which Nami loses with two other pirates and a bounty hunter</unlock>
        <wearable>true</wearable>
        <clothing name="top" generic="swimsuit" position="upper" type="major" img="opponents/nami/collectible08.png" />
    </collectible>
</collectibles>
