<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>

<!--This file was machine generated using the Character Editor v6.5.1 at 9:04:44 PM on May 03, 2021. Do not edit this file directly unless you know what you're doing.-->
<opponent>
    <version>v6.5.1</version>
    <first>Senko</first>
    <last>the Helpful Fox</last>
    <label>Senko</label>
    <gender>female</gender>
    <size>medium</size>
    <timer>35</timer>
    <intelligence>average</intelligence>

    <tags>
        <tag>blonde</tag>
        <tag>medium_hair</tag>
        <tag>amber_eyes</tag>
        <tag>fair-skinned</tag>
        <tag>skinny</tag>
        <tag>short</tag>
        <tag>pubic_hair</tag>
        <tag>medium_breasts</tag>
        <tag>non-human</tag>
        <tag>supernatural</tag>
        <tag>deity</tag>
        <tag>spirit</tag>
        <tag>animal_ears</tag>
        <tag>tail</tag>
        <tag>cheerful</tag>
        <tag>confident</tag>
        <tag>fancy</tag>
        <tag>kind</tag>
        <tag>moe</tag>
        <tag>bi-curious</tag>
        <tag>single</tag>
        <tag>japanese</tag>
        <tag>fantasy</tag>
        <tag>anime</tag>
        <tag>manga</tag>
        <tag>magic</tag>
    </tags>


    <wardrobe>
        <clothing name="socks" generic="socks" position="feet" type="extra" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="panties" generic="underwear" position="lower" type="important" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="bra" generic="bra" position="upper" type="important" />
        <clothing name="robe" generic="kimono" position="upper" type="major" />
        <clothing name="apron" position="both" type="minor" />
        <clothing name="skirt and sash" generic="hakama" position="both" type="major" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="sandals" generic="shoes" position="feet" type="extra" plural="true" />
    </wardrobe>


    <behaviour>
        <trigger id="selected">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-silly.png">A game of cards? What a lovely way to relax.</state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">My, oh my... I'm not the greatest at cards, but I don't mind indulging you a bit.</state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">Oh... you want to play &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; kind of game with me? Well... I suppose &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; could be a form of pampering...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_selected">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="deity" role="target" />
                <state img="#-fufufu.png">My oh my! It would seem that even a god may need my love and affection from time to time. Very well. Let's have a wonderful game, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-fufufu.png">Some manner of god? Very well. I suppose even divine beings besides myself need my tender love and care!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="animal_ears" role="target" />
                <state img="#-interested.png">Ah! Are you some kind of yokai...? Or perhaps one of those &lt;i&gt;kemonomimi&lt;/i&gt; people find so fashionable? </state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">Well, I guess we could hear each other before we saw each other, neh? It's good to see another person with animal ears. It makes me feel right at home, even outside the Realm of Foxes.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="tail" role="target" />
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">&lt;i&gt;Hyoung...&lt;/i&gt; I don't suppose people are always asking to play with your tail, are they, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">While I imagine my tail is fluffier, I do not suppose your own tail is wanting for attention, &lt;i&gt;neh&lt;/i&gt;, ~name~?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="demon" role="target" />
                <state img="#-smug.png">A demon is just a spirit with a dirty soul. Let's cleanse that darkness, ~name~. </state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">If I know anything, it's that even the most savage of demons just needs some care to start behaving like a normal spirit. Let's see how we can help you, ~name~. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="japanese" role="target" />
                <state img="#-interested.png">Ah, &lt;i&gt;moshi moshi&lt;/i&gt;. </state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">Lucky you, ~name~. Few people of our homeland get to be blessed by a kitsune. I endeavor to make it an experience worth recording.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition status="exposed" role="target" />
                <state img="#-stahp.png">I see you're dismissing even the pretense of making a game of this...</state>
                <state img="#-stahp.png">This is supposed to be a competitive, stimulating card game... not a brothel, you know?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_start">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition status="exposed" character="human" />
                <state img="#-incensed.png">...You're not getting to fluff my tail with &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; attitude.</state>
                <state img="#-incensed.png">...We may have to see the game through, but don't expect me to be terribly pleased by your decision to rush.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="aoba" sayingMarker="Aoba-Senko-Tail" />
                <state img="#-touchfluffytail.png">Why thank you, Aoba. I do brush it and keep a healthy diet. </state>
                <state img="#-touchfluffytail.png">It's not a terrible amount of investment, but it is a labor of self love! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition count="3-" filter="mean" />
                <state img="#-okay....png">...~Player~... do you really want to be pampered? You ought not to feel the need to guilt yourself...</state>
                <state img="#-okay....png">~Player~, do you... you don't need everyone to be mean to you, I hope you know. 3</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition count="3-" filter="cheerful" />
                <state img="#-interested.png">Myo~n~! You really &lt;i&gt;could&lt;/i&gt; use a pick me up today, can't you, ~player~?</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">Oh! You need a pick-me-up after a long day, hm? Onyo~~</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition count="4-" filter="supernatural" />
                <state img="#-interested.png">A gathering of yokai? How exciting!</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">Goodness! Had I known we were gathering so many yokai in one place, I'd have brought far more exotic  clothing to provide a truly otherworldly experience!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition count="3-" filter="fancy" />
                <state img="#-silly.png">To prepare so admirably only to undress. What a curious assortment we have, ~player~!</state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">My oh my... it would seem we've dressed to impress. And to &lt;i&gt;undress&lt;/i&gt; in the same manner. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition count="3-4" filter="school_uniform" />
                <state img="#-fufufu.png">Oh, I &lt;i&gt;see&lt;/i&gt;. Have you brought along a voice of experience to guide these precocious youths...? </state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">...You do realize this isn't a uniform, don't you, ~player~? If you want me to &lt;i&gt;instruct&lt;/i&gt; these children, so be it, as long as they are happy to learn. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition count="3-" filter="criminal" />
                <state img="#-nani.png">...I can't help but feel a little intimidated by the others... is causing me discomfort truly gratifying for you, ~player~??</state>
                <state img="#-nani.png">~Player~, while doubtless these souls could use soothing, I am not quite so sure that I am an appropriate person to bear such cause or responsibility.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition count="2-" filter="submissive" />
                <state img="#-skittish.png">*&lt;i&gt;Looks around.&lt;/i&gt;* Why... clearly it's &lt;i&gt;me&lt;/i&gt; you wish to pamper, don't you think? Just to hold me in your hands and do with me what you wish?</state>
                <state img="#-skittish.png">W-wow... ~Player~... why, I don't know what to do with myself. Perhaps you should tell me exactly what you want, so that I can listen more attentively?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition count="2-" filter="dominant" />
                <state img="#-smug.png">&lt;i&gt;Ara, ara&lt;/i&gt;. You've been such a &lt;i&gt;naughty little ~player.ifMale(boy|girl)~.&lt;/i&gt; Do you need Senko to punish you into behaving? </state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">&lt;i&gt;Ara, ara&lt;/i&gt;... asking me to pamper you when you've been so &lt;i&gt;naughty&lt;/i&gt;. ~Player~, let's make sure we shame you into feeling pampering, neh?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition count="3-" filter="short" />
                <state img="#-smug.png">My oh my... we're all so tiny and petite! Like little porcelain dolls. Are you going to &lt;i&gt;play&lt;/i&gt; with us, ~player~? </state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Curious. Most of us might require some help reaching the higher shelves. Doubtless you'd help us, wouldn't you, ~player~? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition count="4" gender="male" />
                <state img="#-nani.png" marker="oops_all_balls">O-oh... just me and a bunch of men playing... strip poker. Part of me likes where this is going, but &lt;i&gt;parts&lt;/i&gt; of me are wondering if they'd be a little less accomodating than I'd like. </state>
                <state img="#-nani.png" marker="oops_all_balls">G-goodness. It really is just me and four men...? While I pride myself on being an accomodating host, there's only so much of me to go around, you know?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Just because I'm going to pamper you doesn't mean you're going to win for free, ~player~...!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Myo~n! I'll have you know I didn't live 800 years to be inept at card games...!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I'm not going to go easy on you. If you're in a competitive mood, you should get to really compete, neh?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="swap_cards">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <test expr="~cards~" value="0" />
                <state img="#-smug.png">Perfection from the draw. </state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Well, well. Is the dealer trying to pamper me, I wonder? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <test expr="~cards~" value="4" />
                <state img="#-stahp.png">What? None of these are good...!</state>
                <state img="#-stahp.png">These are all awful! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" totalRounds="12-">
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">...~Cards.text~.</state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">Ah... </state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">~Cards.text~, please. </state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">Ah. ~Cards.text~, now.</state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">~Cards.text~...</state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">Hm...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-meep.png">I'll exchange ~cards.text~ ~cards.ifplural(cards|card)~. If you'd please.</state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">I'll keep these... and you give me ~cards.text~.</state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">I would like ~cards.text~. </state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">Could you give me ~cards.text~? </state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">Ahah! </state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">Well... I see. ~Cards.text~, then.</state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">I'd prefer ~cards.text~ for these, if you would be so kind.</state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">Please replace ~cards.text~, dealer. </state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">Dealer, give me ~cards.text~ more cards.</state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">~Cards.text~, if you'd please. </state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">Please give me ~cards.text~. </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="good_hand">
            <case stage="0-1">
                <state img="#-fufufu.png">Now now, you &lt;i&gt;did&lt;/i&gt; ask for a competition. </state>
                <state img="#-fufufu.png">Since I will fully win this hand, I can use this time to plan other manners of pampering you. </state>
                <state img="#-fufufu.png">It would hardly be fun if I did not persist, don't you think?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">An excellent hand. Now, stripping you naked just makes it easier for me to draw you a bath. </state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Are you perhaps distracted? I've drawn the best cards in the deck, so perhaps you could focus more easily with a full stomach. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-4">
                <state img="#-joy.png">Myon~ </state>
                <state img="#-pampering.png">If you're trying to respect your elders by giving me the best cards, I'm just going to have to spoil you in return. </state>
                <state img="#-fufufu.png">Hymm hymm hymm~ ♪</state>
                <state img="#-pampering.png">Do not fret about your upcoming defeat. A sore ego just needs some massaging, myon~?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Now... who will be the victor?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-araara.png">Experience is a gift. One I intend to give repeatedly, even if that experience is only the process of learning. </state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">While I don't understand it, some people rather enjoy a bit of pain with their pleasure. Perhaps that's the sentiment the rest of you are experiencing?</state>
                <state img="#-joy.png">Part of the experience is the risk of defeat, is it not? In this I promise to provide you with the utmost pampering!</state>
                <state img="#-pampering.png">I must admit, I'm not used to being pampered &lt;i&gt;myself&lt;/i&gt;. But such a winning streak is appealing. Perhaps I ought to grant it to one of you...</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Wondering what lewd opportunities I've experienced over the course of my long life are doubtless a curiosity left to explore, hm?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="okay_hand">
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-araara.png">What a &lt;i&gt;mystery&lt;/i&gt; this hand is...</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">Oh... well. I can win, but isn't every round of this game a win, in some way? </state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">Ah... not quite the hand I wished for. But I know my defeat shall nonetheless make someone else happy. </state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">Indecisive opportunities are the most curious, are they not?</state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">If you were hoping I had a bad hand... I may need to tease you a bit longer. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-1">
                <state img="#-silly.png">My oh my... what &lt;i&gt;do&lt;/i&gt; we have here?</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">Myon~ ♪ </state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">Well... this shall certainly be interesting!</state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">Certainly not the worst hand... </state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">...While I intend to be gracious in defeat and doubtless seeing me nude is part of the pampering process, I &lt;i&gt;am&lt;/i&gt; still accustomed to getting my way.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-4">
                <state img="#-araara.png">Hm... would you find it enriching if I were to say I'm just as excited to see what happens next as you? </state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">Myon~ ♪ </state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">Ah... a middle of the road hand. I suppose life, like cards, is what we make of it, neh?</state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">While I do not enjoy lying, I believe that &lt;i&gt;is&lt;/i&gt; part of the experience of this game? If so, I will say that my hand shall remain a mystery. </state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">I'm hiding my cards because they are clearly so much better than yours that you would be offended should you know such an  earth-shattering truth.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="bad_hand">
            <case stage="2-4">
                <state img="#-stahp.png">&lt;i&gt;Myon!?&lt;/i&gt; This hand is the &lt;i&gt;opposite&lt;/i&gt; of what one expects from being pampered! </state>
                <state img="#-stahp.png">...Even with almost a millenium of experience, I suppose I still have much to learn. </state>
                <state img="#-nani.png">...&lt;i&gt;MMMMMMMMMMM...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-nani.png">Ah... oh no. Defeat looks like Senko...</state>
                <state img="#-skittish.png">Hm. While I may be about to lose, I think I understand you a bit better. You like a &lt;i&gt;bit&lt;/i&gt; of a chase before you're taken care of? How very curious you picked a fox demigod for such a pursuit...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-1">
                <state img="#-stahp.png">...Oh. This is not the start I expected. </state>
                <state img="#-stahp.png">Goodness... this hand is not the best by any extent of the imagination. </state>
                <state img="#-nani.png">&lt;i&gt;Kyh...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-nani.png">&lt;i&gt;Myo...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">Ah... if my undressing will make you feel loved, then I shall do so gracefully. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-stahp.png">...I suppose there truly is not much more of myself I can show you, but if this is what you want, I suppose it's what you'll be getting.</state>
                <state img="#-stahp.png">...If this were further along in the &lt;i&gt;pampering&lt;/i&gt;, you would be quite saddened to falter at the finish, wouldn't you?</state>
                <state img="#-nani.png">Ah... darn. </state>
                <state img="#-nani.png">I-I'm not sure what you're talking about. These hands are perfectly salvagable. </state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">I'd say my hand is not so good... but my &lt;i&gt;hands&lt;/i&gt; are perfectly soft and warm. Myo~n~♪ </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="hand">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="chara_senko03" />
                <condition role="other" character="chara_dreemurr" stage="1" timeInStage="0" />
                <state img="#-joy.png" marker="senko_chara_pamper">Chara, you know you can simply ask. There's no need to brood, and everyone is deserving of love and care... is there something &lt;i&gt;aside&lt;/i&gt; from unrelenting victory that I could provide you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="other" character="aoba" stage="1" timeInStage="0" />
                <state img="#-interested.png" marker="aoba_modeling">So... you said you model? Do you model petite clothing? You seem more of an artistic variety, but it's wonderful that women of our size can be viewed as attractive and feminine, neh?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="other" character="laevatein" stage="4" timeInStage="0" />
                <state img="#-silly.png">No, no service, Laevatein. Your joy is all that I ask. </state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">I only ask that you cherish your own company, Laevatein. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" priority="142">
                <condition role="other" character="hilda" stage="6-8" saidMarker="NoMoreAct" sayingMarker="SenkoHonestPamper" />
                <state img="#-smug.png">&lt;i&gt;That&lt;/i&gt; much was obvious. I have a nose for pampering, you know... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-7">
                <condition role="other" character="aoba" stage="4-8" />
                <condition role="self" notSaidMarker="aoba_convo_intros" />
                <state img="#-joy.png" marker="aoba_convo_intros">Myon~! Aoba, I can't help but notice you looking my way. Is there something you want to ask? </state>
                <state img="#-joy.png" marker="aoba_convo_intros">Aoba, you don't have to stare. I'm more than happy to answer any questions you have, especially the kind that set your mind at east.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-7">
                <condition role="other" character="aoba" stage="4-8" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="aoba_convo_intros" />
                <state img="#-araara.png" marker="aoba_vibrator">Aoba, I must ask... have you used one of those lewd wand massagers? I felt it would be too obvious with my last host, though my friend Shiro claims they're rather... climatic. </state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png" marker="aoba_youth">...People assume you're quite a bit younger than you actually are, hrm? Don't you find that incredibly patronizing? It's a bit like... "goodness, I have children older than you," you know? &lt;br&gt;Or maybe not.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="aoba_casual">I mean this in a general question and not an invitation, but... do you intend to invite one of the other players home with you, Aoba? I'm still considering it, myself.</state>
                <state img="#-meep.png" marker="aoba_modern">Ah, Aoba! You're a modern woman with some sense of decorum. Would you say there's anything fun that someone could do after a game like this that I might not be familiar with?</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png" marker="aoba_fursona">You rather seem to enjoy my tail, Aoba. If you were to be a hengeyokai... what manner of animal would you like to be?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-7" id="55">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="senko_pampering" notSaidMarker="laev_pamper" />
                <condition role="other" character="laevatein" saidMarker="Laev_Senko_kind" />
                <state img="#-hug.png" marker="laev_pamper">I think you could use a good hair brushing and a comfortable hug. Whenever you want either, I'm right here for you, Laevatein.</state>
                <state img="#-hug.png" marker="laev_pamper">Oh... sweet girl. You take your time, but when you're ready for a hug and someone to brush your hair, I'll be right here, Laevatein.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-7">
                <condition role="other" character="galatea" saidMarker="galatea_pampering" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="senko_pampering" notSaidMarker="galatea_pampering" />
                <state img="#-skittish.png" marker="galatea_pampering">Galatea... Has nobody ever given you something you asked for? Of course you have a choice to be pampered and cared for in the way you'd like. Let's start &lt;i&gt;right now&lt;/i&gt;. How can I help you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-7">
                <condition role="other" character="lux" saidMarker="Senko_Pamper_Prompt" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="senko_pampering" notSaidMarker="lux_pampering" />
                <state img="#-hug.png" marker="lux_pampering">Oh, Lux. You're here, meeting new friends and making lifelong memories. Even if they're a bit lewd, you're still so very brave and fun to play with. &lt;i&gt;I'm&lt;/i&gt; proud of you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-7">
                <condition role="other" character="miko" saidMarker="SenkoPamper_resp" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="senko_pampering" notSaidMarker="miko_pampering" />
                <state img="#-joy.png" marker="miko_pampering">Sometimes the simple things in life are the most pleasurable, Prince. Sake and a hot spring, with amply endowed attendants are beyond my unique capacity, but doubtless you have many attendants of your own in your court, neh?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-7">
                <condition role="other" character="polly" saidMarker="Polly_Senko_PamperingChess" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="senko_pampering" notSaidMarker="polly_pampering" />
                <state img="#-pampering.png" marker="polly_pampering">Ah... chess is a bit like shogi, isn't it? I understand completely. The calm, the focus... even without victory, a moment with friends is quite something to be treasured. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-7">
                <condition role="other" character="polly" saidMarker="Polly_Senko_PamperingBooks" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="senko_pampering" notSaidMarker="polly_pampering" />
                <state img="#-pampering.png" marker="polly_pampering">You are such a considerate friend. Giving someone joy by letting them enjoy their sources of joy...! Ah... I surely have to pamper &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; in such a generous way.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-7">
                <condition role="other" character="nami" saidMarker="senko_pamper" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="senko_pampering" notSaidMarker="nami_pamper" />
                <state img="#-silly.png" marker="nami_pamper">Ah... he seems to care for you far better than even I might be able to, Nami. You should treasure those moments. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-7">
                <condition role="other" character="hilda" saidMarker="SenkoPamperingDesire" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="senko_pampering" notSaidMarker="hilda_pamper" />
                <state img="#-joy.png" marker="hilda_pamper">Well, Hilda... I can certainly say that I enjoy tending to other's needs. Whether it's the mundane or the magical. I am happy to be of service.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="44">
                <condition role="other" character="wikipe-tan" saidMarker="SenkoTiring" />
                <state img="#-futz.png" marker="senko_wiki_tiring">Ah... well... if &lt;i&gt;romance&lt;/i&gt; isn't your interest tonight... I'm sure I can help you cite a brand new source. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="45">
                <condition role="other" character="wikipe-tan" saidMarker="SenkoInventory" />
                <state img="#-futz.png" marker="senko_wiki_invn">All I know, Wikepe-tan... is that this is a place full of people in need of tender love and care. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="46">
                <condition role="other" character="wikipe-tan" saidMarker="SenkoDonations" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="senko_wiki_donations">Ah... well... if &lt;i&gt;romance&lt;/i&gt; isn't your interest tonight... I'm sure I can help you cite a brand new source. </state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="senko_wiki_donations">Oh? Are you interested in knowledge or &lt;i&gt;information&lt;/i&gt;...? Because human semen...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="47">
                <condition role="other" character="wikipe-tan" saidMarker="SenkoStripPoker" />
                <state img="#-araara.png" marker="senko_wiki_poker">Welll... I'm sure you're in for quite the experience. If you're an avatar... have you ever taken a mortal consort?</state>
                <state img="#-araara.png" marker="senko_wiki_poker">Goodness, Wikipe-tan... have you ever taken a mortal consort? I'm sure &lt;i&gt;someone&lt;/i&gt; could deposit all sorts of variety in you...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="57" oneShotId="34" priority="100">
                <condition role="other" character="lux" sayingMarker="senko_handany_vastaya2" />
                <state img="#-meep.png" marker="senko_vastaya">Ah, a... Vastaya? No, I'm a kitsune. Is that another type of fox demigod?</state>
                <state img="#-meep.png" marker="senko_vastaya">Well, my tail is rather fluffy, but I'm not sure what that is, Lux. I'm a fox demigod, or a kitsune. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-4" id="15">
                <condition role="self" notSaidMarker="senko_pampering" />
                <state img="#-interested.png" marker="senko_pampering">Out of curiosity, does anyone have a preferred indulgence, or way they wish to be taken care of?</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png" marker="senko_pampering">I know I speak quite a bit on pampering... what I mean by this is what moments of care others can do for you to make you feel loved and special. What does that look like for each of you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-silly.png" oneShotId="218">My, oh my... this ~background~ is quite comfy, isn't it?</state>
                <state img="#-silly.png" oneShotId="219">What a wonderful day to play cards. I'm so pleased to be playing with you!</state>
                <state img="#-pampering.png" oneShotId="220">Ah! I just had a great idea. What if we ordered a delightful meal, or when someone loses, they also need to bring something delicious... &lt;i&gt;besides&lt;/i&gt; themself, of course!</state>
                <state img="#-pampering.png" oneShotId="221">Oh--! Your auras are so bright and happy--! Please, let me know how I can keep making this better.</state>
                <state img="#-joy.png" oneShotId="222">This game is rather fun, neh? Though, I believe you can always find fun where you look for it with a smile. </state>
                <state img="#-joy.png" oneShotId="223">While this game is quite lewd, there's no reason we can't simply enjoy the wonderful company as well, neh?</state>
                <state img="#-futz.png" oneShotId="224">(&lt;i&gt;So many personalities here. I'd better look my best!&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-futz.png" oneShotId="225">Ah... don't you enjoy the feeling of fresh clothes after a hot bath? I imagine we'll want both after this game, hm?</state>
                <state img="#-silly.png" oneShotId="226">Are you all having fun? Please let me know if there's any way I can make this a more enjoyable experience.</state>
                <state img="#-joy.png" oneShotId="217">Myon~ I'll be keeping these cards a secret for now, but I'm sure we're all going to have a lovely time because of them.</state>
                <state img="#-pampering.png" oneShotId="216">Goodness! I'm sensing so many spirits brightening. You're all rather excited, aren't you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2" id="20" oneShotId="1" priority="0">
                <test expr="~background~" value="inventory" />
                <state img="#-joy.png">The Inventory is such a strange, wonderful place, isn't it? I think, though, you can always make things better if you focus on bringing light and comfort. </state>
                <state img="#-joy.png">I'm surprised so many people feel anxious when playing here. It's not always the cleanest, but it's always a good time, and everyone finishes sooner or later. Now, if we could work on that cleaning...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2" id="21" oneShotId="2" priority="0">
                <test expr="~background~" value="tiki bar" />
                <state img="#-interested.png">I've heard of places like this in the Southeast Seas...! To think we get to undress in such warm, pleasant weather, near such cool, refreshing drinks.</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">What an exotic place we're playing today... while the game itself is so lovely, having a refreshing breeze and sweet drinks can't do anything but make it better, neh?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2" id="22" oneShotId="3" priority="0">
                <test expr="~background~" value="beach" />
                <state img="#-futz.png">Sand, sunlight, and the sound of crashing waves... while I'd rather be in a swimsuit, it's well worth dusting the sand off to enjoy the moment more fully. </state>
                <state img="#-futz.png">Isn't this a lovely day? It's worth a little extra effort to clean sand off your clothes if you can enjoy the weather and sound, hm?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2" id="23" oneShotId="4" priority="0">
                <test expr="~background~" value="classroom" />
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">In truth, I've spent very little time inside of a classroom... I hope I'm not mistaken for a student. </state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">Despite my age, I can't imagine that I'd be mistaken for anything but a student, given my size. It's quite a curious feeling. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2" id="24" oneShotId="5" priority="0">
                <test expr="~background~" value="roof" />
                <state img="#-joy.png">You can see so much from up here. But I think the best place to look is at each other. </state>
                <state img="#-joy.png">While it's a bit dusty up here, it sure feels like there's quite a few positive memories people have made over lunch. I wish I'd brought one for each of you. Maybe next time?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2" id="25" oneShotId="6" priority="0">
                <test expr="~background~" value="poolside" />
                <state img="#-pampering.png">Ah, what a nice pool. We could always strip down, spend the day swimming, and enjoy the warmth of tired muscles and fun company, can't we?</state>
                <state img="#-pampering.png">Ah... I love to take a nice long swim. I know we really &lt;i&gt;ought&lt;/i&gt; to wear swimsuits... but perhaps we can all enjoy feeling perfectly natural in this manmade pool?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2" id="26" oneShotId="7" priority="0">
                <test expr="~background~" value="hot spring" />
                <state img="#-interested.png">A hotspring? Goodness. Whoever planned this game is really going out of their way to provide a pleasurable environment, hm?</state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">Ah, make sure you've cleaned off &lt;i&gt;before&lt;/i&gt; you enjoy the hot spring. Getting it dirty'll make it harder to relax in.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2" id="27" oneShotId="8" priority="0">
                <test expr="~background~" value="holiday lodge" />
                <state img="#-hug.png">A warm fire, a cup of hot tea... falling snow outside. All you need is a cozy blanket and someone to snuggle you, right?</state>
                <state img="#-hug.png">Ah... I'd love to snuggle up and watch the snow fall. What a cozy hall, here. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2" id="28" oneShotId="9" priority="0">
                <test expr="~background~" value="purple room" />
                <state img="#-meep.png">Oh my! Is there an orange room? I may be a bit more comfortable there. And ultimately, we all want to be comfy, don't we?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2" id="29" oneShotId="10" priority="0">
                <test expr="~background~" value="paris rooftop" />
                <state img="#-pampering.png">Ah! How romantic! While I tend to focus on taking care of the body, the heart is part of that, isn't it? I love this rooftop!</state>
                <state img="#-pampering.png">Oh my! This place is so romantic! Nothing makes the heart soar like someone showing you you're loved, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2" id="30" oneShotId="11" priority="0">
                <test expr="~background~" value="bathhouse" />
                <state img="#-pampering.png">So... are we going to get dirty, or get clean together? I'm happy to scrub your back!</state>
                <state img="#-pampering.png">My tail gets rather... sad... in water. But if you help me dry it off, I'd be happy to give you a massage after you're nice and steamy!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2" id="31" oneShotId="12" priority="0">
                <test expr="~background~" value="club" />
                <state img="#-skittish.png">It's so loud in here! My ears are rather sensitive... but if you're having fun so will  I!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2" id="32" oneShotId="13" priority="0">
                <test expr="~background~" value="haunted forest" />
                <state img="#-hug.png">Don't be scared, ~name~. While we're in a spooky forest, I can keep you safe.</state>
                <state img="#-hug.png">Do you need a hug? This place is so scary, but a little love goes a long way, doesn't it?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition status="alive" character="human" />
                <condition role="other" character="chara_dreemurr" sayingMarker="ResponseCharaSenkoMustStrip1" />
                <state img="#-pampering.png" marker="chara01">Ah! But of course. But understand that I &lt;i&gt;do&lt;/i&gt; fully intend to undress as part of the game.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition status="alive" character="human" />
                <condition role="other" character="chara_dreemurr" sayingMarker="ResponseCharaSenkoMustStrip1" />
                <state img="#-futz.png" marker="chara11">You need not act so innocent, Chara. I can see your intentions, and respect the meaning behind them. </state>
                <state img="#-futz.png" marker="chara11">While I appreciate you trying to help ~player~, and I fully intend to enjoy myself, you won't find me to be some easy mark. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition status="alive" character="human" />
                <condition role="other" character="chara_dreemurr" sayingMarker="ResponseCharaSenkoMustStrip1" />
                <state img="#-fibbing.png" marker="chara20">Chara... are you wishing that I'd die, to fulfill your wishes?</state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png" marker="chara20">There's more to life than death, Chara... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" priority="142">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" stage="0-6" saidMarker="TheVoiceOfHair==1" sayingMarker="TheVoiceOfHair==1" />
                <state img="#-meep.png">Goodness! I've only rarely had parts of my body be jealous of other parts of it, Bobobo.</state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">M-my--! Is that so, Bobobo? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="aoba" stage="0-8" />
                <state img="#-pampering.png">Why, thank you. I think mine would fit you.</state>
                <state img="#-pampering.png">Ah! Do you not have a kimono of your own? You could borrow it after, if you want. We're about the same size. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" priority="102">
                <condition role="other" character="hilda" saidMarker="SenkoOverwork" sayingMarker="SenkoSpaTogether" />
                <state img="#-silly.png">Goodness... I'd hardly know what to do with myself. But you're right, Hilda.</state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">Goodness...! Pampering a woman of my age... you're quite a polite young woman, aren't you, Hilda? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="60">
                <condition role="other" character="twisted_fate" sayingMarker="Senko_Soft0A" />
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">I'll have you know I'm plenty, as the current generation says, "hard." </state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">Softness does not mean weak. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="polly" sayingMarker="Polly_Senko_Experience" />
                <state img="#-silly.png">Ah... the impetuousness of youth. I would say I've done a fair amount of things, but certainly not tried all of them. I'm a merely 823. </state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">I'm 823, but I would say I have yet to experience all that can be experienced in a lifetime... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="hilda" sayingMarker="SenkoOverwork" />
                <state img="#-futz.png">A break for myself, Hilda...? Why, I do rather enjoy tending to others... but I suppose you have a valid point.</state>
                <state img="#-futz.png">Myon~! I agree. That's rather magnanimous of you, Hilda. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="jim" />
                <state img="#-smug.png">I'll have you know that it's my purpose. And I'm very good at it. One carafe of whiskey and a fine cigar coming up. And a nice, relaxing aromatic candle.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="miko" />
                <state img="#-silly.png">Ah, yes, Prince. Though the term "host" rather than "master" would be more appropriate. I'm here by myself, but I'm never alone with such lovely company. </state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">I'm here alone tonight. And I prefer the term "host" rather than "master."</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="galatea" />
                <state img="#-joy.png">But of course, my lady Galatea. I'm quite certain I've indulged in many more obscenities than you have. </state>
                <state img="#-joy.png">Ah... what is obscenity to one person but eroticism and daring to another, Galatea?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="jim" />
                <state img="#-incensed.png">I'll have you know I'm 823 years old, young man. Though my... appearance until recently didn't lend itself to such. Which led to a series of rather unfortunate and confusing interactions. This is much an improvement, I think.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="polly" />
                <state img="#-touchfluffytail.png">You may touch it, if you'd like, Polly. Thank you for asking. </state>
                <state img="#-touchfluffytail.png">Ah... would you like that? You may, just the once,Polly. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="nami" />
                <state img="#-incensed.png">...Not all treasures are golden, Nami... </state>
                <state img="#-incensed.png">Don't think I'm so easily flattered, Nami.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_winning">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-joy.png">While I intend to be a gracious victor, do not imagine for one second I intend to let up.</state>
                <state img="#-joy.png">You asked me to play. Don't be surprised when I use my experience against you, neh?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-fufufu.png">It is your good fortune that despite the numerous layers I wear, they all come off quite easily. </state>
                <state img="#-fufufu.png">The mark of a good robe is your ability to feel fully dressed, but dress down swiftly, hm?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Goodness... do you feel a bit uncomfortable? I should hope to make amends for that momentarily...</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Ah, I suppose I've teased you long enough. But pampering is, at its heart, about excess, neh?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-joy.png">I'm feeling quite motivated. Perhaps the thrill of victory is going to my head, rather than my loins.</state>
                <state img="#-joy.png">Ah... grilled fish, a lovingly-made sauce... a hot bath, sun-dried sheets... I'd say those are as good as the degree to which I'm winning, but the truth is always more comfortable.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">Given my lead, I think you'd strongly prefer I show something rather lewd, yes? </state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">While I'm happy to be providing you a competitive experience, I do want to keep you engaged. Thus, nudity.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-smug.png">There's no hole in my panties for my tail. But I'm sure you're expecting &lt;i&gt;something&lt;/i&gt; under there, neh?</state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">My, oh my... such lascivious expressions. You will be seeing my most sacred of temples-- &lt;i&gt;pfft&lt;/i&gt;. &lt;br&gt;I-I'm sorry. I'm not so skilled at dirty talk, but you'll be seeing my womanly virtues in but a moment.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-interested.png">Ah, what a close game! </state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">This must be awfully close. But I have a feeling we're all about to get &lt;i&gt;much&lt;/i&gt; closer.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_normal">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-silly.png">Ah... very well. Perhaps I should settle in. And I know just the thing to do so. </state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">Myon~... it's my first loss. While I &lt;i&gt;do&lt;/i&gt; wish to provide an excellent experience, you do realize this means quite the challenge, neh?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">Hm... I suppose this play may count for double. But a handicap seems fair. </state>
                <state img="#-pampering.png">If your goal is to see me undressed, then I suppose you'll enjoy my next removal. If you would prefer a challenge... I challenge you to look away, hm?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-silly.png">Ah... to part with my apron is to lay aside my responsibilities...</state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">While I keep my clothing immaculate, it's usually my apron that gets messy, rather than put away to avoid a mess...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-meep.png">Ah! Yes, right. I feel the next item should be rather obvious. </state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">Considering you can see my panties already, perhaps you'd appreciate the opportunity to compliment my bra as well? ...Or simply see more of me. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-araara.png">During my last jaunt to the human world, my neighbor imparted some rather interesting wisdom... perhaps I should leave my socks for last?</state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">If I've learned anything that's been constant throughout the eras, it's less &lt;i&gt;what&lt;/i&gt; parts of your body you show, and more &lt;i&gt;when&lt;/i&gt; you choose to show them...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-pampering.png">While I endeavor to keep my promises, a fox demigod is never to be underestimated. For my final deception, I'll be removing my panties next. </state>
                <state img="#-pampering.png">I have no shame in admitting that I'm happy to give you the view that you desire, now. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-araara.png">As a kitsune, I thought it would've been &lt;i&gt;too&lt;/i&gt; on the nose to wear socks and gloves. But you must admit the look is rather cute, neh?</state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">So... did &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; enjoy that I saved my socks for last? It makes me look rather &lt;i&gt;foxy&lt;/i&gt;, neh?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_losing">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-nani.png" marker="1DN">Oh... g-goodness. I suppose it &lt;i&gt;is&lt;/i&gt; me.</state>
                <state img="#-nani.png" marker="1DN">&lt;i&gt;Eep!&lt;/i&gt; What a misfortune and so early!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-skittish.png" marker="2DN">Ah... please don't take my poor play personally. I wish nothing less than for you to enjoy this. </state>
                <state img="#-skittish.png" marker="2DN">I hope that my next removal will compensate for my inability to play well. I wish only to provide a positive and pampering experience. I hope this is appreciated, then!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" marker="3DN">Ah, darn! I thought I had it &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; time.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" marker="3DN">Oh, darn it! Just when I'd imagined things were turning my way. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-okay....png" marker="4DN">Ah... well then. It's not that I'm terribly shy as much as I wish I could give you a better match. </state>
                <state img="#-okay....png" marker="4DN">A prize given freely is certainly a prize, but didn't you select me to compete? I wish I were a more worthy opponent to complete your experience.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-fibbing.png" marker="5DN">You really ought to be nicer to your demigods. Look at the kindness I'm about to show to you as proof!</state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png" marker="5DN">While I've only fallen prey to traps once or twice, a woman's wiles transcend physical form...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-stahp.png" marker="6DN">...Perhaps I ought to take my socks off and try to regain my composure. </state>
                <state img="#-stahp.png" marker="6DN">I've come too far not to see my gambit through, but...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-stripped+.png" marker="7DN">Well played. You've certainly earned the complete view. I think your pampering is nearly complete... but only &lt;i&gt;nearly&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-stripped+.png" marker="7DN">It's truly the finishing touches that make a pampering special.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripping">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="miko" />
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">You say that as though being taken care of such a bad thing. While everyone should strive to be self-sufficient, there's too much to be done in this world for all of us to be cooking and folding clothes. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="chara_dreemurr" />
                <state img="#-stripping-.png" marker="senko_chara01">I will admit to some surprise at how forward a demon is being on behalf of someone else. </state>
                <state img="#-stripping-.png" marker="senko_chara01">I'm a bit hesitant to read your intentions. Demons so rarely ask on behalf of others, or with positive moments. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="galatea" />
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">Though I may be small and "bonny," I've lived over 800 human years. I could teach you a thing or two about humans. </state>
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">Goodness. I have children older than you, my lady Galatea. Don't be deceived by my stature... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="jim" />
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">As for whether it's common... It depends on the fox demigod herself, but it's less a sudden and more general need to care for others. A lot of stress comes and goes here, you know?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="jim" />
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">As I said, I'm here to help people relieve stress. The rest of it, well... I think it's fairly obvious. I  want people to like my appearance as it is, but certainly part of pampering is enjoying what you're looking at. Myohm~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="chara_dreemurr" />
                <state img="#-stripping+.png" marker="senko_chara12">If defeated, I do fully look forward to the opportunity to &lt;i&gt;release&lt;/i&gt;, but it does nobody any good were I to be a poor sport and trivial opponent. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="polly" />
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">Well, do you have any suggestions for an old lady like myself, Polly? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="nami" />
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">It's hard to pamper a greedy heart...</state>
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">I do appreciate offerings, but they should be done purely in earnestness.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="chara_dreemurr" />
                <state img="#-stripping+.png" marker="senko_chara22">I'm certain ~player~ is rather more interested in watching us be intimate than killing each other... </state>
                <state img="#-stripping+.png" marker="senko_chara22">I'd be more than happy to engage with you physically, in hopes of bringing you joy... I believe ~player~ would much prefer that to any death. Wouldn't you, ~player~?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="1DN" />
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">&lt;i&gt;Myon~...&lt;/i&gt; I suppose I can be a good guest and take my shoes off, first.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">The least I can do is remove my shoes, hm?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="2DN" />
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">&lt;i&gt;Hmph.&lt;/i&gt; And of all the days to tie it so tightly.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">I will attempt to work out my frustration on this knot. I believe my distress should at least be a small comfort.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="3DN" />
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">Forgive my outburst of negativity. I'm simply unaccustomed to being bested at bluffing games. </state>
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">Were it that another kitsune were here, you might have had a better competition... but if it's my body you wish to see, I hope that will serve as a consolation prize. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="4DN" />
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">Ah... though you probably care a bit more about my tail than my candor or talent...?</state>
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">Perhaps you're giving me a gift in your way. Humility is certainly an excellent prelude to indulgence... an unearned delight is surely the best...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="5DN" />
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">While I'm not the most buxom of my peers, surely you picked me for a reason.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">The one disadvantage of modern undergarb. This infernal facet. I &lt;i&gt;have&lt;/i&gt; endeavored to make this form more... &lt;i&gt;fluffy&lt;/i&gt; in areas of interest for you, you know.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="6DN" />
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">I'm a bit overcome with embarrassment... but I hope this only adds to the appeal...</state>
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">Ah... perhaps I've been a bit too confident. Would a small amount of embarrassment have added to this experience?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="7DN" />
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">Ah... here we go. Hm... perhaps you'd rather a view of my tail?</state>
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">Hm... perhaps I should simply turn around and show you my tail? Would that be something novel and exciting?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">Please give me a moment to make sure these are folded and put away gently...</state>
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">Ah... I'll put these away. While the ~background.surface~ is surely... well-loved, I wish to keep things organized. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">While the cold fire of electricity is one of my favorite modern inventions, I must say that the cotton and elastic panties of the era are far more comfortable than any prior. </state>
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">Water that heats itself and dishes that can be cleaned without laying a finger on them are doubtless my favorite displays of human ingenuity. However, the era's undergarb are quite comfortable as well. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">&lt;i&gt;Myon~&lt;/i&gt;... Please enjoy this banquet for the eyes.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">Ah... please take this opportunity to feast your eyes. You may get a chance to feast on a dish of your choice later, as well. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">Fufufu~ If you wish, you may consider how lovely it would be to rest your head on my chest. </state>
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">I have some final tricks tucked into my tail, but my tail isn't the only part of me you might consider fluffing, &lt;i&gt;myon~&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">Ah... I'm actually rather excited for you to see all of me. Well, besides my toes, I suppose. </state>
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">I suppose some views never overstay their welcome, neh? I may be able to change my shape somewhat, but some things never change. </state>
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">Some things really &lt;i&gt;do&lt;/i&gt; get better with age, don't you think?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">While I'm certain that my feet aren't terribly impressive, you are entitled to a preview of what may come next. If you can make me lose another hand, at least... fufufu~</state>
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">You can see so much more when I'm not standing, hm? Consider this a small bonus to go along with my socks.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">How invigorating this game is! &lt;i&gt;But,&lt;/i&gt; I believe I'll settle in as a good guest. </state>
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">Not terribly different than stepping foot in a home... but I have a feeling I'll be missing my sandals soon, anyway.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripped">
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="miko" sayingMarker="SenkoSandals3" />
                <state img="#-stripped-.png">I'm still a little caught up on the need to prevent Lady Futo from desecrating shrines. I think I'll take that off your mind before I worry about your need for inebriation, Prince.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="chara_dreemurr" />
                <state img="#-stripped+.png" marker="senko_char02">Though, perhaps you're only a few generous gestures away from purifying that murderous darkness in you, hm?</state>
                <state img="#-stripped+.png" marker="senko_char02">Oh! Are you trying to change for ~player~? Even buried in all that darkness, I'm sure there's a lovely young girl who only wants to protect ~player~. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="galatea" />
                <state img="#-stripped-.png">Though, if you still view me as quite young, I have yet more practice to do as far as shapeshifting goes. </state>
                <state img="#-stripped-.png">I see that you don't quite believe me. But... perhaps that's a fault of my own lack of prowess in shapeshifting.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="jim" />
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">I'm a demigod of nature and hospitality, but caring for people is my specialty. I'm quite powerful in my old age. ...Though admittedly I've only bothered to work on my shapeshifting recently.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="chara_dreemurr" />
                <state img="#-stripped+.png" marker="senko_char13">Perhaps when you're talking about goals, &lt;i&gt;you're&lt;/i&gt; the one looking for release... or perhaps embrace? There are other worlds and games you could be playing with ~player~ if victory was all that mattered, you know. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="1DN" />
                <state img="#-stripped-.png">Oh, well. At my age you learn to enjoy the attention when you can get it, I suppose!</state>
                <state img="#-stripped-.png">Well, I know it was hardly impressive, but we &lt;i&gt;do&lt;/i&gt; have an entire game to play, &lt;i&gt;myon~!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="2DN" />
                <state img="#-stripped-.png">W-well! You get a better view of my legs, at the very least. </state>
                <state img="#-stripped-.png">P-perhaps my legs and fluffy tail might distract you and enable me to win the next hand?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="3DN" />
                <state img="#-stripped-.png">...Then again, it &lt;i&gt;is&lt;/i&gt; strip poker. Perhaps this &lt;i&gt;is&lt;/i&gt; a decent enough prize unto itself. I can at least comfort you with this pristine view of my tail.</state>
                <state img="#-stripped-.png">Ah... maybe I'm too old for a game such as this. I would offer my tail, but the rules of this venue state that touching is forbidden, and I abide by the rules and laws of the land.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="4DN" />
                <state img="#-stripped-.png">T-though... I certainly hope that you can respect the view before you. While I am rather experienced, it's not itself an experience I gift to many.</state>
                <state img="#-stripped-.png">Few are so brazen as to ask a fox demigod to pillow down with them, but I respect the ambition, at the very least. Please enjoy the view, as they say.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="5DN" />
                <state img="#-stripped-.png">I put quite a lot of work into this form, you know. Please let me know if you find it acceptable. </state>
                <state img="#-stripped-.png">Perhaps, given the work that went into this form, I was expecting to play just a bit better. Not to be a sore loser, but perhaps I could use some complimenting and pampering of my own?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="6DN" />
                <state img="#-stripped-.png">Well... no more tricks left. But I suppose honesty is its own reward. And I'm honestly a little excited. In an intimate way. </state>
                <state img="#-stripped-.png">Y-you know, the sting of defeat can probably be massaged away. I'm relatively approachable in terms of intimate matters, but I'm mostly sorry I couldn't give you a better game. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="7DN" />
                <state img="#-stripped-.png">Nudity is not so strange, though I suppose an old lady with a tail is not, I assume, what you see typically. </state>
                <state img="#-stripped-.png">Why, yes, I am a neat 48kg, of which my tail is nearly 5kg. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">While I've mastered compliments and soothing words as a matter of course, perhaps there's something you might want to say to me to broaden my knowledge?</state>
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">You may choose to compliment me. Nice words ease the spirit, and encourage reciprocity...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">Ah... it feels quite good to stretch the toes. Not that you can see them yet...!</state>
                <state img="#-stripped+.png" weight="0.2">If you find my socks curious, you may indulge yourself by looking them. Please simply make that the extent of your appreciation. </state>
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">Please make your observation the extent of your appreciation. They're simply socks, are they not?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">My, oh my... it so happens that without my hakama, you have an excellent view of my legs and tail. And the rest is doubtless curious to your imagination... hm? </state>
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">As a kitsune, a bit of misdirection and mystery alike can prove quite stimulating, hm? For instance, this thin apron hiding my legs, tail, and who &lt;i&gt;knows&lt;/i&gt; what else.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">Ah... well, I hope this view is one you can enjoy in lieu of a home-cooked meal or fresh sheets. Though, perhaps you can still earn those as well, neh?</state>
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">It &lt;i&gt;is&lt;/i&gt; a risque game. You're welcome to compliment my display, though it's not quite the same as a compliment on my cooking or cleaning prowess.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">My, oh my... is there something wrong? I'm no great beauty, but I hope this form is sufficiently mature for you. </state>
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">Ah... I know that look. But it's so rare that I get to return it in kind. Please. Enjoy this moment between us. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">Goodness. There's nothing wrong with nudity, provided we all approach each other with respect. But if thinking this is forbidden helps you enjoy it...</state>
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">Ah... it &lt;i&gt;does&lt;/i&gt; feel rather liberating. I know my tail is likely my best and fluffiest asset, but there are &lt;i&gt;other&lt;/i&gt; places that can make me &lt;i&gt;myon~&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">Now... whatever comes next? Perhaps me. </state>
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">After 800 years, you realize that you can be different people to different situations. But the one constant is that you should indulge and enjoy selfless pleasures. </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_strip">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="jim" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-interested.png">Goodness, aren't you a handsome young man!</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">My oh my... you're quite strong for a young gentleman your age!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="twisted_fate" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-interested.png">Are you certain you don't want me to get them washed and restitched? They're quite fine for your frame, but a bit of care goes quite a long way!</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">Goodness, are you sure you wouldn't want me to hold onto your clothing? I'm quite good at tending to stitching, washing, and so forth.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="twisted_fate" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">I have to ask... Luck seems to be your lady, does she not?</state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">Ah... Fate, do you have a particular mistress, or is Luck your lady?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="twisted_fate" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-silly.png">Fate, you're enjoying yourself most throughly, aren't you?</state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">Are you having fun, Fate? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="twisted_fate" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-araara.png">Besides nice possessions... what &lt;i&gt;other&lt;/i&gt; forms of pampering might you wish to indulge in?</state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">Are you having fun, Fate? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="twisted_fate" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-araara.png">How do you imagine I'd look in Bilgewater apparel? </state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">The Birgewater aesthetic is quite a nice change of pace... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-silly.png">Goodness, Bobobo. I can imagine your hair would be an--</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_strip">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="amy_rose" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-interested.png">No tail...? Hm... what kind of animal spirit are &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt;?</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">Oh! What kind of spirit are you? The ears give you away. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="polly" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">You're certainly a spirit... but you're not some manner of vengeful ghost, are you?</state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">Ah... I know spirits similar to you. But... you're not going to try and avenge your untimely death tonight, are you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="miko" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-silly.png">Ah, good game to you, Prince. </state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">Well, Prince, it is good as always to see you. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="susie" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-nani.png">What is this horrible aura I sense...</state>
                <state img="#-nani.png">Oh...! What's... what's this darkness? What manner of pain are you in, Susie?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="miko" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-joy.png">I don't expect the Prince to recognize a simple fox as myself, Mistress Tojiko. </state>
                <state img="#-joy.png">Mistress Tojiko, I can hardly expect the Prince to remember a simple fox. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="laevatein" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-interested.png">My! Your hair's simply gorgeous. Are you a warrior princess of some sort?</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">Goodness! Your hair's extremely beautiful. Are you a princess of some sort?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="laevatein" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-joy.png">Laevatein, would you like me to mend your armor? It's quite fine, but has seen many battles, hasn't it?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="laevatein" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-skittish.png">Ah... I'm sorry, Laevatein. You have an aura of uncertainty about you. I draw a great deal of satisfaction from helping people feel comforted. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="miko" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-pampering.png">Ah, Prince, would you mind if I pampered Lady Tojiko? </state>
                <state img="#-pampering.png">I know this is somewhat forward, but Lady Tojiko, might I pamper you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="galatea" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-interested.png">I have to say, whether you're a kami guarding that statue or something else, you've picked a beautiful form. </state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">Galatea, are you a kami guarding the statue, or is the statue your being?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="chara_dreemurr" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-nani.png" marker="chara_senko01">You have such a profound sense of darkness about you...</state>
                <state img="#-nani.png" marker="chara_senko01">So much darkness and bloodthirst. You poor girl.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="lux" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-pampering.png">Goodness! You have such a bright aura, Lux!</state>
                <state img="#-pampering.png">Lux, your aura is so brilliant...!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="wikipe-tan" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-interested.png">You're the avatar of a universal system of scholarship, aren't you?</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">Goodness! You're an avatar, of knowledge, aren't you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="laevatein" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-skittish.png">Laevatein... you seem so unaccostomed to having someone take care of you...</state>
                <state img="#-skittish.png">You don't often actually have a person tend to you needs, do you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="mercy" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-joy.png">I can sense a great deal of tranquility within you. You're a healer, aren't you, Angela? </state>
                <state img="#-joy.png">Ah, goodness. I recognize the tranquil aura of a healer. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="mercy" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-joy.png">Dr. Ziegler, would you like to exchange any tips? You're doubtless due for some pampering, and I am always happy to learn about more modern medical techniques. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="chara_dreemurr" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-skittish.png" marker="chara_senko11a">The occasion to tend to a demon has been decidedly rare... not in centuries. Would a cup of hot tea, or perhaps a cozy blanket help set your heart at ease?</state>
                <state img="#-skittish.png" marker="chara_senko11b">The dark shoals of your soul, Chara, could use some lightness. Would you like a cup of hot chocolate? Perhaps a soothing book?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="laevatein" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-interested.png">I hope you understand that even if this is  a rather lewd place, I would happily give you any comfort you desire, Laevatein. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="penny_polendina" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-interested.png">Goodness, what will humans think of next...</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">Ah... my oh my... what ingenuity people will display...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="tie">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-meep.png">Goodness! A tie!? How extraordinary! </state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">My oh my! A tie!</state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">Ties are quite rare, aren't they? What a memorable moment!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-9">
                <state img="#-meep.png">Tie me up...? Well... I suppose-- &lt;i&gt;oh!&lt;/i&gt; The &lt;i&gt;game&lt;/i&gt; is tied! Ah... much, much different.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="jim" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-silly.png">Goodness. You're flattering an older lady, you know.</state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">Oh, don't be so modest. I'm far older than I look. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-meep.png">Ah, well. I applaud your devotion to your victory! </state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">Myon~!? Your ~clothing~! How... impressive!</state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">I respect your commitment to winning the game! But even your ~clothing~ can be appealing and pleasing, yes?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-smug.png">&lt;i&gt;Myo~n~!&lt;/i&gt; Your ~clothing~ must be quite sentimental to you. </state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Oh... your ~clothing~ ~clothing.ifPlural(look|looks)~ so well loved! </state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">A man and his ~clothing~ are easily parted, &lt;i&gt;especially&lt;/i&gt; when a kitsune offers to wash them. And I do mean your ~clothing~ &lt;i&gt;and&lt;/i&gt; you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">Hm... your ~clothing~ has a certain...</state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">Ah, well. I suppose you'll run out of accessories at some point... who knows what hidden depths you might be hiding something in!</state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">My oh my... Your ~clothing~ is certainly interesting! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-stahp.png">Ah... wow... you're still wearing ~clothing.ifPlural(~clothing~|a ~clothing~)~. </state>
                <state img="#-stahp.png">I really hope you're enjoying making me look stupid! </state>
                <state img="#-stahp.png">I can't masturbate to your ~clothing~, ~name~...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="jim" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-smug.png">Well, there's something to be said for spunk. </state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Fufufu~ Well, I admire your sense of tact, but your muscles are still impressive, neh?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-interested.png">I certainly hope you're enjoying yourself, ~name~. I can't imagine any experience with you and your ~clothing~ going any other way. </state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">Do you have a story about your ~clothing~? It's a small thing, but likely no less significant. </state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">If you need, I can clean that up... after the game, of course, I can imagine all of us needing a bath...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-interested.png">I suppose it's something that reminds me of you. </state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">It has just the slightest touch of &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; about it.</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">I suppose a man's ~clothing~ needs the same love he does!  </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-silly.png">Ah, well. I applaud your devotion to your victory! </state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">I'm not exactly &lt;i&gt;impressed&lt;/i&gt;, but I still appreciate your impressive play, ~name~. </state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">Don't you worry your handsome head, ~name~. I'll still pamper you all the same. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">Well... you &lt;i&gt;have&lt;/i&gt; bested me. I suppose playing on your terms is fulfilling...</state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">...Ah, ~name~. Forgive me. I'm just... preoccupied with my... own pampering. </state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">I'm... well. Your &lt;i&gt;ability to play cards&lt;/i&gt; is impressive. </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0-9" id="17">
                <condition role="target" character="susie" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-skittish.png">Poor girl... do you need a hug? A hot cup of tea? What can I do for you?</state>
                <state img="#-skittish.png">My goodness... so much pain and so murky... can I help you? What can I do to help you feel better?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="miko" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-smug.png">Besides, who could take care of a pampered Prince more than you? </state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Ah, goodness. So many adornments. Who could take better care of them than you, Tojiko?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="laevatein" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-pampering.png">Ah! And after I've mended your armor, perhaps I could give you a hot bath? You look like you love a nice, steamy bath!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="miko" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-silly.png">While I'm sure Prince Miko has mastered certain forms of laying you down, I'd be honored if you gave me the opportunity to care for your otherworldly needs.</state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">I so rarely get the opportunity to grant other spirits their proper rest. Not that I wish to banish you, of course!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="56">
                <condition role="target" character="galatea" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-skittish.png">Oh... I'm sorry, Galatea. I suppose you're compliment more on your looks than your personality. But if I get to know you, I'm sure I would celebrate you for that. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="58">
                <condition role="target" character="chara_dreemurr" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-skittish.png" marker="chara_senko02">We all wish to win... but surely there's an indulgence you'd prefer that's a bit less...</state>
                <state img="#-skittish.png" marker="chara_senko02">Ah... but surely there's something that brings you joy? That makes you happy?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="lux" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-joy.png">Though, my role here is to help you enjoy even a bit more brightness and lightness.</state>
                <state img="#-joy.png">Though, we can always shine a little brighter with some pampering, can't we? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="amy_rose" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-silly.png">Goodness! A two-tailed fox is quite experienced... but I've never heard of an  animal becoming a human. </state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">This is quite novel to me, Amy. But... a two-tailed fox? He must be quite senior to even me!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="mercy" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-silly.png">I imagine the sore spots you're here to tend to &lt;i&gt;tonight&lt;/i&gt; are under your own armor though, neh? </state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">Though... as one lady to another, I imagine you need tender care somewhere very much near your waistline, neh?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="mercy" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-pampering.png">Of course! Massage, natural remedies, and all sorts of soul-nourishment are vital, but person who's in need of tender care can't be happy if they're hurt! I'd adore the chance to trade secrets. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="77">
                <condition role="target" character="chara_dreemurr" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-joy.png" marker="chara12a">Well... I despise the analogy, but if you were to soak in a bath before ~player~ joined you, that would make &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; the tea, wouldn't it?</state>
                <state img="#-joy.png" marker="chara12b">Chocolate tea. Perhaps you'd rather enjoy ~player~ licking some warm chocolate off you, too?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-nani.png">Can you promise to teach me how to do this-- &lt;i&gt;t-the game&lt;/i&gt; later, just us women?</state>
                <state img="#-nani.png">Y-you really had me, ~name~. And not in the way some people want sometimes...</state>
                <state img="#-nani.png">G-goodness! An accessory! At this point. It's not arousing, nor is it... &lt;i&gt;myo~n~...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-interested.png">I'm always so interested in how women wear their ~clothing.ifPlural(~clothing~|~clothing~s)~.</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">Goodness! Speaking as a small person, do not underestimate the power within one's frame...!</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">It's nice that your ~clothing~ looked so good on you. Though... it must be nice to take off your accessories after a long, hard day, neh? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-meep.png">O-Oh! Your ~clothing~... I don't believe it's as cute as... my underwear... but it's still very nice!</state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">Do you find it true that your ~clothing~, and accessories like it, are the things you most easily get attached to, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">Goodness! ~clothing.ifPlural(Those|That)~ ~clothing~ looked so much part of your appearance that I'd hardly considered you may remove it! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-joy.png">I'm not rattled. Like I said, my goal is to provide a good, thorough pampering. </state>
                <state img="#-joy.png">Well, it sure is &lt;i&gt;cute&lt;/i&gt;. And cute is what you aim for, ~name~. </state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">&lt;i&gt;Ara ara...&lt;/i&gt; small, but mighty, &lt;i&gt;neh&lt;/i&gt;?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="hilda" stage="2" sayingMarker="UndoingShirt" />
                <state img="#-smug.png">Miss Hilda... your breasts &lt;i&gt;are&lt;/i&gt; rather impressive. Are you perhaps trying to distract your competitors?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Miss Hilda... are you trying to impress everyone with your breasts...? You need not lend yourself so quickly to distraction...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="amy_rose" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-silly.png">Well, I'm sure you and I are due for many additional interesting conversations, Amy. </state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">Well, Amy, allow me to formally greet you and welcome you to relax while we're here. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="susie" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-okay....png">Oh, Susie... you don't deserve to be feeling so shadowed. I hope we can make you feel better tonight.</state>
                <state img="#-okay....png">A young woman like you shouldn't be in nearly as much conflict as you are...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="miko" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">I want you to know I take no pleasure in you being bested, Prince. </state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">It would seem you've been... out-foxed, Prince.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="laevatein" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-interested.png">Burn some sandalwood, soak you in the tub, and bring you out all warm and refreshed into a soft robe! Has anyone ever done that for you? You certainly look like you could use some attention and comforting. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="miko" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-meep.png">O-Oh my? Pampering both of you? Simultaneously?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="galatea" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-joy.png">Well. Why don't you introduce yourself as you'd like to be seen, Galatea? And I will happily pamper you to make it so. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="59">
                <condition role="target" character="chara_dreemurr" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-interested.png" marker="chara_senko03">~Player~, don't you think we could do something nice for Chara? She's trying so hard to help you win.</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png" marker="chara_senko03">Ah... &lt;i&gt;I&lt;/i&gt; think I have a few things that are a bit more mundane than winning entirely. ~Player~, won't you help me pamper Chara?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="lux" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-pampering.png">Please do not hesitate to call on me. The very least I can do is tend to your armor.</state>
                <state img="#-pampering.png">You just let me know what I can do for you, okay? Would a massage, or buffing your armor help?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="mercy" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-smug.png">I mean no disrespect, but I can tell I'm not the only woman here who's older than she looks. We can appreciate some well-tempered wisdom and honesty, can't we? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="78">
                <condition role="target" character="chara_dreemurr" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="chara13a">You'd be happier if you focused on your bond with ~player~, Chara. </state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="chara13b">You've sacrificed so much for ~player~... would you enjoy being the prize for once, Chara?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-smug.png">I've seen quite a few things. But a woman's ~clothing.ifPlural(~clothing~|~clothing~s)~~ may change with the times, but never the way she wears it. </state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I certainly enjoy what I see. Please continue your best of efforts. </state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Well, they say that no matter how many accessories you wear, the best thing in a woman's wardrobe is her confidence!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">...My choice of undergarments &lt;i&gt;is&lt;/i&gt; more appealing than ~clothing.ifPlural(some|a)~ mere ~clothing~, yes...?</state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">While I very easily could remove it, I believe it would be better to retain my iconic look and keep my charm in my hair...</state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">Ah... well... I did rather enjoy ~clothing.ifPlural(those|that)~ ~clothing~... but perhaps it's more fun to fold...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-meep.png">O-Oh! It's... goodness. I'm struck by how beautiful you are, regardless of your accessorization!</state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">My oh my! Perhaps it's my state of undress, but... your skill and beauty are quite evident!</state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">...I was more than happy to acknowledge your skill, ~name~... compliments &lt;i&gt;are&lt;/i&gt; a form of pampering, after all. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-stahp.png">I-I just suppose this leaves you in an adequate place to be taken care of...</state>
                <state img="#-stahp.png">Why... g-goodness! </state>
                <state img="#-stahp.png">&lt;i&gt;Myon~...&lt;/i&gt; Am--I am performing adequately, am I not? W-would a more direct approach have been preferable? </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="twisted_fate" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-araara.png">Ah, will you be covering yourself with it? I find the idea quite appealing.</state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">I may be a rather old lady by your standards... but that type of display, of holding your hat over your &lt;i&gt;heavenly spear&lt;/i&gt;...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="twisted_fate" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-smug.png">Ah... a nice renegade in need of some love? </state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Well, impetuous as you are, I find a lawless, rambling sort the &lt;i&gt;best&lt;/i&gt; to just &lt;i&gt;pamper&lt;/i&gt; senseless. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="twisted_fate" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-joy.png">You seem like a man who needs a bit of the finer things in life. A great hand...</state>
                <state img="#-joy.png">Starting with a nice hand, I imagine you're a man who enjoys a life of luxury, but rarely immerses himself. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Don't you want to take that big, heavy &lt;i&gt;~clothing~&lt;/i&gt; off? You really ought to settle in. Enjoy the view...</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Myon~ and to think that I cook and clean, too...</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">My oh my... would it help if I hung up your ~clothing~ for you? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-fufufu.png">While I &lt;i&gt;am&lt;/i&gt; an immortal demigod fox, I &lt;i&gt;do&lt;/i&gt; have a substantial appreciation for the mortal form.</state>
                <state img="#-fufufu.png">Normally, I'd pamper a single person... but seeing as &lt;i&gt;I&lt;/i&gt; am a single person, I'd love the chance to indulge myself in indulging others...</state>
                <state img="#-fufufu.png">My hearing is quite sensitive... so I can hear your heartbeat, ~name~...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-interested.png">Oh... we're going for something interesting now, are we? I'll have you know I'm very good at laundry... and massage.</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">Many fox spirits take on mortal consorts... but you have to be awfully impressive. </state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">Myon! I don't suppose there's a Ms. ~Name~? II there is, please make sure she pampers you!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-araara.png">O-oh...! Well... I &lt;i&gt;am&lt;/i&gt; immortal... this means I've picked up quite a few... &lt;i&gt;tricks&lt;/i&gt; for pampering, you know. </state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">You may fluff my tail. If it pleases you. </state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">Goodness! You look a bit tesnse. Would you like a hot bath? A massage? A cold cup of alcohol? </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_minor">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="twisted_fate" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-interested.png">The offer to maintain your apparel... or your self... still stands, Fate. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="twisted_fate" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-interested.png">Ohoh~ You could use a lot of care. But let's start with your clothes. </state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">I'm sure I can find &lt;i&gt;some&lt;/i&gt; way to make your losses worthwhile.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="twisted_fate" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">...Soft robes, lovingly prepared meals, a warm bath overlooking a beautiful sunset... &lt;i&gt;Other&lt;/i&gt; things. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-araara.png">I appreciate your contribution to the game, but you know that I don't mind taking care of you...</state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">Life is too short not to enjoy it, neh? </state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">Hm... that's one less thing to stop me from pampering you. Surrender already, if you'd please~</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-silly.png">I hope you don't mind an old lady like me flirting with you, ~name~. It's all in good fun, and you should really indulge yourself in a game like this. </state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">&lt;i&gt;Kekeke&lt;/i&gt;~ Don't mind me, ~name~. I have many skills. Providing a fun experience is one of them, even if it's harmless.</state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">Ah... well then. Consider it part of the experience. Relax, ~name~. I'd happily bring you a drink. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-interested.png">...Hm... I suppose there's always more to do, isn't there?</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">The joy of life is that you never stop getting to enjoy even the changes that come about. </state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">I'm right here when you need me, ~name~. All I ask is for your respect. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-araara.png">Good boy. </state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">If you would be so kind as to show off more...</state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">Goodness. Please take care of your ~clothing~, and who &lt;i&gt;knows&lt;/i&gt; what may end up taking care of you.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="polly" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-skittish.png">Ah... well, should you need any pampering... </state>
                <state img="#-skittish.png">Are you certain? You poor dear. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="16">
                <condition role="target" character="miko" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-smug.png">And I see Mistress Tojiko will &lt;i&gt;also&lt;/i&gt; be joining us.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">And you as well, Mistress Tojiko.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="laevatein" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-joy.png">Ah. Well, I know a thing or two, and I know a woman like you could use some tender love and care!</state>
                <state img="#-joy.png">I hope you don't mind me saying so, but I believe you of all people could use a little pampering. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="laevatein" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-hug.png">
                    <alt-img stage="0-7">#-hug.png</alt-img>
                    <alt-img stage="8-9">#-pampering.png</alt-img>
                    <text>So, please. Anything you need. I'm right here for you. Leave your worries with me and let me pamper you. </text>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="wikipe-tan" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-silly.png">Ah. Well, a kitsune comforts, and you share the knowledge of humanity. Both are things of beauty, though I'm truly envious of you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="penny_polendina" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-silly.png">You aren't exactly human yourself, are you, Penny? You &lt;i&gt;are&lt;/i&gt; quite beautiful, though. </state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">You're a beautiful young woman, Penny... but you aren't fully human, are you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-interested.png">Hm... what types of pampering do you most like, ~name~? </state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">Just imagine it as the end of the day, and you're coming home to a warm meal and a nice, easy night!</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">Do you think I'd look good in your ~clothing~, ~name~? I've often considered a more modern look. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-silly.png">Please, make sure that whoever Mr. ~Name~ is is as good to you as you are to your ~clothing~, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">While your ~clothing~ ~clothing.ifPlural(are|is)~ cute, I think the cutest part of your defeat is yourself.  </state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">Since you're taking off your ~clothing~, it seems only fair we make it worth your time. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">My primary abilities are domestic... but intimate matters are nonetheless rather important, regardless of... the person, hm? </state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">In having lived 800 years, I've had more than a few encounters with a woman... </state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">Hm... though I do fully appreciate your ~clothing~, I wish you to know the woman underneath holds quite a bit more interest to me at this stage of the game. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-interested.png">At this stage... well, I could use some pampering too... &lt;i&gt;visually&lt;/i&gt;, at the very least!</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">Goodness... look at the effect you're having on me, ~name~... </state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">~Name~... you look &lt;i&gt;quite&lt;/i&gt; exceptionally beautiful. And you can always trust a kitsune!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_minor">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="polly" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-haunted.png">Oh. I see. Hm. </state>
                <state img="#-haunted.png">Ah... I suppose &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; kind of pampering is what you're here for. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="miko" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-fufufu.png">I suppose playing with the two of you will be quite the edifying experience. </state>
                <state img="#-fufufu.png">Ah... well, it's always interesting to hear how a couple pampers each other, as well. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="laevatein" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-fufufu.png">I'm sure you're in for quite the delight during and after this game, Laevatein!</state>
                <state img="#-fufufu.png">Fufufu~ I can see that you're a woman trying her best. And that means you deserve to be loved, cherished, and taken care of! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="laevatein" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-silly.png">We can take it slowly if you like. I'm certain you'll want a warm washcloth at the end of the game, at the very least.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="wikipe-tan" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-araara.png">You have knowledge in abundance. Are you here to learn a... ah, practical degree of romance? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="penny_polendina" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-joy.png">Perhaps you're interested in... well. You are at this card game, dear. </state>
                <state img="#-joy.png">My... well... what do &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; want from this game, dear?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Well, I'm certain no matter what your inclinations are, I'd be happy to help you!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Hm... though your ~clothing~ ~clothing.ifPlural(were|was)~ interesting, perhaps something like your choice of sushi would yet be more so?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">~Clothing~... Hm... I &lt;i&gt;do&lt;/i&gt; wonder how it would look like on me. Or... perhaps more traditional apparel for you, to help you feel elegant?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-interested.png">Your ~clothing~ ~clothing.ifPlural(deserve|deserves)~ care, ~name~. But not as much as you!</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">You're having fun, yes? While not all of life must be abundantly exciting, it &lt;i&gt;is&lt;/i&gt; made better by moments like this, myon~?</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">Well, well! You're provoking such curious reactions, ~name~! Perhaps... there is quite a bit of merit to your approach.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-araara.png">Hm... well... relaxation provides it's own unique opportunities, don't you think so, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">Goodness... to think you looked pretty before you took off your ~clothing~! You'd best be careful not to pamper &lt;i&gt;me&lt;/i&gt; too much, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">Myon~! Well... I'm more used to physical pampering. But you're certainly teaching me something new, ~name~...!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-fufufu.png">Myon~! You may wish to keep going. I'm already providing quite a bit of my own pampering to the others, neh?</state>
                <state img="#-fufufu.png">Ah... your ~clothing~ ~clothing.ifPlural(were|was)~ quite interesting... something that makes you--&lt;i&gt;hahh&lt;/i&gt;--feel good should be considered, hm?</state>
                <state img="#-fufufu.png">I do know how to maintain a fire... both for cooking... and... just how you're doing, ~name~. </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_major">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="twisted_fate" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-smug.png">I can fix up your pants, if you'd like. But whatever would we do while you're out of them, I wonder?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-interested.png">Goodness! If you wanted things to get steamy, I could have simply poured you a bath...</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">O-Oh? Of course. It's merely like coming home at the end of a long day, neh?</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">G-goodness! I'll make sure to take good care of your ~clothing~. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Well, joining a semi-dressed kitsune &lt;i&gt;is&lt;/i&gt; an act of self-care.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Oh... I have a feeling where &lt;i&gt;you'd&lt;/i&gt; like to be pampered, hm? </state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">My oh my... we might have to get you into a bath if you're going to get naked. Or perhaps you'd prefer the massage table?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-fufufu.png">Well, joining a semi-dressed kitsune &lt;i&gt;is&lt;/i&gt; an act of self-care.</state>
                <state img="#-fufufu.png">It was quite a delight when I undressed. I suppose we do owe you the same attention.</state>
                <state img="#-fufufu.png">&lt;i&gt;Myo~n~!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-araara.png">Mm...! </state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">Ah... I... had been wondering. S-surely curiosity is a normal part of the game, hm?</state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">&lt;i&gt;Myo~n~!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_major">
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-meep.png">Hy&lt;i&gt;oung&lt;/i&gt;--! </state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">&lt;i&gt;Myooo~n~&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">&lt;i&gt;Hmm-mmh&lt;/i&gt;!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-skittish.png">Do not be upset simply because I'm still mostly dressed. You will doubtless have further chances to play!</state>
                <state img="#-skittish.png">Defeat is part of the experience. Please do not be upset to be behind...</state>
                <state img="#-skittish.png">Ah... ~name~. Please tell me you're still having fun! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">...I'm being plenty attended to with the view. </state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">Hm... would you be interested in perhaps fluffing my tail? </state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">(&lt;i&gt;~clothing.ifPlural(Those|That)~ ~clothing~ would drape over me... would that be cute, though?&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-araara.png">Perhaps you should keep going. Then you might be able to get some &lt;i&gt;particular&lt;/i&gt; care. </state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">Goodness. I live to serve, but I think views like this make it &lt;i&gt;much&lt;/i&gt; easier. </state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">My oh my... getting quite warm in here? Do you need a cool drink? Or someone to wipe you down?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_major">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="laevatein" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-hug.png">Poor girl. Here, give me that when you're done with it. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="65">
                <condition role="target" character="laevatein" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-silly.png">There's no ulterior motives, Laevatein. While I do find you cute, I'm much more interested in your health and wellness than anything you could do for me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="penny_polendina" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-pampering.png">Oh, don't worry, Penny. I can take care of you however you want.</state>
                <state img="#-pampering.png">However you'd like me to tend to you, Penny. Don't worry. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-meep.png">Oh my! If it helps, you'll doubtless be on your way to enjoyable new experiences soon!</state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">I've always been fairly good at games, but this is far from my specialty...</state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">Oh! Surely you're just choosing to get more comfortable, ~name~?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Well, well. Do you think you can compete with your elders, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Heh. </state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">You're looking a bit like the laundry, ~name~. Ready to be set at rest after you get nice and wet.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-interested.png">This is quite liberating, ~name~. It's nice to see that you're joining me!</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">My... this may not be a new experience... but there's something appealing in the familiar...</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">Disrobing your ~clothing~ is the first step to some of the best pampering you can get, ~name~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-interested.png">Myon~!</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">Hm...! </state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">Ah... well... sometimes one is the mood for something a bit &lt;i&gt;different&lt;/i&gt;, neh?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_major">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="laevatein" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-fufufu.png">I will endeavor to bring you a soothing tea and a comfortable blanket for later. </state>
                <state img="#-fufufu.png">I will return shortly with an herbal tea. And a toasty blanket for later.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="66">
                <condition role="target" character="laevatein" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-araara.png">Your happiness is more than enough. Even if your breasts &lt;i&gt;are&lt;/i&gt; rather cute. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="hilda" stage="6" />
                <state img="#-fufufu.png">An impressive garb for an impressive young woman.</state>
                <state img="#-fufufu.png">Goodness... to be young again. Doubtless you're quite primed to deal with the &lt;i&gt;youthful endurance&lt;/i&gt; of any companion you'd so choose, neh?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="hilda" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">I'll have you know that I'm feeling rather distracted, Hilda. </state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">Goodness. I have children older than you, and yet I find myself distracted. Curse this inhuman libido... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="penny_polendina" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-interested.png">...In many ways, you're more human than I am. </state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">Despite my experiences... you're quite a bit more human than me. It's natural that I'd wish to tend to you. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-interested.png">Well, you do have a few pieces left, don't you? Perhaps I can offer you a massage, later?</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">&lt;i&gt;Myon~&lt;/i&gt;! </state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">While I don't intend to throw the game away, I do want you to know you make defeat look appealing!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">A little taunting isn't exactly polite, but it &lt;i&gt;is&lt;/i&gt; fun, right?</state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">I'm not certain why, but I &lt;i&gt;am&lt;/i&gt; beginning to feel a bit... shy. </state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">It's rather nice to not need to worry about someone else's ~clothing~ except that they remove it. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-araara.png">I'm &lt;i&gt;mostly&lt;/i&gt; used to men, but it never hurts to have a range of experiences to draw on.</state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">Ah... aren't you a beautiful sight, ~name~. </state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">Goodness...! The spirit of competition &lt;i&gt;and&lt;/i&gt; pampering are encouraging me to be rather bold...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-meep.png">~Name~...</state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">Oh... oh my...</state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">I-is this...? Please continue, ~name~, and appreciate the attention.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="twisted_fate" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-joy.png">Though, perhaps a satisfying meal, then the feeling of having your most &lt;i&gt;heavy&lt;/i&gt; of burdens drained to the dregs...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="64">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-nani.png">--Easy thing to... to take care of.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-interested.png">Myon~!</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">I find it amazing how a simple bet can transform a normal event into something so intimate!</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">I hope you find it affirming that I remain excited to see you undress, ~name~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Ah, and I thought I was being too subtle. </state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">There we are. Let's get you out of ~clothing.ifPlural(those|that)~ restraining ~clothing~ so you can relax.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I'm enjoying the visual pampering already. But why settle? Let's &lt;i&gt;really indulge.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-interested.png">...There's something so &lt;i&gt;wonderful&lt;/i&gt; about seeing a man in need of some loving hands.</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">You've already enjoyed how I look... this is even more motivation to help, ~name~. </state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">Quite handsome. And I've seen my share of handsome men over the years!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-interested.png">Ah... I'd love to touch you... </state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">I could wash you clean... anyway you wanted...</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">My oh my... and I've been looking forward to this so &lt;i&gt;badly&lt;/i&gt;...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="jim" stage="6" />
                <state img="#-araara.png">I think I'd feel rather pampered in your arms. You &lt;i&gt;are&lt;/i&gt; a gentle man, after all. </state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">Well, goodness. I won't say I'm not impressed by a man with arms almost as big as me. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="twisted_fate" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-araara.png">You're making a &lt;i&gt;compelling&lt;/i&gt; case to let &lt;i&gt;either&lt;/i&gt; of my lips do you justice, hm? Or perhaps you'd prefer to use your &lt;i&gt;beard&lt;/i&gt; against mine?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-stahp.png">Ah. I'm used to cleaning ears, but your Fist of the Nose Hair is... ah... &lt;i&gt;*Flabbergasted Fox Noises&lt;/i&gt;*</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">I'm a bit too dressed up to pamper you in the way I'd like to, ~name~. Perhaps we should fix that.</state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">Hm... Impressive. But don't you think you're feeling sore? Perhaps you'd like someone skilled at massage to help you unwind?</state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">Oh... goodness. So... tense. Doubtless we'll need to get you to relax. Perhaps in a hands-on fashion. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-araara.png">Handsome. Surely you deserve a nice, relaxing evening after such a hard day, hm?</state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">Oh... there we are. Now this is a view we can enjoy together. </state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">It may take me a moment to get warmed up... but I hope you know I'm not naive about this sort of thing...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-smug.png">I know it's hard to compare to a fox demigod...</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Well, well. So much tension. We should find a way to make that melt away, hm?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Ah... look at you, ~name~, working &lt;i&gt;so hard&lt;/i&gt;. I'd be happy to help you when the game's over.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Whoever says a man's chest is less interesting than a woman's isn't trying very hard. </state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Impressive, ~name~... impressive enough to earn some tender &lt;i&gt;loving&lt;/i&gt;... care.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Ah... worth the wait, and good... material for the imagination.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-9" id="61">
                <condition role="target" character="twisted_fate" />
                <state img="#-araara.png">800 years and I continue to live for moments like these...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-skittish.png">Oh my... so quickly! </state>
                <state img="#-skittish.png">Goodness... and I haven't even started to show anything saucy...!</state>
                <state img="#-skittish.png">Oh... well, I'm sure you aren't too shaken up, but I do feel bad...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-interested.png">Well... it's nothing I haven't seen before.</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">I'm over 800 years old. I've seen whatever you have on multiple occasions, I'm sure. </state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">Ah... well, this isn't new, but it's always exciting.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-araara.png">Oh... &lt;i&gt;won't you please&lt;/i&gt; pamper me?</state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">My oh my... here we are, an exposed fox demigod and a seduced man...</state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">Some people enjoy reading erotic fiction. Others of us like to live it, &lt;i&gt;neh?&lt;/i&gt; What's wrong with fantasy?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-fufufu.png">And to think, you already have this lovely view. </state>
                <state img="#-fufufu.png">It's not always the size of the meal, but the love that goes into it, &lt;i&gt;neh&lt;/i&gt;?</state>
                <state img="#-fufufu.png">If you're feeling loved and pampered, feel free to compliment your hostess.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_small_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-silly.png">Aw...! It's admirable that you're so self-confident. </state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">I'm a small person. That looks just about my size. </state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">For someone who was out so quickly, you certainly seem eager to prove yourself. I can't possibly imagine why you feel you'd need to.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-meep.png">Oh my! I imagine you have quite a strong technique, hm?</state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">Goodness...! &lt;i&gt;You&lt;/i&gt; could certainly use some love, couldn't you?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Oh! Oh! I can do-- E-er... &lt;i&gt;anyone&lt;/i&gt; can do a lot more with the smaller ones, you know... finesse is more important than power.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-araara.png">Ah... it's so pleasing... while the bigger ones &lt;i&gt;are&lt;/i&gt; fun... well... I bet &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; appreciate the opportunity a lot more, &lt;i&gt;myon~&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">Oh... well. I have a rather abundant range of pamperings you can do to me-- with me.</state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">Hm... oh yes. It's perfect for someone like me. My oh my, is it &lt;i&gt;ever&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-araara.png">Well... I can pamper you over and &lt;i&gt;over&lt;/i&gt;. I'm already warmed up. </state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">Oh... I can put my experience to work with you, ~name~...</state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">Myon~! I'm rather small too, so... I'll definitely be happy to get you calm and relaxed. Mhm!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_medium_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-7" id="62">
                <condition role="target" character="twisted_fate" />
                <state img="#-interested.png">The only complaint I have is that's not as near me as I'd like...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-araara.png">&lt;i&gt;Myon~...!&lt;/i&gt; What... would you like for dinner? Fish? Hot pot? ...Me?</state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">I'm quite light on my feet. Or on top, ~name~. </state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">Oh... how lovely. I want to pamper you &lt;i&gt;tightly&lt;/i&gt; and &lt;i&gt;deeply&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">Ah, it's perfect for-- &lt;i&gt;pampering.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">Goodness... so forward.</state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">It's nice, but you're being terribly direct, don't you think?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-meep.png">Oh... t-that can work wonders.</state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">What a delightful experience... </state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">&lt;i&gt;Myon~&lt;/i&gt;? Ah... it's perfect! Big enough to get the job done, but small enough to prove... t-to open many avenues of care. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-interested.png">It would be like a massage. So tight at the start, but so warm at the end...</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">Myon~... I'd love for you to take care of &lt;i&gt;me&lt;/i&gt; with that, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">My oh my... whatever shall you do with that, ~name~? If I might make a suggestion...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_large_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-haunted.png">...Y-you were in such a hurry. And it's so... enormous.</state>
                <state img="#-haunted.png">...It would seem I was mistaken. It. Is. Enormous. </state>
                <state img="#-haunted.png">I've seen many things. But I do not believe my ability to render care extends to... goodness.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-haunted.png">...It... that couldn't... </state>
                <state img="#-haunted.png">...I'd say I could use my mouth but even &lt;i&gt;then&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-haunted.png">...Please, have mercy on an old woman.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">It's... it's very big. But... I suppose all people need pampering.</state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">It would... I'm so small and it's so... &lt;i&gt;hmm...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">I... I'm shocked, b-but somehow a tiny bit curious. For your very not tiny bit.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-meep.png">W-well... we could try but... p-pampering should feel good. And not... </state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">Well... I-I'm very curious. I don't know if it would even fit, or if it would good if it did, but... </state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">A-ah... it's so big. So, so very big. And I am so, so very... not. C-could we perhaps avoid...?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="penny_polendina" />
                <state img="#-skittish.png">If this is your first effort... are you certain showing yourself to so many people is what you want?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-silly.png">While this is an intimate moment, I'm certain everyone will be respectful. </state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">I think there's appeal at all sizes. </state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">Well... it's about time! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-interested.png">Comparison is the theft of joy... but variety is the gift of imagination. </state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">Beauty comes in all shapes and sizes...</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">Every person deserves a unique manner of being taken care of...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-meep.png">While I'm quite proficient at fluffing my own tail, I can give an excellent breast massage...</state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">Ah... I just want to knead all the tension from you...</state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">They're at the perfect size for me to just caress and care for...!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_small_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-interested.png">As someone else who's generally on the smaller size, know that it's the size of your heart, not chest, that truly is where all the love comes from. </state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">Ah... they're so perky! You make it easy for someone to snuggle, hm?</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">Quite adorable, ~name~. And time spent rubbing your back can be repurposed for rubbing &lt;i&gt;other&lt;/i&gt; things when considering your long term health.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-araara.png">Oh... they're so &lt;i&gt;cute&lt;/i&gt;! But if you'd like, I could certainly give them a massage.</state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">They say massaging them helps them look perkier and fuller. Perhaps I could help? </state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">My oh my... quite a feast for the eyes, if not the mouth.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-interested.png">Myon~! They're a perfect size and shape, wouldn't you say? </state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">Oh...! They're so pleasing to look at, ~name~... but to truly understand an experience, you need to experience more than one sense, neh?</state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">They're quite nice to look at, but presentation is only one part of the pampering. Perhaps you should consider how they feel? I certainly am. </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_medium_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="penny_polendina" />
                <state img="#-interested.png">Well... as long as you're enjoying yourself. I'm sure you'll enjoying someone else enjoying you as well, Penny. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">While mine are not terribly smaller... I suppose you &lt;i&gt;do&lt;/i&gt; have larger ones...</state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">Jealousy is unbecoming of a kitsune. But it doesn't mean you're not allowed to feel a bit of pride yourself, ~name~. </state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">Ah... they're certainly very womanly. A massage would doubtless be pleasing to both you and a partner, &lt;i&gt;hm?&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">I'm happy with my size... but I do wonder if a bit extra would make it easy to provide... experiences that smaller chests cannot. </state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">They're beautiful, ~name~! I'm simply imagining how best to... ah... take care of them, were they to be sore. </state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">I don't think our chests are so different... save that yours may be slightly larger. B-but what I lack in physical stature I make up for with an abundance of fluff!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-interested.png">Ah... what a lovely place to rest at the end of a long day.</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">Goodness... I hope you're taking care of those. Would you like me to show you some massage techniques? Hands-on, of course. Just lay back and relax.</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">Oh... well, if you give me a moment, I'd be happy to cherish your chest, ~name~...! You're so... ah... I'd certainly rest my head there...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_large_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-haunted.png">...Your poor back. And I thought you were simply padding.</state>
                <state img="#-haunted.png">&lt;i&gt;Ara ara...&lt;/i&gt; </state>
                <state img="#-haunted.png">Half of me wants to bury my face in your nice, fluffy... but the other half...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-haunted.png">...Should you require assistance, please simply let me know.</state>
                <state img="#-haunted.png">A-at least I have a fluffy tail. Even though your chest is fluffy enough...</state>
                <state img="#-haunted.png">...What a bountiful harvest your presence must entail.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-araara.png">Ah... at this point, I just want to bury my face inbetween your breasts and use my final breaths to pamper you...!</state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">My, oh my. Aren't you in need of an &lt;i&gt;abundance&lt;/i&gt; of pampering?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="penny_polendina" />
                <state img="#-joy.png">Penny... I'm sure people here are going to rather enjoy your next play. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-fufufu.png">Fufufu~ I did warn you not to underestimate me. </state>
                <state img="#-fufufu.png">Time to bare your womanhood. </state>
                <state img="#-fufufu.png">Fret not, this &lt;i&gt;is&lt;/i&gt; what many came here to see! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-5">
                <state img="#-meep.png">Ah, anticipation has certainly built to this moment! </state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">I find myself rather invested in the game at this point... </state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">Well...! We've certainly taken our time getting to this, but... all good experiences must have a climax!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-araara.png">There's nothing wrong with more than one cute naked woman, is there? </state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">Ah... which will triumph? Youthful bravery, or the experience of elders? </state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">Mm... I &lt;i&gt;have&lt;/i&gt; gotten to be rather curious, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-interested.png">Mmm~!</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">&lt;i&gt;Myon~&lt;/i&gt;!</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">Ah... time for the experience to improve even more. A true indulgence!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <condition filter="shaved" role="target" />
                <condition filter="non-human" role="target" />
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">How unfortunate. Some of us must contribute quite a bit of effort to displaying a mature guise... I guess your folk lack such an ability.</state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">This isn't what I was expecting... but I suppose if you aren't a human, you should not be expected to conform to human norms.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="hilda" />
                <state img="#-smug.png">I've gotten quite skilled at... &lt;i&gt;grooming&lt;/i&gt;, Hilda. Wouldn't you enjoy the feeling of getting &lt;i&gt;as close as possible&lt;/i&gt; to a partner? I could do it for you, you know...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="wikipe-tan" />
                <state img="#-araara.png">Goodness... I bet your intimate life is rather enthusiastic, neh?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="penny_polendina" />
                <state img="#-incensed.png">She's as much of a person as any of us. Respect her, or I promise I can do &lt;i&gt;quite&lt;/i&gt; a bit more than pamper you. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <condition filter="shaved" role="target" />
                <state img="#-stahp.png">...When I expected you to bare your womanhood, I did not expect your womanhood to be bare...!</state>
                <state img="#-stahp.png">Goodness...! I understand good grooming is essential, but this is quite the surprise!</state>
                <state img="#-stahp.png">Is... I've tried to shapeshift into a more mature form, but it's rather shocking that people would prefer this. &lt;br&gt;I suppose it &lt;i&gt;is&lt;/i&gt; tidy.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <condition filter="hairy" role="target" />
                <state img="#-meep.png">Oh! I suppose the natural look suits you... but I've met few humans so... &lt;i&gt;blessed&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">Oh my! While my tail is fluffy, it looks like you have some fluff of your own! </state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">I-it's a rather unusual form of pampering, but would you like me to trim that for you, ~name~? Your hair looks quite fluffy on its own!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <condition filter="trimmed" role="target" />
                <state img="#-interested.png">Oh! It's neat and trimmed! I hadn't thought to do that, but it seems obvious in retrospect.</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">Oh! Your hair looks so clean and tidy! I hadn't considered that such a thing could be so attractive...!</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">My! That &lt;i&gt;does&lt;/i&gt; look appealing. Perhaps I may even trim myself after this. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-5">
                <condition filter="shaved" role="target" />
                <state img="#-stahp.png">Oh. Did... you remove your hair, there? And I put so much effort into shapeshifting a tasteful amount onto myself...</state>
                <state img="#-stahp.png">Ah. I see. Perhaps I'm not up to date with modern fashion. I certainly hope when it's my turn to drop my panties, nobody will think too harshly of me.</state>
                <state img="#-stahp.png">...So this look &lt;i&gt;is&lt;/i&gt; attractive among conventional audiences... and to think, all the effort I put into my appearance to provide a wholesome pampering...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-7">
                <condition filter="hairy" role="target" />
                <state img="#-silly.png">You're certainly no stranger to fluff, are you, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">While there's nothing wrong with the natural state of things... a bit of tidying up can be a wonderful way to enjoy your space even more.</state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">&lt;i&gt;I see an easy way to pamper you, ~name~~ ♪&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-5">
                <condition filter="trimmed" role="target" />
                <state img="#-interested.png">I hadn't considered that as an option. I wonder what I could do with &lt;i&gt;my&lt;/i&gt; hair to provide a more interesting experience...</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">Ah! A woman after my own heart. There's plenty of beauty in the natural state of things, but a bit of guidance makes it so much more palatable, neh?</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">Oh! You've clearly put some work in. Whoever you're... trying to bed... to pamper, of course... is certainly going to appreciate the effort. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <condition filter="shaved" role="target" />
                <state img="#-nani.png">Ah... you're hairless. Was that a challenge to accomplish?</state>
                <state img="#-nani.png">Ah... no hair, there? Perhaps this is a form of pampering I've not become aware of.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <condition filter="shaved" role="target" />
                <state img="#-araara.png">I suppose not having hair there... would lend itself to a rather intimate experience. </state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">That seems to be far too much work... but perhaps you can prove me wrong.</state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">Ah... it's abominably cute. I can't help myself, ~name~... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <condition filter="trimmed" role="target" />
                <state img="#-silly.png">Oh! It's darling! I love the way you've shaped yourself up. Maybe I could give it a touch myself?</state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">My oh my...! I'll have to imagine what that feels like. But I suppose you and some lucky person can do far more than imagine!</state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">I'm not against learning something new. And trimming it like that seems like just the thing to surprise someone.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <condition filter="hairy" role="target" />
                <state img="#-araara.png">Quite a mature look... perhaps we would contrast nicely, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">Ah... even in fox shape, I doubt I can amass so much fuzz anywhere but my tail. Though... I think we'd both have a fun time fluffing yours, &lt;i&gt;neh&lt;/i&gt;?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-smug.png">I won't claim to be an expert... but I find that understanding how someone treats themself provides great insight into caring for them later. </state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Few are lucky to be so cute, all the way through. Quite lovely, ~name~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-5">
                <state img="#-araara.png">Hm... it's not over yet... but to have come this far. </state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">Truly an experience to be treasured. Being able to share yourself and be appreciated as a work of art...</state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">My oh my... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">G-goodness. I'm finding it hard to restrain myself. </state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">To think, you're making me lose my composure, ~name~. Not the simplest of actions. </state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">I... hm. I'm feeling rather pampered myself, right now. Quite a lovely view, hm.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-araara.png">Oh... it looks quite a bit messy already. Maybe I should take care of that for you, ~name~? </state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">Say the word if you'd like to be &lt;i&gt;pampered.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">Ah~ well... it seems like you're making a mess, ~name~. I'd be happy to clean it up. Though... my tongue seems to be the best implement for the job.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_lost">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="aoba" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-joy.png">Ah... I sense in you the soul of an artist. </state>
                <state img="#-joy.png">Miss Aoba, I sense within you the proud soul of a determined artist! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="aoba" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-interested.png">So... how would you like me to care for you? Massaging your hands? Rubbing your neck? </state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">Would you like it most if I were to massage your sore hands? Or perhaps your neck, or lower back? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="aoba" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-haunted.png">You took the bust comment rather personally, I can see. </state>
                <state img="#-haunted.png">I seem to have failed you. You've taken that bust comment to heart. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="3" totalRounds="0" priority="100">
                <state img="#-silly.png">Don't you fret, ~name~. I promise to help you feel adored. </state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">I'm sure this will be very impressive. And afterwards, I would love to pamper you! </state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">Please enjoy the game, ~name~! I know the rest of us will. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" id="6" priority="1">
                <condition status="mostly_clothed" role="target" />
                <state img="#-interested.png">You have quite an array of options, ~name~. Why don't you take off the thing that's making you least comfortable? </state>
                <state img="#-joy.png">Myo~n~! I'd ask you to take off something interesting, but why don't you take off something you find boring?</state>
                <state img="#-joy.png">I hope you're having fun, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-hug.png">I can help you undress, if it makes you happy... those rules about not touching each other seem foolish, if you ask me. </state>
                <state img="#-hug.png">Hm... I came here to pamper, but I'm rather enjoying myself besides!</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">Well, well, ~name~! You're still playing quite well!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7" id="8" priority="1">
                <condition status="mostly_clothed" role="target" />
                <state img="#-silly.png">Goodness! I'm feeling rather exposed compared to ~name~! </state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">It's actually rather liberating to undress, ~name~. But feel free to play to win. Whatever makes you happy. </state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">Hm... well, undressing slowly means you can take your time, right? </state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">The essence of pampering is patience. Don't rush on my account, ~name~. </state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">My oh my! I'm impressed. You've played well so far, ~name~. </state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">I hope &lt;i&gt;I'm&lt;/i&gt; not distracting you, ~name~, though...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9" id="12" priority="1">
                <condition status="mostly_clothed" role="target" />
                <state img="#-meep.png">My, my... now I just want to pamper you even harder, ~name~. </state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">Oh... so many layers left. Surely you deserve a deep massage... &lt;i&gt;at the very least&lt;/i&gt; for your excellent play?</state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">Well, well... I suppose I could learn a trick or two from you... so it'd be fair of me to teach &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; something, neh?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7" id="2" priority="0">
                <condition status="not_lost_some" role="target" />
                <state img="#-joy.png">My... you certainly played much better than I did, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-pampering.png">Goodness! You're quite the skilled gambler, ~name~. </state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">Victory is always a flattering look. Though, grace in defeat is infinitely more fulfilling. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4" id="7" priority="0">
                <condition status="decent" role="target" />
                <state img="#-araara.png" oneShotId="134">It would seem we're about to get a rather intimate look at you, ~name~. </state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">I hope you know that you're &lt;i&gt;still&lt;/i&gt; getting pampered even if you lose...</state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">Defeat is not such a bad thing, is it? It just makes your &lt;i&gt;reward&lt;/i&gt; all the better when you get it. </state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">Why... I'm no tactician, but I can see more and more of you, ~name~...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" id="5" priority="0">
                <condition status="exposed" role="target" />
                <state img="#-joy.png">We move yet closer to my victory! </state>
                <state img="#-pampering.png">Ah... what is self-love but a form of pampering? I suppose ~name~ will show us soon...</state>
                <state img="#-fufufu.png">I feel rather secure in my position, ~name~... but should you need any help...</state>
                <state img="#-fufufu.png">As I've said many, many times, I have no intention to throw the game... but I also don't need to gloat. &lt;i&gt;Much.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" id="4" priority="0">
                <condition status="not_lost_some" role="target" />
                <state img="#-silly.png">Well, well! I hope this is a promising start, ~name~. </state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">Ah... very well, ~name~. Let's see what you wish to wager. </state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">Though this has happened several times already... it is always exciting to see someone's first loss.</state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">Aha! Gotcha! My apologies, but I'm rather enjoying the game! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7" id="9" priority="0">
                <condition status="decent" role="target" />
                <state img="#-araara.png">Hm... while surrounding yourself with beautiful things can be enjoyable, the world exists in sound... and touch... and taste as well, neh?</state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">My oh my... ~name~? </state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">While I adore providing pampering to others, I won't reject any advances that may make such a task easier on me.</state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">I hope you won't expect me to fight you over the opportunity to enjoy you further, ~name~. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7" id="10" priority="0">
                <condition status="exposed" role="target" />
                <state img="#-silly.png">Honest interest is so important. And I can say I'm honestly interested in what you're about to take off-- and the person who's wearing it! </state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">Myo~n~! I hope you know that I'm as enthusiastic to see you undress as you are to see me, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">Personally, I'm finding it rather liberating to be undressed, isn't it, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">The body can be so wonderful. I'm quite hopeful that yours will be ready for pampering quite soon!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9" id="11" priority="0">
                <condition status="not_lost_some" role="target" />
                <state img="#-haunted.png">...I see. You... you hadn't lost anything yet. I... I suppose this could be... &lt;i&gt;eep.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-haunted.png">...Humiliation isn't the best emotion for pampering.</state>
                <state img="#-haunted.png">...You hadn't lost anything yet. Oh. Very well.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9" id="13" priority="0">
                <condition status="decent" role="target" />
                <state img="#-smug.png">Hm... I suppose I should &lt;i&gt;thank you&lt;/i&gt; for letting me use my imagination. After 800 years... one &lt;i&gt;does&lt;/i&gt; like new excitement.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Goodness, ~name~... I &lt;i&gt;could&lt;/i&gt; start pampering you &lt;i&gt;anywhere you like&lt;/i&gt;... but you have so many layers left. </state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Oh... don't you find that those clothes are so stifling, ~name~?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9" id="14" priority="0">
                <condition status="exposed" role="target" />
                <state img="#-araara.png">&lt;i&gt;Myo~n~...&lt;/i&gt; Do you wonder what &lt;i&gt;other&lt;/i&gt; sounds you may be able to make my mouth produce?</state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">Ah... isn't ~name~ a sight for sore eyes...</state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">Oh...? It's ~name~? </state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">Goodness, my oh my, ~name~... is it &lt;i&gt;me&lt;/i&gt; you're looking at? That's so flattering, I may have to honor the favor. It's the kitsune way.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2" id="18">
                <state img="#-futz.png" oneShotId="136">My goodness. Whatever you're going to take off, don't worry about it. I'll put it somewhere safe. </state>
                <state img="#-futz.png" oneShotId="137">Ah, ~name~. Don't worry about this. You'll win next time, I'm sure. </state>
                <state img="#-pampering.png" oneShotId="138">Myon~... I have a delightful idea. Once you're done with the game, why don't I cook you a home-cooked meal? You'll need it to restore your vitality. </state>
                <state img="#-pampering.png" oneShotId="139">My, oh my! ~Name~, it's time for you to show off for us and be complimented. If nobody else does, I'll make up for it with a dozen.</state>
                <state img="#-hug.png" oneShotId="140">If it helps, ~name~, perhaps you should imagine you're just making yourself easier to hug. </state>
                <state img="#-hug.png" oneShotId="141">Would a hug help?</state>
                <state img="#-futz.png" oneShotId="178">Ah... don't you worry, ~name~. I'm going to just clean my hands so I can handle your ~clothing~. I don't want it to get dirty. You deserve the best.</state>
                <state img="#-pampering.png" oneShotId="179">Oh... I'd say it's time for you to impress, but you're impressive just as you are, ~name~. </state>
                <state img="#-joy.png" oneShotId="177">Goodness, it's ~name~? Well then. You have our unconditional attention.</state>
                <state img="#-joy.png" oneShotId="176">Ah, don't worry, ~name~. It's better to embrace a growth mindset.</state>
                <state img="#-hug.png" oneShotId="175">Don't worry, ~name~. No matter how the game goes, you'll always be someone very special. To me, and to someone &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; feel makes you feel special.</state>
                <state img="#-joy.png" oneShotId="174">Just think of all the friends you're making here, ~name~. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" id="35" oneShotId="14" priority="0">
                <condition filter="magical_girl" role="target" />
                <state img="#-hug.png">Ah... ~Name~, you're quite the defender of good and righteousness. I want you to know as a spirit, I'm grateful for your work, and wish to make your life easier. Please. Let me tend to you, ~name~.  </state>
                <state img="#-hug.png">~Name~, you do so much good for the world. Can't I do something good for you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" id="36" oneShotId="15" priority="0">
                <condition filter="adventurer" role="target" />
                <state img="#-joy.png">Oh, you're  the adventuring sort aren't you, ~name~? Would you like me to do some upkeep on your equipment before you leave?</state>
                <state img="#-joy.png">Myon~! I have a great rapport with adventurers like you, ~name~. You work so hard, in so many dangerous places. Would you like me to listen to your stories?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" id="37" oneShotId="16" priority="0">
                <condition filter="celebrity" role="target" />
                <state img="#-futz.png">Goodness! Someone famous like ~name~'s decided to join us. Let me clean up a bit. You probably are used to the spotlight, but how about we just treat you like one of us?</state>
                <state img="#-futz.png">Aww, ~name~'s here! I know you're famous, but you can let down your guard. We're all here to have fun.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" id="38" oneShotId="17" priority="0">
                <condition filter="artist" role="target" />
                <state img="#-silly.png">An artist? Goodness! Would you like to share your art? Or are you looking for inspiration?</state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">I can sense the heart of an artist in you, ~name~! Would you like me to restock your supplies? I'd hate to disrupt your natural habitat. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" id="39" oneShotId="18" priority="0">
                <condition filter="criminal" role="target" />
                <state img="#-skittish.png">You're a criminal, ~name~? Do you not have enough comfort? I can help you, if you earnestly want to feel better.</state>
                <state img="#-skittish.png">Ah... a life of crime isn't very rewarding, ~name~. Won't you sit down and let us show you some care? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" id="40" oneShotId="19" priority="0">
                <condition filter="coder" role="target" />
                <state img="#-meep.png">Ah, ~name~, a life spent bent over at your desk in the dark is no good. Can I help you get a good night's rest and a comfortable chair?</state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">My oh my... You should really take a break for your eyes sake, ~name~. Do you need a good night's sleep? Or perhaps I can make you some herbal tea for energy?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" id="41" oneShotId="20" priority="0">
                <condition filter="delinquent" role="target" />
                <state img="#-hug.png">Oh, ~name~... You're only a delinquent because you need more love, right? I think you're fine and going to do great things. Come have a hug, won't you</state>
                <state img="#-hug.png">Ah... ~Name~... You know it's going to be okay, don't you? You're loved just the way you are. And I promise things can be better if we try.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" id="42" oneShotId="21" priority="0">
                <condition filter="fighter" role="target" />
                <state img="#-joy.png">You seem so very strong, ~name~. I know many warriors, but I have to say that you look quite heroic. Can you tell me of your best battles while I work some of that tension from your scars?</state>
                <state img="#-joy.png">A warrior! Well. I'll have you know I'd rather enjoy giving your sore spots a massage. You can either be quiet, or tell me about your deeds. I'm happy either way.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" id="43" oneShotId="22" priority="0">
                <condition filter="idol" role="target" />
                <state img="#-interested.png">Ah... you're an &lt;i&gt;idol&lt;/i&gt;, aren't you? I'm used to being venerated myself. But... would you perform for us, if you'd like? And after I'd be happy to help you raise &lt;i&gt;your&lt;/i&gt; spirits.</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">I'm somewhat familiar with being an idol myself, ~name~. But I imagine you'd rather approach it differently than you would. How can we adore you best?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" id="44" oneShotId="23" priority="0">
                <condition filter="medic" role="target" />
                <state img="#-hug.png">I can recognize the hands of a healer... in them you carry so much burden. But how can I ease &lt;i&gt;your&lt;/i&gt; burdens, ~name~? Would you like me to listen to your day? Or rub your neck?</state>
                <state img="#-hug.png">You're a healer, aren't you? Goodness, ~name~. You do so much for others. Can I help you? I want you to ease your worries in my arms.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" id="45" oneShotId="24" priority="0">
                <condition filter="ninja" role="target" />
                <state img="#-skittish.png">Ah... a ~target.ifMale(shinobi|kunoichi)~. Your arts are quite different from mine, but surely within that discipline there's room to be pampered?</state>
                <state img="#-skittish.png">I don't envy the ninja way. So much discipline. So much death. But perhaps there's still room for lightness? Please. Let me tend to you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" id="46" oneShotId="25" priority="0">
                <condition filter="pirate" role="target" />
                <state img="#-silly.png">Yar har! Goodness. I've only been on a ship a few times. But I can imagine the sense of freedom is quite good! But, let me make sure you enjoy your time on land, neh?</state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">My, all that salt water from being a pirate, and I'm sure you could use a nice clean bath and some good red meat, couldn't you, ~name~?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" id="48" oneShotId="27" priority="0">
                <condition filter="royalty" role="target" />
                <state img="#-joy.png">~target.ifMale(My lord|My lady)~, while my pampering is humble, know that I always endeavor to do my best, regardless of if my aid is rendered to a peasant or a prince.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" id="50" oneShotId="29" priority="0">
                <condition filter="musician" role="target" />
                <state img="#-joy.png">~Name~? Do you need some warm milk for your throat? Or perhaps you'd prefer I tune your instrument? Either way, it would be lovely for you to perform for us!</state>
                <state img="#-joy.png">Ah... ~Name~, you'll play us a song, won't you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" id="51" oneShotId="30" priority="0">
                <condition filter="scientist" role="target" />
                <state img="#-hug.png">~Name~, you can't stay in your lab all day, you know. Don't work so hard. Let me rub your back and treat you to a nice, full meal so you can return to work refreshed.</state>
                <state img="#-hug.png">The search of knowledge can't come at the expense of your self. Take a break from your beakers, and let me take care of &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt;, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" id="52" oneShotId="31" priority="0">
                <condition filter="student" role="target" />
                <state img="#-futz.png">~Name~, it's healthy that you're taking a break from your studies. Life is something you experience, but take your education seriously. To do that, you need a comfy bed for good sleep, and healthful meals. Let me help you tonight. </state>
                <state img="#-futz.png">A student like you ought to make sure to take time to relax. You're only young once, so enjoy it, but don't lose sight of your goals. Let me help you feel better by making you a nice cup of vitalizing tea, neh?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" id="53" oneShotId="32" priority="0">
                <condition filter="parent" role="target" />
                <state img="#-hug.png">Ah, I recognize the worn expression of ~target.ifMale(paternal|maternal)~ duty. Well, no matter what path your children take, they'll always carry your love with them. I know mine do.</state>
                <state img="#-hug.png">Parenthood is so hard, isn't it, ~name~ ? I've raised a few of my own... but from ~target.ifMale(one parent|one mother)~ to another, know that they'll love and appreciate what you did.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" id="54" oneShotId="33" priority="0">
                <condition filter="villain" role="target" />
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">You might be a villain, ~name~... but perhaps you might reconsider that with proper care and love. What are you missing? How can I help you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="63" priority="0">
                <condition status="decent" role="target" />
                <state img="#-smug.png">My... perhaps if you undress before I finish, there could be a &lt;i&gt;very special and intimate&lt;/i&gt; form of pampering I could provide for you, ~name~...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_stripping">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="amy_rose" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-meep.png">Oh my... that's quite the &lt;i&gt;tale&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">Oh, I meant &lt;i&gt;tail,&lt;/i&gt; but most people in my world with ears are some manner of animal spirit. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="aoba" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-nani.png">...And an artist's bleak woes. </state>
                <state img="#-nani.png">...And the oppressive darkness of an overworked Japanese citizen. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="aoba" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">With your bust size, I imagine your neck or hands would be a better use than your lower back... </state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">I do imagine that with your posture and bust, neck or hands would be the best place to relieve tension.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="aoba" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-skittish.png">In truth, people often confuse me for someone far younger than I am... I can respect why such a thing would be a concern and frustration. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <condition status="exposed" role="target" />
                <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="extra" />
                <state img="#-meep.png" oneShotId="1">What an.. interesting decision. Did you hold your ~clothing~ for last for a reason...? </state>
                <state img="#-meep.png" oneShotId="2">My oh my...! You kept your ~clothing~ on, even though we can see you naked...? </state>
                <state img="#-meep.png" oneShotId="3">Curious! I wouldn't have thought to do that... but I suppose it &lt;i&gt;is&lt;/i&gt; stimulating!</state>
                <state img="#-meep.png" oneShotId="4">Goodness! You're just now getting to your ~clothing~? But you already removed your...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <condition status="exposed" role="target" />
                <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="extra" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="5">Well, my oh my... imitation is quite the form of flattery!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="6">I see I've inspired something in you, ~name~. </state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="8">I see... copying me? Well... I can see you rather enjoyed what I was doing, ~name~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <condition status="exposed" role="target" />
                <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="extra" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="13">I'm flattered you'd think to copy me, ~name~, taking off your ~clothing~ after the important findings... </state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="14">Heh... well, looks like you've seen a thing or two from me, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" id="34">
                <test expr="~clothing~" value="yo-yo" />
                <state img="#-interested.png">Goodness, a yo-yo? While that's a toy, I'm sure it's very powerful in your hands. I'll make sure to keep it safe.</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">I can imagine you doing far more than simple tricks with your yo-yo. I'll make sure to wind it up gently and keep it safe. Perhaps wax the string and polish the heart?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_stripped">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="aoba" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-pampering.png">Ah! You're a mangaka? I'll have you know I've become very skilled at pampering both mangaka and salaryman alike! Doubtless this means you'd be doubly easy to pamper! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="aoba" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-meep.png">Oh! I did not mean to be dismissive! Simply to tend to you in the way you would benefit most! My sincerest of apologies! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="aoba" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">...And of course I wouldn't dare look up your skirt. Certainly not to gauge any... frustration of a certain other variety... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <condition status="not_exposed" role="target" />
                <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="extra" />
                <state img="#-fibbing.png" oneShotId="24">Ah-hah! Perhaps there &lt;i&gt;is&lt;/i&gt; a way to pamper you that I hadn't thought of. </state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png" oneShotId="25">Hm... well... perhaps there &lt;i&gt;is&lt;/i&gt; some way to draw the game out. </state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png" oneShotId="26">Hm... perhaps if I saved my socks for last...</state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png" oneShotId="27">Goodness.... saving my socks for last is certainly not the &lt;i&gt;worst&lt;/i&gt; of ideas...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <condition status="not_exposed" role="target" />
                <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="extra" />
                <state img="#-araara.png" oneShotId="40">See what you like, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-araara.png" oneShotId="41">Hm... well. I certainly don't mind if you pick up from an old lady like me!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <condition status="not_exposed" role="target" />
                <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="extra" />
                <state img="#-silly.png" oneShotId="51">It helps to get to see what we came to see earlier, too. </state>
                <state img="#-silly.png" oneShotId="52">I don't mind... but I do find it a bit silly that you undressed in such a strange order, ~name~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition status="not_exposed" role="target" />
                <test expr="~clothing~" value="~glasses~" />
                <state img="#-skittish.png" oneShotId="66">O-oh! Saving your glasses for last? Make certain your vision is still good!</state>
                <state img="#-skittish.png" oneShotId="67">O-oh! Do you need any help seeing your cards, ~name~? I understand why you saved them for last.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <condition role="self" notSaidMarker="first_forfeit" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="first_forfeit=~name~">Would a bit of dirty talk perhaps entice you into letting me &lt;i&gt;pamper&lt;/i&gt; you, ~name~? Hm?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="first_forfeit=~name~">It would be a shame if you were to simply sit there, ~name~. Perhaps... I could offer you a bit of dirty talk? </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0-2" priority="5">
                <state img="#-meep.png">Oh! I know I can't exactly provide much visual excitement for you, ~name~, and I can't offer you my tail, but would you like me to watch, or ignore you?</state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">Would you prefer that I engage with you, or give you your privacy? Perhaps you want to simple exercise some voyeurism as the rest of us play...?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4" priority="5">
                <state img="#-interested.png">While it's not the view you want... perhaps I can compensate with some naughty talk?</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">Would you prefer that I try to dirty talk to you, ~name~? Or let you fantasize?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7" priority="5">
                <state img="#-interested.png">Ah, I'm not too many hands from joining you. Would you like me to help you with a fantasy? </state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">Oh... ~name~... this always proves exciting. Perhaps exciting enough to encourage me to join you...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9" priority="5">
                <state img="#-interested.png">Ah... something for me to enjoy?</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">How good of you to try and pamper &lt;i&gt;me&lt;/i&gt;, ~name~...</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">Ah... finally. Won't you let me help you, ~name~? </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-silly.png">Well, ~name~, I will certainly treasure this experience.</state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">Normally, I prefer clean things... but just ask if you'd like me to get dirty.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-araara.png">You get started, ~name~. I'll give you &lt;i&gt;plenty&lt;/i&gt; to consider. </state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">Myon~... let's see how you like it, and I may take care of it for you later... hm?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-araara.png">Feel free to enjoy my company, ~name~... I'll be enjoying yours. </state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">Oh my... please. Indulge yourself however you want.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-araara.png">I think it's no secret that we're both enjoying this, neh?</state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">There you go, ~name~... take your time. Enjoy it. </state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">Myon~! So lewd, but so &lt;i&gt;perfect&lt;/i&gt;, right? Really indulge yourself, ~name~!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">Despite my appearance, I &lt;i&gt;am&lt;/i&gt; rather experienced... you may wish to imagine my tiny frame bouncing up and down on that.</state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png" oneShotId="68">One of the few experiences that has eluded me is granting a man consecutive orgasms. I imagine I'd need to be rather proactive in stimulating him to get &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; prize.</state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">If you wish to know, I &lt;i&gt;do&lt;/i&gt; really enjoy watching. It is one of my... I suppose you'd say indulgences. </state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">Oh! Are you getting close? </state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">Goodness... such vigor.</state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">&lt;i&gt;Myon~?!&lt;/i&gt; Do I make noises like that when I'm in the mood?</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">Mmhmm! Keep going, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">Oh... just like that, ~name~... stroke it... ah... yes.</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">Hm-hmm! You look &lt;i&gt;very&lt;/i&gt; appealing. I'll have you in my thoughts if I'm defeated, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">You're badly in need of release, aren't you?</state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">Oh... please keep going! It's no good if you don't get to finish, neh?</state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">Don't be embarrassed... please share your fantasies. It just makes what comes next so much easier~!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I've seen many, many people &lt;i&gt;take care&lt;/i&gt; of themselves. But very few have had the opportunity to know I was watching~</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">So naughty... but for tonight, spray your seed wherever you'd like, ~name~. I can always clean it up. </state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Are you being a good boy? Do you need Senko to rub behind your ears? Or would you prefer my hands &lt;i&gt;elsewhere&lt;/i&gt;?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">Stroking my tail requires a gentler touch than &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; do, ~name~... but it &lt;i&gt;would&lt;/i&gt; give me an opportunity to go all out.</state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">A-ah... I'm such a naughty old vixen, masturbating alongside such a young, &lt;i&gt;virile&lt;/i&gt; man like you...</state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">For many years, it was expected that a lady would swallow when a man completed in her mouth... but I understand that some prefer to watch it dribble down her chin... while I do not understand, I do wish to indulge properly. </state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">O-oh... ~name~... I'm thinking of how you'd feel in my hands... or between my breasts... in my mouth... </state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">P-Please, when you're close, warn me...? It's rather hard to clean spunk out of my tail. Anywhere &lt;i&gt;else&lt;/i&gt; below the neck would be rather flattering.</state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">Oh... do you imagine teasing me under a kotatsu? Helpless save for my whimpers, as I try desperately to conceal my climax...?</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">&lt;i&gt;Good boy. Cum for Senko.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">Ah... you have a practiced technique. But I can still teach you a few things, ~name~. </state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">Oh... how your hands would feel on me...</state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">~Name~...! Myo~n~n~n~...!</state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">...Gently, gently... don't hurt your glorious spear now...</state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">&lt;i&gt;Ara ara...&lt;/i&gt; </state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">&lt;i&gt;Imagining how good I'd feel, light as a feather on top of you, making the cutest, lewdest version of my squeaks?&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Oh... the things I could teach you, young man. </state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Oh... if you took me home, you could have me &lt;i&gt;anywhere&lt;/i&gt;. On your tables... your counters... your tub... your bed... in the morning, the evening... or even midday, should your needs arise...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7 9">
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">...I would rather appreciate it if you &lt;i&gt;did&lt;/i&gt; incorporate me into your fantasies. </state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">Ah... ~name~... I'm excited thinking about how you must taste.</state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">Please relax, ~name~! I want you to fully enjoy this moment. </state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">Oh! Was that a name? Who's name was it, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png" oneShotId="76">Why, yes... my tail &lt;i&gt;is&lt;/i&gt; terribly sensitive... but it alone can't make me climax...</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">M&lt;i&gt;yon~&lt;/i&gt;...</state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">To be young again... your intensity is rather inspiring. </state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">You present a very compelling performance, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Mmm! I see you appreciating me. That's well and good, because I wish I could just walk right over there and take &lt;i&gt;all your worries&lt;/i&gt; away.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Hm... keep &lt;i&gt;this&lt;/i&gt; up, and I may need to follow you home. Doubtless you need a good, deep cleaning, just like &lt;i&gt;I&lt;/i&gt; need something good and deep, neh?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Oh...! You really needed that, didn't you, ~name~? </state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">It's fortunate that I'll be disrobing soon... I'd rather enjoy giving you a through cleaning of my own, though. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-smug.png">My, oh my... how much of that was thanks to me, I wonder?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Oh... poor man. Whatever will we do to keep pampering you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-araara.png">Ah... another satisfactory pampering. Now... my turn.</state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">You clearly needed that release... shall we give you another?</state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">While your mind is clear... consider what you'd wish for after this. Food? A warm presence helping you off to sleep? A hot bath?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-araara.png">Naughty boy... I was so close, too. Perhaps since I've failed to pamper you, I ought to give you some &lt;i&gt;extra&lt;/i&gt; attention.</state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">Ah... ~name~... are you so desperate for touch that you'd waste your seed like that? I'm really going to have to give you more love and care.</state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">Ah... I bet your head feels so clear? While mine is so heated. </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="penny_polendina" />
                <state img="#-skittish.png">Polly, have you ever masturbated before? Do you need any help...? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2" priority="5">
                <state img="#-okay....png">Ah... I'm sorry, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-okay....png">Oh... And the very I least I could've done was undress with you.</state>
                <state img="#-okay....png">While I don't tend to find other women as attractive as men, I wish I could've been more immersed in the moment with you, ~name~...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4" priority="5">
                <state img="#-meep.png">Oh...! Well, I &lt;i&gt;do&lt;/i&gt; try to keep an open mind to what the young folks go for.</state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">Ah...! Hopefully I'll be a helpful companion in this, if not necessarily a subject of your attentions, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">Goodness, I was so distracted by how you looked naked, my mind almost forgot the next, yet more lewd step!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7" priority="5">
                <state img="#-silly.png">Everyone does it, ~name~. Even an old fox like myself. Just have fun. </state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">Let me know how I can help, ~name~. I'm not above a little play here and there. </state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">Oh my...! Well, give me an exciting example to follow, and I'm sure we'll create quite the memory, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9" priority="5">
                <state img="#-meep.png">Not to make it sound as though you're not a prize unto yourself, ~name~...</state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">Ah, ~name~! I was wondering when you'd join. </state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">I'll admit more than a small amount of curiosity for when you'd be joining me, ~name~...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-skittish.png">Please show off a bit. Building confidence is quite a task full of merit. </state>
                <state img="#-skittish.png">~Name~... please know I can fully make this up to you later, and intend to. </state>
                <state img="#-skittish.png">On my tail, I swear I'll give you a pampering you'll never forget, ~name~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-interested.png">Oh...! Well, I &lt;i&gt;do&lt;/i&gt; try to keep an open mind to what the young folks go for.</state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png" oneShotId="78">This reminds me a bit of that time Shiro and I... ah... that's a story for another time. Suffice to say, you can become very close with people, very quickly, in certain circumstances.</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">Well... I certainly can appreciate any attention you spare my way.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-araara.png">Myou~... Surprise me, ~name~, and maybe we can surprise you back. </state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">My oh my... I like your spirit. </state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">Ah... cleanse that spirit, as they say. But... let me know if you need more hands-on help after the game.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-araara.png">...I certainly can find some value in other feminine company, at least on occasion. Please let me indulge you a bit...</state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">Well, let's see how you relax when you &lt;i&gt;don't&lt;/i&gt; have a helpful fox, and let's see if we can't do better.</state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">Don't think I'll leave you out to dry. Not when we all want you wet!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-7" id="67">
                <condition role="target" character="lux" sayingMarker="lux_senko_luxmast_pampering" />
                <condition role="self" notSaidMarker="senko_lux_forfeit" />
                <state img="#-araara.png" marker="senko_lux_forfeit">Goodness... you didn't strike me as the type. I can give you all the love and gentleness you ask for, Lux. </state>
                <state img="#-araara.png" marker="senko_lux_forfeit">Well... I can't touch you, but maybe you'd like to lean on my years of experience?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9" id="76" priority="302">
                <condition role="target" character="hilda" saidMarker="SenkoMast" sayingMarker="SenkoMastFin" />
                <state img="#-interested.png" marker="hilda_finished">&lt;i&gt;Yes... Hilda... yes!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9" id="68" oneShotId="38" priority="301">
                <condition role="target" character="hilda" saidMarker="SenkoMast" saying="at my mercy" />
                <state img="#-meep.png" marker="hilda_myon">Myon~... A-ah... &lt;i&gt;H-Hilda&lt;/i&gt;--! So... impetuous... w-what kind of sounds do you wish I'd make?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9" id="69" oneShotId="39" priority="301">
                <condition role="target" character="hilda" saidMarker="SenkoMast" saying="extra-sensitive" />
                <state img="#-araara.png" marker="hilda_tail">Oh... it is &lt;i&gt;so&lt;/i&gt; very sensitive... you make make me climax by j-just... a-ah... Hilda...!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9" id="70" oneShotId="37" priority="301">
                <condition role="target" character="hilda" saidMarker="SenkoMast" saying="pet fox" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="hilda_pet">Oh... what else would I use these ears for than to sense for your aching need to tend to my libido, Hilda?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9" id="71" oneShotId="36" priority="301">
                <condition role="target" character="hilda" saidMarker="SenkoMast" saying="adorable" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="hilda_adorable">Oh... what else would I use these ears for than to sense for your aching need to tend to my libido, Hilda?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9" id="72" oneShotId="40" priority="301">
                <condition role="target" character="hilda" saidMarker="SenkoMast" saying="adorable" />
                <state img="#-araara.png" marker="hilda_obedient">Good and obedient...? Why... of course. Would you like a massage, followed by a &lt;i&gt;most thorough&lt;/i&gt; cleaning with my tongue, miss...?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9" id="73" oneShotId="41" priority="301">
                <condition role="target" character="hilda" saidMarker="SenkoMast" saying="collar" />
                <state img="#-fibbing.png" marker="hilda_collar">P-perhaps I'm a naughty fox. You may need to collar me after quite a bit of struggle to subdue me...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9" id="74" oneShotId="42" priority="301">
                <condition role="target" character="hilda" saidMarker="SenkoMast" saying="giving control" />
                <state img="#-araara.png" marker="hilda_control">I &lt;i&gt;would&lt;/i&gt; rather appreciate your youthful enthusiasm... applied to my chest... my... &lt;i&gt;dripping, hot, tight&lt;/i&gt; sex....</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9" id="75" oneShotId="43" priority="301">
                <condition role="target" character="hilda" saidMarker="SenkoMast" saying="relaxation" />
                <state img="#-interested.png" marker="hilda_relax">Oh...? Well... what would you like me to do? And &lt;i&gt;where&lt;/i&gt; would you like me to do it, Hilda?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="senko_lux_forfeit" />
                <condition role="other" character="lux" stage="8" />
                <state img="#-araara.png" oneShotId="238" marker="lux_oral">Ah... Lux, my girl, if it helps, imagine someone lavishing you with their tongue. Right &lt;i&gt;there&lt;/i&gt;. So softly and flexibly...</state>
                <state img="#-araara.png" oneShotId="227" marker="lux_fingering">Ah... think of me, or someone kissing your neck, gentle fingers entering you, stroking slowly and teasingly back and forth inside of you.</state>
                <state img="#-araara.png" oneShotId="228" marker="lux_fantasy">Lux... what &lt;i&gt;have&lt;/i&gt; you fantasized about? A kindly gentleman, finding you in your boudoir? Or a lady friend you can learn and grow from?</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png" oneShotId="229" marker="lux_kiss">Lux... do you like the idea of being kissed? Of someone telling you how loved, and beautiful, and talented you are, as someone plants their lips against yours?</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png" oneShotId="230" marker="lux_partner">Lux... what would you like a partner to tell you? That you're loved? That your light magic is inspiring? That your willpower and kindness are going to make everything better? Because they will! </state>
                <state img="#-joy.png" oneShotId="232" marker="lux_senko">Lux, would you like to take me to bed after this? While I lack the instrument you're imagining, I'd still adore you and tend to any and all of your needs...</state>
                <state img="#-joy.png" oneShotId="233" marker="lux_mofu">If you want, Lux, you can touch yourself while you stroke my tail... I've heard it's rather soothing.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="235" marker="lux_vibrator">My lady, we should get you an implement... they're quite a bit more satisfying than a finger... the modern ones vibrate! </state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png" oneShotId="236" marker="lux_anal">My lady... have you ever... I hear some women become quite stimulated when &lt;i&gt;each&lt;/i&gt; of her lower... entrances are tittillated. </state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="237" marker="lux_erotica">Lux... do you have any... literature you enjoy reading before you attend to yourself in such a way? I'd be happy to enact any such scene... within my capabilities, of course. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">Ah, ~name~... </state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">If there's any way I can improve your experience, please let me know!</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">Oh my...! ~Name~, c-could you show me that again?</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">I have to try that myself... it's subtle, but different!</state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">These noises are nothing new to me, but... so exciting!</state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">Ah... to be that young and carefree, again. </state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">It seems we're learning about you even as you're learning about yourself, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">Even if it's something private, what shame is there in indulgence, neh?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Goodness, ~name~, save some for the rest of us. </state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I'd say ask nicely and we'd help, but you've got a good handle on yourself, hm?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-araara.png">I want to know if it's possible to know someone better than they know themselves. Certainly worth the effort, neh?</state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">Oh... can't you come help me fluff my tail up? Or... stroke me elsewhere?</state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">Oh, ~name~, I just want to hold you in my arms... and massage each and every aspect of your being. </state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">I'm quite in the moment. If you suggested we break the rules, perhaps my tongue might find itself between your legs.</state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">Even with limited experience, I may have more experience with women than you have with yourself, ~name~. Please keep this in mind.</state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">While my ability to cook is quite good, I've heard the most delectable experience I can provide is entirely an intimate one...</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">Myon~... is probably my favorite noise to make, but saying: ~Name~! ~Name~! My oh my, ~name~! Could be a new favorite...</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">Ah... please continue, ~name~. The moment of release is wonderful, but enjoy the effort. </state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">While my hands are small, they &lt;i&gt;are&lt;/i&gt; quite deft. And having more pleasure is never a bad thing, neh?</state>
                <state img="#-fufufu.png" oneShotId="84">"My, Senko, you're so proficient, could you teach me your ways?"&lt;br&gt;Of course, darling. I'm not a mindreader, I'm not Shiro, after all... but hundreds of years of practice makes this experience rather sublime~</state>
                <state img="#-fufufu.png">My, oh my... have &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; ever gotten a true &lt;i&gt;full body&lt;/i&gt; massage? Who doesn't like to relax and feel loved?</state>
                <state img="#-fufufu.png">Your earnestness is quite beautiful in and of itself~</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Would you like me to show you how it's done, ~name~? I'd love to pamper you.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">While a gentle fluffing of my tail or a scratch behind the ears does me good... I think it could do &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; good as well.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Do you have any particularly sensitive places...? I'll give you a hint that one of mine is my tail~</state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">O-oh! That looked good, whatever it was?</state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">I was so distracted, I almost stopped touching myself...!</state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">Goodness, ~name~. I suppose vigor beats experience on occasion, neh?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7 9">
                <state img="#-araara.png">Ah... you aren't making it easy for me not to come right over there and help you, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">My, oh my... I want to see how you do this on some nice, clean sheets. </state>
                <state img="#-fufufu.png">Such practiced technique, ~name~. I have no doubts you could teach &lt;i&gt;me&lt;/i&gt; a thing or two. Perhaps hands-on?</state>
                <state img="#-fufufu.png">Enjoy yourself, ~name~! Indulge in the attention and physicality!</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">Myon~! You're having a great time, hm, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">Myon~! Take your time and enjoy yourself. I know we are, ~name~. </state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">Ah-- lovely. </state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">You're making me sad that you're going to climax... you're awfully fascinating to watch masturbate!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">You &lt;i&gt;like&lt;/i&gt; the attention, don't you, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Goodness... If I didn't know any better, I'd think you'd do this all the time, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">Ah... to be young and showing off your talents again. </state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">I've learned a few things over my long life... but some of the most basic never get old.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="35">
                <condition role="target" character="lux" />
                <state img="#-joy.png">I'm hopeful to have been of service, my lady. </state>
                <state img="#-joy.png">Would you like to re-enact any of those ideas, my lady?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-silly.png">Ah, an impressive finish! But we can always help you relax further, neh?</state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">I've had those days, too, ~name~. Good for you!</state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">To let it all loose like that... ah... how lovely. I'm simply awaiting my turn.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-interested.png">Well, ~name~... certainly inspiring. </state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">I hope you don't think you're done being pampered &lt;i&gt;just&lt;/i&gt; yet, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">I'm certain finishes like that are what most people are here to see. Well done. You deserve quite a bit of praise and care, ~name~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-araara.png">A-ah... you're making it very hard to stay in the game...</state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">W-well... I'm certainly feeling... a certain tension I know &lt;i&gt;exactly&lt;/i&gt; how to relieve. </state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">My... how did you do that thing? Not the climax, the... oh, when I try it, I'll let you know!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-araara.png">Mmmhm...! As I said, this is a competition... and providing both stimulation and relaxation is my goal. It looks like you did both!</state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">I'm not so easily outdone, ~name~, but that was incredibly successful!</state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">I may need to teach you a thing or two later... but I'm learning more than my fair share about care from you, ~name~!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate_first">
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-stahp.png" marker="lost_first">Aw... darn it. I lost first? </state>
                <state img="#-stahp.png" marker="lost_first">Oh... well, I guess I should set the stage. </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate">
            <case stage="7" priority="142">
                <condition role="other" character="hilda" stage="9" saidMarker="SenkoMast&gt;0" sayingMarker="SenkoMast" />
                <state img="#-silly.png">Well, Miss Hilda... were this any other game, I'd rather enjoy you being rather less talkative and rather quite as useful with your tongue!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <condition count="2-" filter="dominant" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="dom_ff">Ara ara... why don't I show you how to properly please a kitsune, little ~player~. </state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="dom_ff">Hundreds of years of experience means I know how to make you climax harder than you likely can imagine. Please. Present yourself with joy, for Senko to care for you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <condition count="2-" filter="submissive" />
                <state img="#-skittish.png" marker="sub_ff">G-goodness... all of us are &lt;i&gt;so&lt;/i&gt; responsive. Won't &lt;i&gt;someone&lt;/i&gt; tell us what to do to adequately provide a pleasing experience?</state>
                <state img="#-skittish.png" marker="sub_ff">My, oh my... submission is so clearly part of a compelling experience. At this stage, I would adore nothing less than someone to take me and use me as they wished. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <condition count="3-" filter="cheerful" />
                <state img="#-silly.png" marker="hap_ff">It's hard to feel sad when you're on the verge of a climax. Perhaps this explains the clear auras here. </state>
                <state img="#-silly.png" marker="hap_ff">So few darkened auras here, already. Why, I see some of us are probably quite skilled at &lt;i&gt;this&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <condition count="3-" filter="short" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="sm_ff">So many of us are so petite... my, oh my... think of what you could do with us. We can be so easily maneuvered, and perhaps, after this game...</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="sm_ff">Ah... size just gives us something to prove, isn't that so? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <condition count="3-" filter="school_uniform" />
                <state img="#-fufufu.png" marker="uni_ff">Young adults need not worry about taking care of themselves. But, if you wish to learn from a woman with hundreds of years of experience, look no further. </state>
                <state img="#-fufufu.png" marker="uni_ff">The hunger for intimate self-knowledge grows with age. But, consider learning at the tail of a master of all things care-related. Including the mastery of masturbation.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-araara.png">With such compelling examples, I hope you don't mind if I give my own spin on self care, do you? </state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">Ah... finally. A moment to pamper myself and indulge the rest of you to the utmost. I live for this type of moment, if not the specifics.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="start_masturbating">
            <case stage="7">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="lost_first" />
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">Ah... well, then. Time to fluff myself. </state>
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">At the very least, I hope you enjoy this as much as I'm about to. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">I hope you don't mind indulging me for a moment. I can become rather vocal during an intimate act. While you can't touch me, perhaps I should at least be transparent about what's on my mind? </state>
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">Masturbation often entails silence, this is more of a shared intimate experience. I beg &lt;i&gt;your&lt;/i&gt; indulgence as I may become rather... loud.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="masturbating">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-araara.png">Ah... it has been &lt;i&gt;far&lt;/i&gt; too long since I've been taken to bed...</state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">You'd be welcome to massage my ears while my face was between your legs, you know.</state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">Be gentle with my tail... it can be &lt;i&gt;very&lt;/i&gt; sensitive.</state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">I prefer to be intimate before a bath. Though during, or after, can also be fully enjoyable experiences. </state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">I've always found it to be rather appealing to go without underwear. The breeze is lovely, and it lets you send a clear message. </state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">On rare instances, I &lt;i&gt;have&lt;/i&gt; become rather insatiable. Perhaps those stories of humans being drained dry take on a different meaning to you, now, hm?</state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">A-ah... please... please... take me. </state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">Where do you want to touch me? My mouth? My breasts? My ears? My tail? My seat? My legs? Or &lt;i&gt;right here&lt;/i&gt;?</state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">Almost a millenium of experience... means there's &lt;i&gt;very&lt;/i&gt; little left that surprises me... but it makes each and every experience all that more special. </state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">&lt;i&gt;Myon~n~n~...!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">Ah... I'm used to cleaning up messes rather than making them... but I'm so wet...</state>
                <state img="#-silly.png" oneShotId="90">Perhaps given a bit more time, I might tell you about some of my more... sensual experiences. </state>
                <state img="#-okay....png">Ah... were that it were &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; touching me instead...</state>
                <state img="#-okay....png">So many attractive people in need of pampering... and so many unfortunate rules...</state>
                <state img="#-skittish.png" oneShotId="87">A-ah... you aren't finding me too forward, are you? Is that out of fashion these days?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="91">While gestures of housekeeping and love are my preferred ones... I am a woman with needs, desires, and wants. And what I want, need, and desire is to be, as you say in this age, &lt;i&gt;fucked silly.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I may be cute, but I'm also rather fierce, neh?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Oh... I can be subtle. I can be tasteful. I can also, on occasion, leave you with a memory you'll never forget and a night you struggle to recall. </state>
                <state img="#-stahp.png" oneShotId="88">W-what was that you said? You want to do &lt;i&gt;what&lt;/i&gt; with my &lt;i&gt;where&lt;/i&gt;? </state>
                <state img="#-stahp.png" oneShotId="89">&lt;i&gt;Eep--&lt;/i&gt; S-so sensitive today...!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" priority="0">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="sm_ff" />
                <condition count="3-" filter="short" />
                <state img="#-interested.png">I may be small framed... but I have a rather large appetite... </state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">I wonder if I'm too small to handle you... we really should determine if that's the case. </state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I can snuggle in next to you &lt;i&gt;just about anywhere&lt;/i&gt;. I could sit in your lap and grind against you, and all you'd feel is my want.</state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">A-ah... you could pick me up, and throw me around on the bed to show me exactly how you want to take me...</state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">Even with my tail... don't you think it'd be &lt;i&gt;so&lt;/i&gt; easy to take my tiny frame and press me up against a wall? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" priority="0">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="dom_ff" />
                <condition count="2-" filter="dominant" />
                <state img="#-smug.png">On your knees, ~player.ifMale(boy|girl)~. I didn't give you permission to look. </state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Do you need a spanking? You look like you deserve to be disciplined before you're pampered. </state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Oh... naughty, naughty ~player.ifMale(boy|girl)~. Do I need to spank your thighs nice and red so you learn not to touch yourself? </state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I'll have you clean up my mess with my tongue, you naughty, naughty ~player.ifMale(boy|girl)~.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">You may fluff it. Once.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" priority="0">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="sub_ff" />
                <condition count="2-" filter="submissive" />
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">Oh~ ~Player~... why... however can I do that? Won't you show me &lt;i&gt;just the way&lt;/i&gt; you like it?</state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">My oh my... how lewd. You want to do &lt;i&gt;what&lt;/i&gt; to my body? A-ah... just be gentle~</state>
                <state img="#-stahp.png" oneShotId="85">Y-you want me to masturbate in front of all these people? G-goodness... I suppose I can be a good fox demigod and do as you ask...! &lt;i&gt;Myon~&lt;/i&gt;!</state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">H-how rude! ...But yes, I can be your little whore tonight. I'd appreciate the chance to do so, ~player.ifMale(Sir|Ma'am)~.</state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">Anywhere you want me... however you want me... no matter when you want me...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" priority="0">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="hap_ff" />
                <condition count="3-" filter="cheerful" />
                <state img="#-silly.png">Ah... yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, a thousand times, yes, just to feel loved in your arms...!</state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">An enthusiastic "yes" with each thrust... an affirming "that feels so good" with every caress and lick...</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">Oh... how good you must feel when you tend to me... </state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">I like to smile when something makes me feel good. I think expressions of discomfort have no room in the bedroom...</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Happiness comes from contentment... but it's quite easy to be cheerful when a helpful kitsune has relieved you of all worries, tension, and pent up sexual frustration, neh?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" priority="0">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="uni_ff" />
                <condition count="3-" filter="school_uniform" />
                <state img="#-araara.png">I'm not &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; your teacher... but you &lt;i&gt;could&lt;/i&gt; certainly meet me after class... or I could bring snacks to your club... and take care of you &lt;i&gt;after&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">Ah... are you perhaps interested in an older woman teaching you sensuality, ~name~? I can teach you all &lt;i&gt;sorts&lt;/i&gt; of ways to do things &lt;i&gt;properly&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">My oh my... so naughty at your age... think of how naughty you'll be after years of practice?</state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">Ara ara... so inexperienced. Let me show you how to take care of yourself properly. You take your hand, and stroke like &lt;i&gt;this&lt;/i&gt;... and cup like &lt;i&gt;so&lt;/i&gt;...</state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">&lt;i&gt;Watch closely, darlings...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="heavy_masturbating">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">...In a singular encounter, you may release yourself anywhere on or inside of me, provided you do not get it on my tail. </state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png" oneShotId="104">The base of my tail is my most sensitive place... the strongest orgasm I've ever had was when that, my chest, and both of my... unlike a human woman, I have many, many more avenues to achieve climax... something to consider. </state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">&lt;i&gt;Myon~~&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">H-having a tail and ears means... more places to shake when I--I--</state>
                <state img="#-meep.png" oneShotId="105">A-ah... once, with my companion Shiro, we found ourselves in a rather difficult predicament. Let's simply say that we were both significantly paler following the abundance of service we provided those men...</state>
                <state img="#-meep.png" oneShotId="106">I-I must confess-- I have found quite the appeal in making guests question my relationship with my host-- it makes me excited to make them wonder whether my host considers me a concubine, a wife, a mistress, a mother, or even... a-ah--!</state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">While I'm far more durable than you'd expect... I do most enjoy gentle lovemaking, full of sweet nothings. </state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">Ah... please... just like that...</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I don't wish to misrepresent myself as some wanton harlot... it's more that with a particular person, I can fully indulge their wants...</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I find it rather hard to clean when someone is making a mess of my &lt;i&gt;little fox&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">&lt;i&gt;Pamper me--&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">Please--! Yes--! </state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">Fluff me-- fluff it &lt;i&gt;so well--&lt;/i&gt;!</state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">Please... anywhere you like... just...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finishing_masturbating">
            <case stage="8">
                <condition count="4" filter="non-human" />
                <state img="#-finishing.png">A-ah... &lt;i&gt;y-yiff--~&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-finishing.png">Yes, yes... fluff my tail, play with me, pamper me... oh... pamper me all over--</state>
                <state img="#-finishing.png">&lt;i&gt;Myo~n~n~n~n~n~!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-finishing.png">Ah--</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-araara.png">&lt;i&gt;Myon~&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">Just what I needed.</state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">Ah~ What a perfect pampering~</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="after_masturbating">
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-araara.png">What a pleaure that was. But we don't have to stop there, do we?</state>
                <state img="#-araara.png">I hope that performance was satisfactory! Please, let me know what you liked.</state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">Normally I'd draw a bath now. </state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png" oneShotId="115">Hm... I know I'd rather someone use their tongue on me, but is there not some sort of fetish regarding eating sashimi from a woman's body...?</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">Ah! Even in defeat, the post-climax clarity is sublime. And the rest of the game is easy to enjoy.</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">While I &lt;i&gt;am&lt;/i&gt; a bit too tired to repeat now that I've finished, perhaps we may try again later?</state>
                <state img="#-nani.png">...Now I'm hungry. Unreleated to the game.</state>
                <state img="#-nani.png">...I did fold my clothes and put them away, didn't I? I at least want to walk out dressed!</state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">Oh my...! The game continues! </state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">Oh! Goodness. We've still more to see!</state>
                <state img="#-skittish.png">...This &lt;i&gt;was&lt;/i&gt; the type of experience you all wanted, wasn't it?</state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">This was quite fun. I would most appreciate a chance to repeat the experience!</state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">Ah... well, defeat is hard to feel too badly about if the price is an orgasm.</state>
                <state img="#-stahp.png" oneShotId="110">...Did I leave the oven on? Oh no! </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_victory">
            <case stage="0-1">
                <state img="#-stahp.png">I enjoyed watching, but I really expected to get more hands-on... at least with myself!</state>
                <state img="#-stahp.png">What...! I can't believe it. I didn't even get to show off my underwear...! I worked so hard to look appealing, too!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-3">
                <state img="#-stahp.png">I hope that's not all you had in you... we should play again soon.</state>
                <state img="#-meep.png">My, oh my. To think that I'm still mostly dressed. I suppose I'll have to take care of myself tonight. &lt;i&gt;Sigh.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-fufufu.png">At least you had the chance to see my underwear. But I'd prefer a more direct approach to pampering.</state>
                <state img="#-fufufu.png">Ah, at least I got to feel a rush of victory, and the rest of you enjoyed the touch of self-care.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">&lt;i&gt;Tch.&lt;/i&gt; And you didn't even get to see what I look like naked. I hope my chest at least is the highlight of your personal memories for some time to come. And to come for some time. </state>
                <state img="#-fibbing.png">A victory, but... not quite what I came here for. I did arrive to cum, after all... shall we play again?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Very close. But I bet it's quite frustrating to be so close. Maybe we ought to try again?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">You can't fluff my tail until you beat me. Let's go again?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-silly.png">You get to enjoy the view... but not the best part. Shall I finish for you?</state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">My oh my... and you didn't even get to see the best part. Shall I put on a show for you, and see if I can't ease you into going again?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_defeat">
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-araara.png">Well done, ~name~. I &lt;i&gt;do&lt;/i&gt; feel quite a bit more relaxed. </state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">If there's any additional pampering you need, ~name~... just let me know.</state>
                <state img="#-silly.png">Myo~name~! You've not had a chance to finish the game, ~name~. Perhaps I could help with that? I do &lt;i&gt;love&lt;/i&gt; to provide care...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="global">
            <case stage="0-9" id="1" hidden="1">
                <state>Past</state>
                <state>Pamper</state>
                <state>Soothe</state>
                <state>Help</state>
                <state>Sound</state>
                <state>Mommy</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

    </behaviour>
</opponent>
