<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>

<!--This file was machine generated using the Character Editor v6.7.8 at 10:39:39 PM on November 29, 2022. Do not edit this file directly unless you know what you're doing.-->
<opponent>
    <version>v6.7.8</version>
    <first>Steve</first>
    <last>Harrington</last>
    <label>Steve</label>
    <gender>male</gender>
    <size>large</size>
    <timer>25</timer>
    <intelligence>average</intelligence>

    <nicknames>
        <nickname for="captain_america">Cap</nickname>
    </nicknames>


    <wardrobe>
        <clothing name="underwear" generic="underwear" position="lower" type="important" />
        <clothing name="pants" generic="pants" position="lower" type="major" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="shirt" generic="shirt" position="upper" type="major" />
        <clothing name="sunglasses" generic="glasses" position="head" type="extra" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="jacket" generic="jacket" position="upper" type="minor" />
        <clothing name="shoes" generic="shoes" position="feet" type="extra" plural="true" />
    </wardrobe>


    <behaviour>
        <trigger id="selected">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-Calm.png">This is where the cards are happening, yeah? Name's Steve.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_start">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition count="3-" filter="short" role="other" />
                <state img="#-Tired.png">Always the goddamn babysitter...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition count="0" gender="female" />
                <state img="#-Upset.png">Hey, where's all the chicks at?! Ugh... Let's just get this circle jerk over with.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-Showoff.png">That's Steve Harrington, by the way. That mean anything to you? ...Yeah, let's just get started.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" hidden="1" addCharacterTags="dead_by_daylight,video_game">
                <condition filter="dead_by_daylight" />
                <state>Gives Steve the Dead by Daylight tag.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="swap_cards">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-Confused.png">Gimme, uh... Shit, ~cards.text~?</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png">Let's see... Yeah, I'll take ~cards.text~.</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png">Let's take ~cards.text~. That's what Henderson would probably do.</state>
                <state img="#-Ugh.png">~Cards.text~, and then I'll just hope for the best.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="good_hand">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="20">When I was growing up, we didn't have all these video games and shit. We had cards, so I'm pretty damn good at them.</state>
                <state img="#-Smug.png">It's not &lt;i&gt;just&lt;/i&gt; luck, alright? There's a layer of strategy involved, and I happen to be a master.</state>
                <state img="#-Confident.png">I might not be the king of Hawkins anymore, but I don't gotta be to kick ass.</state>
                <state img="#-Confident.png">See? I know what I'm doing. ...Sometimes.</state>
                <state img="#-Confused.png">Hey, are we allowed to bluff? Jeez, uh, this hand really blows...</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">This'll shut up all those girls in science class who said I can't count to ten.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-Confident.png">Heh. Let's see you say I don't win anything after this one, Henderson!</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Ladies love guys who're good with kids, right? Well, I happen to be a pretty damn good babysitter.</state>
                <state img="#-Smug.png">It's all in the hair.</state>
                <state img="#-Confident.png">I knew this was my year. The Pacers started kicking ass, and so will I!</state>
                <state img="#-Smug.png">And the Harrington pride lives on another day.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">I know she has a boyfriend right now and all... But playing a game like this with Nance, man...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6">
                <state img="#-Showoff.png" oneShotId="19">Gotta have the right body to be a monster slayer. The chest hair makes 'em think you're tough. Like a bear.</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png">I'm feelin' a comeback coming on. Always get a second wind during the fourth quarter.</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">I'm actually a certified lifeguard, so if anybody feels like taking a dip after this, you've got no worries.</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Can't keep a good babysitter down.</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png">Yeah, suck on this! &lt;br&gt;...The, uh, the cards, I mean.</state>
                <state img="#-Smug.png">This is what Hawkins delivers. Only the very best.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="okay_hand">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-Cringe.png">You ever hear about me working at Scoops Ahoy -- that never happened, alright?</state>
                <state img="#-Confused.png">This place connects to other dimensions, yeah? I better not see any freaky monsters running around.</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png">I just had a great idea! ...Nope, I lost it.</state>
                <state img="#-Tired.png">I wouldn't mind playing for money too. Keeping your hair like this on minimum wage ain't easy.</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png" oneShotId="23">Starting to think the sunglasses were a bad idea...</state>
                <state img="#-Ugh.png">Yeah, alright... This one's on me. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-Interested.png" oneShotId="10">Any of you into drinking? I was a party animal when I was younger, but I never liked hangovers. Usually stick to hanging out with Robin on the weekends now.</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png">Do the people working this joint get paid at all? ...Think they're hiring?</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png">Could really go for some ice cream right now. Wonder if they'll still take my employee discount at Scoops Ahoy...</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png" oneShotId="25">This guy I know, Jonathan... Real strung out and anxious all the time. Guys like that always become stoners, right?</state>
                <state img="#-Tired.png">Why is my luck always so shit? C'mon, otherworldly forces! Throw me a bone for once!</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png">Fuck me, man... Ah, shit, that came out wrong...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6">
                <state img="#-Thinking.png" oneShotId="5">Y'know, I asked Robin if she wanted to come with. Figured we could appreciate the ladies together. She's never done good in front of crowds, though.</state>
                <state img="#-Tired.png">You might think things were easier for me when I was rich. ...Well, they &lt;i&gt;were&lt;/i&gt;, but it helps not to think about it like that.</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png" oneShotId="40">Had another one of those "getting chases by a guy with a bunch of bear traps" dreams last night. Least I wasn't naked.</state>
                <state img="#-Ugh.png">This is what I get for never paying attention when they were talking about probabilities.</state>
                <state img="#-Flirt.png">My friends keep making fun of me for the chest hair. I'm telling you, it works!</state>
                <state img="#-Ugh.png">Too bad I lost my lucky underwear in the wash.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="bad_hand">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-Tired.png" oneShotId="1">These kids have been running me ragged. Gotta get away from 'em sometimes. &lt;br&gt; ...They're not &lt;i&gt;my&lt;/i&gt; kids, just so you know.</state>
                <state img="#-Upset.png">Ah, whatever. It's all bullshit luck anyway...</state>
                <state img="#-Confused.png">...Shit.</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png">Wait, that was a six? Damn it, thought it was a nine...</state>
                <state img="#-Tired.png">And here's the part where I regret not having some extra belts to take off, right?</state>
                <state img="#-Ugh.png">Getting my ass kicked is just a regular Sunday at this point.</state>
                <state img="#-Sad.png" oneShotId="71">Chief Hopper kept Hawkins safe... and then he got captured by Russians. Real bummer.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-Tired.png">Hawkins High has gone to shit ever since I left. Least I still got Sinclair holding down the basketball team for me.</state>
                <state img="#-Sad.png" oneShotId="29">I used to be a real, uh... "Casanova," Robin called me. Now I can't even get a second date. Shit sucks, man.</state>
                <state img="#-Tired.png">Eh, this is better than putting up with customers all day, at least...</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png">Whose dick do I gotta suck to get a half-decent hand? ...Wait, uh, I didn't mean it like that...</state>
                <state img="#-Ugh.png">Man, I hate being the stupidest guy in the room. ...Wish it didn't happen so often.</state>
                <state img="#-Confused.png">Anybody wanna swap? No? Even if I throw in a free VHS?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6">
                <state img="#-Upset.png">I've been having these... weird dreams lately. It's really dark, foggy... Usually getting chased by some guy with a mask. It feels way too real.</state>
                <state img="#-Sad.png" oneShotId="67">I'm not &lt;i&gt;just&lt;/i&gt; interested in one night stands, alright? Finding the girl that's right for me has been pretty tough.</state>
                <state img="#-Annoyed.png">Hey, y'know what I got to say to the guy dealing these cards?</state>
                <state img="#-Tired.png">Chill out, Harrington. You're just naked in front of a bunch of strangers... Probably just a dream.</state>
                <state img="#-Confused.png">Be a &lt;i&gt;real&lt;/i&gt; convenient time for my hidden psychic powers to kick in... </state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Eh, this ain't so bad. It's fun to show off the bod every now and then.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="hand">
            <case stage="0-8" id="5" totalRounds="5-">
                <condition role="other" character="takatoshi" stage="0-6" sayingMarker="CloningBlues" />
                <state img="#-Serious.png">Yeah, that's a no. I definitely wouldn't be the same guy if I didn't have somebody like Nancy to kick my ass into shape.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="self" timeInStage="0" />
                <condition role="other" character="natsuki" stage="5-8" sayingMarker="natsuki34" />
                <state img="#-Smug.png">Ahh, c'mon, you know you like it. Makes me look tough, right? Don't tell me you like softer guys.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="6">
                <condition role="other" character="takatoshi" stage="4-6" sayingMarker="LovePrompt" />
                <state img="#-Tired.png">Well, uh, I fell in love with a girl that turned out to be gay, so... does that count?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="7">
                <condition role="other" character="eichi" stage="0-4" sayingMarker="eichi_spnatihell" />
                <state img="#-Cringe.png">Don't say that, man. I don't wanna think about if I actually died all the times I went into that hellhole.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="other" character="takatoshi" saidMarker="YakisobaPan1" />
                <state img="#-Cringe.png" oneShotId="630">Look, man, I like food as much as the next guy, but... What you did? That's just weird.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-6" id="1" oneShotId="3" totalRounds="5-">
                <state img="#-Interested.png" oneShotId="628" marker="SongPrompt">Random question, but any of you guys decided on a favorite song? Y'know, just in case.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="okino" stage="0-7" sayingMarker="steve_80sman1" />
                <state img="#-Confused.png" marker="OkinoShoes1Reply">I mean... yeah, I'm &lt;i&gt;from&lt;/i&gt; the 80s. I know time is kinda fucked here, but still.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="leon" stage="1-7" sayingMarker="leon01" />
                <state img="#-Calm.png">Gotta be honest, Hawkins is going to hell right now. Still love the place, though. That's why I'm sticking around.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="leon" stage="0-7" sayingMarker="leon11" />
                <state img="#-Tired.png">Trust me, you do &lt;i&gt;not&lt;/i&gt; want me to be the guy enforcing the law. I barely even passed high school.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="15">
                <condition role="other" character="revy" stage="0-7" sayingMarker="steve0" />
                <state img="#-Tired.png" marker="RevyShoes1Reply">Yeah, yeah, rub it in. I still get plenty of chicks, y'know? It's just everything else in my life that's gone to shit.</state>
                <state img="#-Serious.png" marker="RevyShoes1Reply">Hey, I peaked in high school, but I still get plenty of ladies. Just... not any that I wanna put a ring on just yet.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="16">
                <condition role="other" character="jura" stage="0-6" sayingMarker="steve0" />
                <state img="#-Thinking.png" marker="JuraShoes1Reply">You keep dudes as prisoners? That's messed up. How's a guy gonna get hairspray in prison?</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png" marker="JuraShoes1Reply">Hey, whoa, did you just say you keep guys as prisoners? Can't exactly blame them for not having a lotta hairspray...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="17">
                <condition role="other" character="meia" stage="0-5" sayingMarker="steve0" />
                <state img="#-Ugh.png" marker="MeiaShoes1Reply">Well, depends on how your crew lost that money. I don't exactly got a tragic backstory.</state>
                <state img="#-Tired.png" marker="MeiaShoes1Reply">Unless the people you roll with lost their money because of their douchebag dads, I don't think they'd have much pity for me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="natsuki" stage="0-8" sayingMarker="natsuki11" />
                <state img="#-Calm.png">Me? Honestly, I'm just some guy. Making 2 bucks an hour and keeping a bunch of kids from killing themselves, that's my deal.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="senko" stage="0-7" sayingMarker="senko11" />
                <state img="#-Confused.png">You think so? I mean, most people would call me a douchebag. Maybe it's a little early to think I'm sweet...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="22">
                <condition role="other" character="dwight" stage="0-7" sayingMarker="steve_ms0" />
                <state img="#-Happy.png" marker="DwightShoes1Reply">I guess my reputation has spread pretty far. Hey, what guy &lt;i&gt;doesn't&lt;/i&gt; enjoy a good time with some chicks, huh?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="23">
                <condition role="other" character="dwight" stage="0-7" sayingMarker="steve_ms1" />
                <state img="#-Calm.png" marker="DwightJacket1Reply">You think? Shit's always so crazy -- gotta have one guy bringing up the mood, y'know? Guess it's gotta be me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="29">
                <condition role="other" character="dwight" stage="0-7" sayingMarker="steve_ms2" />
                <state img="#-Thinking.png" marker="DwightSunglasses1">Well, honestly, I use a lot of products. Can't imagine you're drowning in 'em where you are.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="marinette" stage="0-8" sayingMarker="mari01" />
                <state img="#-Ugh.png" marker="MarinetteShoes1Reply">You think it's just an act? ...Well, you're not &lt;i&gt;totally&lt;/i&gt; wrong, but I try to be tough.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="marinette" stage="0-8" sayingMarker="mari11" />
                <state img="#-Ugh.png" marker="MarinetteJacket1Reply">Yeah, that whole jock life was never for me. Just a bunch of douchebags laughing about being jerks.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="marinette" stage="0-8" sayingMarker="mari21" />
                <state img="#-Showoff.png" marker="MarinetteSunglasses1Reply">I know a little bit of French, I'll have you know. Ahem... &lt;i&gt;Avez-vous un petit ami?&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="13">
                <condition role="other" character="cheryl" sayingMarker="steve_shoesA" />
                <state img="#-Showoff.png" marker="CherylShoes1Reply">Ah, y'know, it's what I'm here for. Protecting the ladies is just what I do.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="14">
                <condition role="other" character="cheryl" sayingMarker="steve_jacketA" />
                <state img="#-Ugh.png" marker="CherylJacket1Reply">You must not've been around Hawkins lately. Me and Nance haven't been a thing for... a while. She's with Jonathan.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="natsuki" sayingMarker="natsuki01" />
                <state img="#-Showoff.png">The sunglasses are a part of my look. I figured most ladies dig it. ...What, you don't?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="natsuki" sayingMarker="natsuki21" />
                <state img="#-Happy.png">...Nah, I don't need 'em. Can't hide behind 'em forever, am I right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="natsuki" sayingMarker="natsuki31" />
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Yeah, I'm only a medium asshole. ...But thanks.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="kumatora" sayingMarker="steveGreet" />
                <state img="#-Tired.png" marker="KumatoraShoes1Reply">Yeah, thanks. I get that a lot.</state>
                <state img="#-Tired.png" marker="KumatoraShoes1Reply">Jesus, why does everybody wanna kick the shit out of me so bad?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="18">
                <condition role="other" character="dunban" sayingMarker="dunban_steve_hair1" />
                <state img="#-Serious.png" marker="DunbanShoes1Reply">Hey, man, I don't spill the beans so early. Let's just say that you gotta experiment. Learn what works for you.</state>
                <state img="#-Serious.png" marker="DunbanShoes1Reply">&lt;i&gt;My&lt;/i&gt; secret ain't gonna be your secret. You gotta dedicate some time to it. Try shit until something works.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="33">
                <condition role="other" character="cheryl" sayingMarker="steve_stage2A" />
                <state img="#-Confused.png" marker="CherylSunglasses1Reply">It's kind of a blur, honestly... But bein' around you is making some stuff come back. Stuff I thought was just a dream.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="natsuki" sayingMarker="natsuki41" />
                <state img="#-Tired.png" marker="NatsukiPants1Reply">Well, you gotta take care of it, of course. Leave it alone for too long and I'll look like Captain Caveman.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5" oneShotId="1">
                <condition role="self" consecutiveLosses="3-" />
                <state img="#-Annoyed.png">Alright, c'mon! What asshole is stacking the deck here?!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-Ugh.png">It's me? Alright, alright, don't cream your pants now...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-Tired.png">Yeah, yeah, I got it. I just got shitty luck, alright? Well, it ain't all bad.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-Tired.png">I'm up again? Yeah, alright, this ain't so bad. Better than being in Hawkins right now, at least.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-Confident.png">See, now &lt;i&gt;this&lt;/i&gt; is the fun part for you guys. Prepare to be wowed by the Harrington charm!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-Confused.png">Well... shit.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-Calm.png">It's a good thing I already lost all my dignity. I'd be real pissed otherwise.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripping">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="OkinoShoes1Reply" />
                <condition role="other" character="okino" stage="0-7" sayingMarker="steve_80sman2" />
                <state img="#-Stripping.png" marker="OkinoShoes2Reply">Hey, you sayin' I'm some kind of trend chaser? Cause I am trend &lt;i&gt;setter&lt;/i&gt;. Give it a few years, everybody's gonna be copying my style.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="leon" stage="1-7" sayingMarker="leon02" />
                <state img="#-Stripping.png">Uh... yeah, I can see what you mean. Bein' a cop and all. Must be in trials a lot...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="natsuki" stage="0-8" sayingMarker="natsuki12" />
                <state img="#-Stripping.png">Trust me, you do &lt;i&gt;not&lt;/i&gt; want me being the guy teaching your kids. I barely passed high school. Couldn't even get into college.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="senko" stage="0-7" sayingMarker="senko02" />
                <state img="#-Stripping.png">My "aura?" Well, looking after these kids &lt;i&gt;has&lt;/i&gt; aged me ten years. ...Seriously, though, I don't get it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="marinette" stage="0-8" sayingMarker="mari02" />
                <state img="#-Stripping.png" marker="MarinetteShoes2">Observe all you want, for all I care.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="25">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="CherylShoes1Reply" />
                <condition role="other" character="cheryl" sayingMarker="steve_jacketB" />
                <state img="#-Stripping.png" marker="CherylJacket2Reply">Yeah, well, we're still &lt;i&gt;friends&lt;/i&gt;. Just not... together. Plenty of fish in the sea, I say.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="natsuki" sayingMarker="natsuki22" />
                <state img="#-Stripping.png">Thanks! ...I think. I'll take it as a compliment from someone cute like you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="natsuki" sayingMarker="natsuki32" />
                <state img="#-Stripping.png">You're lucky you didn't meet me in high school. I wasn't always like this. But thanks to girls like you, I'm learning how to be a good dude.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="34">
                <condition role="other" character="cheryl" sayingMarker="steve_stage2B" />
                <state img="#-Stripping.png" marker="CherylSunglasses2Reply">Ah, don't be like that. I remember you, and how much ass you kicked out there. I remember you're someone special, Cheryl. That's the important part to me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="36">
                <condition role="other" character="cheryl" sayingMarker="steve_shoesB" />
                <state img="#-Stripping.png" marker="CherylShoes3Reply">Hey, I get plenty of chicks! Just, y'know, most of 'em don't stick around for long.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="natsuki" sayingMarker="natsuki42" />
                <state img="#-Stripping.png" marker="NatsukiPants2Reply">And what's wrong with a girl goin' all natural, huh? I don't mind. I mean, shit, not like I got room to complain.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" priority="51">
                <test expr="~background.location~" value="indoors" />
                <state img="#-Stripping.png">If there's one thing I learned from movies, it's that chicks love a guy that wears sunglasses indoors.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" priority="51">
                <test expr="~background.dark~" value="true" />
                <state img="#-Stripping.png">...Honestly, I can't see shit with these things on anyway. Too damn dark.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <test expr="~background.location~" value="outdoors" />
                <state img="#-Stripping.png">Now I just gotta hope the sun doesn't get my in eyes. You hear me, sun? I got important things to look at here.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-Stripping.png">I love the place, but ever since those monsters started showing up, shit's just gone to Hell. All cause of that girl.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-Stripping.png">It's a good thing we ain't playing for cash right now. Think I've got more ex-girlfriends than I do cash in my pocket right now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-Stripping.png">...You shoulda seen what I wore in high school. Nancy, my old girlfriend, she always hated that polo shirt...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-Stripping.png">Alright, just the pants, yeah? I've already come this far. No big deal in my book.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-Stripping.png">I like to think I've got a few charm points, but this one might be my biggest... and I mean that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-Cringe.png">You shouldn't be seeing this, alright? If you are, submit a bug report.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" priority="0">
                <condition count="2-" gender="male" />
                <state img="#-Stripping.png">So, uh, you guys enjoyin' the view? Cause I'm actually getting a little more into this than I thought.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripped">
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="leon" stage="1-7" sayingMarker="leon03" />
                <state img="#-After.png">Thanks, man. When shit hits the fan, we gotta be there for each other. That's how we survive. &lt;br&gt;...Wait, the hell am I talking about?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="leon" stage="0-7" sayingMarker="leon13" />
                <state img="#-Showoff.png">Ahh, it's nothing special. Sometimes a guy's just gotta step up, y'know? If nobody else'll keep people safe, I guess it's up to me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="natsuki" stage="0-8" sayingMarker="natsuki13" />
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Yeah? Well, I say I'm a pretty damn good babysitter. That's my way of showing I care.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="natsuki" stage="0-4" sayingMarker="natsuki23" />
                <state img="#-Smug.png">A magician never reveals his secrets. But hey, come over to my place, and I can just show you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="natsuki" stage="5-10" sayingMarker="natsuki23" />
                <state img="#-Horny.png">You're pretty forward, aren't you? Heh, well, I do love a girl who knows what she wants. Hope you don't mind me joining you in the shower.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="senko" stage="0-7" sayingMarker="senko03" />
                <state img="#-Flirt.png">Just keep on lookin' cute over there and I'll relax in no time.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="marinette" stage="0-8" sayingMarker="mari03" />
                <state img="#-Flirt.png" marker="MarinetteShoes3Reply">Yeah? Well, everybody's got their weak points... on the inside &lt;i&gt;and&lt;/i&gt; out.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="natsuki" sayingMarker="natsuki33" />
                <state img="#-Happy.png">You like it? Heh, knew you would. Haven't met a girl that doesn't.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4" id="19">
                <condition role="other" character="dwight" sayingMarker="steve_chestreveal" />
                <state img="#-Showoff.png">Sorry, man, it's just genetics. This is one good thing my douchebag dad ever gave me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="35">
                <condition role="other" character="cheryl" sayingMarker="steve_shoesC" />
                <state img="#-Cringe.png" marker="CherylShoes3Reply">There's two definition of "lady killer" here, and I don't like either of 'em!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="other" character="natsuki" sayingMarker="natsuki43" />
                <state img="#-Flirt.png" marker="NatsukiPants3Reply">Listen, for me what matters most is whether or not we "click," y'know? I like a girl with some hair, but I just like girls in general, and I think you and I are clicking pretty well.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition count="0" gender="female" />
                <state img="#-After.png">...Might be better to throw down cash than do this with a bunch of guys, though. No offense, but that's not really my speed...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <condition count="0" gender="female" />
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png">Alright, dickheads, don't stare. I was just... thinking about that girl I was with last night, and it got me like this. That's all.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-Ugh.png">Those kids, man... Little shits always cause trouble. Especially the biggest shit of 'em all, Henderson. And &lt;i&gt;I'm&lt;/i&gt; the lucky guy that gets to babysit 'em.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-After.png">Now, &lt;i&gt;clothes&lt;/i&gt;, I can do. I'm an eligible bachelor right now, so, uh... &lt;i&gt;ladies&lt;/i&gt;?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-Calm.png">I was skeptical at first, but you guys aren't so bad. Nice to hang with, even without all the, uh, porn stuff.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4" id="3">
                <state img="#-Showoff.png">Either way, though, I'm &lt;i&gt;way&lt;/i&gt; better without it. Nothing ladies love more than nuzzling up in the chest hair!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5" id="4">
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png">Yeah, yeah, I know it's obvious. Us guys can't help it, y'know? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-Horny.png">Damn, I'm all fired up. Winning's nice and all, but I think losing would feel better right now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4" priority="0">
                <condition count="2-" gender="male" />
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png">I guess I've still got things to learn about myself. Like... well, maybe bein' with a guy is worth a shot.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_strip">
            <case stage="0-8" id="38">
                <condition role="target" character="okino" stage="0" />
                <test expr="~okino.costume~" value="default" />
                <state img="#-Showoff.png" marker="OkinoRibbon1A">I was hoping for lookers, but I didn't expect someone so cute to show up. Dig the braids.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="39">
                <condition role="target" character="okino" stage="0" />
                <test expr="~okino.costume~" cmp="!=" value="default" />
                <state img="#-Confused.png" marker="OkinoRibbon1B">You're pretty cute for a guy, aren't ya? N-Not like that's my thing, but...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="10">
                <condition role="target" character="leon" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Confused.png" marker="LeonGloves1">Hey man, do I know you from somewhere? I feel like I've seen you out drinking with Chief Hopper or something.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="11">
                <condition role="target" character="anatoly" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Confused.png">...Hey dude, are you Russian? No problem with that, but... had some bad experiences with Russians.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="12">
                <condition role="target" character="leon" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-Showoff.png" marker="LeonGloves1">I know a thing or two about monsters. Wonder how our experiences would stack up.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="20">
                <condition role="target" character="leon" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-Happy.png" marker="LeonJacket1">Hope life's been treating you a little better lately, man. I know both of us have been through some shit.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="24">
                <condition role="target" character="dwight" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-Thinking.png" marker="DwightBelt1">Here's one thing I could never wrap my head around, man. So we're buddies with Ash Williams, getting chased around by Michael Myers, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="26">
                <condition role="target" character="dwight" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Confused.png" marker="DwightBracelets1">Dwight, right? I... definitely know you from somewhere. You go to Hawkins 'round the early 80s?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="27">
                <condition role="target" character="dwight" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-Tired.png">So which is your least favorite to face, anyway? Mine's gotta be that vomit chick. Always made me wish we could stop and take a shower...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="28">
                <condition role="target" character="dwight" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-Thinking.png" marker="DwightTie1">I remember... those hooks, and all those big-ass dudes slashing at us... Shit, man, where did I even learn how to fix a generator?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-Ugh.png">Looks like I got competition.</state>
                <state img="#-Upset.png">Trying to upstage me, buddy? Well, we'll see about that.</state>
                <state img="#-Cringe.png">Let's just... try not to make this weird, okay?</state>
                <state img="#-Smug.png">See? I can kick some ass too when I feel like it.</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png">It's, uh, just like being in the locker room, right? Except everybody's staring at your dick.</state>
                <state img="#-Confident.png">Who's the man?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-6">
                <state img="#-Calm.png">Hey, man, we can just hang. This doesn't have to be weird if we don't &lt;i&gt;make&lt;/i&gt; it weird.</state>
                <state img="#-Confused.png">So, uh... This a typical ~weekday~ for you, or...?</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png">Look, seeing other dudes, naked, no big deal. Place like this, though? ...Kind of a big deal.</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png">Been looking forward to this. ...B-Because I wanted to win!</state>
                <state img="#-Serious.png">Alright, alright, nobody likes a showoff. Let's keep this quick.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-Confused.png">Talk about a circle jerk...</state>
                <state img="#-Ugh.png">I'll just, ah... try to keep my eyes closed...</state>
                <state img="#-Cringe.png">Don't look, don't look... Ah, shit, I'm lookin'...!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-Calm.png">Well, you've already seen my dick, so... Fair's fair.</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png">...Ah, fuck, why am I getting into this...?</state>
                <state img="#-Ugh.png">Look, it's not that I like guys. Who &lt;i&gt;hasn't&lt;/i&gt; thought about suckin' dick every now and then?</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png" set-size="small">Stay down, penis...!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_strip">
            <case stage="0-8" id="8">
                <condition role="target" character="marinette" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Confused.png" marker="MarinetteYoYo1">Y'know, I've read some of Henderson's comics. Never thought I'd meet somebody who looks like they jumped out of 'em.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="9">
                <condition role="target" character="marinette" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-Flirt.png" marker="MarinetteBodysuit1">Not really &lt;i&gt;my&lt;/i&gt; style, but a suit like that on a lady like you? I kinda dig it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="21">
                <condition role="target" character="amy" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Confused.png" marker="AmyBlazer1">...Hey, uh, is anybody else getting bad vibes offa this chick? I mean, no offense, but...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="30">
                <condition role="target" character="cheryl" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Ugh.png" marker="CherylBoots1">Take it a lot of crazy shit happens in this "Silent Hill" place. Sounds a lot like Hawkins, honestly.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="31">
                <condition role="target" character="cheryl" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-Confused.png" marker="CherylSocks1">Man, I just... can't shake this feeling. I know the place you're talking about. With that elementary school, right...?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="32">
                <condition role="target" character="cheryl" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-Thinking.png" marker="CherylWristbands1">What's with that guy with the triangle hat, anyway? Never figured out what his deal is.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-Showoff.png">Hey, y'know what me and my grandpa that fought in the war have in common? &lt;br&gt;We &lt;i&gt;won&lt;/i&gt;!</state>
                <state img="#-Smug.png">Just couldn't beat the Harrington special, huh? No, no, I get it.</state>
                <state img="#-Smug.png">Y'see, it's the little things that make it all worth it.</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png">We should get to know each other, ~name~. Mind telling me a little about yourself?</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Girls dress fine and all in the eighties, but it's always nice meeting someone with her own style.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-6">
                <state img="#-Flirt.png">Now &lt;i&gt;this&lt;/i&gt;, this I like.</state>
                <state img="#-Smug.png">Fair's fair, alright? Don't go playing chicken now.</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">You ain't gonna think less of me if I said I was waiting for this, yeah?</state>
                <state img="#-Flirt.png">What's better than watching a girl undress, huh? ...Other than doing it in private.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">I'm no pervert, I'm just... picking up what I didn't learn in sex ed.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-Horny.png">Aw yeah... Good job, guys...</state>
                <state img="#-Smug.png">Mind taking this nice and slow?</state>
                <state img="#-Interested.png">Hoping for something good... A guy can dream.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-Sad.png">Ah, shit... Guess I shoulda lasted a little longer.</state>
                <state img="#-Upset.png">Aw, c'mon! You're picking &lt;i&gt;now&lt;/i&gt; to get your ass kicked?</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Well, I don't mind. Should serve as a good memory, at least.</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png">Shit, how's my hair? Gotta look good for moments like this.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="tie">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-Ugh.png">...Well, that was a good way to waste a minute.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="leon" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Confused.png" marker="LeonGloves2">I got plenty of nightmares, man, but I don't see what that has to do with you and me. ...'Sides, I'm not old enough to drink.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="dwight" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-Confused.png">Well, it's just... Where I'm from, those guys are from movies. It's all fake. So how the Hell are they real...?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" oneShotId="2">
                <condition gender="female" role="other" />
                <state img="#-Cringe.png">C'mon, dude, you're embarrassing yourself in front of the chicks...!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6 8">
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Don't underestimate how much the small stuff helps your look, man.</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png">Nice ~clothing~. Really added a lot of, uh, style. ...Look, I know how to dress myself, but other guys are a mystery.</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png">Worry a little less about your ~clothing~ and more about your hair. It does wonders. </state>
                <state img="#-Confused.png">Feels like we didn't all have to stand around and wait for this.</state>
                <state img="#-Tired.png">You're putting me to sleep over here, dude.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-Ugh.png">You're getting all the attention right now cause of &lt;i&gt;~clothing.ifPlural(those|that)~&lt;/i&gt;?</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png">Ah, yeah... You always know how to treat me, Nance...</state>
                <state img="#-Ugh.png">Eh. Not like I wanted to see better.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="leon" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-Thinking.png" marker="LeonGloves3">It's weird, though... I definitely know you from somewhere. Not from Hawkins, but... Oh well. I ain't gonna sweat it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6 8">
                <state img="#-Ugh.png">Wow, yeah, my dick's really twitchin' over here. Let's get a move on.</state>
                <state img="#-Showoff.png">Hey, man, don't be shy. I mean, I know I'm hot shit and all, but it's no big deal.</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png">Let's just keep it nice and friendly like this, yeah? Yeah.</state>
                <state img="#-Confused.png">So, uh... you guys don't actually think I'm that dumb, right? I mean, I'm playing into it, but...</state>
                <state img="#-Tired.png">Just a buncha guys standing around talking about fashion. Always wondered what sleepovers are like for girls.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-Calm.png">It's fine. I was just gonna fantasize anyway...</state>
                <state img="#-Upset.png">...Can we get going now, please?</state>
                <state img="#-Tired.png">Almost put my dick to sleep while you're at it...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="marinette" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Happy.png" marker="MarinetteYoYo2">So you're a real hero, huh? Keepin' the streets safe by dark and all that?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6 8">
                <state img="#-Calm.png">Ahh, this is fine. We can work up to the bigger stuff.</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Don't gotta be nervous around me. I'm the nicest guy coming out of Hawkins you'll ever meet.</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png">Yeah, girls don't exactly drop their panties right away for me anymore.</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Listen, I've learned to take what I can get at this point.</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png">Hey, I'm sure you look great with or without ~clothing.ifPlural(those|it)~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-Tired.png">...Eh, oh well...</state>
                <state img="#-Ugh.png">I'm mean, I'm not gonna bitch about it, but...</state>
                <state img="#-Sad.png">Mind giving me a little help over here...?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="marinette" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-Showoff.png" marker="MarinetteYoYo3">Well, I'm kind of a hero myself. I don't wear a get-up or anything, but any of those kids'll tell you I'm a real badass.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6 8">
                <state img="#-Interested.png">...Huh? Oh, no, I'm totally paying attention.</state>
                <state img="#-Flirt.png">Don't really care about the ~clothing~. Just how you look with ~clothing.ifPlural(them|it)~ off.</state>
                <state img="#-Confused.png">So, uh... you make that yourself? Can never tell with girls...</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png">See? The small things &lt;i&gt;do&lt;/i&gt; matter.</state>
                <state img="#-Flirt.png">Honestly, ~clothing.ifPlural(they|it)~ brought the look together. I'm more worried about taking it apart.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-Flirt.png">Alright, let's pick up the pace...</state>
                <state img="#-Ugh.png">I'd get it if you weren't interested in dudes, but...</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png">A little more...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="anatoly" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Confused.png" marker="AnatolyShoes2">That's... not in Russia. Alright. Shoulda paid attention in Geography. What's it like there?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="leon" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-Calm.png" marker="LeonShoes2">Me? Kids call 'em "Demogorgons." Some of 'em are like dogs -- others are bigger than you and me. Fought a few of 'em.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="leon" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-Tired.png" marker="LeonJacket2">I mean, I thought those Demo-things were bad, but that Nemesis guy packs a fuckin' punch. Never wanna go up against him again...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6 8">
                <state img="#-Confused.png">I get that it's the point, but aren't you worried about ruining your look?</state>
                <state img="#-Confident.png">Fashion, man. Chicks love a guy that's dressed well.</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">I'll make a note on ~clothing.ifPlural(those|that)~ for Henderson. Poor kid needs to learn how to dress well.</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png">We're, uh... moving a little fast here, aren't we?</state>
                <state img="#-Ugh.png">I'm just glad we're keeping it to this for now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png">I-I mean, I wasn't hoping for anything more...</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png">Yeah, alright, let's just keep it to this...</state>
                <state img="#-Confused.png">And just when I was thinking you're kinda cute... Huh? What'd I say?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_minor">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="leon" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-Thinking.png" marker="LeonShoes3">...Wait, how the hell do you know about that? Nobody outside of Hawkins should... This is weird, man.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="leon" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-Confused.png" marker="LeonJacket3">Huh? No, wait, I... Shit, I've definitely hauled ass away from him with you. And that... dude in the trenchcoat. Real bastards, both of 'em...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6 8">
                <state img="#-Calm.png" oneShotId="78">Now don't tell anybody I told you this, but... four puffs of Farrah Fawcett spray when your hair is damp. Trust me.</state>
                <state img="#-Ugh.png">Well, I know who I wouldn't be looking at if I was jackin' off... N-Not that I'd be looking at you anyway...</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png">Just make sure you don't get anything sticky on ~clothing.ifPlural(those|that)~.</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png">Now let's just keep this show movin' along.</state>
                <state img="#-Ugh.png">Don't start feeling all cocky just cause you're not losing yet, dude.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-Upset.png">Had me worried for a second there. Almost thought I'd say something weird...</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png">Alright, back to the fun part...</state>
                <state img="#-Upset.png">Guess this really isn't doing anything for you. W-Well, what do I care?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0-6 8">
                <state img="#-Confident.png">Hey, be honest with me. Am I your type or what?</state>
                <state img="#-Flirt.png">I like a girl who doesn't beat around the bush.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">Now I'm just thinking about what you look like with even less.</state>
                <state img="#-Upset.png">Huh. Nance could rock that... B-But you rock it damn well too, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">No rush, no rush. Always nice to get a girl ready first.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-Calm.png">Hey, I'll take it.</state>
                <state img="#-Interested.png">C'mon, just a little bit more...</state>
                <state img="#-Ugh.png">You, uh... wanna give a guy some help...?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_minor">
            <case stage="0-6 8">
                <state img="#-Flirt.png">See, this is the kind of thing every guy dreams about.</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Man, Robin doesn't know what she's missing.</state>
                <state img="#-Showoff.png">So... a movie after this, maybe?</state>
                <state img="#-Flirt.png">So there are beautiful girls outside of Hawkins after all, huh?</state>
                <state img="#-Smug.png">Teasing me with the anticipation? That means you like me, yeah?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Not bad. I'll take it...</state>
                <state img="#-Flirt.png">Worth the wait? We'll see...</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png">Yeah, just like that...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_major">
            <case stage="0-6 8">
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png">Well. That's, uh... Huh.</state>
                <state img="#-Interested.png">...Y'know, I don't hate this as much as I thought I would.</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png">I'm not sure if I like that I've been looking forward to this.</state>
                <state img="#-Confused.png">Well, you're... not a &lt;i&gt;bad&lt;/i&gt; looking dude...</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png">Never felt like this in the locker room...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png">Maybe I'm just too horny right now...</state>
                <state img="#-Tired.png">Fuck, I can't stop...</state>
                <state img="#-Confused.png">Damn, that's... Why is that hot...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_major">
            <case stage="0-6 8">
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png">...Wonder if any guys had a crush on me in high school. Maybe I'd be a little more open to it now...</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png">Not that this applies to me, but do you think girls like it when guys swing both ways?</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png">This guy, Eddie, called me "big boy" once. Still don't know why I liked it so much...</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png">Maybe picking up guys at my jobs woulda been easier...</state>
                <state img="#-Confused.png">This is all Robin's fault, man. She tells me she likes girls, and now I'm feeling all weird about guys...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-Horny.png">Well, this ain't so bad...</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">I guess trying something new could be fun...</state>
                <state img="#-Confused.png">N-Never felt this way about any of those douchebags in high school...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_major">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="marinette" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-Ugh.png" marker="MarinetteBodysuit2">...And of course, right after I say that...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6 8">
                <state img="#-Flirt.png">See, now this is what every guy lives for.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">Nothing better than peeling away a girl's clothes in the bedroom.</state>
                <state img="#-Interested.png">About time, right?</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">Finding a cute girl and getting her out of her clothes is what gets me out of bed in the morning.</state>
                <state img="#-Smug.png">All this for me? You shouldn't have, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-Flirt.png">You know how to help a guy out...</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">Ah, fuck, I'm leaking...</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">And all that losing is now worth it...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_major">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="marinette" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-Horny.png" marker="MarinetteBodysuit3">...Well, this ain't so bad either.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6 8">
                <state img="#-Calm.png">If you need a testimonial, I've got at least one guy on record saying I'm "not a douche."</state>
                <state img="#-Showoff.png">Hey, you know I'm actually a monster slayer? Just throwing that out there.</state>
                <state img="#-Smug.png">I don't win a lot, but when I do, I win &lt;i&gt;big&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png">Does it mean anything to you if I say I'm great with kids?</state>
                <state img="#-Smug.png">I think we're gonna get along &lt;i&gt;just&lt;/i&gt; fine.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-Interested.png">Nice. Now that that's out of the way...</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">C'mon, just join me already...</state>
                <state img="#-Interested.png">About time we're done with all the stalling...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-Calm.png" oneShotId="451">Well, we'll see how we stack up.</state>
                <state img="#-Interested.png" oneShotId="452">You keep yourself in shape, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-Confused.png" oneShotId="453">I'm not all about this, but chicks sure are.</state>
                <state img="#-Ugh.png" oneShotId="454">You're gonna steal all the spotlight before I can even have it, man.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-6 8">
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png" oneShotId="460">What do I care about some dude's chest, huh?</state>
                <state img="#-Ugh.png" oneShotId="462">Yeah, yeah. It's all about the muscle.</state>
                <state img="#-Tired.png" oneShotId="461">Seen so many dudes with their shirts off... Man, sports are kinda gay, huh?</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png" oneShotId="459">Guess I stuck it out to this point for a reason...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png" oneShotId="487">...Huh...</state>
                <state img="#-Flirt.png" oneShotId="467">I'm... actually looking forward to this...</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png" oneShotId="468">Well, I guess we're about to learn what I like...</state>
                <state img="#-Confused.png" oneShotId="469">Man, the atmosphere here is making me feel all weird...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-Showoff.png" oneShotId="608">I try to keep myself in decent shape. We should work out sometime.</state>
                <state img="#-Interested.png" oneShotId="609">I thought you'd be all flabby or something. Why are you here if you're a decent-looking dude?</state>
                <state img="#-Showoff.png" oneShotId="610">Yeah, yeah, just you wait. I'll take all the attention back before you know it.</state>
                <state img="#-Ugh.png" oneShotId="611">Next you'll pour a water bottle over your head or something. That's what all the douches in high school did.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-6 8">
                <state img="#-Smug.png" oneShotId="624">Chest hair, man. You gotta have chest hair.</state>
                <state img="#-Confident.png" oneShotId="625">So long as girls like to cuddle up in it, you're doing something right.</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="626">Looking good, man, looking good!</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png" oneShotId="627">I'm more about what a girl has up there, but... I can kinda see the appeal.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png" oneShotId="616">Wait... Why am I...?</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png" oneShotId="617">Huh... Maybe dudes aren't so bad either...</state>
                <state img="#-Confused.png" oneShotId="618">...Weirdly smooth...</state>
                <state img="#-Confused.png" oneShotId="619">So, uh... Do you shave, or...?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-Confused.png" oneShotId="492">Didn't think I'd be seeing so much penis today, but here we are.</state>
                <state img="#-Ugh.png" oneShotId="493">Alright, man, whip it out. C'mon.</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="494">Reminds me of comparing dicks in the shower. Ah, high school.</state>
                <state img="#-Tired.png" oneShotId="495">Doesn't really &lt;i&gt;bother&lt;/i&gt; me, just... not my thing.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-6 8">
                <state img="#-Horny.png">Okay, so if I'm a little interested in guys, then...</state>
                <state img="#-Flirt.png">I guess the build-up makes you a lot more excited, huh...</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png">Well, don't keep us waiting... E-Everybody else, I mean.</state>
                <state img="#-Cringe.png">Alright, man. Lay it on me. ...N-Not literally!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-Calm.png" oneShotId="500">Hey, man... About time, if you ask me.</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png" oneShotId="501">Fair's fair...</state>
                <state img="#-Flirt.png" oneShotId="502">Well, I need &lt;i&gt;something&lt;/i&gt; to look at...</state>
                <state img="#-Tired.png" oneShotId="503">You really know how to make a guy wonder...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_small_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-Tired.png" oneShotId="508">...That's just sad, dude.</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png" oneShotId="509">I won't give you a ton of shit, but... man.</state>
                <state img="#-Interested.png" oneShotId="510">You're just a grower, not a shower, am I right?</state>
                <state img="#-Ugh.png" oneShotId="511">Don't sweat it. I don't care either way.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-6 8">
                <state img="#-Flirt.png" oneShotId="524">...Huh. Honestly, kinda cute.</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png" oneShotId="525">I'm sure some girls are into that... and some guys.</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png" oneShotId="526">Look, man, I know this is rich coming from me, but it's really about how you use it.</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png" oneShotId="527">Well, at least we know who's the bottom here...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-Thinking.png" oneShotId="516">...Hmm...</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png" oneShotId="517">I'm still working out how I feel about this...</state>
                <state img="#-Smug.png" oneShotId="518">What's that guy say in the movie...? "Say hello to my little friend..."</state>
                <state img="#-Confused.png" oneShotId="519">Guess it depends on how you use it...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_medium_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-Thinking.png" oneShotId="536">Think that's a good size for girls. Too much more and you might hurt 'em.</state>
                <state img="#-Smug.png" oneShotId="537">Trust me, I'm still a little ahead of you.</state>
                <state img="#-Smug.png" oneShotId="538">Hey, man. Nice cock.</state>
                <state img="#-Interested.png" oneShotId="539">Starting to think you wouldn't be such a bad wingman.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-6 8">
                <state img="#-Thinking.png" oneShotId="548">...Huh. That might be my preference...</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png" oneShotId="549">I... guess it comes down to if you know how to handle it.</state>
                <state img="#-Interested.png" oneShotId="550">Shit, man, why are you here? You could pick up chicks easy with that.</state>
                <state img="#-Flirt.png" oneShotId="551">You're not half bad like this. Now I gotta wonder if you're a grower.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-Confused.png" oneShotId="556">Damn... Bigger than I thought...</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png" oneShotId="557">You're... not such a bad-looking dude...</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png" oneShotId="558">F-Fuck...</state>
                <state img="#-Interested.png" oneShotId="559">A little on the smaller side is nice too...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_large_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="huge_penis" role="target" />
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">Jesus, man! You're gonna rip somebody in half!</state>
                <state img="#-Surprised.png">Fuck! I thought &lt;i&gt;mine&lt;/i&gt; was big!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-Ugh.png" oneShotId="564">Jesus, planning to whack some monsters to death with that?</state>
                <state img="#-Serious.png" oneShotId="565">Bigger isn't always better, man. Gotta know what to do with your hands too.</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png" oneShotId="566">Have to wonder which of us is bigger...</state>
                <state img="#-Tired.png" oneShotId="567">That alone isn't enough to attract girls. Trust me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-6 8">
                <state img="#-Thinking.png" oneShotId="572">...Have you ever tried to lick your own tip? It... doesn't feel that great.</state>
                <state img="#-Flirt.png" oneShotId="573">...You wanna compare?</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png" oneShotId="574">Here's a tip: tight jeans. Helps hide it.</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png" oneShotId="575">Man, can't believe I didn't notice that...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-Confused.png" oneShotId="583">Must not be fun having that in your ass...</state>
                <state img="#-Cringe.png" oneShotId="582">This isn't what I meant when I called you a huge dick...</state>
                <state img="#-Confused.png" oneShotId="581">Damn, man... How does somebody even get their mouth around that...?</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png" oneShotId="580">Now I know how my girlfriends feel...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="255">I remember seeing my first pair of boobies. It was all downhill from there.</state>
                <state img="#-Smug.png" oneShotId="256">This is always my favorite part.</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="257">All guys like boobies. The guys that don't don't count.</state>
                <state img="#-Interested.png" oneShotId="258">The best part of a woman &lt;i&gt;and&lt;/i&gt; a chicken.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-6 8">
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="263">Good things &lt;i&gt;do&lt;/i&gt; come to those who wait!</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="264">I'm already showing off, so don't you think this is fair?</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png" oneShotId="265">A guy's chest isn't much. A girl's is everything.</state>
                <state img="#-Flirt.png" oneShotId="266">Way better than seeing it in movies.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-Horny.png" oneShotId="271">Well, this is about to get a whole lot easier...</state>
                <state img="#-Interested.png" oneShotId="272">I can already tell a lot, but seeing it is the important part...</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png" oneShotId="273">Fuck, I'm already excited...</state>
                <state img="#-Interested.png" oneShotId="274">No use comparing boobs. They're all great in their own right...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_small_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-Smug.png" oneShotId="294">Big things come in small packages... Heh.</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="291">I'm always just happy to see a pair of titties.</state>
                <state img="#-Smug.png" oneShotId="292">Don't get down on yourself, ~name~. &lt;i&gt;I'm&lt;/i&gt; sure as shit enjoying this.</state>
                <state img="#-Flirt.png" oneShotId="293">Just as cute as the rest of you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-6 8">
                <state img="#-Horny.png" oneShotId="299">Small boobs, big nips, that's always a great combo.</state>
                <state img="#-Flirt.png" oneShotId="300">Hey, if they're smaller, that just means they're more sensitive, right?</state>
                <state img="#-Serious.png" oneShotId="301">Any kind of guy that doesn't like boobs of all sizes ain't worth your time, alright?</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png" oneShotId="302">If you don't appreciate 'em, maybe I could teach you to.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-Horny.png" oneShotId="307">Wouldn't mind getting my mouth around 'em...</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png" oneShotId="308">Always nice to play with...</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="309">Just makes it easier to press our bodies together...</state>
                <state img="#-Smug.png" oneShotId="310">You ain't gonna hear me complaining...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_medium_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="323">I'd like to meet the guy that doesn't like a nice pair of boobies.</state>
                <state img="#-Flirt.png" oneShotId="324">Goddamn... Are your nips hard already?</state>
                <state img="#-Interested.png" oneShotId="325">Well shit, how am I supposed to look at anything else now?</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png" oneShotId="326">Even better than the girls in Hawkins.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-6 8">
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="339">See, this is what I keep telling Robin. &lt;i&gt;Everybody&lt;/i&gt; loves boobies!</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png" oneShotId="340">Only wish I could've taken off your ~clothing~ myself.</state>
                <state img="#-Flirt.png" oneShotId="341">This is the greatest thing a man could ask for.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png" oneShotId="342">What can I say? Some guys like butts, me, I'm all about what's up there.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-Horny.png" oneShotId="347">Nice for getting them around your dick, if you ask me...</state>
                <state img="#-Interested.png" oneShotId="348">Trying to steal all of my attention, huh...?</state>
                <state img="#-Interested.png" oneShotId="349">Nothing I love more in the world... than boobs.</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="350">Been a little while since I've seen those outside of magazines...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_large_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="huge_breasts" role="target" />
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">Christ! Feel like my eyes are gonna bulge out of my head!</state>
                <state img="#-Cringe.png">That's... Yeah, okay, that's just excessive.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-6 8">
                <state img="#-Horny.png" oneShotId="371">Man... You have no idea how much I wanna get my mouth around those.</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="372">I just can't help but stare, y'know? This is what every guy dreams about!</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png" oneShotId="373">I like boobs of all size, but these are always my favorites.</state>
                <state img="#-Interested.png" oneShotId="374">See, here's a lady who knows how to make guys go crazy.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-Smug.png" oneShotId="363">And I thought basketballs were the only big round things that're fun to play with.</state>
                <state img="#-Flirt.png" oneShotId="364">You must get a lotta stares out in public, right? Well, add me to the list.</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png" oneShotId="365">You've gotten a million guys offering to hold those for you, right? ...Well, it is tempting...</state>
                <state img="#-Interested.png" oneShotId="366">Damn, to get your hands on those things...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-Surprised.png" oneShotId="386">Holy &lt;i&gt;shit&lt;/i&gt;...</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png" oneShotId="385">What I wouldn't do to get my dick between those...</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png" oneShotId="384">You're teasing me, ~name~, you're teasing me...</state>
                <state img="#-Smug.png" oneShotId="383">I'm sure I don't need to tell you how hot you are...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-Confused.png" oneShotId="391">Whoa. Bit early for this, isn't it?</state>
                <state img="#-Confident.png" oneShotId="392">Well, ain't the first time I've gotten a girl out of her panties with my shirt on.</state>
                <state img="#-Ugh.png" oneShotId="393">At least wait till I get these sunglasses off...</state>
                <state img="#-Smug.png" oneShotId="394">A little eager, aren't you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-6 8">
                <state img="#-Calm.png" oneShotId="399">Not my favorite, but damn if I'll be the one complaining.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png" oneShotId="400">I just wanna see more of your body. Especially if it tells me how excited you are.</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="401">Reminds me of... Ah, you don't wanna hear about all my dates. Let's just enjoy this.</state>
                <state img="#-Smug.png" oneShotId="402">I already know you're beautiful. Just really wanna reinforce that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="407">Getting ready to join me...?</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png" oneShotId="408">Definitely one of the best parts...</state>
                <state img="#-Interested.png" oneShotId="409">Wonder how excited you are...</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png" oneShotId="410">I just wanna shut up and enjoy this...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-Tired.png" oneShotId="427">C'mon, ~name~, you're making me wanna throw.</state>
                <state img="#-Interested.png" oneShotId="428">Damn... I'm more impressed by your hips, honestly.</state>
                <state img="#-Smug.png" oneShotId="429">Already wet? I have that effect on girls.</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="430">Making all the other girls in the world look bad.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-6 8">
                <state img="#-Horny.png" oneShotId="435">You've got... &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; nice thighs.</state>
                <state img="#-Interested.png" oneShotId="436">With hips like those, how do you not have guys on you constantly?</state>
                <state img="#-Flirt.png" oneShotId="437">You're just making me wanna take you out more and more.</state>
                <state img="#-Showoff.png" oneShotId="438">So... any of your excitement cause of me?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="443">Finger-lickin' good...</state>
                <state img="#-Flirt.png" oneShotId="444">Just so ya know... I've always got condoms...</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png" oneShotId="445">Don't think I'll last much longer...</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png" oneShotId="446">Damn... Gotta slow down a little...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_lost">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition filter="dead_by_daylight" role="target" />
                <condition filter="villain" role="target" />
                <state img="#-Ugh.png">The hell is going on with ~name~...? Feels like my heart's about to pump out of my chest...</state>
                <state img="#-Confused.png">Shit, I should grab a flashlight and... Wait, what? The hell am I saying...?</state>
                <state img="#-Confused.png">I know you from somewhere, ~name~? You kick the shit outta me or something? Feels that way...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition filter="dead_by_daylight" role="target" />
                <condition filter="hero" role="target" />
                <state img="#-Serious.png">Alright, ~name~, listen up. Key to being a good babysitter? Be the first thing between them and danger.</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png">Y'know, ~name~, I think you and I could be good friends. I feel like there's camaraderie between us.</state>
                <state img="#-Serious.png">Listen up, ~name~ -- don't ever let anything keep you down. Feel sorry for yourself for a bit, find your second wind, and keep on going.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_stripping">
            <case stage="7">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" />
                <state img="#-Cringe.png">C'mon, man, we're trying to masturbate here...!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" />
                <state img="#-Shocked.png" oneShotId="72">Dude, what the &lt;i&gt;fuck&lt;/i&gt;?!</state>
                <state img="#-Surprised.png" oneShotId="73">Jesus, and I thought I'd seen it all...!</state>
                <state img="#-Annoyed.png">What the &lt;i&gt;Hell&lt;/i&gt; do you think you're doing, asshole?!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png" oneShotId="79">Man... Alright. Just don't get anything on me, yeah?</state>
                <state img="#-Ugh.png" oneShotId="80">Yeah, yeah, don't cream your pants before you even start.</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png" oneShotId="81">This is pretty goddamn weird, but I guess I did sign up for it.</state>
                <state img="#-Confused.png" oneShotId="82">Damn, already? I'm not even that good at poker.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-6 8">
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png" oneShotId="143">S-So you're really gonna... Well, don't let me stop you...</state>
                <state img="#-Confused.png" oneShotId="144">Man. Did &lt;i&gt;not&lt;/i&gt; think there'd be a part of me that was waiting for this tonight.</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="145">I-I don't care if you look, really. Hell, just go for it.</state>
                <state img="#-Flirt.png" oneShotId="146">Not too late to leave, man, but... honestly, I don't want you to.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="231">About time, dude...</state>
                <state img="#-Interested.png" oneShotId="232">Floor's nice and clean, so get on down here.</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png" oneShotId="233">Never masturbated to another guy before... First time for you too?</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png" oneShotId="234">Guess we should both give it our best...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-Cringe.png" oneShotId="151">Just... make it snappy.</state>
                <state img="#-Ugh.png" oneShotId="152">Nothing against you, man, it's just not my thing.</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png" oneShotId="153">No use holding back any more.</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png" oneShotId="154">I'm really just thinking about how much you suck at poker.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-6 8">
                <state img="#-Thinking.png" oneShotId="162">I've never even thought about guys like this, so... good time to practice flirting...?</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="161">I know this is a quick turnaround, but... Hey, if I like dudes, more fish in the sea for me, right?</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png" oneShotId="160">I'm no good at studying, but I'll try to pay attention if ~name~ shows us how it's done.</state>
                <state img="#-Confused.png" oneShotId="159">My dick feels all weird... Even weirder than the rest of me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png" oneShotId="247">Alright, let's do this...</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png" oneShotId="248">Now &lt;i&gt;this&lt;/i&gt; is a circle jerk...</state>
                <state img="#-Interested.png" oneShotId="249">You scratch my back, I scratch yours?</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="250">No problems over here...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-Ugh.png">It's nothing all that special...</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png">I mean... You do you, man. Literally.</state>
                <state img="#-Cringe.png">...Yeah, this is weird.</state>
                <state img="#-Confused.png">Probably a good thing that Robin didn't show up.</state>
                <state img="#-Tired.png">...You finished yet?</state>
                <state img="#-Ugh.png">Talk about rockin' out with your cock out...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-6 8">
                <state img="#-Thinking.png">...Well, at least the pool of people I can hit on is getting bigger...</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png">Shit, man... You're way more eager than I've ever been.</state>
                <state img="#-Confused.png">Hey, how do you decide who's on top between guys...?</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png">Sometimes you get your dick sucked, sometimes you're the one suckin' dick. That's life.</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png">Ah, Jesus... Fine, I'm getting turned on. You happy?</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">That look on your face... Fuck, I hate that that's hot...</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png">Deep breaths, man. You, uh, look like you could use 'em.</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png">I almost wanna... No, no, don't make it weird...</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png">How am I more into dudes than at least one girl I know...?</state>
                <state img="#-Flirt.png">I've never kissed a guy before... First time for everything?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png">Fuck, am I leaking...?</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png">Am I pent up, or... is it because of ~name~...?</state>
                <state img="#-Interested.png">First time in my life I've ever &lt;i&gt;wanted&lt;/i&gt; to suck a dick...</state>
                <state img="#-Interested.png">Shit, man... That's hot...</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">&lt;i&gt;Fuck&lt;/i&gt;...</state>
                <state img="#-Confused.png">I'm feelin' so damn weird right now... But so damn &lt;i&gt;good&lt;/i&gt;...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-Cringe.png" oneShotId="87">Away from the hair, man, away from the hair!</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png" oneShotId="88">That... wasn't 'cause of me, right...?</state>
                <state img="#-Serious.png" oneShotId="89">You're gonna clean that up, right?</state>
                <state img="#-Ugh.png" oneShotId="90">Feel bad for the janitor that's gotta wipe that up.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-6 8">
                <state img="#-Confused.png" oneShotId="115">Did you just turn me gay? No, wait, I still like girls. Phew.</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png" oneShotId="116">Shit... A-Almost wish I coulda joined you...</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png" oneShotId="117">Never seen another guy finish before. Honestly? Kinda like it...</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png" oneShotId="118">Look, I'm not gonna say anything weird about licking it up, but... Shit, now I'm thinking about it...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png" oneShotId="131">Fuck... &lt;i&gt;Why&lt;/i&gt; is that so hot...?</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png" oneShotId="132">I'm getting there too...</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="133">Beat me to it, huh... Well, I'm closing in...</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png" oneShotId="134">Not waiting for me? Then I'll just have to pick up the pace...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="3-6 8">
                <state img="#-Horny.png" oneShotId="163">Don't get me all excited &lt;i&gt;now&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png" oneShotId="164">Tell me you haven't been waiting for this too, guys.</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="165">Starting to see why those kids love games so much.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png" oneShotId="166">And I already thought I've been as hard as I can get...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-Flirt.png" oneShotId="179">Hey, now... Trying to seduce me before I'm even showing off my boxers?</state>
                <state img="#-Interested.png" oneShotId="180">Nothing wrong with a girl who's a little eager.</state>
                <state img="#-Confident.png" oneShotId="181">Come to papa Steve!</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png" oneShotId="182">Oh, shit, you're already out? Almost feel bad.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="171">Hell yeah...</state>
                <state img="#-Interested.png" oneShotId="172">Finally, something good...</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="173">Hope it's as good for you as it is for me...</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png" oneShotId="174">Tell me again why we aren't just all over each other...?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-Thinking.png" oneShotId="187">I'm gonna enjoy this, but man, wish I could be more direct about it.</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="188">Wish I had more to show you, but hopefully this'll do.</state>
                <state img="#-Ugh.png" oneShotId="189">Man, and I still gotta play this game? I just wanna watch ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-Flirt.png" oneShotId="190">See, I can still get girls to drop their panties for me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-6 8">
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="198">Time to kick back and enjoy, right?</state>
                <state img="#-Showoff.png" oneShotId="197">Feel free to stare, ladies. Totally free of charge.</state>
                <state img="#-Flirt.png" oneShotId="196">Feel like I'm gonna have to come back for another round.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png" oneShotId="195">Robin would get a kick out of this. I know I am.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-Horny.png">I've kept this spot nice and warm for you... Just saying.</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png">Weird way to do this, but I ain't complaining...</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png">Masturbatin' with random girls... Good way to spend a ~weekday~...</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">You're joining me? Too kind, ~name~, too kind.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png">Goddamn it, now I'm all pent up...</state>
                <state img="#-Confused.png">Don't make me &lt;i&gt;want&lt;/i&gt; to lose now!</state>
                <state img="#-Showoff.png">I know I'm not much to stare at right now, but...</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">And I didn't even have to buy you dinner first.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">I bet my fingers could treat you better.</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png">Never seen a girl do this before...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-6 8">
                <state img="#-Horny.png">I could treat you to a movie. And we can make out during the boring parts.</state>
                <state img="#-Showoff.png">I'll have you know, I'm a killer. A &lt;i&gt;lady&lt;/i&gt; killer.</state>
                <state img="#-Flirt.png">I'm not that high school heartthrob anymore, but I know how to a treat a girl to a good time.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">Damn... Is it always this wet, or is that because of me?</state>
                <state img="#-Flirt.png">Are you this good cause you're lonely? I can fix that.</state>
                <state img="#-Ugh.png">Wish I could join you. Instead I'm just hanging around like an asshole.</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">I'm used to getting stares. How 'bout you, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">Damn, this place is awesome.</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png">Does this count as a first date?</state>
                <state img="#-Tired.png">I'd offer to take you back to my place, but... You don't wanna see my crappy apartment.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-Horny.png">Nice...</state>
                <state img="#-Flirt.png">The noises ~name~ is making... Damn, that's hot...</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">You know how to make this easier, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">Fuck, my dick...</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">Y'know... I'm pretty good with my tongue...</state>
                <state img="#-Flirt.png">Wish it was my fingers instead?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-Flirt.png" oneShotId="207">Real nice. Just hope you can wait a little longer next time.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png" oneShotId="208">It's a good thing these pants are so tight.</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png" oneShotId="209">Jesus... And I haven't even gotten out of my pants yet.</state>
                <state img="#-Smug.png" oneShotId="210">Think this is the most fun I can have without taking my dick out.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-6 8">
                <state img="#-Flirt.png">I help you out with that at all?</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">See? Ladies still love me.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">Would it have helped at all if I was tugging my dick?</state>
                <state img="#-Flirt.png">Feels like a waste to spill it all like that, if you ask me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-Horny.png">Well, that's a help...</state>
                <state img="#-Flirt.png">Nice, ~name~... &lt;i&gt;Really&lt;/i&gt; nice.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">Only wish I coulda helped you...</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">I'm gettin' there too...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate_first">
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-Surprised.png">Wha... Damn it, really? Give a guy a break already!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate">
            <case stage="6">
                <condition count="-1" status="alive" role="opp" />
                <state img="#-Horny.png">I mean, c'mon... After everything we've seen, do you &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; wanna be the guy to win right now?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-Horny.png">Well, I was gonna have to get this thing down one way or another, right?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="start_masturbating">
            <case stage="6">
                <condition count="0" gender="female" />
                <state img="#-Starting.png">...Look, this is weird for me. I've never really done anything like this with other guys, but... might not be as hard as I expected...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-Starting.png">Keep your eyes on the prize, alright? I know that's what &lt;i&gt;I'll&lt;/i&gt; be doing.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="masturbating">
            <case stage="7" priority="0">
                <condition gender="male" role="other" character="human" />
                <test expr="~human.tag.straight~" value="false" />
                <state img="#-Confused.png" oneShotId="631">What a weird-ass way to find out I like guys...</state>
                <state img="#-Upset.png" oneShotId="632">I blame ~player~ for all this... Stupid sexy bastard...</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png" oneShotId="633">Now I'm gonna be thinking about dicks all day...</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="634">Thought I was a basketball guy, but now I'm swinging for the other team...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-Thinking.png">Ah, fuck, Nance... You always know how to treat me...</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">At this rate... don't even gotta worry about my hand getting tired...</state>
                <state img="#-Smug.png">And &lt;i&gt;this&lt;/i&gt; is the reason the girls in Hawkins High were all over me.</state>
                <state img="#-Confused.png">Never been that good with my hands... Always preferred someone else's...</state>
                <state img="#-Upset.png">Man... I gotta get laid...</state>
                <state img="#-Showoff.png">Kinda nice to have some eyes on you, huh...?</state>
                <state img="#-Ugh.png">Ah, shit... Shoulda brought a napkin...</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">Thinkin' about girls is nice, but... I've got plenty of eye candy right here...</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png">What guy &lt;i&gt;doesn't&lt;/i&gt; have a magazine under his bed, huh...?</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png">Don't worry. I got plenty of stamina...</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png">Damn, it's been too long...</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Like what you see?</state>
                <state img="#-Confident.png">It's alright, you can stare. I dig the attention.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="heavy_masturbating">
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-Thinking.png">Ugh, damn... N-Nance... &lt;i&gt;Fuck&lt;/i&gt;...</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png">Jesus... I-I can already feel it...</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">&lt;i&gt;Hah...&lt;/i&gt; C'mon...</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png">I've just gotta... A little more...</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png">I-I'm gonna...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finishing_masturbating">
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-Finishing.png">&lt;i&gt;Nn... Ah, fuck...!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Damn... Gotta catch my breath after that. Didn't know this was such a good way to get your rocks off.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="after_masturbating">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-Upset.png">I should hit up Nance... J-Just to see how she's doing, alright?</state>
                <state img="#-Confused.png">I never liked going at it when I'm alone that much, really. Guess it's a good thing I'm not alone here...</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png">Glad the ~background.surface~ is clean. I thought it'd be all sticky with... y'know.</state>
                <state img="#-Confused.png">Hey, how's my hair look?</state>
                <state img="#-Tired.png">Wish I could say I had a date after this. Wouldn't be here if that was true.</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png">I keep seeing the dude from Evil Dead in my dreams. Hope he doesn't awaken something in me.</state>
                <state img="#-Tired.png">I get enough of standing around at my job. Nice to take a seat now and then.</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">So, who here wants to be the lucky one to join me to the next Hawkins basketball team match?</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">Now, see, if I knew about this place a couple years back, senior biology woulda been way easier.</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Here's a free tip for ya; girls love nothing more than a guy that makes them laugh.</state>
                <state img="#-Smug.png">Honestly, I think I got the sweetest deal right now. I can just sit down and look at boobs.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_victory">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-Upset.png">...What? Man, the &lt;i&gt;one&lt;/i&gt; time I actually win something!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-6">
                <state img="#-Smug.png">Too distracted by the muscles, huh? Guess you were no match for the Harrington style.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_defeat">
            <case stage="8">
                <condition count="2-" gender="male" role="opp" />
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png">Well, uh... Guess I learned something about myself today.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-Confident.png">Well, can't be too mad. Next time, though? You'll see just how much ass I can kick.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

    </behaviour>
</opponent>
