<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<metadata>
    <owner>revy</owner>
    <noteworthy>
        <case name="Meia Fight" min="7" max="7">
            <description>Revy gets into a nude fistfight with Meia.</description>
            <trigger tag="stripped" alsoPlaying="meia" alsoPlayingStage="5" priority="161">
                <state img="meiablank.png"></state>
            </trigger>
        </case>
        <case name="Jura Grope" min="7" max="7">
            <description>Revy forcibly inspects Jura's breasts for fakeness by groping them.</description>
            <trigger tag="female_crotch_is_visible" target="jura" targetStage="" targetSaidMarker="revy_grope">
                <state img="meiablank.png"></state>
            </trigger>
        </case>
        <case name="Female Player Focus" id="1" min="7" max="7">
            <description>Revy starts dirty-talking the female player....whether she likes it or not.</description>
        </case>
        <case name="Male Player Focus" id="2" min="7" max="7">
            <description>Revy starts dirty-talking the male player....whether he likes it or not.</description>
        </case>
    </noteworthy>
    <hidden />
    <responses />
    <notes />
    <nextId>2</nextId>
    <markers>
        <marker scope="Public" name="businessway">Revy tells HK416 they can do things the business way or the hard way.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="butt">Revy will show her butt upon stripping, provided there's no targeted responses.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="female">Revy addresses the female player the first time she strips.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="femplayerfinish">Revy sees that the female player has finished.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="femplayerfuck">Revy pays special attention to the female player in her dirty-talk.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="femplayerloss">Revy sees that the female player must masturbate.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="friends">"What, you think I don't have friends?  I got my whore friend Eda, I got Dutch, who signs my checks--maybe I'll melt &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; into glue."</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="futaba_jura_real">Revy tells Futaba that Jura's breasts are real.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="hands">"Ah Christ, the horse is one of those fuckin' Jesus Freaks who wants everyone to hold hands.  Remind me to melt &lt;i&gt;her&lt;/i&gt; later."</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="ini_short">Revy thinks she can come up with something better to insult than the male player's height, which Ini suggests.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="male">Revy addresses the male player the first time he strips.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="maleplayerfinish">Revy sees that the male player has finished.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="maleplayerfuck">Revy pays special attention to the male player in her dirty-talk.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="maleplayerloss">Revy sees that the male player must masturbate.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="music">Revy asks the table what kind of music they like.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="nag1">Revy chastizes Nagisa for doubting herself.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="rotten">"Bitch, I got plenty of friends, and they're all as rotten as I am.  Why don't I just melt your face with a heated barrel?"</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="secretariat">"And &lt;i&gt;I&lt;/i&gt; bet I could melt you down into glue, Secretariat."</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="showdown">Revy sees that the game is down to her and one other player.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="stance">Revy still holds a fighting stance after punching Meia.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="twilight_yukio">Revy tells Twilight that Yukio wasn't worth her sympathy.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="wiismoke">Revy doesn't care about Trainer's warning that smoking will make her breasts sag.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="yukio_suicide">Revy mentions that the last schoolgirl she saved killed herself.</marker>
    </markers>
</metadata>
