<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<collectibles>
    <collectible id="band_shirt" img="opponents/critical_darling/x_collectable_band_shirt.png" thumbnail="opponents/critical_darling/x_collectable_band_shirt.png">
        <title>Melting Dreamscape T-shirt</title>
        <subtitle>I thought she said she didn't have any...?</subtitle>
        <text>She literally can't afford to give you another, so be sure to take good care of it, wash with like colors, cold water, tumble dry low.</text>
        <unlock>Play a match against Critical Darling (you don't have to win).</unlock>
        <hide-details>true</hide-details>
        <wearable>true</wearable>
        <clothing name="shirt" generic="shirt" position="upper" type="major" />
    </collectible>
    <collectible id="sexy_photo" status="online" img="opponents/critical_darling/x_collectible_photo.png" thumbnail="opponents/critical_darling/x_collectible_photo.png">
        <title>A Sexy Picture Of A Guitar</title>
        <subtitle>Oh, and Ibuki's there too.</subtitle>
        <text>A picture of Ibuki with her guitar, a Dean Flying V. This is the guitar her ice guitar, "Icy Dean," is based on. She saved up for quite a while to buy it. There were cheaper guitars available, but she really wanted a Flying V and Dean was the only maker she could find that builds them for left-handed guitarists.</text>
        <unlock>Win a match against Critical Darling.</unlock>
        <hide-details>true</hide-details>
    </collectible>
    <collectible id="band_photo" status="online" img="opponents/critical_darling/x_collectable_bandmates.png" thumbnail="opponents/critical_darling/x_collectable_bandmates.png">
        <title>A Photo Of Melting Dreamscape</title>
        <subtitle>The REAL Melting Dreamscape, not those proxies from before.</subtitle>
        <text>Ibuki and her bandmates, Charlotte (top left), Kara (top right), and Emily (bottom right), posing for a publicity photo. Ibuki met them when Charlotte found her in a music store trying to play northpaw guitars southpaw. She taught her the differences between differently-handed guitars, and later introduced her to Kara and Emily. Charlotte and Kara shared a music theory class in college, and they met Emily when she signed up for bass lessons from Charlotte.</text>
        <unlock>Play a game with Critical Darling's preset table, "Meling Dreamscap."</unlock>
        <hide-details>true</hide-details>
    </collectible>
    <collectible id="dragon_grandpa" img="opponents/critical_darling/x_collectable_dragongrandpa.png" thumbnail="opponents/critical_darling/x_collectable_dragongrandpa.png">
        <title>Dragon Grandpa</title>
        <subtitle>At least it's not a bear...</subtitle>
        <text>A weird plushie that randomly appeared one day. Ibuki is fairly convinced that it has some kind of monster hiding inside or will otherwise lead to her death, so she asked you to take it. "My breathin' feels funky just lookin' at it," she said. You know very well that it's just a normal, albeit lame, plushie and that her fear is completely irrational.</text>
        <unlock>Play Critical Darling with any three Danganronpa opponents.</unlock>
        <hide-details>true</hide-details>
    </collectible>
    <collectible id="doodle" img="opponents/critical_darling/x_collectable_doodle.png" thumbnail="opponents/critical_darling/x_collectable_doodle.png">
        <title>The Doodle That Started It All</title>
        <subtitle>Thanks for sticking with her!</subtitle>
        <text>BlueKoin here, pardon the fourth wall break. This is a scan of the doodle that brought Critical Darling to life. Yes I know it's all fuzzy and stuff, I draw real small... I got the idea to make a bunch of super-powered wrestlers, and since I had discovered my love for Ibuki Mioda around this time, I couldn't help but make one based on her (with some Judy Nails and Yumi Yoshimura mixed into the design too). I gave her ice powers, playing off of how one interpretation of the name "Ibuki" I found was "Ice breath," and to prevent her from being restricted to her rocker theme for attacks and special moves. I had so much fun building up her backstory that she snowballed into a SPNatI project, and even took over as the protagonist of the wrestling story I was originally working on.</text>
        <unlock>Play a game with Critical Darling after unlock all of her other collectibles.</unlock>
        <hide-details>true</hide-details>
    </collectible>
</collectibles>
