<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<metadata>
    <owner>guzma</owner>
    <noteworthy>
        <case name="Most Humiliating Moment" id="13" priority="Noteworthy" min="0" max="8">
            <description>Prompts other characters to tell of their most embarrassing/humiliating moments.</description>
        </case>
    </noteworthy>
    <hidden />
    <responses>
        <response id="1" opponent="revy" opponentId="4" />
        <response id="2" opponent="revy" opponentId="3" />
        <response id="3" opponent="aimee" opponentId="1" />
        <response id="4" opponent="aimee" opponentId="2" />
        <response id="8" opponent="navi" opponentId="2" />
        <response id="9" opponent="navi" opponentId="3" />
        <response id="14" opponent="emi" opponentId="5" />
        <response id="15" opponent="florina" opponentId="8" />
        <response id="16" opponent="catria" opponentId="5" />
        <response id="17" opponent="shimakaze" opponentId="5" />
        <response id="18" opponent="aella" opponentId="1" />
        <response id="19" opponent="chihiro" opponentId="181" />
        <response id="21" opponent="chihiro" opponentId="2" />
        <response id="22" opponent="chihiro" opponentId="1" />
        <response id="23" opponent="chihiro" opponentId="213" />
    </responses>
    <notes />
    <labels />
    <prefixes />
    <nextId>26</nextId>
    <markers>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Acerola">Referenced when playing with a princess. Acerola is a supposed descendant of royalty who is always seen wearing rags.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="AetherSlip">Guzma nearly reveals his connection to the Aether Foundation.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Chazz_RichPeople">Guzma brings up how annoying rich people are.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="chazztoy">Guzma calls Chazz's duel disk a toy</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Chihiro_awkward">Guzma suggests that Chihiro surrenders due to how awkward he is already.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Chihiro_callout">Guzma calls Chihiro out for muttering while Guzma was taking off his bracelets.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Chihiro_computer">Guzma questions why th computer is getting cards.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Chihiro_kid">Guzma calls Chihiro a kid.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Chihiro_nerd">Guzma asks why Chihiro's even playing if he's so awkward and calls him a nerd.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Chihiro_return">Guzma comments on Chihiro's return.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Chihiro_reveal">Guzma comments on Chihiro's gender reveal.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Chihiro_ribbon">Guzma points out how Chihiro seems uncomfortable taking off even just the ribbon.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Chihiro_stripping">Guzma is impatient during Chihiro's final stripping phase.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Chihiro_why">Guzma asks why Chihiro dressed up like a girl.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="DarkGymLeader">It took us 8 generations to get a Dark type gym.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Ditto">Mentioned when playing with Navi. Ditto is a Pokemon that can shapeshift into anything.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Elesa_Leak">Guzma threatens to leak Elesa's presence at the game to the public.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Elesa_Rip">Guzma threatens to rip off Elesa's clothes if she isn't quick to remove them.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Elesa_Start">Guzma's hatred of popular trainers is revealed.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Elesa_Threat">Guzma threatens to make Elesa regreat coming to the game.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Elio">The male player character of Generation 7. Mentioned when the player is male and is stripping.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="forest">The background is the spooky forest.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Gladion">Mentioned when playing with Ryuko. Gladion is the rebelious son of the Aether Foundation president.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Guzma_SkullSpeech" />
        <marker scope="Public" name="Guzma_SkullSpeech2" />
        <marker scope="Public" name="Ilimia">Referenced when playing with a school uniform character. Ilima is a school student and a Normal-Type trial captain.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Kahili">Referenced when playing with Pit. Kahili is a Flying-type trainer and golfer. Her hair also gives the appearance of wings.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="KevinDurant1">One of Guzma's lines based on a Kevin Durant tweet. Only appears when playing with Haru.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="KevinDurant2">Another one of Guzma's lines based on a Kevin Durant tweet. Only appears when playing with Haru.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Kiawe">Mentioned when playing with Rinkah. Kiawe is a Fire-type Trial captain who's always shirtless.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="kids">The game's got lots of kids in it.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="LiteratureClub" />
        <marker scope="Public" name="Megu_BoobBully">Guzma bullies megumin because she's smol and childlike.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Mimikyu">Just Google this one.....</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="MostHumiliatingMoment">Prompt Marker that ecourages other characters to share embarrassing/humiliating moments.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Nanu">Mentioned or referenced when playing with a gloomy character. Nanu is an exteremly apathetic cop.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Natsu_BoobBully">Bullying Natsuki because her tits are tiny.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Natsu_BoobBully1">Bullying Natsuki because her boobs aren't big.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Natsu_BoobBully2">Bullying Natsuki because her mammaries are miniture.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Natsu_Bully1">Bullying Natsuki because her stature is smol.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="NatsuIsAKid">Bullying Natsuki because she looks like a child.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Olivia">Referenced when playing with a scantily clad character. Olivia is a model and a Rock-type Island Kahuna.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Pit_OutfitBully1">Bullying Pit because his clothes are crappy.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Pit_OutfitBully2">Bullying Pit because what he wears is weird.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Pit_OutfitBully3">Bullying Pit because we can.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="PitIsAKid">Bullying Pit because he acts like a kid.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Plumeria">Mentioned when playing with a stoic girl. Plumeria is a high-ranking member of Team Skull.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Pokedex">Mentioned when playing with Kizuna or Navi. The in-universe Pokemon Encylopedia.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Ryuji_Invite">Guzma invites Ryuji to join Team Skull, if he can impress him.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Ryuki">Referenced when playing with a musician. Ryuki is a Dragon-type trainer and rockstar.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="ryuko_lashout">Guzma responds angrily to Ryuko's comment about him dying his hair.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Wicke">Referenced when playing with a nerdy character. Wicke is a thicc scientist lady from the Aether Foundation who has mostly pink highlights.</marker>
    </markers>
</metadata>
