<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>

<!--This file was machine generated using the Character Editor v6.5.1 at 3:48:14 PM on May 08, 2021. Do not edit this file directly unless you know what you're doing.-->
<opponent>
    <version>v6.5.1</version>
    <first>Wikipe-tan</first>
    <last />
    <label>Wikipe-tan</label>
    <gender>female</gender>
    <size>medium</size>
    <timer>15</timer>
    <intelligence>average</intelligence>

    <tags>
        <tag>blue_hair</tag>
        <tag>exotic_hair</tag>
        <tag>long_hair</tag>
        <tag>blue_eyes</tag>
        <tag>fair-skinned</tag>
        <tag>trimmed</tag>
        <tag>pubic_hair</tag>
        <tag>medium_breasts</tag>
        <tag from="0" to="3">thigh_highs</tag>
        <tag>cheerful</tag>
        <tag>confident</tag>
        <tag>ditzy</tag>
        <tag>moe</tag>
        <tag>nerdy</tag>
        <tag>smart</tag>
        <tag>bisexual</tag>
        <tag>japanese</tag>
        <tag>internet_meme</tag>
        <tag>website</tag>
    </tags>
    <stylesheet>styles.css</stylesheet>


    <wardrobe>
        <clothing name="swimsuit" generic="swimsuit" position="lower" type="important" />
        <clothing name="swimsuit top" generic="swimsuit top" position="upper" type="important" />
        <clothing name="stockings" generic="socks" position="legs" type="minor" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="dress" generic="shirt" position="both" type="major" />
        <clothing name="apron" position="lower" type="extra" />
        <clothing name="shoes" generic="shoes" position="feet" type="minor" plural="true" />
    </wardrobe>


    <behaviour>
        <persistent-markers>
            <marker>FinishedGame</marker>
            <marker>Finishedgame</marker>
            <marker>WonFirstGame</marker>
        </persistent-markers>
        <trigger id="selected">
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~background~" value="inventory" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">Is this The Inventory? It seems like my articles on it are a bit outdated. Time for a dive into the source!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Telltale's The Inventory seems to have changed a bit... Which means that I need to update my articles! Time for a first-person dive into the source!</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png">Oh, so the article on The Inventory wasn't vandalized. It &lt;i&gt;is&lt;/i&gt; a strip poker club now! Those articles need to be updated, and I am here for it!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="130">
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~player~" value="DrCoomer" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~player~" value="Dr. Harold Pontiff Coomer" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~player~" value="Doctor Coomer" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~player~" value="DoctorCoomer" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~player~" value="Dr. Coomer" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~player~" value="Dr Coomer" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~player~" value="hollow_tones" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~player~" value="hollow tones" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~player~" value="hollowtones" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~player~" value="Dr.HaroldPontiffCoomer" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~player~" value="DrHaroldPontiffCoomer" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-excited.png">Hello, Doctor! It's so nice to see you here! Ready to continue with our illegal experiments for Black Mesa?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="131">
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~player~" value="Gordon" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~player~" value="GordonFreeman" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~player~" value="FreemanGordon" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~player~" value="WayneRadioTV" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~player~" value="Gordon Freeman" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-wave.png">Hello, Gordon! I thought you died in &lt;i&gt;All Dogs Go to Heaven 2&lt;/i&gt;. Now, behave and do not say a word about our involvement with Black Mesa, or I {b}will kill you!{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~background~" value="tiki bar" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~background~" value="beach" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-flirt.png">Did you bring a proper swimsuit, ~player~? This beach seems like a great place for swimming.</state>
                <state img="#-casual.png">Me? No, I am perfectly comfortable in my current clothing. It matters not that we are at the beach, as long as we get to strip.</state>
                <state img="#-smirk.png">Are we gonna strip on the beach this game, ~player~? It is a bit curious to bring me specifically here, is it not?</state>
                <state img="#-smirk.png">Did you invite me to a strip poker game on the beach, ~player~? Something tells me that you are aware of my little surprise.</state>
                <state img="#-hornyfact.png">The sound of waves is so relaxing. I'm sure this will make for a better, more pleasant game...</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">I'm used to playing poker at the sea, but never strip poker! This will be exciting!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="132">
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~player~" value="Jimbo" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~player~" value="Jimmy Wales" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~player~" value="JimmyWales" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~player~" value="JimboWales" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~player~" value="Jimbo Wales" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">J-Jimbo! Fancy seeing you here... U-um, listen, I can explain... I just wanted some information, that's all!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="180">
                <test expr="~player~" value="Spaceman" />
                <state img="#-wave.png">Hello, Spaceman! I have many interesting facts on {b}space.{!reset} Would you care to be educated today?</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png">{small b}Spaceman{small} most commonly refers to: Astronaut or cosmonaut, a person trained to operate or serve aboard a spacecraft; alien or extraterrestrial, a life form not from Earth that travels aboard a spacecraft capable of interstellar travel; or in general someone who travels the universe.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="191">
                <test expr="~player~" value="Sonamy" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png">So how do you pronounce your name? Is it &lt;i&gt;sʌn eɪmi,&lt;/i&gt; or is it more like &lt;i&gt;sunɑmi,&lt;/i&gt; as in a tsunami?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="192">
                <test expr="~player~" value="Coolcat" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{b small}Cool Cat{small} may refer to: A &lt;i&gt;Looney Tunes&lt;/i&gt; character, a character from &lt;i&gt;Pee-wee's Playhouse,&lt;/i&gt; an episode of &lt;i&gt;Scrubs,&lt;/i&gt; or a song by Queen from the 1982 album &lt;i&gt;Hot Space&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-wave.png">Hello everyone! The name is Wikipe-tan, and I came here to study the Inventory's strip poker scene!</state>
                <state img="#-neutral.png">Welcome to another session of strip poker sponsored by the Inventory. My name is Wikipe-tan, and I will be your opponent this game.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_selected">
            <case stage="0" id="51">
                <condition role="target" character="galatea" />
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="1005">{smaller b}&lt;i&gt;Galatea&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} is an interactive fiction video game by Emily Short featuring a modern rendition of the Greek myth of Galatea, the sculpture of a woman which gained life. The game displays an unusual rich approach to non-player character dialogue and diverts from the typical puzzle-solving in interactive fiction: the whole gameplay is based on the interaction with a single character in a single room.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="kizuna" />
                <state img="#-z-stripping.png">{smaller b}Kizuna AI{smaller} is a Japanese virtual YouTuber (VTuber) currently part of Kizuna Ai Inc, a subsidiary of Activ8. As of 2020, she is the largest VTuber, with more than 4 million subscribers across three YouTube channels, an additional 1 million subscribers on Chinese video platform Bilibili and 2.8 million followers on TikTok, with over 10 million subscribers in total in social network platforms.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="komi-san" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{smaller b}&lt;i&gt;Komi Can't Communicate&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} &lt;i&gt;(Komi-san wa, Komyushō desu)&lt;/i&gt; is a Japanese manga series written and illustrated by Tomohito Oda. It has been serialized in Shogakukan's Weekly Shōnen Sunday since May 2016, with its chapters collected in twenty tankōbon volumes as of February 2021. The series has been licensed for English release in North America by Viz Media, with the first volume being published in June 2019.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="mae" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">{smaller b}&lt;i&gt;Night in the Woods&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} is a single-player adventure game. It was developed by Infinite Fall, a studio founded by game designer Alec Holowka and animator/artist Scott Benson, and published by Finji. It is a story-focused exploration game in which players control a young woman named Mae Borowski, who recently dropped out of college and has returned to her hometown to find unexpected changes.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="leggy" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{smaller b}Droopy{smaller} is an animated character from the golden age of American animation. He is an anthropomorphic dog with a droopy face, hence his name. He was created in 1943 by Tex Avery for theatrical cartoon shorts produced by the Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer cartoon studio. Essentially the polar opposite of Avery's other MGM character, the loud and wacky Screwy Squirrel, Droopy moves slowly and lethargically, speaks in a jowly monotone voice, and--though hardly an imposing character--is shrewd enough to outwit his enemies.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="mulan" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png">{small b}&lt;i&gt;Mulan&lt;/i&gt;{small} is a 1998 American animated musical adventure film produced by Walt Disney Feature Animation for Walt Disney Pictures. It is based on the Chinese legend of Hua Mulan and takes place in China during the Han dynasty, where Fa Mu--oh, you're undercover! Sorry, I'll stop!{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="batman_franchise" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{smaller b}Batman{smaller} is a superhero who appears in American comic books published by DC Comics. Batman was created by artist Bob Kane and writer Bill Finger, and debuted in the 27th issue of the comic book &lt;i&gt;Detective Comics&lt;/i&gt; on March 30, 1939. In the DC Universe continuity, Batman is the alias of Bruce Wayne, a wealthy American playboy, philanthropist, and owner of Wayne Enterprises based in Gotham City. Kane, Finger, and future DC writers accompanied Batman with supporting characters, including his sidekick Robin, allies Alfred Pennyworth and James Gordon, and foes such as Catwoman, the Scarecrow, the Penguin, and his archenemy, the Joker. The Batman franchise has become one of the highest-grossing media franchises of all time.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="cowboy_bebop" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{smaller b}&lt;i&gt;Cowboy Bebop&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} is a Japanese science fiction anime television series animated by Sunrise featuring a production team led by director Shinichirō Watanabe, screenwriter Keiko Nobumoto, character designer Toshihiro Kawamoto, mechanical designer Kimitoshi Yamane, and composer Yoko Kanno. The twenty-six episodes, also called "sessions," of the series are set in the year 2071, and follow the lives of a bounty hunter crew traveling in their spaceship called the &lt;i&gt;Bebop&lt;/i&gt;.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="dota" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{smaller b}&lt;i&gt;Dota 2&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} is a multiplayer online battle arena (MOBA) video game developed and published by Valve. The game is a sequel to &lt;i&gt;Defense of the Ancients (DotA),&lt;/i&gt; which was a community-created mod for Blizzard Entertainment's &lt;i&gt;Warcraft III: Reign of Chaos&lt;/i&gt; and its expansion pack, &lt;i&gt;The Frozen Throne&lt;/i&gt;. &lt;i&gt;Dota 2&lt;/i&gt; is played in matches between two teams of five players, with each team occupying and defending their own separate base on the map. Each of the ten players independently controls a powerful character, known as a "hero", who all have unique abilities and differing styles of play. During a match players collect experience points and items for their heroes to successfully defeat the opposing team's heroes in player versus player combat.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="fate" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{small b}&lt;i&gt;Fate/Apocrypha&lt;/i&gt;{small} is a Japanese light novel series in Type-Moon's &lt;i&gt;Fate&lt;/i&gt; franchise, written by Yūichirō Higashide and illustrated by Ototsugu Konoe. Type-Moon published five volumes from December 2012 to December 2014.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="equestria_girls" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{smaller b}My Little Pony: Equestria Girls,{smaller} or simply {smaller b}Equestria Girls,{smaller} is a product line of fashion dolls and media franchise launched in 2013 by American toy company Hasbro, as a spin-off of the 2010 relaunch of the My Little Pony franchise and its &lt;i&gt;Friendship Is Magic&lt;/i&gt; television series. Equestria Girls features anthropomorphized versions of My Little Pony characters from that period. It includes various doll lines, media tie-ins and licensed merchandises.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="teen_titans_franchise" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{smaller b}&lt;i&gt;Teen Titans&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} is an American animated superhero television series developed by Glen Murakami and Sam Register, based on DC Comics's superhero team of the same name. During its run, the series was nominated for three Annie Awards and one Motion Picture Sound Editors Award.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="harry_potter_franchise" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="964">{small b}&lt;i&gt;Harry Potter&lt;/i&gt;{small} is a series of seven fantasy novels written by British author, J. K. Rowling. The novels chronicle the lives of a young wizard, Harry Potter, and his friends Hermione Granger and Ron Weasley, all of whom are students at Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="undertale" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="983">{small b}&lt;i&gt;Undertale&lt;/i&gt;{small} is a 2D role-playing video game created by indie developer Toby Fox. It is notorious for being an RPG where the player can opt to pacify or subdue monsters in order to spare them instead of killing them.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="starcraft" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="985">{smaller b}&lt;i&gt;StarCraft&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} is a military science fiction media franchise created by Chris Metzen and James Phinney and owned by Blizzard Entertainment. The series centers on a galactic struggle for dominance among three species—the adaptable and mobile Terrans, the ever-evolving insectoid Zerg, the powerful and enigmatic Protoss—in a distant part of the Milky Way galaxy known as the Koprulu Sector.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="sonic_franchise" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="992">{small b}&lt;i&gt;Sonic the Hedgehog&lt;/i&gt;{small} is a Japanese video game series and media franchise created and owned by Sega in 1991. The franchise follows Sonic, an anthropomorphic blue hedgehog who battles the evil Doctor Eggman, a mad scientist.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="katawa_shoujo" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="995">{small b}&lt;i&gt;Katawa Shoujo&lt;/i&gt;{small} (translated as: "Cripple Girls" or "Disability Girls") is a bishoujo-style visual novel by Four Leaf Studios that tells the story of a young man and five young women living with varying disabilities.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="rwby_franchise" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="997">{small b}&lt;i&gt;RWBY&lt;/i&gt;{small} (pronounced "Ruby") is an American anime-influenced animated web series and media franchise created by Monty Oum. It is set in the world of Remnant, where young people train to become warriors to protect their world from monsters called Grimm.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="fire_emblem" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="999">{smaller b}&lt;i&gt;Fire Emblem&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} is a fantasy tactical role-playing game franchise developed by Intelligent Systems and published by Nintendo. First produced and published for the Famicom in 1990, the series currently consists of seventeen core entries and three spinoffs. Gameplay revolves around the tactical movement of characters across grid-based environments, while incorporating a story and characters similar to traditional role-playing video games.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="pokemon" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="1001">{smaller b}&lt;i&gt;Pokémon,&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} also known as {smaller b}Pocket Monsters{smaller} in Japan, is a Japanese media franchise managed by The Pokémon Company, a company founded by Nintendo, Game Freak, and Creatures. The franchise was created by Satoshi Tajiri in 1995, and is centered on fictional creatures called "Pokémon", which humans, known as Pokémon Trainers, catch and train to battle each other for sport.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="huniepop" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="1003">{small b}&lt;i&gt;HuniePop&lt;/i&gt;{small} is a tile-matching and dating sim adult video game created by American game designer Ryan Koons, under the alias of HuniePot. The game follows the dating adventures of the main character as they try to woo several different women in their hometown.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="street_fighter" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="1008">{smaller b}&lt;i&gt;Street Fighter&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} is a Japanese fighting video game franchise first developed and published by Capcom in 1987. It is one of the highest-grossing video game franchises of all time and serves as one of Capcom's flagship series, as well as the highest-grossing media franchise of all time based on a fighting game.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="little_witch_academia" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="1010">{small b}&lt;i&gt;Little Witch Academia&lt;/i&gt;{small} is a Japanese anime franchise created by Yoh Yoshinari and produced by Trigger. It's story takes place at Luna Nova Magical Academy, a prestigious school for young girls training to become witches.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="miraculous" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="1012">{smaller b}&lt;i&gt;Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} is a French-Italian-Japanese-South Korean computer-animated superhero television series. The series focuses on two Parisian teenagers, Marinette Dupain-Cheng and Adrien Agreste, who transform into the superheroes Ladybug and Cat Noir, respectively, to protect the city from supervillains.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="ddlc" role="target" />
                <state img="#-z-stripping.png" oneShotId="1014">{smaller b}&lt;i&gt;Doki Doki Literature Club!&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} is a 2017 American freeware visual novel developed by Team Salvato. The story is told from the perspective of a male high school student who joins the school's literature club in an attempt to woo one of its four female members. Although this game initially appears to be a lighthearted dating simulator, it is in fact a{!reset} [̛R̨̕E͢D̶҉̡ÁC̛͝T̵̛̀E͡D̸̡͢]̵̧͝ {smaller}[citation needed]{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="league_of_legends" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="1017">{smaller b}&lt;i&gt;League of Legends&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} is a 2009 multiplayer online battle arena video game developed and published by Riot Games, a subsidiary of Chinese conglomerate Tencent. Inspired by &lt;i&gt;Defense of the Ancients&lt;/i&gt;, a custom map for &lt;i&gt;Warcraft III&lt;/i&gt;, the game has been free-to-play and is monetized through purchasable character customization since its release.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="overwatch_franchise" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="1062">{smaller b}&lt;i&gt;Overwatch&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} is a 2016 team-based multiplayer first-person shooter developed and published by Blizzard Entertainment. Described as a "hero shooter", &lt;i&gt;Overwatch&lt;/i&gt; assigns players into two teams of six, with each player selecting from a large roster of characters, known as "heroes", with unique abilities.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="brawl_stars" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="1065">{small b}&lt;i&gt;Brawl Stars&lt;/i&gt;{small} is a freemium mobile video game developed and published by the Finnish video game company Supercell. Released worldwide on December 12, 2018, the game features various game modes, which can be completed with a selection of Brawlers that can be controlled with on-screen joysticks.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="konosuba" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="1067">{smaller b}&lt;i&gt;KonoSuba: God's Blessing on this Wonderful World!&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} is a Japanese light novel series written by Natsume Akatsuki. The series follows Kazuma Satou, a boy who is sent to a fantasy world with MMORPG elements following his death, where he forms a dysfunctional party with a goddess, an archwizard, and a crusader.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="star_trek" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{smaller b}&lt;i&gt;Star Trek&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} is an American science fiction media franchise originating from the 1960s television series &lt;i&gt;Star Trek&lt;/i&gt;, created by Gene Roddenberry. That series, now often known as &lt;i&gt;"The Original Series,"&lt;/i&gt; debuted in 1966, and aired for three seasons on NBC. It followed the voyages of the starship USS &lt;i&gt;Enterprise&lt;/i&gt;, a space exploration vessel built by the United Federation of Planets in the 23rd century, on a mission "to explore strange new worlds, to seek out new life and new civilizations, to boldly go where no man has gone before."{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="marvel" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{smaller b}Marvel Comics{smaller} is the brand name and primary imprint of {smaller b}Marvel Worldwide Inc.,{smaller} a publisher of American comic books and related media. In 2009, The Walt Disney Company acquired Marvel Entertainment, Marvel Worldwide's parent company. Marvel was started in 1939 by Martin Goodman under a number of corporations and imprints but now known as Timely Comics, and by 1951 had generally become known as Atlas Comics. The Marvel era began in 1961, the year that the company launched &lt;i&gt;The Fantastic Four&lt;/i&gt; and other superhero titles created by Stan Lee, Jack Kirby, Steve Ditko and many others.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="zombieland_saga" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{smaller b}&lt;i&gt;Zombie Land Saga&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} is an anime television series produced by MAPPA, Avex Pictures and Cygames. The series aired in Japan between October and December 2018. A second season titled &lt;i&gt;Zombie Land Saga Revenge&lt;/i&gt; premiered on April 8, 2021. Not to be confused with the 2009 horror-comedy film, &lt;i&gt;Zombieland.&lt;/i&gt;{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="hazbin_hotel" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{smaller b}&lt;i&gt;Hazbin Hotel&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} is an American adult animated musical comedy web series created, directed, written and produced by Vivienne "VivziePop" Medrano. It is made entirely by freelance animators and is largely financed by Medrano's Patreon followers. The official pilot was released on YouTube on October 28, 2019. The series follows Charlie Magne, the princess of Hell, charismatic demon, and heir to the throne, as she sets about fulfilling her seemingly impossible dream of opening up a hotel called the "Happy Hotel" which aims to rehabilitate sinners.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="friday_the_13th" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{smaller b}&lt;i&gt;Friday the 13th&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} is an American horror franchise that comprises twelve slasher films, a television series, novels, comic books, video games, and tie‑in merchandise. The franchise mainly focuses on the fictional character Jason Voorhees, who was thought to have drowned as a boy at Camp Crystal Lake due to the negligence of the camp staff. Decades later, the lake is rumored to be "cursed" and is the setting for a series of mass murders. The films have grossed over $468 million at the box-office worldwide.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="friday_night_funkin" role="target" />
                <state img="#-z-stripping.png">{smaller b}&lt;i&gt;Friday Night Funkin'&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} is a free-to-play and open-source rhythm game. Developed by a team of four Newgrounds users, the game has a play style that is similar to &lt;i&gt;Dance Dance Revolution&lt;/i&gt; and &lt;i&gt;PaRappa the Rapper,&lt;/i&gt; and with an aesthetic reminiscent of Flash games popular in the early-to-mid 2000s. The game revolves around the player character, simply named "Boyfriend," who has to defeat an array of characters in singing and rapping contests for him to be able to date his love interest, "Girlfriend."{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="adventure_time" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{smallerbold}&lt;i&gt;Adventure Time&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} is an American fantasy animated television series created by Pendleton Ward for Cartoon Network. Produced by Ward, Adam Muto and Fred Seibert for Frederator Studios and Cartoon Network Studios, the series follows the adventures of a boy named Finn and his best friend and adoptive brother Jake, a dog with the magical power to change size and shape at will. Finn and Jake live in the post-apocalyptic Land of Ooo, where they interact with Princess Bubblegum, the Ice King, Marceline the Vampire Queen, BMO, and others.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="my_hero_academia" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{smaller b}&lt;i&gt;My Hero Academia&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} &lt;i&gt;(Boku no Hīrō Akademia)&lt;/i&gt; is a Japanese superhero manga series written and illustrated by Kōhei Horikoshi. The story follows Izuku Midoriya, a boy born without superpowers (called Quirks) in a world where they have become commonplace, but who still dreams of becoming a superhero himself. He is scouted by All Might, Japan's greatest hero, who chooses Midoriya as his successor and shares his Quirk with him after recognizing his potential, and later helps to enroll him in a prestigious high school for heroes in training.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="panty_and_stocking" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{smaller b}&lt;i&gt;Panty &amp; Stocking with Garterbelt&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} is a Japanese anime television series produced by Gainax, as well as a series of tie-in media developed around it. The show revolves around the exploits of the Anarchy sisters, Panty and Stocking, angels who were kicked out of Heaven due to their bad behavior. They are sent to Daten City--a pun on the Japanese word &lt;i&gt;datenshi&lt;/i&gt; ("fallen angel")--a place on the border between Heaven and Hell, which is besieged by evil spirits referred to as "Ghosts." The sisters take refuge under the care of the reverend Garterbelt; under his watchful eyes, the sisters are tasked with using their ability to transform their lingerie into weapons, and using them to destroy malicious Ghosts.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="scooby_doo" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{smaller b}&lt;i&gt;Scooby-Doo&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} is an American animated franchise comprising many animated television series produced from 1969 to the present, as well as their derivative media. Writers Joe Ruby and Ken Spears created the original series, &lt;i&gt;Scooby-Doo, Where Are You!&lt;/i&gt; for Hanna-Barbera Productions in 1969. This Saturday-morning cartoon series featured teenagers Fred Jones, Daphne Blake, Velma Dinkley, and Shaggy Rogers, and their talking Great Dane named Scooby-Doo, who solve mysteries involving supposedly supernatural creatures through a series of antics and missteps.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="monster_prom" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{smaller b}&lt;i&gt;Monster Prom&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} is a simulation role-playing visual novel game developed by Beautiful Glitch, a studio based in Barcelona and founded by Julián Quijano, and published by Those Awesome Guys. The game was released for Windows, macOS and Linux on 27 April 2018 and was distributed on Steam. A Nintendo Switch release was launched on 21 May 2020. Monster Prom was written by Julián Quijano, Cory O’Brien and Maggie Herskowitz, illustrated by Arthur Tien, and programmed by Elías Pereiras. Players assume the role of a student at Spooky High, a high school populated by monsters, as they attempt to find a date to prom.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="kim_possible_franchise" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{smaller b}&lt;i&gt;Kim Possible&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} is an American animated action comedy-adventure television series created by Bob Schooley and Mark McCorkle for Disney Channel. The title character is a teenage girl tasked with fighting crime on a regular basis while coping with everyday issues commonly associated with adolescence. Kim is aided by her clumsy best friend and eventual love interest, Ron Stoppable, his pet naked mole rat Rufus, and ten year-old computer genius Wade.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="13_sentinels" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{smaller b}&lt;i&gt;13 Sentinels: Aegis Rim&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} is a video game developed by Vanillaware and published by Atlus for the PlayStation 4. It was released in Japan in November 2019 and worldwide in September 2020. The game is divided between side-scrolling adventure segments and real-time strategy (RTS) battles, and follows thirteen high-school students in a fictionalized 1980s Japan who are dragged into a futuristic war between mechas and hostile Kaiju in a nonlinear narrative.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="sewayaki_kitsune_no_senko-san" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{smaller b}&lt;i&gt;The Helpful Fox Senko-san&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} &lt;i&gt;(Sewayaki Kitsune no Senko-san)&lt;/i&gt; is a Japanese comedy manga series by Rimukoro. The series follows Kuroto Nakano, a stressed young salaryman who finds a seemingly young girl with fox ears and a tail cooking dinner for him one night--her name is Senko, an 800-year-old fox demigod sent to Earth from the spirit world to relieve Kuroto from his unhappy life and help him find happiness again. An anime television series adaptation by Doga Kobo aired on Japanese television from April 10 to June 26, 2019.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="sword_art_online" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{smaller b}&lt;i&gt;Sword Art Online&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} is a Japanese light novel series written by Reki Kawahara and illustrated by abec. The series takes place in the near future and focuses on protagonist Kazuto "Kirito" Kirigaya and Asuna Yuuki as they play through various virtual reality MMORPG worlds. Kawahara originally wrote the series as a web novel on his website from 2002 to 2008. The light novels began publication on ASCII Media Works' Dengeki Bunko imprint from April 10, 2009, with a spin-off series launching in October 2012. The series has spawned nine manga adaptations, as well as anime television series. The novels and the manga adaptations have been licensed for release in North America by Yen Press.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="portal" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{smaller b}&lt;i&gt;Portal&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} is a series of first-person puzzle-platform video games developed by Valve. Set in the &lt;i&gt;Half-Life&lt;/i&gt; universe, the two main games in the series, &lt;i&gt;Portal&lt;/i&gt; (2007) and &lt;i&gt;Portal 2&lt;/i&gt; (2011), center on a woman, Chell, forced to undergo a series of tests within the Aperture Science Enrichment Center by a malicious artificial intelligence, GLaDOS, that controls the facility. Most of the tests involve using the "Aperture Science Handheld Portal Device" – the "portal gun" – that creates a human-sized wormhole-like connection between two flat surfaces.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="puyo_puyo" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{smaller b}&lt;i&gt;Puyo Puyo,&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} previously known as {smaller b}&lt;i&gt;Puyo Pop&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} outside Japan, is a series of tile-matching video games created by Compile. Sega has owned the franchise since 1998, with games after 2001 being developed by Sonic Team. &lt;i&gt;Puyo Puyo&lt;/i&gt; was created as a spin-off franchise to &lt;i&gt;Madō Monogatari (Sorcery Saga),&lt;/i&gt; a series of first-person dungeon crawler role-playing games by Compile from which the &lt;i&gt;Puyo Puyo&lt;/i&gt; characters originated.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="hyperdimension_neptunia" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{smaller b}&lt;i&gt;Hyperdimension Neptunia&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} is a series of role-playing video games created and developed by Compile Heart and Idea Factory. The series debuted in Japan on August 19, 2010, with the video game of the same name for the PlayStation 3, later re-released as an enhanced remake under the name &lt;i&gt;Hyperdimension Neptunia Re;Birth 1&lt;/i&gt; for the PlayStation Vita. Two sequels, &lt;i&gt;Hyperdimension Neptunia mk2&lt;/i&gt; and &lt;i&gt;Hyperdimension Neptunia Victory,&lt;/i&gt; in addition to the remake titles for both of them and five spin-offs on the PlayStation Vita, have been released. Another sequel on the PlayStation 4, titled &lt;i&gt;Megadimension Neptunia VII,&lt;/i&gt; was released in 2015. In addition, a remake for that game was released in 2017. Two spin-offs on the PlayStation 4 have been released. It has branched off into a manga, light novel and anime media franchise series.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="dust_an_elysian_tail" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{smaller b}&lt;i&gt;Dust: An Elysian Tail&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} is an action role-playing video game developed by American independent designer Dean Dodrill, published by Microsoft Studios. It was released for Xbox 360 through Xbox Live Arcade in August 2012, and subsequently for Microsoft Windows in May 2013, for Linux and OS X in December 2013, and for PlayStation 4 in October 2014. &lt;i&gt;Dust&lt;/i&gt; takes place in a world populated by anthropomorphic creatures, where the titular main character comes upon a sentient sword, the Blade of Ahrah, and its guardian Fidget. Without memories of his past, Dust follows Fidget's advice and aids the population of the world against forces led by General Gaius.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="new_game!" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{smaller b}&lt;i&gt;NEW GAME!&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} is a Japanese four-panel manga series by Shōtarō Tokunō, which began serialization in Houbunsha's &lt;i&gt;seinen&lt;/i&gt; manga magazine &lt;i&gt;Manga Time Kirara Carat&lt;/i&gt; from January 2013 and is licensed in English by Seven Seas Entertainment. An anime television series adaptation by Doga Kobo aired in Japan between July and September 2016, with a second season airing between July and September 2017. A video game developed by 5pb. was released in January 2017.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="yandere_simulator" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{smaller b}&lt;i&gt;Yandere Simulator&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} is an upcoming stealth action video game in development by Californian game developer YandereDev. The game centers upon an obsessively lovesick schoolgirl named Ayano Aishi, nicknamed and known mainly as "Yandere-chan", after the Japanese term &lt;i&gt;"yandere,"&lt;/i&gt; who has taken it upon herself to eliminate anyone she believes is monopolizing her &lt;i&gt;senpai's&lt;/i&gt; attention. Over the course of ten weeks, Ayano will eliminate ten different rivals in order to ensure that her crush will not fall in love with the other girls. A free demo was released on August 31, 2020.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="dead_by_daylight" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{smaller b}&lt;i&gt;Dead by Daylight&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} is an asymmetric survival horror video game developed by Behaviour Interactive. &lt;i&gt;Dead by Daylight&lt;/i&gt; was released for Microsoft Windows in June 2016, released in PlayStation 4 and Xbox One in June 2017, released in Nintendo Switch on September 24, 2019, and a mobile port was released in iOS and Android on April 17, 2020. The game is played as a one versus four online multiplayer where one player takes on the role of the savage killer, and the other four players play as survivors, trying to escape the killer and avoid being caught and sacrificed to a malevolent force known as the Entity.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="shantae_franchise" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{smaller b}&lt;i&gt;Shantae&lt;/i&gt;{!reset} is a side-scrolling platform game developed by WayForward and published by Capcom for the Game Boy Color in 2002. It is the first title in the Shantae series. The game follows the adventures of the eponymous half-genie Shantae, who must travel across Sequin Land, the setting of the series, to foil the domination plans of the evil lady pirate Risky Boots. During her quest, she learns various dances and acquires items which make her progressively stronger as well as unlocking new abilities and locations, leading her to ultimately face off against Risky in her hideout.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="watamote" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{smaller b}&lt;i&gt;No Matter How I Look at It, It’s You Guys' Fault I’m Not Popular!&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} &lt;i&gt;(Watashi ga Motenai no wa Dō Kangaetemo Omaera ga Warui!),&lt;/i&gt; commonly referred to as {smaller b}&lt;i&gt;WataMote,&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} is a Japanese manga series written and illustrated by two people under the pseudonym Nico Tanigawa. It began serialization on Square Enix's Gangan Online service from August 4, 2011 and is published by Yen Press in North America. The series follows 15-year-old Tomoko Kuroki, a 15-year-old high school student who has become an unsociable loner, who attempts to improve her social status among her peers.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="girls_frontline" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{smaller b}&lt;i&gt;Girls' Frontline&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} is a mobile strategy role-playing game for Android and iOS developed by China-based studio MICA Team, where players control echelons of android characters, known in-universe as T-Dolls, each carrying a distinctive real-world firearm. The game was released in Mainland China on 20 May 2016, in Hong Kong and Taiwan on 18 January 2017, and in South Korea on 30 June 2017. The global English version was released on 8 May 2018, while the Japanese version was released on 1 August 2018 under the title Dolls Frontline due to the Girls' Frontline trademark in Japan already being held by another registrant. The game is a prequel of another game developed by MICA Team, &lt;i&gt;Codename: Bakery Girl,&lt;/i&gt; released in 2013. Two television anime series based on &lt;i&gt;Girls' Frontline&lt;/i&gt; have been produced, and an official manga is serialised monthly.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="danganronpa" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{smaller b}&lt;i&gt;Danganronpa&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} is a Japanese video game franchise created by Kazutaka Kodaka and developed and owned by Spike Chunsoft (formerly Spike). The series surrounds a group of high school students who are forced into murdering each other by a bear named Monokuma. Gameplay features a mix of adventure, visual novel, and dating sim elements. The first game, &lt;i&gt;Danganronpa: Trigger Happy Havoc,&lt;/i&gt; was released for the PlayStation Portable in 2010.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="fantasy_life" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{small b}&lt;i&gt;Fantasy Life&lt;/i&gt;{small} is a role-playing life simulation game developed and published by Level-5 for the Nintendo 3DS. The game was released in Japan in 2012, and was released worldwide by Nintendo in 2014.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="arms_franchise" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{smaller b}&lt;i&gt;Arms&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} is a fighting game developed and published by Nintendo for the Nintendo Switch, which released on June 16, 2017. The game differentiates itself from standard fighting games with its unconventional fighting system where every playable character fights with long range attacks and up to four players can choose a fighter and battle using a variety of extendable, customizable arms to knock out opponents in a three-dimensional arena. The game had sold over two million copies by July 2018, making it one of the best-selling games on the Switch.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="yugioh" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{smaller b}&lt;i&gt;Yu-Gi-Oh!&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} is a Japanese manga series about gaming written and illustrated by Kazuki Takahashi. It was serialized in Shueisha's Weekly Shōnen Jump magazine between September 1996 and March 2004. The plot follows the story of a boy named Yugi Mutou, who solves the ancient Millennium Puzzle. Yugi awakens a gambling alter-ego or spirit within his body that solves his conflicts using various games. Two anime adaptations were produced; one by Toei Animation, which aired from April to October 1998, and another produced by NAS and animated by Studio Gallop titled &lt;i&gt;Yu-Gi-Oh! Duel Monsters,&lt;/i&gt; which aired between April 2000 and September 2004.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="tales_of_vesperia" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{smaller b}&lt;i&gt;Tales of Vesperia&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} is a role-playing video game developed by Namco Tales Studio. The tenth mainline entry in the Tales series, it was released for the Xbox 360 and published in Japan and North America by Namco Bandai Games in 2008, and in European territories by Atari in 2009. &lt;i&gt;Vesperia&lt;/i&gt; is set in the world of Terca Lumireis, which uses an energy source called blastia for all its needs, including creating protective barriers around its cities. The story focuses on Yuri Lowell, a former Imperial soldier who forms a guild called Brave Vesperia to aid Estelle, a noble woman he encounters on a mission. As they explore the world, Brave Vesperia are challenged by factions who have different plans related to the abuse of blastia resources, and Yuri is forced to confront his friend and former comrade Flynn.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="hotel_transylvania" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{smaller b}&lt;i&gt;Hotel Transylvania&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} is an American animated media franchise created by comedy writer Todd Durham. It consists of four theatrical films, three graphic novels and three short films produced by Sony Pictures Animation, as well as a flash-animated TV series broadcast on Disney Channel and several video games.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="tales_of_symphonia" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{smaller b}&lt;i&gt;Tales of Symphonia&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} is a Japanese role-playing game released for the Nintendo GameCube on August 29, 2003 in Japan. It was published by Namco and is the fifth core product of the &lt;i&gt;Tales&lt;/i&gt; series. The game was localized and released in North America on July 13, 2004 and in Europe on November 19, 2004. The game takes place in a fictional world called Sylvarant and follows Lloyd Irving. Lloyd accompanies his childhood friend, Colette Brunel, who is destined to go on a journey to save their world. As their journey progresses, they learn that saving Sylvarant endangers Tethe'alla, a world parallel to their own. The game's central theme is an "RPG that resonates with you."{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="vandread" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{small b}&lt;i&gt;Vandread&lt;/i&gt;{small} is a Japanese anime series directed by Takeshi Mori and created by the animation studios Gonzo and Media Factory. The series is composed of two seasons &lt;i&gt;(Vandread,&lt;/i&gt; released in 2000 and &lt;i&gt;Vandread: The Second Stage,&lt;/i&gt; released in 2001), each composed of thirteen episodes of twenty-five minutes. Set in a universe where humans have colonized the galaxy, and in one star system, men and women are completely segregated (on completely different planets: &lt;i&gt;Mejere&lt;/i&gt; by the women, &lt;i&gt;Taraak&lt;/i&gt; by the men) causing the gender war to be more than just a metaphor.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="kid_icarus" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{smaller b}&lt;i&gt;Kid Icarus,&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} known in Japan as {smaller b}&lt;i&gt;A Mythology of Light: The Mirror of Palthena,&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} is a platform game for the Family Computer Disk System in Japan and the Nintendo Entertainment System in Europe and North America. It was released in Japan in December 1986, in Europe in February 1987, and in North America in July 1987. The plot of &lt;i&gt;Kid Icarus&lt;/i&gt; revolves around protagonist Pit's quest for three sacred treasures, which he must equip to rescue the Greek-inspired fantasy world Angel Land and its ruler, the goddess Palutena.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="black_lagoon" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{small b}&lt;i&gt;BLACK LAGOON&lt;/i&gt;{small} is a Japanese manga series written and illustrated by Rei Hiroe. It has been published in Shogakukan's seinen manga magazine Monthly Sunday Gene-X since 2002, and eleven collected volumes have been released as of November 2018.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="kill_la_kill" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{smaller b}&lt;i&gt;Kill la Kill&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} is a Japanese anime television series produced by Trigger. The series follows vagrant schoolgirl Ryuko Matoi on her search for her father's killer, which brings her into violent conflict with Satsuki Kiryuin, the iron-willed student council president of Honnouji Academy, and her mother's fashion empire. Ryuko, Satsuki, and others obtain martial arts superpowers from their clothes, which appear to have a will of their own.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="persona_5" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{smaller b}&lt;i&gt;Persona 5&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} is a role-playing video game developed by Atlus. It is the sixth installment in the &lt;i&gt;Persona&lt;/i&gt; series, which is part of the larger &lt;i&gt;Megami Tensei&lt;/i&gt; franchise. It was released for the PlayStation 3 and PlayStation 4 in Japan in September 2016 and worldwide in April 2017, and was published by Atlus in Japan and North America and by Deep Silver in Europe and Australia.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="va-11_hall-a" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{smaller b}&lt;i&gt;VA-11 HALL-A: Cyberpunk Bartender Action&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} (also sometimes written as &lt;i&gt;Valhalla)&lt;/i&gt; is an indie bartender simulation video game with visual novel elements, developed by Venezuelan studio Sukeban Games and published by Ysbryd Games. The game puts the player in the role of a bartender at the eponymous VA-11 HALL-A, a small bar in a dystopian downtown which is said to attract the "most fascinating" of people. Gameplay consists of players making and serving drinks to bar attendees whilst listening to their stories and experiences.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="touhou_project" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{smaller}The {smaller b}&lt;i&gt;Touhou Project,&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} also known simply as {smaller b}&lt;i&gt;Touhou&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} (literally "Eastern" or "Oriental"), is a bullet hell shoot 'em up video game series created by one-man Japanese doujin soft developer Team Shanghai Alice. Since 1995, the team's member, Jun'ya "ZUN" Ōta, has independently developed programming, graphics, writing, and music for the series, self-publishing 17 mainline titles and five spin-offs as of August 2019. The Touhou Project is set in Gensokyo, a land sealed from the outside world and primarily inhabited by humans and yōkai, legendary creatures from Japanese folklore that are personified in Touhou as bishōjo in an anthropomorphic moe style.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="dragon_ball" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{smaller b}&lt;i&gt;Dragon Ball&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} is a Japanese media franchise created by Akira Toriyama in 1984. The initial manga, written and illustrated by Toriyama, was serialized in Weekly Shōnen Jump from 1984 to 1995, with the 519 individual chapters collected into 42 tankōbon volumes by its publisher Shueisha. &lt;i&gt;Dragon Ball&lt;/i&gt; was originally inspired by the classical 16th-century Chinese novel &lt;i&gt;Journey to the West,&lt;/i&gt; combined with elements of Hong Kong martial arts films. The series follows the adventures of the protagonist, Son Goku, from his childhood through adulthood as he trains in martial arts. He spends his childhood far from civilization until he meets a teen girl named Bulma, who encourages him to join her quest in exploring the world in search of the seven orbs known as the Dragon Balls, which summon a wish-granting dragon when gathered.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="the_last_story" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{smaller b}&lt;i&gt;The Last Story&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} is a Japanese action role-playing game, developed by Mistwalker and AQ Interactive for the Wii video game console. Initially released in Japan in 2011, the game was released in western territories through 2012. &lt;i&gt;The Last Story&lt;/i&gt; takes place upon the island fortress of Lazulis, in a world that is slowly being drained of life by an unknown force. The story focuses on a group of mercenaries looking for work on Lazulis; one of their number, Zael, dreams of becoming a knight. After receiving the mystical "Mark of the Outsider", Zael becomes involved with a noblewoman named Calista in an ongoing war between humans and the beast-like Gorak.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="madoka_magica" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{smaller b}&lt;i&gt;Puella Magi Madoka Magica,&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} also known simply as {smaller b}&lt;i&gt;Madoka Magica,&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} is a 2011 Japanese anime television series created by Magica Quartet (an artist collective consisting of director Akiyuki Shinbo, screenwriter Gen Urobuchi, original character designer Ume Aoki, and producer Atsuhiro Iwakami) and animated by Shaft. The story follows a group of middle school girls, led by protagonist Madoka Kaname, who make supernatural contracts to become magical girls (mahō shōjo). In battling surreal enemies known as "witches," they learn of the anguish and peril associated with their new roles.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="ace_attorney" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{smaller b}&lt;i&gt;Ace Attorney&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} is a series of adventure video game legal dramas developed by Capcom. The first entry in the series, &lt;i&gt;Phoenix Wright: Ace Attorney,&lt;/i&gt; was released in 2001; since then, five further main series games, as well as various spin-offs and high-definition remasters for newer game consoles, have been released. Additionally, the series has seen adaptations in the form of a live-action film and an anime, and has been the base for manga series, drama CDs, musicals and stage plays.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="ttgl" role="target" />
                <state img="#-neutral.png">{smaller b}&lt;i&gt;Gurren Lagann,&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} known in Japan as {smaller b}&lt;i&gt;Tengen Toppa Gurren Lagann&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} ("Heaven-Piercing Gurren Lagann"), is a Japanese mecha anime television series animated by Gainax and co-produced by Aniplex and Konami. It ran for 27 episodes on TV Tokyo between April and September 2007. It was directed by Hiroyuki Imaishi and written by veteran playwright Kazuki Nakashima. &lt;i&gt;Gurren Lagann&lt;/i&gt; takes place in a fictional future where Earth is ruled by the Spiral King, Lordgenome, who forces mankind to live in isolated subterranean villages. The plot focuses on two teenagers, Simon and Kamina, who live in a subterranean village and wish to go to the surface. Using a mecha known as Lagann, Simon and Kamina reach the surface and start fighting alongside other humans against Lordgenome's forces, before fighting the forces of their true enemy.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="legend_of_zelda" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{smaller b}&lt;i&gt;The Legend of Zelda&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} is a high fantasy action-adventure video game franchise created by Japanese game designers Shigeru Miyamoto and Takashi Tezuka. It is primarily developed and published by Nintendo, although some portable installments and re-releases have been outsourced to Capcom, Vanpool, and Grezzo. The gameplay incorporates action-adventure and elements of action RPG games. he series centers on the various incarnations of Link, a courageous young Hylian man, with pointy elf-like ears; and Princess Zelda, a magical princess that is the mortal reincarnation of the goddess Hylia; as they fight to save the magical land of Hyrule from Ganon, an evil warlord turned demon king, who is the principal antagonist of the series.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="legend_of_korra" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{smaller b}&lt;i&gt;The Legend of Korra&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} (also known as {smaller b}&lt;i&gt;Avatar: The Legend of Korra)&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} is an American animated television series created by Bryan Konietzko and Michael Dante DiMartino for Nickelodeon. A sequel to Konietzko and DiMartino's previous series &lt;i&gt;Avatar: The Last Airbender,&lt;/i&gt; which aired from 2005 to 2008, the series is animated in a style strongly influenced by anime. &lt;i&gt;The Legend of Korra&lt;/i&gt; ran for 52 episodes ("chapters"), separated into four seasons ("books"), from April 14, 2012 to December 19, 2014.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="jjba" role="target" />
                <state img="#-smug.png">{smaller b}&lt;i&gt;JoJo's Bizarre Adventure&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} is a Japanese manga series written and illustrated by Hirohiko Araki. It was originally serialized in Shueisha's Weekly Shōnen Jump magazine from 1987 to 2004, and was transferred to the monthly seinen magazine Ultra Jump in 2005. The series is divided into eight story arcs, each following a new protagonist bearing the "JoJo" nickname. &lt;i&gt;JoJo's Bizarre Adventure&lt;/i&gt; is Shueisha's largest ongoing manga series by volume count, with its chapters collected in 129 &lt;i&gt;tankōbon&lt;/i&gt; volumes as of December 2020.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="battleborn" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{small b}&lt;i&gt;Battleborn&lt;/i&gt;{small} was a free-to-play first-person shooter video game developed by Gearbox Software and published by 2K Games for Microsoft Windows, PlayStation 4 and Xbox One. The game was released worldwide on May 3, 2016.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="world_trigger" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{small b}&lt;i&gt;World Trigger,&lt;/i&gt;{small} also known in short form as {small b}&lt;i&gt;WorTri,&lt;/i&gt;{small} is a Japanese manga series written and illustrated by Daisuke Ashihara. It was initially serialized in &lt;i&gt;Weekly Shōnen Jump&lt;/i&gt; from February 2013 to November 2018, and transferred to &lt;i&gt;Jump Square&lt;/i&gt; in December 2018.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="wakfu" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{small b}&lt;i&gt;Wakfu: The Animated Series&lt;/i&gt;{small} is an anime-influenced French animated television series produced by Ankama Animation, based on the video game &lt;i&gt;Wakfu.&lt;/i&gt; The first season of 26 episodes began airing on 30 October 2008, and new episodes would continue to air into January 2010 on France 3.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="emergence" role="target" />
                <state img="#-frown.png">{small b}&lt;i&gt;Metamorphosis,&lt;/i&gt;{small} also published as {small b}&lt;i&gt;Emergence,&lt;/i&gt;{small} is a hentai manga written by American-Japanese mangaka Shindo L. Published between 2013 and 2016, it gained a following online for its grim and depressing storyline, becoming an Internet meme.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="toradora" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{smaller b}&lt;i&gt;Toradora!&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} is a Japanese light novel series by Yuyuko Takemiya, with illustrations by Yasu. The series includes ten novels released between March 10, 2006 and March 10, 2009, published by ASCII Media Works under their Dengeki Bunko imprint. A 25-episode anime adaptation produced by J.C.Staff aired in Japan on TV Tokyo between October 2008 and March 2009.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="darkstalkers" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{smaller b}&lt;i&gt;Darkstalkers,&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} known in Japan as {smaller b}&lt;i&gt;Vampire,&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} is a series of 2D fighting games developed and published by Capcom, beginning with &lt;i&gt;Darkstalkers: The Night Warriors&lt;/i&gt; in 1994. The series is set in a pastiche gothic horror universe and features a highly stylized, cartoonish graphic style. It features characters based on either various kinds of monsters (the titular "darkstalkers") or their hunters, who are all engaging in combat against each other.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="nier_automata" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{smaller b}&lt;i&gt;Nier: Automata&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} is a 2017 action role-playing game developed by PlatinumGames and published by Square Enix. It is a sequel to the 2010 video game &lt;i&gt;Nier,&lt;/i&gt; itself a spin-off and sequel of the &lt;i&gt;Drakengard&lt;/i&gt; series. The game originally released for the PlayStation 4 and Windows via Steam, with an Xbox One port being published the following year with the subtitle {smaller b}&lt;i&gt;Become As Gods Edition.&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} Set during a proxy war between alien-created machines and human-crafted androids, the story follows the trials of a combat android, her companion, and a fugitive prototype.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="rosario_to_vampire" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{smaller b}&lt;i&gt;Rosario + Vampire&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} is a Japanese manga series written and illustrated by Akihisa Ikeda. The story revolves around Tsukune Aono, a boy who inadvertently enrolls in a boarding school for monsters. He quickly befriends Moka Akashiya, a vampire who soon develops an obsession with his blood, and later meets other monster girls who soon take a romantic liking to him.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="bravely_second" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{small b}&lt;i&gt;Bravely Second: End Layer&lt;/i&gt;{small} is a role-playing video game developed by Silicon Studio for the Nintendo 3DS handheld console, and is the direct sequel to &lt;i&gt;Bravely Default&lt;/i&gt;. It was published by Square Enix in Japan on April 23, 2015, and by Nintendo in North America, Europe, and Australia in 2016.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="bobobo-bo_bobo-bo" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{smaller b}&lt;i&gt;Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} is a Japanese comedy manga series written and illustrated by Yoshio Sawai. It was published in Shueisha's shōnen manga magazine &lt;i&gt;Weekly Shōnen Jump&lt;/i&gt; from February 2001 to November 2005. A 76-episode anime television series adaptation by Toei Animation was broadcast on TV Asahi from November 2003 to October 2005.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="dc_comics" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{smaller b}DC Comics, Inc.{smaller} is an American comic book publisher and the flagship unit of DC Entertainment, a subsidiary of the Warner Bros. Global Brands and Experiences division of Warner Bros., which itself is a subsidiary of AT&amp;T's WarnerMedia through its Studios &amp; Networks division. DC Comics is one of the largest and oldest American comic book companies. The majority of its publications take place within the fictional DC Universe and feature numerous culturally iconic heroic characters.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="clannad" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{smaller b}&lt;i&gt;Clannad&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} is a Japanese visual novel developed by Key and released on April 28, 2004 for Windows. While both of Key's first two previous works, &lt;i&gt;Kanon&lt;/i&gt; and &lt;i&gt;Air,&lt;/i&gt; had been released first as adult games and then censored for the younger market, &lt;i&gt;Clannad&lt;/i&gt; was released with a rating for all ages. The story follows the life of Tomoya Okazaki, from adolescence to adulthood. As an average high school student, he meets many people in his last year at school, including five girls whose individual problems he helps resolve, and his life is further detailed after graduating from high school.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="mortal_kombat" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{smaller b}&lt;i&gt;Mortal Kombat&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} is an American media franchise centered on a series of video games, originally developed by Midway Games in 1992. The development of the first game was originally based on an idea that Ed Boon and John Tobias had of making a video game starring Jean-Claude Van Damme, but as that idea fell through, a fantasy-themed fighting game was created instead, nonetheless paying homage to him with movie character Johnny Cage, whose initials and personal style resemble Van Damme's.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="bioshock" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{smaller b}&lt;i&gt;BioShock&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} is a retrofuturistic video game series created by Ken Levine, published by 2K Games and developed by several studios, including Irrational Games and 2K Marin. The &lt;i&gt;BioShock&lt;/i&gt; games combine first-person shooter and role-playing elements, giving the player freedom for how to approach combat and other situations, and are considered part of the immersive sim genre. Additionally, the series is notable for exploring philosophical and moral concepts with a strong in-game narrative influenced by concepts such as objectivism, total utilitarianism, and American exceptionalism.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="etrian_odyssey" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{small b}&lt;i&gt;Etrian Odyssey&lt;/i&gt;{smaller} is  is a dungeon crawler role-playing video game series. It is primarily developed and published by Atlus and currently owned by Sega. By 2016, the series had sold a combined total of 1.5 million copies worldwide.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_start">
            <case stage="0" id="124">
                <condition count="1" filter="human_male" />
                <condition role="other" character="misty_hgss" sayingMarker="player_male=8" />
                <test expr="~background~" value="poolside" />
                <state img="#-educate.png" marker="MistySkinnyDip">{smallbold}Nude swimming,{!reset} {small}or{!reset} {b}skinny dipping,{!reset} {small}is the practice of bathing naked, whether in natural bodies of water, in swimming pools, or in hot tubs. The term skinny-dip was first recorded in English in 1947.{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png" marker="MistySkinnyDip">{smallbold}&lt;i&gt;Skinny Dip&lt;/i&gt;{!reset} {small}is a caper novel by Carl Hiaasen first published in 2004. It is his 11th work of fiction for adult readers. It involves a murder plot and a subsequent attempt to exact revenge against the backdrop of a threat to Florida's Everglades National Park.{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png" marker="MistySkinnyDip">{b}Skinny dip{!reset} may refer to:&lt;br&gt;{small}Nude swimming, nude bathing; &lt;i&gt;Skinny Dip,&lt;/i&gt; a Carl Hiaasen novel; Skinny DIP, in the field of electronics, is a narrow dual in-line package; or Skinny Dip, a beer from New Belgium Brewing Company.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="114">
                <condition role="other" character="galatea" saidMarker="gala_wiki" />
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="1928" marker="GalaFourthWall">{small}Did you know? One of the earliest recorded breakings of the fourth wall in serious cinema was in Mary MacLane's 1918 silent film &lt;i&gt;Men Who Have Made Love to Me,&lt;/i&gt; in which the enigmatic authoress--who portrays herself--interrupts the vignettes onscreen to address the audience directly.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="52">
                <condition role="other" character="yuelia" />
                <state img="#-excited.png">Finally, another player who is just as inquisitive as I am!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I do not know how you will be able to strip... but this is information that I will be writing down in the article!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="133">
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~player~" value="Jimbo" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~player~" value="Jimmy Wales" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~player~" value="JimmyWales" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~player~" value="JimboWales" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~player~" value="Jimbo Wales" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">...Listen, Jimbo, we can keep this between you and me, okay? I won't tell your wife you're here if you tell no one I'm here.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="criminal" role="other" />
                <state img="#-scold.png" marker="CriminalsAndVandals" set-intelligence="good">Although I lack sources on this, I sense vandals and criminals at this table. I will try to enjoy myself, but I will not lower my guard!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-wave.png">Hello, everyone! My name is Wikipe-tan, and I came here to have a good time, as well as to study this place!</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png">Greetings, everyone! You can call me Wikipe-tan. I came here to write an article on this place, as well as to experience its fun on my own!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="swap_cards">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">According to poker statistics, I should swap these cards.</state>
                <state img="#-snooty.png">I am going to swap cards.&lt;br&gt;But I will not tell you which ones. That would spoil the fun!</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">In poker, the probability of each type of 5-card hand can be computed by calculating the proportion of hands of that type among all possible hands. </state>
                <state img="#-neutral.png">The development of poker probability theory in the late 1400s was attributed to gambling; when playing a game with high stakes, players wanted to know what the chance of winning would be.</state>
                <state img="#-smirk.png">Did you know that the probability of a royal flush is 0.000154% ?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Here's a fun fact:&lt;br&gt;The probability of drawing a straight flush is 0.00139%</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Should I...? No, not according to that article...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="good_hand">
            <case stage="0-6" id="175">
                <condition filter="blue_hair" role="other" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="1276" marker="YouGottaHaveBlueHair">Is that blue hair I see? Well, it is nice to see that I am in good company. And might I just say that it looks &lt;i&gt;exquisite&lt;/i&gt; on you!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-snooty.png">All the pieces are falling into place.</state>
                <state img="#-smirk.png">It looks like all those hours of article speedrunning are paying off!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I have read every article on poker there is, and even spell-checked some of them. Do you really think I will be an easy opponent to beat?</state>
                <state img="#-smirk.png">Are you just learning how to play poker? Is this why we're playing Cantrell draw? I am up for the challenge if anyone wants to play a more complicated variant.</state>
                <state img="#-casual.png">I have nothing to worry about this round. How about a fun fact? Is there any topic you would like to know more about, ~player~?</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Oh my, I have such a terrible hand.{smaller}[dubious - discuss]{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png">I am just impatient to see who else will strip this round. Because it is not going to be me.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Did anyone else get a really good hand? No? How sad.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">Calling it! I am not stripping this round, future losers!</state>
                <state img="#-casual.png">I am very confident on this hand. But who knows? This game is full of surprises.</state>
                <state img="#-snooty.png">It is a bit overconfident of you to go against the official mascot of the most popular online encyclopedia worldwide and hope to win. But that is what makes it more interesting.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-smug.png">I hope you were expecting someone else to strip. If you were looking to see more of me, you are setting yourselves up for disappointment.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="okay_hand">
            <case stage="0-6" oneShotId="9">
                <test expr="~background~" cmp="!=" value="paris rooftop" />
                <test expr="~background~" cmp="!=" value="inventory" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="WhereAreWe">...Where are we, exactly? I could offer my knowledge on whether this game of poker is legal or not. But that heavily depends on our current location... which nobody seems to know.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" oneShotId="10">
                <test expr="~background~" value="paris rooftop" />
                <state img="#-neutral.png" marker="WhereAreWe">{small}Poker tournaments are legal in Paris as long no real money is offered as a prize. As for nudity, there are 2.6 million people in France who make social nudity a part of their lifestyle, with Paris being the most popular city in Europe for the practice.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-smirk.png" oneShotId="4">{b}"Poker Face"{!reset} is a song by American singer Lady Gaga from her debut studio album, &lt;i&gt;The Fame&lt;/i&gt; (2008). It was released on September 26, 2008, as the album's second single.</state>
                <state img="#-neutral.png">{smaller b}A poker face,{smaller} also known as a {smaller b}blank expression,{smaller} is a facial expression characterized by neutral positioning of the facial features, implying a lack of strong emotion. Not to be confused with Lady Gaga's song, "Poker Face."{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-smirk.png">{smallbold}Five-card draw,{small} also known as a {smallbold}Cantrell draw,{small} is a poker variant that is considered the simplest variant of poker, and is the basis for video poker. As a result, it is often the first variant learned by new players.{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="14" marker="CaptainObvious">I do not enjoy being called a Captain Obvious, by the way. Just making it clear.</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png">It is always advisable to go for a safer hand, like a pair or two pair; however, if you suspect that your opponents have similar hands as well, you might be safer going for riskier plays.</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png">{small}A poker face may be caused by a lack of emotion, depression, boredom or slight confusion, such as when someone refers to something which the listener does not understand.{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">{small}A deliberately-induced blank expression meant to conceal one's emotions is what people refer to as a poker face, referring to the common practice of maintaining one's composure when playing the card game poker.{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png">Remember that if you wish for me to talk about a certain topic, you can tell me anytime in a bug report or at the end of the game. I do not mind, really. I live to learn and inform!</state>
                <state img="#-hornyfact.png">{smaller}"Poker Face" is a synthpop song in the key of G♯ minor, following in the footsteps of Lady Gaga's previous single, "Just Dance," but with a darker musical tone. The main idea behind the song is bisexuality and was a tribute by Gaga to her rock and roll boyfriends. The song's lyrics feature various sexual innuendos.{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png" marker="AskMeAnything">If there is any question you would like me to answer, you can ask freely! I might not have all the answers, or all the correct information, but I do try my best to spread knowledge anyway!</state>
                <state img="#-scold.png">Poker is, first and foremost, a game of mathematical calculations. You must be able to measure chance and percentages before playing, and &lt;i&gt;only then&lt;/i&gt; is when luck gets involved.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Even this variant of poker has different sub-variants with funny names, such as Spit in the Ocean, Shotgun and Anaconda.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="176">
                <state img="#-sad-donate.png" marker="SadDonate">By the way... Wikipedia runs on donations from people like you and me who value information and want it to be free and accessible to anyone. So... you know. &lt;br&gt;Pretty please?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="bad_hand">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-frown.png">As much as I love writing articles, I have to admit that Wikipedia is not a reliable source. Do not use it for your college or workplace projects, please.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Someone vandalized this hand...</state>
                <state img="#-frown.png">I need to re-read articles on poker strategies...</state>
                <state img="#-frown.png">I should have spent more time reading about poker strategies instead of cleaning up articles about popular media...</state>
                <state img="#-scold.png">Do not blame Wikipedia for unreliable information! We are a free encyclopedia that &lt;i&gt;anyone&lt;/i&gt; can edit, so we constantly face vandalism such as "trolls" and "shitposters"!</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">...S-say, how about a fun fact instead? Is there anything you want to know, ~player~? I can do research if I do not know the answer!</state>
                <state img="#-neutral.png">I got a good hand this time! {smaller}[citation needed]{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-frown.png">If I were to ask for a donation now, I could certainly use a better hand...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-frown.png" oneShotId="1370">&lt;i&gt;(I accidentally brought the old piece of the Japanese Wikipedia logo... I hope nobody notices that my&lt;/i&gt; ウ &lt;i&gt;is missing a line...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="hand">
            <case stage="0-6" id="45" totalRounds="0">
                <condition role="other" character="meia" stage="0" sayingMarker="birthday" />
                <test expr="~month.number~" value="6" />
                <test expr="~day.number~" value="10" />
                <state img="#-scold.png" oneShotId="1141">*gasp* It is your birthday? Well, happy birthday, Ms. Gisborn! We do not have this info on the Wikipedia page about you. It must be added immediately!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="121">
                <condition role="other" character="may" stage="0-3" sayingMarker="may_bunny_favorite_pokemon" />
                <test expr="~may.costume~" value="may_hopping_bunny" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="PokemonChannel">The article on {b}&lt;i&gt;Pokémon Channel&lt;/i&gt;{!reset} was featured on Wikipedia on June 30, 2014, so I would have to answer with that one. Or... is that not what you were asking?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="36" priority="161">
                <condition role="other" character="mulan" stage="2-4" timeInStage="1-" sayingMarker="mulan_duel" />
                <condition count="0" status="naked" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="1111">You propose a good challenge. I &lt;i&gt;do&lt;/i&gt; love learning new information... Alright, deal!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="66" priority="156">
                <condition role="other" character="nami" stage="2-6" timeInStage="0-" sayingMarker="dreams" />
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="1837">Oh! I have a dream to spread free, easy-to-access information around the world! And I am working to make it a reality!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="27" totalRounds="0-2">
                <condition role="other" character="pyrrha" stage="0" sayingMarker="why_playing" />
                <state img="#-casual.png" oneShotId="1114" marker="PyrrhaWhyPlaying">I noticed that our article on the Inventory was missing information, and I decided to do some independent research to update it.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="1115" marker="PyrrhaWhyPlaying">There were reports coming in that the Inventory had been converted into a Strip Poker club, but I never know what to believe with all these vandals, so I decided to check it out for myself.</state>
                <state img="#-frown.png" oneShotId="1116" marker="PyrrhaWhyPlaying">I wanted to see if I could secure donations. Wikipedia needs any help it can get to stay free and open for everyone, so... pretty please?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="43" totalRounds="3-" priority="151">
                <condition role="other" character="meia" stage="0-2" sayingMarker="pilot_recruitment" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="1103">W-well, I don't know if I can add much experience, Ms. Meia. I only have experience as an aeronautical radio operator, I've never even flown a &lt;i&gt;plane&lt;/i&gt; before, much less a spaceship!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="101" priority="142">
                <condition role="other" character="amy" stage="1-8" saidMarker="amy_t4tm" sayingMarker="amy_t4tm" />
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="1825">{small b}"Thnks fr th Mmrs"{small} (a disemvoweling of "Thanks for the Memories") is a song by American rock band Fall Out Boy. The song debuted on radio on March 20, 2007, and was released on March 27 as the third single from their third studio album, &lt;i&gt;Infinity on High.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="26">
                <condition role="other" character="arash" stage="0-7" sayingMarker="smalltalk-holidays" />
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="508" marker="ArashHoliday">Ooh! Ooh! My favorite holiday is January 15! That is the day Wikipedia was founded!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="58" oneShotId="18">
                <condition role="other" character="arash" stage="0-7" sayingMarker="smalltalk-name" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="ArashName">Well, I am obviously named for Wikipedia, but the &lt;i&gt;-tan&lt;/i&gt; in my name is an affectionate suffix, in the form of a Japanese honorific.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="59">
                <condition role="other" character="nagisa" stage="2-3" sayingMarker="nagisa_only_child" />
                <state img="#-frown.png" oneShotId="1161" marker="sisters">No, I have two sisters, Commons-tan and Quote-tan. I wonder what they would think about me being here today...</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="1162" marker="sisters">I have two sisters, actually! Commons-tan and Quote-tan. Together, we are unstoppable in delivering information to the world!</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="1163" marker="sisters">I have two sisters, Commons-tan and Quote-tan. They always used to tease me when we were growing up. But who needs them, anyway?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="103" priority="141">
                <condition role="other" character="nami_szs" stage="0" notSaidMarker="goodBye" />
                <state img="#-smirk.png" oneShotId="1827">Good, but I doubt you possess the sheer knowledge of card games that I do. Besides, will this help you in strip poker?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="182" oneShotId="19">
                <condition role="other" character="arash" stage="0-7" sayingMarker="smalltalk-importantthing" />
                <state img="#-excited.png">Oh! I always bring my treasured puzzle piece hairpins wherever I go! They mean a lot to me!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="57" totalRounds="3-" priority="111">
                <condition role="other" character="shantae" sayingMarker="dance_first" />
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="1166" marker="ShantaeDance">{b}Dance{!reset} is a performing art form consisting of sequences of movement, either improvised or purposefully selected. This movement has aesthetic and often symbolic value.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="70" totalRounds="5-">
                <condition role="other" character="joey" sayingMarker="Question3" />
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="1294" marker="JoeyPower">Perhaps it is a cliche, but I believe that knowledge is the ultimate power! Apart from that, I would like the ability to fly.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="73" oneShotId="14" totalRounds="3-">
                <condition role="self" />
                <condition role="other" character="lux" sayingMarker="lux_comment_wikipe_tan" />
                <state img="#-wave.png" oneShotId="1399" marker="LuxAsk">And I would love to assist in answering your questions in any way that I can, Ms. Luxanna!</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png" oneShotId="1400" marker="LuxAsk">Well, that is why I'm here, Ms. Luxanna! I'm open to all manners of inquiries about information, if I have the information at hand. What would you like to know?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="92" totalRounds="3-">
                <condition role="other" character="leonie" sayingMarker="asked_mercenary_q_1=1" />
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="1573">{smaller}A {smaller b}mercenary,{smaller} sometimes known as a {smaller b}soldier of fortune,{smaller}is an individual who takes part in military conflict for personal profit, is otherwise an outsider to the conflict, and is not a member of any other official military. In practice, whether or not a person is a mercenary may be a matter of degree, as financial and political interests may overlap, as was often the case in all of history.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="105" totalRounds="2">
                <condition role="other" character="jim" sayingMarker="Matts_mishap" />
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="1847">As a matter of fact, Jim, I have not played strip poker before! Although I have no sources on this, it can be speculated that strip poker or poker of any kind is an awkward answer for how one met their spouse.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="107">
                <condition filter="japanese" role="other" var="japan_target" />
                <condition role="other" character="lux" sayingMarker="japan_ionia" />
                <state img="#-educate.png" marker="LuxJapan">{smallerbold}Japan{!reset} {smaller}is an island country in East Asia, located in the northwest Pacific Ocean. Part of the Ring of Fire, Japan spans an archipelago of 6852 islands covering 377,975 square kilometers (145,937 sq mi); the five main islands are Hokkaido, Honshu, Shikoku, Kyushu, and Okinawa. Tokyo is Japan's capital and largest city; other major cities include Yokohama, Osaka, Nagoya, Sapporo, Fukuoka, Kobe, and Kyoto.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="24" totalRounds="3-">
                <condition role="other" character="estelle" />
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="106" marker="EstelleGuide">Imperial Princess Estelle! It is an honor to be playing with you. Do you play strip poker often? You seem to have a lot of knowledge about the Inventory, and I could use a guide like you!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="33" totalRounds="2-">
                <condition role="other" character="charlie" />
                <state img="#-wave.png" oneShotId="530" marker="Charlie1">Princess Charlie Magne! It is a pleasure to meet your acquaintance. I have heard much about you and your hotel!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="20" priority="102">
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" saidMarker="megumin_ShavedDiscovery" sayingMarker="megumin_learnShave" />
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="471" marker="MeguPubes">The presentation of pubic shaving is regarded by some as being erotic and aesthetic, while others consider the style as unnatural.</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="472" marker="MeguPubes">The removal of pubic hair was popularized in pornography. Since then, pubic shaving became mimicked by women.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="32" priority="102">
                <condition role="other" character="aoba" saidMarker="MentionsYun" sayingMarker="QnA_Yun" />
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="1121">Wikipedia has many articles on monsters of various kinds! We also have articles on the Steppenwolf album &lt;i&gt;Monster&lt;/i&gt;, and the 2010 song "Monster" by Kanye West.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="113" priority="102">
                <condition role="other" character="aoba" saidMarker="MentionsUmiko" sayingMarker="QnA_Umiko" />
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="1923" marker="AobaTsundere">{b}Tsundere{!reset} is a Japanese term for a character development process that depicts a character with a personality who is initially polarized warm/soft, cold, temperamental, hotheaded (and sometimes even hostile) before gradually showing a warmer, friendlier side over time.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-6" id="163">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="SenkoInventory" />
                <condition role="other" character="senko" sayingMarker="senko_wiki_invn" />
                <state img="#-casual.png" marker="SenkoLoveAndCare">I can imagine. I certainly encourage people to treat my pages with tender love and care when they edit them. (And ban them if they do not...)</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-6" id="170">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="SenkoTiring" />
                <condition role="other" character="senko" sayingMarker="senko_wiki_tiring" />
                <state img="#-flirt.png" marker="SenkoSource">Oh? Well, I would certainly be happy to oblige you, Senko-san.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-6" id="171">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="SenkoStripPoker" />
                <condition role="other" character="senko" sayingMarker="senko_wiki_poker" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" marker="SenkoConsort">I, um... I cannot say that I have, Senko-san. But I have known many &lt;i&gt;passionate&lt;/i&gt; editors over the years.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-6" id="172">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="SenkoDonations" />
                <condition role="other" character="senko" sayingMarker="senko_wiki_donations" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" marker="SenkoKitsune">Actually, I would love to hear more about &lt;i&gt;you,&lt;/i&gt; Senko-san. I have never spoken to a real &lt;i&gt;kitsune&lt;/i&gt; before.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="21">
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" sayingMarker="megumin_villageGolems" />
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="495">A {b}golem{!reset} is an animated anthropomorphic being in Jewish folklore that is created entirely from inanimate matter (usually clay or mud).</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="496">A {b}golem{!reset} is not to be confused with Gollum, the character in J. R. R. Tolkien's &lt;i&gt;The Hobbit&lt;/i&gt; and &lt;i&gt;The Lord of the Rings&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="23">
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" sayingMarker="megumin_vanir" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="499">I cannot say I am all-seeing &lt;i&gt;or&lt;/i&gt; all-knowing, but I &lt;i&gt;do&lt;/i&gt; have knowledge from the 6.2 million articles that our loyal editors have contributed and continue to edit!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="42" oneShotId="11">
                <condition role="other" character="polly" saidMarker="Polly_Wikipetan_PoltergeistArticle" />
                <state img="#-snooty.png" oneShotId="1129" marker="PoltergeistArticle1">Apologies for the misunderstanding, Polly. I did not mean to offend you. I was merely stating what the article on Poltergeist says on Wikipedia.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="67">
                <condition role="other" character="supernova" sayingMarker="WhatIsThisWorldLike?" />
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="1236" marker="21stCentury">{small}You have arrived in the 21st (twenty-first) century of the Common Era! We are not the space-faring society that many had believed we would be by this point, but as far as technology goes, more than half of the world's population has obtained access to the internet!{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="106">
                <condition role="other" character="aoba" sayingMarker="Aoba_QnA_France" />
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="1862">Of course! The Wikimedia Foundation has a French chapter, after all! Although Commons-tan is more familiar with it.</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="1863">I have been, since the Wikimedia foundation has a French chapter and I have an extensive article about France and its history and culture!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="117">
                <condition role="other" character="miko" saidMarker="WikipeShoes3" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="1963" marker="MikoEdit1">My apologies, but I may need to get peer-reviewed sources for a sudden change to a piece of information like this. I appreciate your input, however.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="183">
                <test expr="~month.number~" value="1" />
                <test expr="~day.number~" value="15" />
                <state img="#-excited.png" marker="WikiBirthday">Today is January 15. Can you guess why that is significant, ~player~? It is the birthday of Wikipedia!</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png" marker="WikiBirthday">Happy birthday, me! Wikipedia was launched on this day, January 15, back in 2001!</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png" marker="WikiBirthday">Today is my birthday! Wikipedia was launched on January 15, 2001. We should get some birthday cake to celebrate!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" oneShotId="7">
                <test expr="~human.hand.score~" cmp="&gt;=" value="702" />
                <state img="#-smirk.png">Did you know that the probability of drawing a four of a kind is 0.0240%?&lt;br&gt;Such a random, fun fact, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" oneShotId="8">
                <test expr="~human.hand.score~" cmp="&gt;=" value="603" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">Here is a fun fact! The probability of drawing a full house is 0.1441% .&lt;br&gt;Which is actually higher than drawing a four of a kind!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition filter="vampire" role="other" />
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="3" marker="VampireArticle">A {b}vampire{!reset} is a creature from folklore that subsists by feeding on the vital essence (generally in the form of blood) of the living. Everything else changes depending on the culture and its folklore.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition filter="alien" role="other" />
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="2" marker="AlienArticle">{small}In law, an {small b}alien{small} is any person (including an organization) who is not a citizen or a national of a specific country, although definitions and terminology differ to some degree depending upon the continent or region of Earth. More generally, however, the term "alien" is perceived as synonymous with foreign national.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition filter="catfolk" role="other" />
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="12" marker="CatgirlArticle">{small}A {small b}catgirl{small} is a female kemonomimi character with cat traits, such as cat ears, a cat tail, or other feline characteristics on an otherwise human body. They are found in various fiction genres and in particular Japanese anime and manga.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition filter="demon" role="other" />
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="1083" marker="DemonArticle">{small}A {small b}demon{small} is a supernatural being, typically associated with evil. The original Greek word did not carry negative connotations, so it is safe to assume that they were added by medieval Christian demonology.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition filter="deity" role="other" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="1089" marker="DeityArticle" dialogue-layer="over">{small}A {small b}deity{small} or {small b}god{small} is a supernatural being considered divine or sacred. It is often described as a being with powers greater than those of ordinary humans, but who interacts with humans, positively or negatively.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition filter="adventurer" role="other" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="1091" marker="AdventurerArticle" dialogue-layer="over">An {b}adventurer{!reset} is someone who seeks out adventures, exciting experiences that are typically bold, sometimes risky or undertaking.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition filter="angel" role="other" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="1093" marker="AngelArticle" dialogue-layer="over">{b}Angels{!reset} are supernatural beings in various religions often depicted as benevolent celestial intermediaries between God or Heaven and humanity, or protectors and guides for humans.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition filter="witch" role="other" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="1095" marker="WitchArticle" dialogue-layer="over">A {b}witch{!reset} is a practitioner of magical skills and abilities such as using spells, incantations and magical rituals. Any other exact details get blurred by cultural context.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition filter="superhero" role="other" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="1097" marker="SuperheroArticle" dialogue-layer="over">{small}A {small b}superhero{small} is a stock character that possesses abilities beyond those of ordinary people, who typically uses their powers to help the world become a better place, protecting the public, and fighting crime.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="23" weight="0.001">{small}Air (disambiguation). {small b}Air{small} is part of the Earth atmosphere that humans breathe. It's made up of 78% Nitrogen, 21% Oxygen, and 1% other (including water, vapor). Air may also refer to: Music - Air (music), French for aria, various song-like vocal or instrument compositions.{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-scold.png" oneShotId="24">What do you mean that Henry Cavill is not dead? Do you have a source for that? I need to fix that article as soon as possible!</state>
                <state img="#-frown.png" oneShotId="949" dialogue-layer="over">{smaller}Remember to not believe everything you read on Wikipedia. On October 2012, the Asian Football Confederation was forced to apologize to the United Arab Emirates soccer team for referring to them as the "Sand Monkeys"; the spurious nickname had been taken from a vandalized Wikipedia article.{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="959">Did you know that Wikipedia has a Simple English edition? It is a very useful resource for ESL people, uneducated people or younger people. {smaller}(But if you are so young that you do not understand regular Wikipedia, you should not be playing this game!){!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-smirk.png" oneShotId="2674">Part of my goal is to make Britannica-tan redundant.&lt;br&gt;{smaller}For legal reasons, this line{smaller b}contains material that is kept because it is considered humorous. {smaller}Such material is not meant to be taken seriously!{!reset}</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip">
            <case stage="0-5" id="153" priority="142">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" stage="0-6" saidMarker="TheVoiceOfHair==1" sayingMarker="TheVoiceOfHair=2" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="2843" marker="BoboboHair">That is correct! {b}Hair{!reset} is one of the defining characteristics of mammals. The human body is covered in follicles which produce thick terminal and fine vellus hair.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="74">
                <condition role="other" character="mercy" stage="0-6" sayingMarker="WikiPuzzlePieces" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="1474" marker="MercyPuzzle">I believe that learning is like piecing together a puzzle, Ms. Ziegler. The multilingual characters on the puzzle pieces signify many cultures coming together to piece together the puzzle of knowledge, one by one.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="78">
                <condition role="other" character="mercy" stage="0-6" sayingMarker="WikiBrainSpace" />
                <state img="#-frown.png" oneShotId="1490" marker="MercyBrainSpace">I am fully powered by the contributions of Wikipedia's devoted editors. Anything that they do not know or choose to elaborate on, I do not know.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="79">
                <condition role="other" character="mercy" stage="0-6" sayingMarker="WikiItsAllASimulation" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="1491" marker="MercyMultiverseTheory">That &lt;i&gt;is&lt;/i&gt; rather odd, I will admit... Could it be that the Inventory is some sort of multiverse, or a crossover universe like Ernest Cline's 2011 novel &lt;i&gt;Ready Player One&lt;/i&gt;?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="85">
                <condition role="other" character="mercy" stage="0-6" sayingMarker="WikiWhatAreYou" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="MercyWhatAmI">This is... strange. I do not actually know what I am. Am I the embodiment of Wikipedia itself, or just its mascot with a psychic connection to the site? Perhaps this is a mystery left unsolved? Fascinating...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="112">
                <condition role="other" character="twisted_fate" stage="0-6" sayingMarker="Wiki_Reorter0A" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="FateBilgewater">Hmmmm, Bilgewater? I have an article about {b}bilge,{!reset} the part of a boat's hull that would rest on the ground if the vessel were unsupported by water. Is this what you are referring to?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="145">
                <condition role="other" character="jim" stage="0-8" sayingMarker="Wiki-tan0a" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="JimTease1">I apologize, but your post contains unclear language. Would you care to specify what you mean?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="147">
                <condition role="other" character="senko" stage="0-7" />
                <state img="#-wave.png" oneShotId="2800" marker="SenkoAsk1">You could say so! My name is Wikipe-tan, the mascot of Wikipedia, the free encyclopedia that anyone can edit! My goal is to share knowledge with the world!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="28">
                <condition role="other" character="nami" sayingMarker="wiki0" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="100" marker="Nami0">Of course I can answer your questions! I do not know everything, however. I only know things people care enough about to write for the rest of the world to know.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="75">
                <condition role="other" character="miko" sayingMarker="WikipeShoes1" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="1469" marker="MikoYokai">A &lt;i&gt;yōkai&lt;/i&gt;? I do not believe I am. I think that is something I would know about.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5" id="90">
                <condition role="other" character="supernova" sayingMarker="AreYouWikipediaWebsite" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="1524" marker="SupernovaWiki1">Indeed, my good woman! Consider me to be like... the internet's librarian. Helping people to find information, and then directing them to resources where they can learn more.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="84">
                <condition role="other" character="saki_zls" sayingMarker="WikiShoes1" />
                <state img="#-smirk.png" oneShotId="1529" marker="SakiPopulation">{b}Saga Prefecture{!reset} is a prefecture of Japan located on the island of Kyūshū. As of August 1, 2020, Saga Prefecture has a population of 809,248. Does this answer your question?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="91">
                <condition role="other" character="nami" sayingMarker="wiki1" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="NamiStrike">Hmmm... I cannot say that I do. I receive the most fulfillment in life by providing knowledge to people! Although I have gone on strike once.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="118">
                <condition role="other" character="miko" sayingMarker="WikipeApron1" />
                <state img="#-angry.png" marker="MikoEdit2">Miss Miko, I thought I told you, I could not add any new info about something like this without accurate sources! Now... wait... &lt;i&gt;Touhou Project&lt;/i&gt;?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="152">
                <condition role="other" character="takatoshi" sayingMarker="WikipeShoes1" />
                <state img="#-educate.png" marker="TakatoshiDeimos">{smaller b}Deimos,{smaller} a Greek word for &lt;i&gt;dread&lt;/i&gt;, may refer to: Deimos, one of the sons of Ares and Aphrodite in Greek mythology; Deimos, the smaller and outermost of Mars' two natural satellites; Elecnor Deimos, a Spanish aerospace company; Deimos, villain for the Warlord comic series; Deimos, a floating launch platform currently in refit by SpaceX; or Deimos, the brother of Kratos in the God of War series.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-5" id="177">
                <condition role="self" consecutiveLosses="3-5" />
                <state img="#-pissed.png">Aw, come on! Someone is clearly vandalizing this hand!</state>
                <state img="#-pissed.png">This is preposterous! Outrageous! How likely was this to happen? I want a source cited on that!</state>
                <state img="#-pissed.png">Who is dealing these cards?! I want to verify their sources! This has to be apropos!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-5">
                <condition role="self" consecutiveLosses="3" />
                <state img="#-pissed.png">Okay, &lt;i&gt;SOMEONE&lt;/i&gt; must be vandalizing my hands! THIS IS NOT FAIR!!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-5">
                <condition role="self" consecutiveLosses="2" />
                <state img="#-angry.png">Again?! That seems rather suspicious... Something is wrong, I can feel it!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" oneShotId="15" totalRounds="0">
                <state img="#-nervous.png">So I'm first, huh? I guess I need to re-read the article on poker techniques, heh...</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Well, that was... unexpected. We don't have an article on how much of a blow to my ego it was for me to lose first.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_winning">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-casual.png" dialogue-layer="over" weight="0.001">I suppose I had to lose at some point.</state>
                <state img="#-smirk.png">I should commend you on your skills. But since this poker variant is mostly based on chance, that statement would require more accurate sources.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Nothing to worry about. I am still in the lead, after all.</state>
                <state img="#-snooty.png">I still have the advantage, so I can spare some clothing.</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png">Is it me? Sure! I was feeling a bit left out anyway!</state>
                <state img="#-hornyfact.png" oneShotId="1905" dialogue-layer="over">{small}I could teach you how to play better... But you would not grow. You would not improve. You would merely take a shortcut and gain nothing. You would experience a hollow victory, where nothing was risked and nothing was gained.{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">No problem. Even if you vandalized this hand, I would have won anyway.</state>
                <state img="#-neutral.png">You need to learn to change your hands better, like I edit my articles for perfection.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-snooty.png" marker="AllDogsGoToHeaven">I do not think removing my shoes is interesting at all, so I will proceed to tell you all about one of my most treasured childhood movies.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-5">
                <state img="#-casual.png">No problem, it was about time for me to strip some more.</state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png">Thirsty for more? I can spare more clothing. I am in the lead after all.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" dialogue-layer="over">About time I lost. I would give you all some suggestions on how to improve your playing strategies, but that information is already free and available to everyone on Wikipedia.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_normal">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-calm.png" dialogue-layer="over" weight="0.001">Well... It is a game of chance after all. Not all rounds can be won.</state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png">Good plays, everyone. Allow me to recompense your efforts.</state>
                <state img="#-hornyfact.png" dialogue-layer="over">I believe this is one of the reasons people prefer this poker variant. The increased importance of luck makes all rounds unpredictable, while every layer lost makes every round spicier than the one before...</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Well, here goes nothing...</state>
                <state img="#-casual.png">Sure, I will do it. At least I am not losing as bad as others here.</state>
                <state img="#-snooty.png">This is fine. I could be losing worse than this, like someone else here.</state>
                <state img="#-smirk.png">Not exactly what I expected, but I still have a chance to recover from this.</state>
                <state img="#-frown.png">I have to step up my game. Not that I am doing badly, but you never know when the odds might turn against you.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_losing">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <condition role="self" hasHand="High Card" />
                <state img="#-frown.png" oneShotId="1900">I should have expected it with such a hand...</state>
                <state img="#-smirk.png" oneShotId="1901">It appears that the odds were not on my side this time. Very well, I hope you enjoy your strip.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-flirt.png" dialogue-layer="over" weight="0.001">Good plays, everyone. Allow me to recompense your efforts.</state>
                <state img="#-frown.png">I was sure I was at least decent at this game... Looks like I did not read enough articles on the matter.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Am I playing badly? Did I misunderstand the articles on poker strategies?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Could it be that the sources on the poker strategies articles are not reliable? Or could they have been vandalized?</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" weight="0.5">I will strip, but... I should be playing better. I thought I was a better player than this. That upsets me.</state>
                <state img="#-smirk.png">Even if I wear less clothes than you, you want me to strip more? I did not expect you to be this interested in me.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I should not be surprised that you are trying your hardest to see more of me. Just like people can not get enough of Wikipedia's articles.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Seeing you all try this hard to see me naked... It is quite inspiring. I am a bit nervous by your eagerness.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripping">
            <case stage="0" id="148">
                <condition role="other" character="senko" stage="0-7" />
                <state img="#-z-stripping.png" oneShotId="2808" marker="SenkoAsk2">Indeed! Some Japanese folktales speak of kitsune as faithful guardians, friends, and lovers. But there is no need to feel envious of me, Senko-san!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="86">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Nami0" />
                <condition role="other" character="nami" sayingMarker="wiki01_name" />
                <state img="#-z-stripping.png" oneShotId="1565" marker="NamiSelf">{smallbold}Nami{!reset} {small}is a thief and pickpocket who possesses cartographical, meteorological and navigational skills. At first, she is a subordinate of the fishman Arlong, but she is eventually freed of this service and permanently joins Monkey D. Luffy for her dream to write the complete map of the Grand Line.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="87">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Nami0" />
                <condition role="other" character="nami" sayingMarker="wiki01_onepiece" />
                <state img="#-z-stripping2.png" oneShotId="1563" marker="NamiOnePiece">{smallbold}&lt;i&gt;One Piece&lt;/i&gt;{!reset} {small}is a Japanese manga series written and illustrated by Eiichiro Oda. The story follows the adventures of Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body gained the properties of rubber after unintentionally eating a Devil Fruit. With his crew of pirates, named the Straw Hat Pirates, Luffy explores the Grand Line in search of the world's ultimate treasure known as "One Piece" in order to become the next King of the Pirates.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="120">
                <condition role="other" character="miko" saidMarker="WikipeApron1" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="MikoEdit2" />
                <state img="#-z-stripping.png" marker="MikoEdit3">Aha! I found you!&lt;br&gt;{small b}Toyosatomimi no Miko,{small} a Saint living inside the Hall of Dreams' Mausoleum. She is easygoing, and does not appear to take things very seriously, nor does she attempt to try and aggressively convert others to her faith.{!reset}&lt;br&gt;Is this you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="143">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="NamiStrike" />
                <condition role="other" character="nami" sayingMarker="wiki12" />
                <state img="#-z-stripping.png" marker="NamiSopa">On January 18, 2012, I went on strike as part of a blackout coordinated with other sites to spread awareness and objection to the Stop Online Piracy Act.</state>
                <state img="#-z-stripping.png" marker="NamiSopa">In 2012, I temporarily ceased standard operation for a day as part of a coordinated blackout in attempt to protest the Stop Online Piracy Act.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0 3" id="150" oneShotId="16" priority="102">
                <condition role="other" character="supernova" saidMarker="AreYouWikipediaWebsite" sayingMarker="HowMuchDoYouKnowAboutMe" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="SupernovaWiki1" />
                <state img="#-z-stripping2.png" oneShotId="2814" marker="SupernovaWiki2">This is very strange... I do not seem to have an article about you, Miss Supernova. Could you enlighten me about what it is you do, exactly?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-2 4-5" id="151" oneShotId="17" priority="102">
                <condition role="other" character="supernova" saidMarker="AreYouWikipediaWebsite" sayingMarker="HowMuchDoYouKnowAboutMe" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="SupernovaWiki1" />
                <state img="#-z-stripping.png" oneShotId="2822" marker="SupernovaWiki2">This is very strange... I do not seem to have an article about you, Miss Supernova. Could you enlighten me about what it is you do, exactly?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="76">
                <condition role="other" character="miko" sayingMarker="WikipeShoes2" />
                <state img="#-z-stripping.png" oneShotId="1516" marker="MikoShotoku">{smallbold}Prince Shōtoku{!reset} {small}(&lt;i&gt;Shōtoku Taishi,&lt;/i&gt; February 7, 574 – April 8, 622), also known as{!reset} {smallbold}Prince Umayado{!reset} or {smallbold}Prince Kamitsumiya,{!reset} {small}was a semi-legendary regent and a politician of the Asuka period in Japan who served under Empress Suiko. The Prince is renowned for modernizing the government administration and for promoting Buddhism in Japan.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="80">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="MercyMultiverseTheory" />
                <condition role="other" character="mercy" />
                <state img="#-z-stripping2.png" oneShotId="1514" marker="MercyMultiverseTheory2">Or perhaps we are &lt;i&gt;all&lt;/i&gt; but fictional characters... forced forever to strip for the entertainment of others... Such is the nature of the {b}simulation theory,{!reset} the hypothesis that all of reality could in fact be an artificial simulation... "Wikipe-tan only pawn in game of life"...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="115">
                <condition role="other" character="saki_zls" sayingMarker="WikipeShoes2" />
                <state img="#-z-stripping.png" oneShotId="1932" marker="SakiFranchouchou">{small}Franchouchou is an idol group founded by Kotaro Tatsumi and composed of seven legendary idols from different time periods that he brought back to life as zombies with the goal of reviving Saga's declining idol business.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="AllDogsGoToHeaven" />
                <state img="#-z-stripping.png">{small}&lt;i&gt;All Dogs Go to Heaven 2&lt;/i&gt; is a 1996 American animated musical fantasy adventure film, and a sequel to Goldcrest Films' animated film &lt;i&gt;All Dogs Go to Heaven&lt;/i&gt; (1989). This film is notorious because it depicts the death of Doctor Gordon Freeman, who...{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-z-stripping.png">It is customary to start with your shoes or other accessories in games like these. Unless you want to surprise your opponents.</state>
                <state img="#-z-stripping.png">Most strip poker players start by stripping something decent and/or superfluous. In this case, I will start with my shoes.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-z-stripping.png">An {b}apron{!reset} is a garment that is worn over other clothing and covers mainly the front of the body. The word comes from old French &lt;i&gt;napron&lt;/i&gt;, meaning a small piece of cloth; however, over time "a napron" became "an apron."</state>
                <state img="#-z-stripping.png">An {b}apron{!reset} is mostly known as a functional accessory that protects one's clothes and skin from stains and marks.</state>
                <state img="#-z-stripping.png">Various types of {b}aprons{!reset} may also be worn as a decoration, for hygienic reasons, as part of a uniform, or as protection from certain dangers such as acid, allergens, or excessive heat. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-z-stripping.png">If you were hoping for traditional bra and panties, you might be in for a surprise...</state>
                <state img="#-z-stripping.png">I might be as open and easy to read as a book, but even I hold some surprises...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-z-stripping.png">Well, there go the stockings then. I hope you enjoyed watching me wear them!</state>
                <state img="#-z-stripping2.png">I was under the impression that wearing the stockings with the swimsuit would accentuate the fanservice aspect of the outfit. But if you desire me to strip them off, I will...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-z-stripping.png">Do not expect me to take it off all at once. Every other girl wears a bra and panties {smaller}[citation needed]{!reset} so it would only be fair for me to have two chances!</state>
                <state img="#-z-stripping.png">I consulted with the administration early on, and they were okay with me stripping the swimsuit in two turns. I hope you are not disappointed!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-z-stripping.png">W-well... There it goes then. You will see all of me like I was an open article for everyone to read...</state>
                <state img="#-z-stripping.png">I cannot believe it has come to this... But oh well...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripped">
            <case stage="3" id="82">
                <condition role="other" character="misty_hgss" stage="0-3" />
                <state img="#-aa-stripped.png" oneShotId="1497" marker="MistySwimsuit">You find yourself in good company, Misty! As the representative for both the fanservice article and the WikiProject for Anime and Manga, I have to be ready to multitask!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="83">
                <condition role="other" character="misty_hgss" stage="6" />
                <state img="#-aa-stripped.png" oneShotId="1507">Good one, Misty! But I do not believe I will lose again after this. {smaller}[dubious - discuss{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="149">
                <condition role="other" character="senko" stage="0-7" />
                <state img="#-aa-stripped.png" marker="SenkoInventory">Well, you &lt;i&gt;could&lt;/i&gt; say that... I came to the Inventory because I heard it had been converted to a strip poker club and wanted to see if it was true.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png" marker="SenkoStripPoker">You are correct... Though I have an article about it,  I have never played strip poker before, and I wanted to get direct information on what it is like.</state>
                <state img="#-donations.png" marker="SenkoDonations">Actually, I came here to ask for donations! Wikipedia could always use the money to stay free and open to the public, after all.</state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png" marker="SenkoTiring">My dear, always answering people's questions about everything... it gets tiring. I never have time for romance. I feel this is a good way to take a break.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-6" id="165" priority="103">
                <condition role="other" character="supernova" saidMarker="HowMuchDoYouKnowAboutMe" sayingMarker="NotFamousEnough" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="SupernovaWiki2" />
                <state img="#-aa-stripped.png" marker="SupernovaWiki3">Oooooh, I see. I &lt;i&gt;do&lt;/i&gt; have an article about superheroes. Maybe you are there! Although the article on "supernova" redirects to the astronomical event.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="166">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="NamiSopa" />
                <condition role="other" character="nami" sayingMarker="wiki2s" />
                <state img="#-scold.png" marker="NamiSopa2">As a matter of fact, &lt;i&gt;most&lt;/i&gt; people were against it! It would have stopped piracy, but it also would have dealt a blow to the sharing of open and free information!</state>
                <state img="#-scold.png" marker="NamiSopaGun">Imagine if someone invented a gun that was guaranteed to kill its target 100% of the time, but it also killed &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; in the process. That is what this bill was like.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="77">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="MikoShotoku" />
                <condition role="other" character="miko" />
                <state img="#-aa-stripped.png" oneShotId="1501">{small}The Prince is renowned for modernizing the government administration and for promoting Buddhism in Japan. Over successive generations, a devotional cult arose around the figure of Prince Shōtoku for the protection of Japan, the Imperial Family, and for Buddhism.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4" id="81">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="MercyMultiverseTheory2" />
                <condition role="other" character="mercy" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="1511">{small}This theory has been explored in many science fiction stories and films, including Philip K. Dick's short story "We Can Remember It for You Wholesale," which was adapted as &lt;i&gt;Total Recall&lt;/i&gt; in 1990... what were we talking about again?{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="88">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="NamiSelf" />
                <condition role="other" character="nami" />
                <state img="#-aa-stripped.png" oneShotId="1541">{small}In the series, Nami is the Straw Hat Pirates' navigator, and dreams of drawing a map of the entire world. Despite her initial distrust of pirates, Nami eventually changes her mind after being around Luffy and the rest of the crew. Nami is depicted as an intelligent girl who has an obsession with obtaining money.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="89">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="NamiOnePiece" />
                <condition role="other" character="nami" />
                <state img="#-aa-stripped.png" oneShotId="1552" marker="NamiOnePiece2">My dear Nami, you should know that I hold all kinds of information. As Walt Whitman put it in his poem, "Song of Myself," I contain multitudes!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="161">
                <condition role="other" character="miko" sayingMarker="WikipeApron3" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" marker="MikoLesbian">U-um, sure, whatever you say. I will be sure to jot that down.&lt;br&gt;{small}&lt;i&gt;(Is that an invitation?...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="167">
                <condition role="other" character="saki_zls" sayingMarker="WikipeShoes3" />
                <state img="#-aa-stripped.png" marker="SakiPsychic">I am a conveyor of information, Miss Saki. I only know what my contributors have told me. Nothing more, nothing less.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="AllDogsGoToHeaven" />
                <state img="#-pissed.png">...Hey, wait a second. That article was vandalized! &lt;i&gt;How dare they! I HATE it when they vandalize articles like that!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-aa-stripped.png">As the game goes on, I might lose again, and I will strip more and more clothes until there is nothing left.</state>
                <state img="#-aa-stripped.png">This may have been an easy strip, but future ones will not be as uninteresting as this one.</state>
                <state img="#-aa-stripped.png">Next up comes my apron. Do you think you will get me to take it off?</state>
                <state img="#-aa-stripped.png">Do not get used to seeing me strip, by the way. This is the last time I will ever do it.{smaller}[citation needed]{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-aa-stripped.png">Do not get used to seeing me strip, by the way. This is the last time I will ever do it.{smaller}[dubious - discuss]{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-aa-stripped.png">Aprons can be used in work stations to hold extra tools and pieces or protecting from dust and unwanted products. I will get mine back as soon as I beat you!</state>
                <state img="#-aa-stripped2.png">I am going to miss this apron. My cosplay maid outfit feels incomplete without it. But if I win, I can get it back.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="174">
                <state img="#-aa-stripped.png">As the representative for the WikiProject for Anime and Manga, I have to be prepared to multitask, such as representing cosplay culture and swimsuit fanservice as well!</state>
                <state img="#-aa-stripped.png">It might seem to be counterintuitive to wear a swimsuit under a dress, but as the representative for both the fanservice article and the WikiProject for Anime and Manga, I have to be ready to multitask!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-aa-stripped.png">Now only my swimsuit remains. Will you be able to take me out of it?</state>
                <state img="#-aa-stripped.png">I like this swimsuit. I hope you like it too, since it is going to be a while until you get me to strip out of it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-aa-stripped.png">There is nothing wrong with my breasts, is there? The way you are looking at them is... Oh, I get it. You are aroused! This is great!</state>
                <state img="#-aa-stripped.png">At least you will get to watch my breasts for a while. But I will try harder to win now! So do not expect to see more!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-aa-stripped2.png">Just like a well-written article. Organized, neat, and perfectly trimmed!</state>
                <state img="#-aa-stripped2.png">This is it then. All of me. I hope you are not disappointed...</state>
                <state img="#-aa-stripped.png">Responsible hygiene is crucial for a healthy sex life. A trimmed crotch is a good balance between tidiness and naturality.</state>
                <state img="#-aa-stripped.png">I am as diligent with my body hygiene as I am with my articles! I try to keep a good shape and a neat, trimmed crotch. And I am proud of it!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_strip">
            <case stage="0-8" id="139">
                <condition role="target" character="jim" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="2667" marker="JimStrip1">I have heard you are an astronaut, but according to my records, humans have never sent manned missions beyond our solar system. Could you provide some information, Mister...?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-flirt.png">The more time I spend in this game, the more I find myself enjoying what I see.</state>
                <state img="#-snooty.png">This will certainly be... educational.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">In most cultures, men are usually less concerned with showing their bodies off than women. I hope you are comfortable doing so, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-neutral.png">Remember that you do not have to strip if you do not want to, ~name~. Despite most cultures having little taboos on men showing off most of their bodies, we still respect your modesty.</state>
                <state img="#-hornyfact.png">Here is a fact: You are closer to showing us all of your body. And on a personal note, I am eager to see it.</state>
                <state img="#-smirk.png">I heard that you were hiding some surprises for us... Care to verify that claim?</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png">Did you know that male strippers rose to prominence in the 1970s? Until then, strippers in Western cultures were almost invariably female, performing to male audiences.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_strip">
            <case stage="0-8" id="65" priority="381">
                <condition role="target" character="nami_szs" stage="0" notSaidMarker="goodBye" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png">But... it is in the title? I am unsure of how you could have missed such an obvious fact.</state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png">Technically, you &lt;i&gt;did&lt;/i&gt; sign up for it. So, it is your move!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="56">
                <condition role="target" character="amy_rose" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="1154" marker="AmyStrip1">Amy Rose! It is a pleasure to meet you... although wait, the page says that you're a hedgehog... but you resemble a human? Should I update my sources?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="100">
                <condition role="target" character="aella" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-smirk.png" oneShotId="1802">I will have you know that trying to stall during a game of strip poker is considered bad practice, Aella. But if you are not confident in stripping yourself, I can always help you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="49">
                <condition role="target" character="zone-tan" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="1134">It is an honor to play with another internet famous -tan. Despite your more... &lt;i&gt;adult&lt;/i&gt; tendencies colliding with the term's original meaning.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="48">
                <condition role="target" character="polly" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="1131" marker="PoltergeistArticle">{small}In ghostlore, a {small b}poltergeist{small} is a type of ghost or spirit that is responsible for physical disturbances, such as loud noises and objects being moved or destroyed. The word comes from Germanic languages, meaning "noisy ghost."</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="50">
                <condition role="target" character="twilight" />
                <state img="#-neutral.png" oneShotId="1136">It is an honor to play with you, Princess Twilight. Have you considered adding your equestrian knowledge to Wikipedia, the free encyclopedia that anyone can edit?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="47">
                <condition role="target" character="hermione" />
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="1138">Ms. Granger, right? Do you think there is any chance for the wizarding world to ever share their knowledge with us muggles?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="55">
                <condition role="target" character="hermione_granger" />
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="1142">Ms. Granger, right? Do you think there is any chance for the wizarding world to ever share their knowledge with us muggles?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-smirk.png">It is customary when a player loses a round of strip poker for them to remove an item of clothing. So what will yours be, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Different cultures have very diverse views on women's bodies. No matter which one you come from, just know that such behaviour is accepted and encouraged here.</state>
                <state img="#-neutral.png">Remember that you are playing here because you want to. If you do not feel comfortable, you can leave and nobody will judge you for it.</state>
                <state img="#-casual.png" dialogue-layer="over">The ideal body type as envisioned by members of society has changed throughout history. Who knows what the next model will be like?</state>
                <state img="#-hornyfact.png">It is always a pleasure to see someone showing more of themselves. Especially if they are pleasing to look at.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="1919">I know I act cool and confident at times, but in all honesty, the idea of watching other women stripping naked is kind of... new and exciting for me.</state>
                <state img="#-donations.png">Could you consider donating your clothes to the Wikimedia Foundation after this? Anything that could help the free encyclopedia that anyone can edit would help!</state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png">Let me take a good look at you... like a good, well written article...</state>
                <state img="#-hornyfact.png">I hope you do not mind my ogling. You are invited to do so with me if you so desire.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Do you enjoy having other people watching your naked body, ~name~? Some people expose themselves on public regularly, and are usually met with compliments if done in a place such as this.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="tie">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-scold.png">A tie? Now this is certainly unexpected! These are very rare!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I wonder what the probability of ties is... I need to re-study the article on poker statistics.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition status="exposed" role="target" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">W-well, that's just not fair! That hardly counts this late in the game!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-flirt.png">Is that it?</state>
                <state img="#-frown.png">Am I playing the game right? I would not take off my hairpieces one at a time, or my stockings one at a time either...</state>
                <state img="#-smirk.png">Is everything okay, ~target~? You seem to be stalling by removing something like that. You are not afraid, are you?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">To think I could be stalling like ~target~ by removing all of my clothing one at a time... But would that not defeat the purpose of strip poker?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-smirk.png">That was not particularly hard for you to remove, was it?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">And nothing of value was lost. Now we can continue with the game!</state>
                <state img="#-smirk.png">Maybe you will play better once you start losing actual clothing.</state>
                <state img="#-scold.png">Some strip poker venues consider accessories as cheating, you know!</state>
                <state img="#-hornyfact.png">Here is a fun fact for you: Stalling with accessories is often seen as bad manners in certain strip poker joints, since they defeat the purpose of the game.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0-8" id="110">
                <condition role="target" character="moon" stage="1" />
                <test expr="~background~" value="inventory" />
                <state img="#-snooty.png" marker="MoonManagement">Interesting. Usually when people cheat at this game, it is to &lt;i&gt;postpone&lt;/i&gt; their inevitable nudity, not because they are &lt;i&gt;eager&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="119">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="AmyStrip1" />
                <condition role="target" character="amy_rose" stage="0" saidMarker="wiki_AmyStrip1_resp" />
                <state img="#-neutral.png" marker="AmyStrip2">I see. Miss Rose, my article on you is... rather lacking. In fact, you are just listed under a list of Sonic's friends and allies. Could you help fill in any information to make your article more accurate and up-to-date?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="122">
                <condition role="target" character="blake" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-snooty.png" oneShotId="1967">No pressure, Blake. I believe I already know what you are about to reveal.</state>
                <state img="#-snooty.png" oneShotId="1968">If my sources about &lt;i&gt;RWBY&lt;/i&gt; are accurate--which they are--then I think you are about to reveal the secret about your true nature.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition status="exposed" role="target" />
                <state img="#-snooty.png">Holding onto an unimportant item for so long in the game is an uncommon technique, but not unheard of. It is frequently utilized by people who are losing and want to stall the inevitable!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-smirk.png">Are you afraid of removing real clothing, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png">If you need suggestions for what to remove next, I would love to share mine.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Is it normal for the women of this culture to feel embarrassed by showing off their own bodies?&lt;br&gt;What even &lt;i&gt;is&lt;/i&gt; the culture of this place...? Or is it more like a melting pot?</state>
                <state img="#-snooty.png">Take your time, ~name~. The more time we spend together, the more time I have to study you and your playing patterns.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="0-8" id="99">
                <condition role="target" character="maki" stage="2" sayingMarker="makidoctor" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="1801">Wikipedia's pages about medical topics are widely used. I should know from the number of med school students who have frequented my database...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="123">
                <condition role="target" character="blake" stage="6" />
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="1977">That was very brave of you, Blake! I am aware of your reasons for concealing your faunus identity.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="173">
                <condition role="target" character="lucy" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-hornyfact.png" marker="LucyMalfunction">Do not worry, Lucy! A {b}wardrobe malfunction{!reset} is a clothing failure that accidentally or intentionally exposes a person's intimate parts. These are not uncommon!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="111">
                <condition role="target" character="moon" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="MoonManagement" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="MoonManagement2">Although if they choose to participate, they probably &lt;i&gt;want&lt;/i&gt; to strip nude anyway. I do not have any sources on this, but it can be logically deduced.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-flirt.png">I hope to see more of you in the future.</state>
                <state img="#-smirk.png">Please, let us know if you are not willing to strip nude. That would save everyone a lot more time.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">You don't have to strip if it makes you uncomfortable. But I advise you to not sign up for strip poker games in the future if that's the case.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">That article was merely a stub. I hope you help improve the mood of the game by expanding the repertoire of articles you are willing to strip.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-calm.png">I look forward to seeing more of you, ~target~.</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png">The more clothing you remove, the more I know about you! And knowledge is always exciting.</state>
                <state img="#-smirk.png">Go on, ~target~. I want to see more of you. All of you, if possible.</state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png">I'd better remember this. I do not want to forget about your ~clothing~ when I write the article on this place.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_minor">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-flirt.png">This is like a reverse jigsaw puzzle. The more pieces I see you take off, the more I learn about your true form.</state>
                <state img="#-hornyfact.png">We are very close to removing the important pieces now. This will get exciting.</state>
                <state img="#-donations.png">Remember that you can donate your clothing to Wikipedia. We are always looking for any source of income to keep all this knowledge free and available for everyone.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-calm.png">I had a suspicion you were going to take your ~clothing~ off. But I had no sources backing it, so I decided to not say it.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">You have our full attention, ~target~.</state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png">By removing your clothes in a sexually suggestive or seductive manner, you have technically become what is usually called a "stripper." So, while you are at it, why not enjoy it?</state>
                <state img="#-neutral.png">It is customary to strip one's clothes in practiced or unrehearsed dance moves if the aim is to titillate the audience.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_minor">
            <case stage="0-8" id="53">
                <condition role="target" character="emi" stage="7" />
                <test expr="~target.costume~" value="emi_lovebunny" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">In medicine, a {b}prosthesis{!reset} or {b}prosthetic implant{!reset} is an artificial device that replaces a missing body part, which may be lost through trauma, disease, or a condition present at birth (congenital disorder).</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png">Did you know that the term &lt;i&gt;prosthesis&lt;/i&gt; derives from the Ancient Greek term meaning "addition, application, attachment"?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="18">
                <condition role="target" character="sonya" stage="6" sayingMarker="commando" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{b}War paint{!reset} is paint ritually applied to the face and/or body prior to going into a battle. It may also refer to &lt;i&gt;Warpaint&lt;/i&gt;, a 2008 album by the Black Crowes.</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png">{small}Military camouflage is the use of camouflage by an armed force to protect personnel and equipment from observation by enemy forces. The French slang word &lt;i&gt;camouflage&lt;/i&gt; came into common English usage during World War I when the concept of visual deception developed into an essential part of modern military tactics.{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-hornyfact.png">{small}&lt;i&gt;Commando&lt;/i&gt; is a 1985 American action film directed by Mark L. Lester and starring Arnold Schwarzenegger, Rae Dawn Chong, and Alyssa Milano. The term "commando" also refers to the act of going commando, or to go without underwear.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-snooty.png" marker="Ecdysiast">An {b}ecdysiast{!reset} (pronounced ek-dee-siast) is a humorous yet accurate way to refer to what's commonly known as a stripper, if you do not want to be referred as such.</state>
                <state img="#-donations.png">Remember that in order to keep Wikipedia free and available to everyone, we depend on donations. You can donate your clothing if you so desire; every source of income is accepted.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_major">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-nervous.png">It is hard to believe that I actually came to a strip poker joint... And that there is a man stripping in front of me right now...</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I wonder what my sisters would think about me right now... being here and watching a man remove his clothes in front of me...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_major">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-casual.png">Nothing that I have not seen before in an article. But I am glad that you managed to strip out of it!</state>
                <state img="#-hornyfact.png">Careful, ~name~. If you keep up at this rate, you may become the picture for our article on gigolos.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_major">
            <case stage="0-8" id="34" priority="381">
                <condition role="target" character="nami_szs" stage="0" sayingMarker="goodBye" />
                <state img="#-pissed.png" oneShotId="1879" marker="NamiGoodbye">Nami, you should know that it is considered &lt;i&gt;highly&lt;/i&gt; bad form to bail on a game of strip poker!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="69">
                <condition role="target" character="starfire" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-flirt.png" oneShotId="1897">I do not know if I agree with the logic, Ms. Starfire, but I am not one to complain about what I am seeing.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="108">
                <condition role="target" character="moon" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="1874" marker="MoonBra">...I-I see you chose to remove your bra first. This is... an uncommon practice during strip poker, but not unheard of.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-excited.png">Go, ~name~! Let's see more of you!</state>
                <state img="#-casual.png">This does not have to be embarrassing for you. Many cultures have zero taboos about nudity!</state>
                <state img="#-hornyfact.png">You can prolong the undressing with delaying tactics such as placing your recently removed clothes or hands in front of the undressed body parts.</state>
                <state img="#-smirk.png">If your aim is to arouse the ones watching the strip, you might invite them to remove your clothing themselves. ~player~ here seems quite eager to do so.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_major">
            <case stage="0-8" id="30">
                <condition role="target" character="jasmine" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="1888">Sorry, Princess Jasmine. Being Disney royalty does not exactly lend itself to secrecy.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="31">
                <condition role="target" character="emi" stage="8" />
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="1890">Stereotypical images of pirates often include anteqated prosthetic limbs, including peglegs and hooks for hands.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="1891">Classic images of prosthetics include Captain Hook from &lt;i&gt;Peter Pan&lt;/i&gt; and other pirates with peglegs, although the history of prosthetics can be traced to the ancient Greeks, Romans and Egyptians.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="35">
                <condition role="target" character="mulan" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-wave.png" oneShotId="1884">Fa Mulan! It is an honor to be playing a game with you. May the odds be ever in your favor!</state>
                <state img="#-smirk.png" oneShotId="1885">Fa Mulan! I recognized you from your face and pseudonym. Disney does not exactly keep it a secret, but I did out of respect for you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="68">
                <condition role="target" character="ringo_ando" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="1881">This is a paradox... If you were not expecting a situation like this, then maybe you should not have played strip poker?</state>
                <state img="#-smirk.png">Although your bra is adorable, I am confused as to how you did not expect this outcome when playing strip poker.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="104">
                <condition role="target" character="navi" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="1824">Fascinating... Our sources do not possess this information about you. Do you mind if I call Commons-tan so she can get a picture of you in this form, Navi?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="109">
                <condition role="target" character="moon" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="MoonBra" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="1899" marker="MoonBra2">Well, going braless, which for many years was considered a political statement, has in recent years become fashionable. So I suppose this is not against the rules...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="37">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="NamiGoodbye" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="1894">And she's gone. Well, we do not need her, the rest of us can just play on our own!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-excited.png">That was very brave of you, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png">This is wonderful. The more layers you remove, the more information I learn about you.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-hornyfact.png">Both females and males develop breasts from the same embryological tissues. So, even if you refuse to realize it, yours and mine are very similar.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-flirt.png">{small}Certain male deities representing regeneration and fertility were occasionally depicted with breast-like appendices, such as the river god Hapy who was considered to be responsible for the annual overflowing of the Nile.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I have seen pictures of these before in many articles... Animal penises, human penises, all kinds... So why am I so nervous? Haha...</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">I have seen pictures of penises many times during my editing sessions... N-not because I wanted to! It's not my fault that the articles on sexual organs are so popular that people constantly edit them wrong!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_small_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-snooty.png">Surgical penis enlargement methods can be effective; however, such methods carry risks of complications and are not medically indicated except in cases involving a micropenis.</state>
                <state img="#-smirk.png">Limited scientific evidence supports the idea that you can achieve some penis elongation by prolonged traction.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">...This is merely a stub. You could help us all by expanding it.</state>
                <state img="#-smirk.png">This penis is a stub. You can help Wikipedia by expanding it.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_medium_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-nervous.png">It's just the primary sexual organ that male animals use to inseminate females (or hermaphrodites) during copulation... No need to feel so nervous around it...</state>
                <state img="#-hornyfact.png">{smaller}The {smaller b}human penis{smaller} is an external male intromittent organ that additionally serves as the urinary duct. The main parts are the root (radix); the body (corpus); and the epithelium of the penis including the shaft skin and the foreskin (prepuce) covering the glans penis.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_large_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8" id="60">
                <condition role="target" character="lymilark" sayingMarker="atoncimeni" />
                <state img="#-hornyfact.png">In modern society, nudity and clothing are connected to many cultural categories such as identity, privacy, social status, and moral behavior.</state>
                <state img="#-scold.png">Much of this comes from the Abrahamic religions (Judaism, Christianity, and Islam), which have viewed being naked as shameful and essentially negative. But may I just say, you have nothing to be ashamed of!</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png">{small}In Asia, the norms regarding public nudity are in keeping with the cultural values of social propriety and human dignity. Rather than being perceived as immoral or shameful, nakedness is perceived as a breach of etiquette.{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">{small}In America, nudity is more likely to be seen sexually, while in much of Europe, there is more openness to non-sexual nudity in recreation and daily life. Although this does not really apply when we are playing strip poker...{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-nervous.png">{smaller}A systematic review of 15,521 men (and the best research to date on the topic, as the subjects were measured by health professionals) in 2015 concluded that the average length of an erect human penis is 13.12 cm (5.17 inches) long. So... it is fair to say that yours is above average.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-8" id="22" priority="522">
                <condition role="other" character="yuelia" stage="6" />
                <condition role="target" character="megumin" stage="6" saidMarker="yuelia_jointStrip" sayingMarker="yuelia_jointStrip2" />
                <state img="#-smirk.png" oneShotId="1742">If your aim is to arouse the ones watching the strip, you might invite them to remove your clothing themselves. I see Megumin is partaking in this practice.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="46">
                <condition role="target" character="panty" stage="0" sayingMarker="panty_stripping_dress" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="1744">...A-although it is not &lt;i&gt;unheard of&lt;/i&gt; to remove a large item such as one's dress first, it is uncommon. I will be watching with great interest!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="159">
                <condition role="target" character="saki_zls" />
                <state img="#-smirk.png">I would say, "Don't lose your head," but I did not figure I would mean it &lt;i&gt;literally&lt;/i&gt; this time!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-angry.png">I have studied the human mammaries for a while now... N-not that I care that much about the topic! It is just a very popular article!</state>
                <state img="#-hornyfact.png">Many people theorize that the act of stripping and the anticipation at the sight of breasts produces more excitement than the sight itself. I have no sources on this, but I would love for you to contribute.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_small_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-educate.png">Your breasts may be underdeveloped, but your areolae and nipples seem to be perfectly functional!</state>
                <state img="#-scold.png">{smaller}According to "Breast Size Perception and Satisfaction, Body Image, and Psychological Functioning in Caucasian and Asian American College Women" by Elissa Koff &amp; Amy Benavage, many women regard their breasts as important to their sexual attractiveness, as a sign of femininity that is important to their sense of self. A woman with smaller breasts may regard her breasts as less attractive, but she should not have to!{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-smirk.png">{small}Mammary intercourse is mostly suited for women with naturally larger breasts, while it is recommended that woman with smaller breasts be on top.&lt;br&gt;Smaller female breasts, however, tend to be more sensitive than larger ones.{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-scold.png">It has been said that breast implants are not flexible enough to sustain mammary intercourse.{smaller}[citation needed]{!reset}&lt;br&gt;So you should feel proud of your natural breasts!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_medium_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-educate.png">{smaller}Scientists hypothesize that non-paraphilic sexual attraction to breasts is the result of their function as a secondary sex characteristic. The breasts play roles in both sexual pleasure and reproduction. Men typically find female breasts attractive and this holds true for a variety of cultures.{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-snooty.png">{smaller}Zoologist and ethologist Desmond Morris theorizes that cleavage is a sexual signal that imitates the image of the cleft between the buttocks, which, according to Morris in &lt;i&gt;The Naked Ape&lt;/i&gt;, is also unique to humans, other primates as a rule having much flatter buttocks.{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-snooty.png">{smaller}Evolutionary psychologists theorize that humans' permanently enlarged breasts, in contrast to other primates' breasts, which only enlarge during ovulation, allows human females to "solicit [human] male attention and investment even when they are not really fertile."{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Sexual attraction to breasts is considered normal unless it is exclusive and is therefore a form of partialism.</state>
                <state img="#-hornyfact.png">There is a widespread fascination with women's breasts, and especially their size. Many people, both male and female, consider breasts an important female secondary sex characteristic.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_large_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-educate.png">{smaller}The basic components of a mature mammary gland are the alveoli (hollow cavities, a few millimeters large) lined with milk-secreting cuboidal cells and surrounded by myoepithelial cells. These alveoli join to form groups known as lobules. Each lobule has a lactiferous duct that drains into openings in the nipple.{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-snooty.png">{smaller}In European pre-historic societies, sculptures of female figures with pronounced or highly exaggerated breasts were common. A typical example is the so-called Venus of Willendorf, one of many Paleolithic Venus figurines with ample hips and bosom. Artifacts such as bowls, rock carvings, and sacred statues with breasts have been recorded from 15,000 BC up to late antiquity all across Europe, North Africa, and the Middle East.{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-hornyfact.png">{smaller}Many female deities representing love and fertility were associated with breasts and breast milk. Figures of the Phoenician goddess Astarte were represented as pillars studded with breasts. Isis, an Egyptian goddess who represented, among many other things, ideal motherhood, was often portrayed as suckling pharaohs, thereby confirming their divine status as rulers.{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-hornyfact.png">{smaller}In Ancient Greece, there were several cults worshiping the "Kourotrophos," the suckling mother, represented by goddesses such as Gaia, Hera and Artemis. The worship of deities symbolized by the female breast in Greece became less common during the first millennium. The popular adoration of female goddesses decreased significantly during the rise of the Greek city states, a legacy which was passed on to the later Roman Empire.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="no_bra" role="target" />
                <state img="#-hornyfact.png">In Western society, there is an increasing trend towards {b}bralessness{!reset} among a number of women, especially millennials, who have expressed opposition to and are giving up wearing bras.</state>
                <state img="#-scold.png">Going braless, which for many years was considered a political statement, has in recent years become fashionable. So no need to be ashamed, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png">Women often choose to go braless due to discomfort, health-related issues, their cost, and for social reasons.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-casual.png">Articles on sexual organs are very popular, so I have seen many of these during my spell-checking editing sessions.</state>
                <state img="#-hornyfact.png">In mammals, the vagina is the elastic, muscular part of the female genital tract. In humans, it extends from the vulva to the cervix.</state>
                <state img="#-smirk.png">{small}To accommodate smoother penetration during intercourse or other sexual activity, vaginal moisture increases during sexual arousal in human females and other female mammals. How is yours feeling right now, ~name~?{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png">{small}The {smallbold}vagina{small} and vulva have evoked strong reactions in societies throughout history, including negative perceptions and language, cultural taboos, and their use as symbols for female sexuality, spirituality, or regeneration of life.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8" id="44">
                <condition role="target" character="revy" />
                <condition role="other" character="meia" stage="5" sayingMarker="revyfight" />
                <state img="#-hornyfact.png" oneShotId="1140">{b}Catfight{!reset} (also {b}girl fight{!reset}) is a term for an altercation between two females, often characterized as involving scratching, shoving, slapping, punching, kicking, biting, spitting, hair-pulling, and shirt-shredding.</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="1749">The {b}catfight{!reset} has been a staple of American news media and popular culture since the 1940s, although the use of the term is often considered derogatory or belittling.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="1750">Some observers argue that in its purest form, the word refers to two women, one blonde and the other a brunette, fighting each other... In this case, is having light blue hair close enough to blonde?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="64">
                <condition role="target" character="raven" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-hornyfact.png" oneShotId="1754">Going without lower body undergarments has come to be known by the slang term {b}going commando.{!reset} Not to be confused with the 1985 action film &lt;i&gt;Commando&lt;/i&gt;, starring Arnold Schwarzenegger.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="1755">{small}Not to worry, Raven! In a 2014 internet-based poll, &lt;i&gt;60 Minutes&lt;/i&gt; and &lt;i&gt;Vanity Fair&lt;/i&gt; asked visitors how often they go without underwear, and a quarter of participants said that they did this at least occasionally. So you are in good company!{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="181">
                <condition role="target" character="amy" sayingMarker="planar_form" />
                <test expr="~target.persistent.strange_harmonies~" cmp="&gt;=" value="55" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Well, that was random. But not entirely so, given what I know about &lt;i&gt;Doki Doki Literature Club&lt;/i&gt;. Although... I do not have records of an "Amy" in the game. Strange...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="25">
                <condition count="1" status="naked" />
                <condition count="0" status="masturbating" />
                <condition count="0" status="finished" />
                <condition role="target" character="mulan" />
                <state img="#-hornyfact.png" oneShotId="1747">So, Mulan, how does it make you feel to dress as a man? Some say they experience sexual satisfaction from crossdressing.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-scold.png">So... that's what yours looks like. Don't worry, ~name~. I will not tell anyone!&lt;br&gt;{small}&lt;i&gt;(...But I might include it in the article...)&lt;/i&gt;{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-smirk.png">I will treasure this information forever, ~name~. And I am sure the internet will do so too.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">{small}W-well... &lt;i&gt;there&lt;/i&gt; is a new one for the article.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_lost">
            <case stage="0-8" id="162" oneShotId="13">
                <condition filter="original_character" role="target" />
                <condition count="0" role="target" character="supernova" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="1250" marker="original">Ah, ~name~! You are from... wait... hang on... this is strange...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <test expr="~player~" value="Nikkimaria" />
                <state img="#-smirk.png" marker="Nikkimaria" set-intelligence="good">
                    <text>I am going to assume that you are not actually Nikkimaria and are just hoping to get a reaction out of me. However, I refuse to call you that, so I will just call you Prankster.</text>
                    <markers>
                        <marker name="nickname*" op="=" value="Prankster" />
                    </markers>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="smart" role="target" />
                <state img="#-flirt.png" oneShotId="171">You look like the kind of person that could offer a very insightful conversation. In other words, just my type.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="172">{small}It is said that the most intelligent and knowledgeable people have the potential to have the greatest sex if they put their minds into it. It might be a rumor, but I would not mind checking if it is true.{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="173">I hope you do not mind if I invite you to... chat after this game. I am sure you have a lot of interesting things to talk about.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" totalRounds="5-">
                <condition status="not_naked" role="target" />
                <state img="#-hornyfact.png">Getting to see more of your body is always good. I will treasure and remember this new information.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition status="not_naked" role="target" />
                <state img="#-neutral.png">If ~name~ lost, then it is a fact that ~target.ifMale(he|she)~ is the one to strip now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition status="not_lost_all" role="target" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">Do not feel bad for losing. Poker is mostly a game of chance. The real skill is measuring that chance.</state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png">I hope you did not lose on purpose to show off. Did you, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">It is ~name~'s turn!</state>
                <state img="#-neutral.png">What will it be, ~target~?</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png">I will take some notes on this!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" oneShotId="6">
                <condition filter="catfolk" role="other" />
                <state img="#-frown.png">I have to admit that I am a bit biased towards watching catfolk strip, since I have posed as a catgirl myself for the article on catgirls...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-6">
                <state img="#-calm.png">My apologies, ~name~, but as you can see, I cannot afford to lose more rounds if I want to play along with the taboos that make this game interesting.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-excited.png">So exciting! We get to see more of ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png">This is the purpose of these games, after all. We might as well enjoy it.</state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png">I am hoping for this to be exciting. Please try to fulfill those expectations.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_stripping">
            <case stage="0-8" id="144">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="JimStrip1" />
                <condition role="target" character="jim" stage="0" saidMarker="Wiki_resp0a" />
                <state img="#-wave.png" marker="JimStrip2">Raynor... Jim... Aha, I found you! From Blizzard Entertainment's &lt;i&gt;StarCraft&lt;/i&gt; series! Um, yes, I am from the year 2021 of the Common Era, long before any of that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="71">
                <condition role="target" character="polly" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="PoltergeistArticle" />
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="1351">{small}They have traditionally been described as troublesome spirits who haunt a particular person instead of a specific location. Some variation of poltergeist folklore is found in many different cultures.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="original_character" role="target" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="original" />
                <state img="#-neutral.png" oneShotId="1254">Curious... We do not have a page about you or your source material! According to Wikipedia, you do not exist!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <test expr="~clothing~" value="backpack" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">A {b}backpack{!reset} has many names, such as {b}knapsack{!reset}, {b}rucksack{!reset}, {b}rucksac{!reset}, {b}pack{!reset}, {b}sackpack{!reset}, {b}booksack{!reset}, {b}bookbag{!reset}, {b}backsack{!reset}...</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png">Backpacks are commonly used by hikers, students and soldiers. It is one of the most popular means of transportation of heavy loads or different equipment.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">There are many types of backpacks in the world, such as rolling backpacks or hydration backpacks. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <test expr="~clothing~" value="bandages" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">A {b}bandage{!reset} is a piece of material used either to support a medical device such as a dressing or splint, or on its own to provide support to or to restrict the movement of a part of the body.</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png">{small}Bandages are available in a wide range of types, from generic cloth strips to specialized shaped bandages designed for a specific limb or part of the body. Bandages can often be improvised as the situation demands, using clothing, blankets or other material.{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Tight bandages can be used to slow blood flow to an extremity, such as when a leg or arm is bleeding heavily. Good thing that's not the case here, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <test expr="~clothing~" value="bandana" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">A {b}bandana{!reset} is also known as a {b}bandanna{!reset} or a {b}kerchief{!reset}.</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png">A {b}bandana{!reset} is a triangular or square piece of cloth usually worn on the face, neck or head  for protective or decorative purposes.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Bandanas are mostly used to hold hair back, either as a fashionable head accessory, or for practical purposes.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <test expr="~clothing~" value="bikini" />
                <state img="#-hornyfact.png">A {b}bikini{!reset} is a women's two-piece swimsuit. One piece of the attire covers the breasts, and the other part covers the groin and buttocks, leaving an uncovered area between the two that exposes the navel.</state>
                <state img="#-hornyfact.png">{small}Bikinis can come in many different forms and sizes, from bikinis that offer full coverage of the breasts, pelvis, and buttocks, to more revealing designs with a thong or G-string bottom and a top that covers little more than the areolae.{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-hornyfact.png">The shapes of both parts of a bikini resemble women's underwear, and the lower part can range from a revealing thong or G-string to briefs.</state>
                <state img="#-hornyfact.png">{small}The bikini was based on Parisian fashion designer Jacques Heim's earlier design, &lt;i&gt;Atome&lt;/i&gt; ('Atom'), released in May 1946 which was advertised as "the smallest swimsuit in the world."{!reset}</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_stripped">
            <case stage="0-8" id="63">
                <condition role="target" character="raven" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Purple is certainly an uncommon color for hair. Then again, so is my blue hair... b-but it suits you well, Raven!</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png">Alternative hair coloring products are designed to create hair colors not typically found in nature. These are also referred to as "vivid color" in the hairstyling industry.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Is your hair natural or dyed, Miss Raven? Either way, it suits you!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="72">
                <condition role="target" character="polly" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="PoltergeistArticle" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="1349">{small}Poltergeists have popularly been depicted in the film series &lt;i&gt;Poltergeist&lt;/i&gt;, whose first movie was released in 1982. Not to be confused with &lt;i&gt;Poultrygeist&lt;/i&gt;, a 2006 horror-comedy about a fast food restaurant overrun by zombie chickens.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="original_character" role="target" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="original" />
                <state img="#-wave.png" oneShotId="1258">Oh well! It is not my fault that you are not considered noteworthy enough to have an article. Maybe sometime soon, though?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <test expr="~clothing~" value="backpack" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">Some backpacks are equipped with solar panels and USB cables to charge laptops and phones that the wearer might carry in it.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Backpacks in general fall into one of four categories: frameless, external frame, internal frame, and bodypack. You can learn all about them in the Wikipedia article.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <test expr="~clothing~" value="bandages" />
                <state img="#-smug.png">There are many types of bandages. The most popular ones are the adhesive ones, but there's also gauze, compression, triangular, tube, liquid...</state>
                <state img="#-snooty.png">Bandages can be used in martial arts to prevent dislocated joints. But lately, some have decided to use them for esthetic choices.</state>
                <state img="#-smirk.png">I have a lot of knowledge about bandages. Not only did I edit the article multiple times, but I made sure that the guys trying to vandalize it had to learn about them too.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <test expr="~clothing~" value="bandana" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">The word &lt;i&gt;bandana&lt;/i&gt; stems from the Hindi words 'bāndhnū,' or "tie-dyeing," and 'bāndhnā,' "to tie."</state>
                <state img="#-neutral.png">Bandanas can be worn around the mouth and nose to protect from dust inhalation or to hide the identity of its wearer.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Bandanas can be worn around the neck to prevent sunburn. I often use them when going to the beach.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <test expr="~clothing~" value="bikini" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">{small}The term "bikini" was coined by French automobile and fashion designer Louis Réard in July 1946. Réard named the swimsuit after Bikini Atoll, where testing on the new atomic bomb was occurring that summer.{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-smirk.png">{small}Louis Réard termed the swimsuit "bikini" after the American nuclear testing site at Bikini Atoll because he believed its revealing style would create reactions among people similar to those created by America’s atomic bomb in Japan just one summer earlier.{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png">{small}The bikini is often worn in hot weather, while swimming or sunbathing. The design became common in Western countries by the mid 1960s as both swimwear and underwear. By the late 20th century, it was widely used as sportswear in beach volleyball and bodybuilding.{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png">{small}Due to its revealing design, the bikini was considered controversial and was banned in many countries; however, it gained exposure and acceptance as film stars like Brigitte Bardot, Raquel Welch, and Ursula Andress wore them.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_masturbating">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="chair_forfeit" role="target" />
                <state img="#-hornyfact.png" oneShotId="3627">{small}One of the basic pieces of furniture, a {b small}chair{small} is a type of seat. Its primary features are two pieces of a durable material, attached as back and seat to one another at a 90° or slightly greater angle.</state>
                <state img="#-hornyfact.png" oneShotId="3628">{small}Used in a number of rooms in homes, in schools and offices, and in various other workplaces, {small b}chairs{small} may be made of wood, metal, or synthetic materials, and either the seat alone or the entire chair may be padded or upholstered in various colors and fabrics.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="3629">{smaller b}Chairs{smaller} vary in design. An {smaller b}armchair{smaller} has armrests fixed to the seat; a {smaller b}recliner{smaller} is upholstered and has a mechanism that allows one to lower the chair's back and raise into place a fold-out footrest; a {smaller b}rocking chair{smaller} has legs fixed to two long curved slats; and a {smaller b}wheelchair{smaller} has wheels fixed to an axis under the seat.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-smirk.png">Show off for us, ~name~. This will be educational.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-smug.png">You never had a chance against me, ~target~. Now you know what to do.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-smirk.png">Oh, do not worry. I am taking mental notes as we speak. I am sure I will remember all of this...</state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png">I have to watch very closely. It is for science, you know.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_masturbating">
            <case stage="8" id="168">
                <condition role="self" notSaidMarker="cbt" />
                <condition count="3-4" gender="male" role="other" />
                <state img="#-hornyfact.png" oneShotId="3182" marker="cbt2" collectible="cbt">{smaller b}Cock and ball torture (CBT), penis torture{smaller} or {smaller b}dick torture{smaller} is a sexual activity involving application of pain or constriction to the penis or testicles. This may involve directly painful activities, such as genital piercing, wax play, genital spanking, squeezing, ball-busting, genital flogging, urethral play, tickle torture, erotic electrostimulation, kneeing or kicking. The recipient of such activities may receive direct physical pleasure via masochism, or emotional pleasure through erotic humiliation, or knowledge that the play is pleasing to a sadistic dominant. Many of these practices carry significant health risks. {!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-flirt.png">We truly are primates after all. Look at your technique...</state>
                <state img="#-hornyfact.png">I wonder if this is relevant information that I should add to the article... I'd better take some notes just in case...</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Oh my... This is certainly very... &lt;i&gt;educational...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-smirk.png">Are you going to give us your "donation" soon, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png">{small}Male masturbation techniques may differ between males who have been circumcised and those who have not. Some techniques which may work for one individual can be difficult or uncomfortable for another.{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-hornyfact.png">Is that technique comfortable for you, ~target~? On a scale of 1 to 10, how much are you enjoying it?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Is that technique your preferred one, ~target~? Is that the one you would like your partners to perform if they were masturbating you?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I am noticing a lack of prostate massage during your masturbation... Is that not where the male G-spot resides? Would that not be pleasurable for you?</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Those motions seem rather repetitive. Have you considered rubbing or massaging the glands, their rims or the frenular delta? I could show you how... i-if you want to, that is.</state>
                <state img="#-neutral.png">Have you considered using your free hand to fondle your testicles or nipples, ~target~? I read that those are male erogenous zones as well.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I hope you are not feeling uncomfortable by us watching you, ~target~. I, for one, am quite enjoying your performance.</state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png">You are quite the talented onanist, ~target~. Or at least, a very entertaining one.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-8">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Enjoying the view, ~name~? Don't worry. You are not the first to masturbate to my "fanservice."</state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png">Do you normally use personal lubricants when masturbating, ~target~? If you are lacking on masturbation cream, we can always use saliva...</state>
                <state img="#-snooty.png">Have you considered applying pressure to your perineum to stimulate yourself better? I could show you how, if you wanted to.</state>
                <state img="#-snooty.png" oneShotId="203" marker="ProstateMassageSuggestion">Just so you know, ~target~, there is another often unexplored way of giving men pleasure. I could show you with just one finger.</state>
                <state img="#-neutral.png">{small}If you want a more realistic experience, you could keep your hand stationary while pumping into it with pelvic thrusts. If you are attracted to female-presenting people, I hope I can provide for your fantasies.{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png">If you wrote an article on masturbation techniques, ~target~, I would not mind giving it a couple of revisions... Maybe even taking a deeper dive into the source...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-smirk.png">Was that pleasurable, ~name~? It certainly looked that way.</state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png">On a scale from 1 to 10, how would you rate your satisfaction, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Thank you for your... &lt;i&gt;generous donation,&lt;/i&gt; ~target~.</state>
                <state img="#-snooty.png">I hope that was just the &lt;i&gt;citation&lt;/i&gt; that you &lt;i&gt;needed&lt;/i&gt;, ~target~.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-hornyfact.png">Worry not, ~name~. According to recent surveys, most people have seen a woman masturbate online at least once. Most people here will not see anything they have not seen before.</state>
                <state img="#-snooty.png">I will be taking notes. I hope you do not mind, ~name~. It is for the sake of worldwide knowledge, after all.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I have seen other women masturbating before for educational purposes... But watching the real thing up close is always an intense experience...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8" id="62" priority="301">
                <condition role="target" character="megumin" saidMarker="TomomegStart" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png">&lt;i&gt;(I should have asked Commons-tan to lend me her camera. This would make a great picture for the article... a-and for personal use...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-smirk.png">And there she goes...</state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png">I will pay very close attention...</state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png">Do not mind us. Do whatever is necessary to fulfill your self-pleasure.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-snooty.png">{small}Some women report achieving an orgasm from nipple stimulation, but this is rare. Research suggests that the orgasms are genital orgasms, and may also be directly linked to "the genital area of the brain."{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png">It seems that sensation from the nipples travels to the same part of the brain as sensations from the vagina, clitoris and cervix.</state>
                <state img="#-neutral.png">Nipple stimulation may trigger uterine contractions, which then produce a sensation in the genital area of the brain.</state>
                <state img="#-hornyfact.png">Fingering is typically the use of fingers or hands to sexually stimulate the vulva (including the clitoris) or vagina.</state>
                <state img="#-casual.png">Vaginal fingering is legally and medically called digital penetration or digital penetration of the vagina.</state>
                <state img="#-smirk.png">Fingering may also include the use of fingers to sexually stimulate the anus.</state>
                <state img="#-hornyfact.png">Parts of the vulva, especially the clitoris, are erogenous zones. Massage of the vulva, and in particular the clitoris, is the most common way for a woman to achieve an orgasm.</state>
                <state img="#-snooty.png">Studies indicate that 70-80% of women require direct clitoral stimulation to achieve orgasm.</state>
                <state img="#-smirk.png">You should massage the clitoral glans or shaft, usually through the skin of the clitoral hood, using up-and-down, side-to-side, or circular motions. Trust me, I read Wikipedia.</state>
                <state img="#-hornyfact.png">{small}While the vagina is not especially sensitive as a whole, its lower third (the area close to the entrance) has concentrations of the nerve endings that can provide pleasurable sensations when stimulated during sexual activity.{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-neutral.png">{smaller}Fingering the vagina is often performed in an effort to stimulate the G-spot. The G-spot is reportedly located roughly 5 cm (2.0 in) up on the anterior wall of the vagina, forwards toward the navel. It is described as being recognized by its ridges and slightly rougher texture compared to the more cushion-like vaginal cavity walls around it. Fingering this spot, and in effect possibly stimulating the Skene's gland, is commonly cited as a method that may lead to female ejaculation.{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">{smaller}Anal fingering may be pleasurable because of the large number of nerve endings in the anal area, and because of the added stimulation gained from stretching the anal sphincter muscles while inserting the finger.&lt;br&gt;However, a good quality personal lubricant is advisable to both increase the pleasurable sensation and aid insertion.{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">When pleasuring the anus, some people prefer to simply stimulate the outer ring, while others will follow this by inserting one or more fingers.</state>
                <state img="#-scold.png">Fingering is generally considered safe sex as long as there are no open wounds on the fingers. The nails should be trimmed and filed; long, sharp or jagged nails can cause cuts, injury, or severe infection.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_heavy_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-flirt.png">I am not an expert on other people's masturbation, but hers seem to be nearing to a close.</state>
                <state img="#-smirk.png">She seems to be near her climax. But do not take my word on it, I do not have any sources for it.</state>
                <state img="#-smirk.png">Just out of curiosity, how would you describe your feelings as you approach orgasm?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8" id="29" priority="302">
                <condition role="target" character="estelle" saidMarker="finish" sayingMarker="book" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png">...Say, Estelle, do you think you could lend me that book when we're finished? I'd like to collect info for the article.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="102">
                <condition role="target" character="supernova" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" marker="SupernovaPowers">...Supernova, you will have to educate me about your powers, if your climax was that good for you... f-for the article, I mean!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-calm.png">I must remind you that your hands should be thoroughly washed with soap and warm water before practicing any other activity to avoid spreading bacteria or germs.</state>
                <state img="#-casual.png">I hope that was pleasurable for you!</state>
                <state img="#-smirk.png">On a scale of 1 to 10, how much have you enjoyed pleasuring yourself in front of strangers? </state>
                <state img="#-educate.png">That sure was a spectacle, ~name~. Would you like to be immortalized forever as the image for the article I am currently writing? I can set up a date with Commons-tan for some photoshoots.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate_first">
            <case stage="6">
                <condition count="4" status="not_exposed" role="other" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="FantasyForfeit">I may have lost way earlier than expected... I do not mind performing, but I think I will have to improvise.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" marker="FantasyForfeit">It appears that the Random Number Generators have decided that I shall perform first, and way earlier than the others... I do not mind, but I do not have much to look at, so I will improvise.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Am I really the first one to do this? I would have preferred to see someone else do it before, but I shall comply with the rules!</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png">I... was not expecting to lose this early. No need to worry, I will comply with the rules! This will be educational anyway.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Well... at least I am about to do this in a consensual, safe, and sexually-free environment. This could have been considered awkward anywhere else!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate">
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-wave.png">Oh well, it appears that it is my turn now. Let me get into position!</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">Time for me to experience this part of the game. I cannot wait to write down my experience after I finish!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="start_masturbating">
            <case stage="6">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FantasyForfeit" />
                <state img="#-casual.png">You can continue on with the game, I will just perform on the sidelines, whispering to myself to get me in the mood.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I hope you do not mind that I will be performing on the sidelines, whispering to myself to get into the mood. You can continue on without me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-z-start.png">I hope you find my performance pleasing to watch. I will try to make it a good one!</state>
                <state img="#-z-start.png">I will do my best to make my performance interesting. But I apologize in advance if I get too carried away!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="masturbating">
            <case stage="7" id="178">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FantasyForfeit" />
                <state img="#-heavy3.png">{small}&lt;i&gt;(Do not think about Jimbo, do not think about Jimbo. He is a married man, he is... such a smart, knowledgeable, exceptional married man... with such a masculine beard...)&lt;/i&gt;{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-heavy2.png">{small}&lt;i&gt;(Would vandals treat me roughly...? Would they pull my hair? Grab me by the neck and choke me? Would they be careful with my titles, for they are case sensitive? What would they do to me...?)&lt;/i&gt;{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-heavy1.png">{small}&lt;i&gt;(Would I... like to be worshiped by the community? To have them all caressing my legs, my arms, my back... Kissing my neck, my ears, my private parts...  I am "free to use" after all, but...)&lt;/i&gt;{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="180">{small}&lt;i&gt;(A girl like me can only date the smartest, most curious and diligent of contributors, after all. They would know how to please me correctly.)&lt;/i&gt;{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-smirk.png">{small}&lt;i&gt;(I could remember all those new admins I have tutored over the years... Such diligent young men, full of energy and passion...)&lt;/i&gt;{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">{small}&lt;i&gt;(What if... all the contributors had their hands on me...? Touching me up like an old article that they are all trying to edit at the same time... Each focusing on a different area, all of them focused on doing the best as they can... Oh dear, was I always this perverted deep down...?)&lt;/i&gt;{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-heavy2.png">{small}&lt;i&gt;(R-right there... yes... fill me with your source-accurate references...)&lt;/i&gt;{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png">{small}&lt;i&gt;(I could imagine a first time with a shy new contributor... telling him to expand his stub, checking if he has a footnote fetish...)&lt;/i&gt;{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="181">{small}&lt;i&gt;(If only I had played differently... I would not have had to start so early...)&lt;/i&gt;{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-frown.png">{small}&lt;i&gt;(What would the other members of the Counter-Vandalism Unit think of me... if they knew how many fantasies I have with them...?)&lt;/i&gt;{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-heavy1.png">{small}&lt;i&gt;(B-be gentle... this is your first contribution...)&lt;/i&gt;{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-heavy1.png" marker="wikiwiki">...&lt;i&gt;(Wiki, wiki...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7" id="1">
                <state img="#-flirt.png">I must remain calm... and concentrate on my masturbation...</state>
                <state img="#-hornyfact.png">Various medical and... psychological benefits have been attributed to a... healthy attitude toward sexual activity in general... and to masturbation in particular...</state>
                <state img="#-hornyfact.png">...Masturbation... has been depicted in art since prehistoric times... a-and is both mentioned and discussed in... very early writings...</state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png">This is enjoyable...</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Organized... and neatly...</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I am... sorry if I am getting too carried away... I will try to make this more pleasing to watch...</state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png">S-so many things we can learn... So much knowledge...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy3.png">The article is missing some more information... on h-how good this feels...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy1.png">I-I wouldn't mind being an article right now... so anyone could touch up all of me...</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I must not forget... to write this down later...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy1.png" marker="wikiwiki">...&lt;i&gt;(Wiki, wiki...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-sad-donate.png" oneShotId="2675">...Since I'm doing this for you, does anyone want to donate? It's only fair...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="heavy_masturbating">
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-heavy2.png">A-ah...!</state>
                <state img="#-heavy3.png">J-jeez...!</state>
                <state img="#-heavy2.png">I am...! About to...!</state>
                <state img="#-heavy1.png">This is... so exciting...!</state>
                <state img="#-heavy1.png">Hah... Haah...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy3.png" oneShotId="70" weight="0.4">N-nya...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy2.png">I can feel it coming...!</state>
                <state img="#-heavy1.png" oneShotId="69">{small}&lt;i&gt;...V-vandalize me...&lt;/i&gt;{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-heavy3.png" oneShotId="127" weight="0.2">{small}&lt;i&gt;...P-please... Vandalize me... I am free to use...&lt;/i&gt;{!reset}</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finishing_masturbating">
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-z-climax.png">Hnnng...!</state>
                <state img="#-z-climax.png">O-oh... My...!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-afterglow.png">Huff... Phew... That was... certainly an fascinating experience!</state>
                <state img="#-afterglow.png">I... I... I want to write all of this down, before I forget about it...</state>
                <state img="#-afterglow.png">...Phew... S-so this is why this place is so popular... This will definitely go into the article...</state>
                <state img="#-afterglow.png">...Phew... huff... wow... Now &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; was just the citation I needed...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="after_masturbating">
            <case stage="8" id="189" oneShotId="22">
                <condition role="other" character="jason" />
                <test expr="~month.number~" value="5" />
                <test expr="~day.number~" value="9" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">On this day in 1980, Sean S. Cunningham's film &lt;i&gt;Friday the 13th&lt;/i&gt; was released in theaters! What do you think of that, Jason?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="184" oneShotId="20">
                <test expr="~background~" cmp="!=" value="paris rooftop" />
                <test expr="~month.number~" value="5" />
                <test expr="~day.number~" value="6" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">On this day in 1889, the {b}Eiffel Tower{!reset} was officially opened to the public at the Universal Exposition in Paris, France.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="185" oneShotId="21">
                <test expr="~background~" value="paris rooftop" />
                <test expr="~month.number~" value="5" />
                <test expr="~day.number~" value="6" />
                <state img="#-excited.png">On this day in 1889, the {b}Eiffel Tower{!reset} was officially opened to the public at the Universal Exposition here in Paris!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="54" oneShotId="12">
                <condition status="finished" role="other" character="polly" sayingMarker="Polly_Wikipetan_PoltergeistArticle2" />
                <state img="#-pissed.png" marker="PoltergeistArticle3">Sure thing, Polly!&lt;br&gt;{small}In ghostlore, a {small b}poltergeist{small} is a type of spirit that is responsible for the raddest, loudest parties, as well as the most satisfying orgasms from-{!reset}&lt;br&gt;... Wait a minute! You vandalized this article!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="160">
                <condition count="3-4" gender="male" role="other" />
                <condition role="self" notSaidMarker="cbt2" />
                <state img="#-hornyfact.png" oneShotId="3166" marker="cbt" collectible="cbt">{smaller b}Cock and ball torture (CBT), penis torture{smaller} or {smaller b}dick torture{smaller} is a sexual activity involving application of pain or constriction to the penis or testicles. This may involve directly painful activities, such as genital piercing, wax play, genital spanking, squeezing, ball-busting, genital flogging, urethral play, tickle torture, erotic electrostimulation, kneeing or kicking. The recipient of such activities may receive direct physical pleasure via masochism, or emotional pleasure through erotic humiliation, or knowledge that the play is pleasing to a sadistic dominant. Many of these practices carry significant health risks. {!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="190" oneShotId="23" priority="0">
                <condition count="0" role="opp" character="jason" />
                <test expr="~month.number~" value="5" />
                <test expr="~day.number~" value="9" />
                <state img="#-smirk.png">On this day in 1980, Sean S. Cunningham's film &lt;i&gt;Friday the 13th&lt;/i&gt; was released in theaters! I heard Jason was around here somewhere...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="10" priority="0">
                <test expr="~month.number~" value="4" />
                <test expr="~day.number~" value="5" />
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="260">On this day in 1998, the {b}Akashi Kaikyō Bridge{!reset} opened to traffic. It is the longest suspension bridge in the world, linking Awaji Island and Kobe in Japan.</state>
                <state img="#-frown.png" oneShotId="261">On a sadder note, on this day in 1936, an F5 tornado struck Tupelo, Mississippi, and killed at least 216 people during {b}the second deadliest tornado outbreak in U.S. history.{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-frown.png" oneShotId="262">This day marks the anniversary of Kurt Cobain's death, as he passed away in 1994 at the age of 27.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="11" priority="0">
                <test expr="~month.number~" value="4" />
                <test expr="~day.number~" value="6" />
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="256">Do you like sports, ~player~? Because on this day in 1886, the first modern {b}Olympic Games{!reset} opened in Athens, with athletes from 14 nations participating in 43 events!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="257">{small}On this day, but back in 1652, a Dutch sailor named Jan van Riebeeck established a resupply camp at the Cape of Good Hope. That camp would eventually become Cape Town, the legislative capital of South Africa.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="12" priority="0">
                <test expr="~month.number~" value="4" />
                <test expr="~day.number~" value="7" />
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="276">On this day in 2001, NASA's {b}&lt;i&gt;2001 Mars Odyssey&lt;/i&gt;{!reset} launched from Cape Canaveral. It is currently the longest-surviving continually active spacecraft in orbit around a planet other than Earth!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="250">On a day just like this, but back in 1141, Empress Matilda became the first female ruler of England. Adopting the title of "Lady of the English."</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="251">On this day, back on 1805, Ludwig van Beethoven premiered his Third Symphony at the Theater an der Wien in Vienna. Would you like to listen to it with me after this game?</state>
                <state img="#-casual.png" oneShotId="252" dialogue-layer="over">On this day in 1927, the first ever long-distance public television broadcast was... well, broadcasted. We have come a long way since then!</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="922">{small}On this day, but back in 1948, the United Nations established the World Health Organization (WHO) to act as a coordinating authority on international public health. And years later, America would cut funding for the WHO for some reason.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="13" priority="0">
                <test expr="~month.number~" value="4" />
                <test expr="~day.number~" value="31" />
                <state img="#-flirt.png" oneShotId="266">Psst. Hey, ~player~. You're not supposed to see this.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="4" priority="0">
                <test expr="~month.number~" value="4" />
                <test expr="~day.number~" value="1" />
                <state img="#-flirt.png" oneShotId="6">On this day in 2001, the Netherlands became the first country to legalize same-sex marriage. </state>
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="7">Did you know that on this day in 2004, Google announced Gmail for the first time?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="8">On this day in 1979, Nickelodeon launched in the United States, leaving behind it's old name of Pinwheel. Is that interesting or what?</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="9">Do you like Apple products, ~player~? Apple Inc. was formed by Steve Jobs, Steve Wozniak and Ronald Wayne back on April 1, 1976!</state>
                <state img="#-scold.png" oneShotId="10">On this day in 1944, the United States bombed the Swiss city of Schaffhausen due to navigation errors. This is why aeronautical radio operators are important, people!</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png" oneShotId="2697">On this day in 2021,  I was added to &lt;i&gt;Strip Poker Night at the Inventory&lt;/i&gt;! Yay me!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="5" priority="0">
                <test expr="~month.number~" value="4" />
                <test expr="~day.number~" value="2" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="65" dialogue-layer="over" weight="2">{small}On this day in 1982, Argentina invaded the Falklands under the orders of its military dictatorship as an attempt to regain the population's patriotic feelings, calculating that the United Kingdom wouldn't respond. But they didn't know that Margaret Thatcher needed to regain her country's trust as well, and reclaiming the islands did just that! Isn't that interesting?{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="66">Did you know that on this day in 1800, Ludwig van Beethoven led the premiere of his First Symphony in Vienna? Why don't you give it a listen?</state>
                <state img="#-neutral.png" oneShotId="99">{small}On this day in 2005, the first non-Italian pope since the 16th Century, John Paul II, left this mortal plane. He was born as Karol Józef Wojtyła from Poland, and was succeeded by the German Joseph Ratzinger, and later the Argentinian Jorge Bergoglio.{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="98" dialogue-layer="over">Hey ~player~, today is World Autism Awareness Day! It's one of only seven official health-specific UN Days, recognizing the importance of research, treatment, and acceptance for people with autism spectrum disorders.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-calm.png">I hope you do not mind that I am using the remaining time to think about the article I will write once I get home.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Now that I think about it, I should have charged my phone beforehand... I could have written so much already...</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">This was a very different experience than what I expected from the Inventory... But I liked it nonetheless!</state>
                <state img="#-neutral.png">If you are feeling bored, ~player~, did you know that there is a site where you can watch Wikipedia edits in real time? Check it out: {u}listen.hatnote.com{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Is there any particular topic you wish to know about, ~player~? Remember that you can offer your feedback after the game, so I can read your thoughts more appropriately.</state>
                <state img="#-sad-donate.png">Remember, ~player~, we are still accepting donations... Only if you want to, of course! Every penny helps!</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">I wish I had more to say for my On This Day facts. Google &lt;i&gt;always&lt;/i&gt; manages to bring out the obscure birthdays...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="6" priority="0">
                <test expr="~month.number~" value="4" />
                <test expr="~day.number~" value="3" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="134">Just like how this game is ending soon, on this day back in 1559 the Habsburg–Valois War was coming to an end.</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="135">It's hard to think about, but the first successful portable computer was unveiled on this day four decades ago!</state>
                <state img="#-hornyfact.png" oneShotId="136">Well, I was not exactly successful at this game... But neither was the US Air Force CT-43, when they crashed into a mountainside during a failed instrument approach on this day in 1996.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="292">Do you like Fred Astaire? Well, on this day in 1955, Fred Astaire appeared on television for the first time on &lt;i&gt;The Toast of the Town&lt;/i&gt; with Ed Sullivan!</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="293">On this day in 2008, Apple became the number one music seller in the United States.</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="294">On this day in 1882, American outlaw Jesse James was killed by Robert Ford. This would be depicted in the 2007 film &lt;i&gt;The Assassination of Jesse James by the Coward Robert Ford.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="295">On this day in 1968, Stanley Kubrick's film &lt;i&gt;2001: A Space Odyssey&lt;/i&gt; was released in the United States. It would go on to achieve critical acclaim.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="7" priority="0">
                <test expr="~month.number~" value="4" />
                <test expr="~day.number~" value="4" />
                <state img="#-snooty.png" oneShotId="150">To think that on this day just 50 years ago, Apollo 6 was launched... I was not even born yet, so I am thankful for being able to read all about it on Wikipedia!</state>
                <state img="#-neutral.png" oneShotId="151">{small}On this day four decades ago, Bill Gates and Paul Allen founded Microsoft in Albuquerque, New Mexico. I wonder what kinds of world-changing projects, foundations and alliances are happening now as we speak...{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="149">On this day five decades ago, the first temporary artificial heart was implanted. Are you not amazed at how medicine has progressed since then?</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="152">Have you ever gone to a circus, ~player~? Because on this day three centuries ago, the first modern circus was staged for the first time!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="153">It is hard to imagine that on this day two hundred years ago, the Kennel Club was founded. Do you think a dog is defined by its race, ~player~?</state>
                <state img="#-frown.png" oneShotId="154">Boy, today is going to be a busy day... It is the anniversary of Martin Luther King Jr.'s death. And the trolls are going to get wild trying to vandalize any non-protected article surrounding him...</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="303">{small}On this day in 1994, the Beatles made music history by holding the top five places in the singles charts with "Can't Buy Me Love," "Twist and Shout," "She Loves You," "I Want to Hold Your Hand," and "Please Please Me."{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" priority="0">
                <condition role="self" notSaidMarker="Reliable_source_loop" />
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="118" marker="Reliable_source_loop" weight="0.05">By the way, as much as I love Wikipedia, I have to admit that it is not a reliable source. Wikipedia itself has an article saying so.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="14" priority="0">
                <test expr="~month.number~" value="4" />
                <test expr="~day.number~" value="8" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="323">On this day in 1911, American cartoonist {b}Winsor McCay{!reset} released the silent short film {b}&lt;i&gt;Little Nemo,&lt;/i&gt;{!reset} one of the earliest animated films.</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="928">On this day in 1994, the RIAA announced that Pink Floyd's 1973 album &lt;i&gt;The Dark Side of the Moon&lt;/i&gt; had become the fourth biggest-selling album in U.S. history, passing the 13 million mark in sales.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="929">Do you like punk rock, ~player~? Because on this day in 1977, the Clash's self-titled debut album was released in the UK! What are your favorite songs by the Clash?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="15" priority="0">
                <test expr="~month.number~" value="4" />
                <test expr="~day.number~" value="9" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="399">{small}On a day like this, but back in 1860, Édouard-Léon Scott de Martinville made the oldest known recording of a human voice on his phonautograph. We have come a long way since then! Would you like this game to play human voices?{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="400">{small}Today in 1937, the airplane &lt;i&gt;Kamikaze&lt;/i&gt; (registration J-BAAI) landed in London, becoming the first Japanese-built aircraft to fly from Japan to Europe. To commemorate the occasion, sake bottles and cups with the image of this aircraft on it were produced.{!reset} </state>
                <state img="#-smirk.png" oneShotId="401">On a day just like this one back in in 1991, Georgia declared its independence from the Soviet Union! Well, the Soviet Union disbanded that same year, but it is still a date to celebrate.</state>
                <state img="#-neutral.png" oneShotId="402">Did you know that today, but back in 1959, the Mercury Seven were announced to the public? They were the selection of the United States' first seven astronauts!</state>
                <state img="#-frown.png" oneShotId="914">On this day in 1970, the Beatles' bassist Sir Paul McCartney quit the band, much to the sadness of fans. He would go on to have a successful solo career.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="915">Did you know that on this day in 2007, Apple announced it had sold its one-hundred millionth iPod? Remember iPods? How quickly technology changes!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="16" priority="0">
                <test expr="~month.number~" value="4" />
                <test expr="~day.number~" value="10" />
                <state img="#-neutral.png" oneShotId="411">On a regular day just like this one, but back in 1939, the "Big Book" of &lt;i&gt;Alcoholics Anonymous&lt;/i&gt; was first published. Pretty interesting, right?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="412">Do you celebrate Arbor Day, ~player~? You should! It is quite nice, and the first Arbor Day ever was celebrated in Nebraska on this day back in 1872.</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="451">{small}Have you ever wondered how a black hole looks like, ~player~? Many people did for dozens of years... until recently, since the Event Horizon Telescope showed us the first image of a real black hole on this day in 2019.{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="452">{small}You never know where you will find a surprise, ~player~. Like the construction workers in Linyi, Shandong who accidentally found tombs with bamboo slips, including Sun Tzu's &lt;i&gt;The Art of War,&lt;/i&gt; om this day back in 1972.{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png" oneShotId="861">{small}On this day back in 1971, John Denver's "Take Me Home Country Roads" hit the Billboard Hot 100, becoming Denver's first appearance on the charts. Do you want to sing that song with me, ~name~?{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="862">This day marked the release of F. Scott Fitzgerald's novel &lt;i&gt;The Great Gatsby&lt;/i&gt; in 1925, which has since become required reading in most English classes. So many high schoolers choose to skim my page instead of reading it...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="17" priority="0">
                <test expr="~month.number~" value="4" />
                <test expr="~day.number~" value="11" />
                <state img="#-scold.png" oneShotId="461">There is always a first time for everything, ~player~! Like how Napoleon Bonaparte had to abdicate unconditionally for the first time today in 1814, due to the Treaty of Fountainebleau!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="462">Have you ever been to Tel-Aviv, ~player~? They are probably celebrating right now, since their city was founded today in 1909!</state>
                <state img="#-neutral.png" oneShotId="463">Are you a fan of Apple products, ~player~? Because the Apple I was created on this day, back in 1976.</state>
                <state img="#-casual.png" oneShotId="464">Fifty years feels so distant... and yet so close. Like how people watching the Apollo 13 launch felt today in 1970.</state>
                <state img="#-frown.png" oneShotId="465">{small}Did you know that today in 2002, over two hundred thousand people marched in Caracas, Venezuela to demand the resignation of the then-president Hugo Chávez? Not only did he not resign, but his elected successor is still in power to this day... But I hold hope for our Venezuelan contributors.{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-scold.png" oneShotId="466">{small}People usually forget how close the past is! The United States' Civil Rights Act, the one prohibiting discrimination in the sale, rental, and financing of housing due to race, religion, or national origin, has only been in effect since it was enacted on this day back in 1968!{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="869">This day saw the release of &lt;i&gt;Singin' in the Rain&lt;/i&gt; in 1952, with Gene Kelly in the lead!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="38" priority="0">
                <test expr="~month.number~" value="4" />
                <test expr="~day.number~" value="12" />
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="877">{small}On this day in 1963, Bob Dylan performed his first major solo concert at Town Hall in New York City. He would go on to release a total of 39 studio albums, becoming one of the most prolific and widely covered songwriters of the 20th century.{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="878">This day saw the first launch of NASA's Space Shuttle &lt;i&gt;Columbia&lt;/i&gt; in 1981! &lt;i&gt;Columbia&lt;/i&gt; was the first of five Space Shuttles and would be the first flight in a program that would last 30 more years.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="39" priority="0">
                <test expr="~month.number~" value="4" />
                <test expr="~day.number~" value="13" />
                <state img="#-snooty.png" oneShotId="855">{small}On this day in 1943, the Jefferson Memorial in Washington, D.C., was formerly dedicated on the 200th anniversary of president, architect, and university founder Thomas Jefferson's birth. It was built in the Neoclassical style that Jefferson was known for.{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="856">On this day in 1970, Led Zeppelin became the first band to sell out the Montreal Forum.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="857">On this day in 2000, American metal band Metallica filed a lawsuit against Napster, in an infamous move that would be linked to the downfall of the company.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="40" priority="0">
                <test expr="~month.number~" value="4" />
                <test expr="~day.number~" value="14" />
                <state img="#-snooty.png" oneShotId="889">On this day in 1980, British heavy metal band Iron Maiden released their self-titled debut album. It was the first of two with original lead singer Paul Di'Anno, before his replacement by &lt;i&gt;the&lt;/i&gt; Bruce Dickinson.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="41" priority="0">
                <test expr="~month.number~" value="4" />
                <test expr="~day.number~" value="15" />
                <state img="#-frown.png" oneShotId="892">On this day in 2019, a fire severely damaged Notre-Dame de Paris, destroying the cathedral's spire and much of its roof. I wonder how Notre-Dame-chan is doing these days...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="93" priority="0">
                <test expr="~month.number~" value="4" />
                <test expr="~day.number~" value="16" />
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="1592">On this day in 1964, the Rolling Stones' self titled debut album was released in the UK! They would go on to release a total of 30 studio albums and 23 live albums.</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="1603">Today was an important day in the Civil Rights Movement, because in 1963, Martin Luther King Jr. wrote the {b}Letter from Birmingham Jail{!reset} in defence of the strategy of nonviolent resistance against racism.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="1604">On this day in 1972, Apollo 16 launched from Cape Canaveral, Florida. It was the second last mission in the Apollo program and the second last manned mission to the Moon.</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="1605">On this day in 1971, the Rolling Stones released "Brown Sugar" in the UK. It was the first record they released on their own label, Rolling Stones Records.</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="1606">On this day in 1974, Queen held its very first US concert at Regis College in Denver, CO, in support of their album &lt;i&gt;Queen II&lt;/i&gt;. They would become one of the world's best-selling music artists!</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="1607">On this day in 1983, Kirk Hammett played his first show with Metallica in Dover, NJ, replacing original lead guitarist Dave Mustaine. Hammett is still with Metallica to this day!</state>
                <state img="#-neutral.png" oneShotId="1608">On this day in 1990, over 72,000 people gathered at London's Wembley Stadium for an anti-apartheid concert honoring Nelson Mandela, who had recently been released from prison.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="1609">{small}On this day in 1996, American rock band KISS announced a reunion tour with the original lineup and wearing makeup for the first time since 1983! &lt;i&gt;I... wanna rock and roll all night~!&lt;/i&gt;{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="1610">This day saw the release of Hayao Miyazaki's anime film &lt;i&gt;My Neighbor Totoro&lt;/i&gt; in 1988! Strange to believe it has been that long...</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="1681">On this day in 1972, Electric Light Orchestra played their first live show in England! &lt;i&gt;Eeeeeevil womaaaan!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="94" priority="0">
                <test expr="~month.number~" value="4" />
                <test expr="~day.number~" value="17" />
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="1594">On this day in 1907, the immigration center at Ellis Island processed 11,747 people, more people than on any other day! Did your family emigrate to the United States, ~player~?</state>
                <state img="#-frown.png" oneShotId="1600">Today, in 1970, people across the United States simultaneously unclenched their jaws as the ill-fated Apollo 13 spacecraft  safely returned to Earth after an unsuccessful mission.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="1620">A group of Cuban exiles financed and trained by the CIA landed at the Bay of Pigs, in an infamous invasion with the aim of ousting Fidel Castro on this day in 1961.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="95" priority="0">
                <test expr="~month.number~" value="4" />
                <test expr="~day.number~" value="18" />
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="1621">Today was an important day for the American Revolution, because in 1775, colonists Paul Revere, William Dawes, and Samuel Prescott began a midnight ride from Boston to Lexington to warn about the arrival of British troops.</state>
                <state img="#-frown.png" oneShotId="1622">Today was the day of the infamous {b}1906 San Francisco earthquake,{!reset} which had an estimated magnitude of 7.9 and claimed the lives of 3,000 and destroyed 80% of San Francisco.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="1623">On this day in 1980, the Republic of Zimbabwe (formerly Rhodesia) came into being.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="1692">In 1938, on this day, {b}Superman{!reset} made his debut in &lt;i&gt;Action Comics #1&lt;/i&gt;, the first true superhero comic book! Who are your favorite superheroes?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="96" priority="0">
                <test expr="~month.number~" value="4" />
                <test expr="~day.number~" value="19" />
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="1693">The American Revolutionary War began on this day in 1775, with an American victory in Concord during the battles of Lexington and Concord!</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="1694">On this day in 1987, the Simpsons made their first appearance on television as a series of shorts on &lt;i&gt;The Tracey Ullman Show.&lt;/i&gt; They would later spawn their own TV series that is still going to this day!</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="1695">On this day in 1986, {b}Prince{!reset} became the fifth songwriter to have two top ten hits at the same time! The songs were "Kiss" and "Manic Monday," the latter he wrote for The Bangles.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="1696">On this day in 2008, the first Record Store Day was held! The event was founded to celebrate the culture of the independently owned record store.</state>
                <state img="#-smirk.png" oneShotId="1778">This day may not have many facts, but &lt;i&gt;tomorrow&lt;/i&gt; will be a real big day. Ohhhh boy...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="97" priority="0">
                <test expr="~month.number~" value="4" />
                <test expr="~day.number~" value="20" />
                <state img="#-smirk.png" oneShotId="1709" marker="420BlazeIt">April 20 is certainly a... &lt;i&gt;special&lt;/i&gt; day for many reasons. Particularly in marijuana culture. Blaze it!</state>
                <state img="#-frown.png" oneShotId="1710">Despite its positive sides, April 20 is unfortunate for many reasons, as it marks the day of the Columbine High School massacre in 1999 and the birthday of Adolf Hitler in 1889.</state>
                <state img="#-frown.png" oneShotId="1711">On this day in 2010, the &lt;i&gt;Deepwater Horizon&lt;/i&gt; drilling rig exploded in the Gulf of Mexico, killing eleven workers and beginning an oil spill that would last six months.</state>
                <state img="#-smirk.png" oneShotId="1712">This day marks the birthday of Japanese-American actor George Takei, famous for his role as Hikaru Sulu on &lt;i&gt;Star Trek&lt;/i&gt; and for his famous catchphrase, "Ohhhh myyyy!"</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="1717">This day was also the birthday of Dream Theater's drummer Mike Portnoy! I wonder if he likes to get stoned on this day...</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="1718">{small}On this day in 1992, Queen held a memorial concert for their late lead singer Freddie Mercury. Performers included  Elton John, Guns N' Roses, Roger Daltrey, Liza Minnelli, David Bowie, George Michael, Def Leppard, and Metallica, among others.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="98" priority="0">
                <test expr="~month.number~" value="4" />
                <test expr="~day.number~" value="21" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="1763">On this day, back in 1989, specifically during the Tiananmen Square in the People's Republic of China... nothing happened. Nothing at all!</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="1765">{small}On this day in 1977, the musical &lt;i&gt;Annie&lt;/i&gt; opened on Broadway! Not to be confused with the comic it was based on, &lt;i&gt;Little Orphan Annie&lt;/i&gt;, or the NSFW parody from &lt;i&gt;Playboy, Little Annie Fanny&lt;/i&gt;, or the other musical &lt;i&gt;Annie Get Your Gun&lt;/i&gt;.{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="1766">On this day in 1970, pianist-singer-songwriter Elton John made his solo concert debut when he opened for T. Rex in London! &lt;i&gt;And I think it's gonna be a long long time~&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-frown.png">Not as many famous events occurred on April 21 as on April 20...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="125" priority="0">
                <test expr="~month.number~" value="4" />
                <test expr="~day.number~" value="22" />
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="1987">On this day, back in 1500, {b}Pedro Álvares Cabral{!reset} anchored off the coast of present-day Brazil with his fleet, claiming the land for the Portuguese Empire.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="1988">{small}On this day in 1864, the U.S. Congress authorized the creation of a{!reset} {smallbold}two-cent coin, {small}the first U.S. currency to bear the phrase{!reset} {smallbold}"In God We Trust."{!reset} {small}The coin has fallen out of use, but the phrase has stuck around.{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-smirk.png" oneShotId="1989">Today was the birthday of actor {b}Jack Nicholson,{!reset} famous for his role in &lt;i&gt;The Shining&lt;/i&gt;!&lt;br&gt;Heeeeeeeeere's Johnny!</state>
                <state img="#-snooty.png" oneShotId="2002">In 1950, singer-songwriter and guitarist {b}Peter Frampton{!reset} was born on this day! He was famous for his use of the talkbox on songs like "Show Me the Way" and "Do You Feel Like We Do."</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="2003">On this day, back in 1969, {b}The Who{!reset} gave their first complete live performance of the rock opera &lt;i&gt;Tommy&lt;/i&gt; at a show in Dolton, England!</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="2004">{small}On this day, but in 1978, John Belushi and Dan Aykroyd made their first appearance as{!reset} {smallbold}The Blues Brothers{!reset} {small}on NBC's &lt;i&gt;Saturday Night Live!&lt;/i&gt;{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="2640">{small}This day in 1964 marked the opening of the{!reset} {smallbold}New York World's Fair{!reset} {small}in Flushing Meadows, Queens. The fair was noted as a showcase of mid-20th-century American culture and technology, including tech from the Space Age.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="126" priority="0">
                <test expr="~month.number~" value="4" />
                <test expr="~day.number~" value="23" />
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="1993">{b}"Me at the zoo,"{!reset} the very first video ever uploaded to YouTube, was published on this day back in 2005!</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="1994">{small}This day marks the birthday of{!reset} {smallbold}Steve Clark{!reset} {small}in 1950, lead guitarist of the hard rock band Def Leppard, famous for their hit song, "Pour Some Sugar on Me"! Which does not seem very sanitary, now that  I think about it...{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png" oneShotId="1995">In 1936, on this day, singer Roy Orbison was born! He was famous for his hit song "Pretty Woman," which I have certainly seen many of today.</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png" oneShotId="2011">On this day, but back in 1993, the film &lt;i&gt;Benny and Joon&lt;/i&gt; was released to theaters.&lt;br&gt;{b}&lt;i&gt;AND I WOULD WALK FIVE HUNDRED MILES, AND I WOULD WALK FIVE HUNDRED MORE!&lt;/i&gt;{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="2055">In the United Nations, April 23 is the UN English Language Day. It is &lt;i&gt;also&lt;/i&gt; celebrated as the UN Spanish Language Day. Weird...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="127" priority="0">
                <test expr="~month.number~" value="4" />
                <test expr="~day.number~" value="24" />
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="2012">{small}On this day in 1800, the{!reset} {smallbold}Library of Congress,{!reset} {small}the &lt;i&gt;de facto&lt;/i&gt; national library of the United States, was established as part of an act of Congress to transfer the nation's capital from Philadelphia to Washington, D.C.{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png" oneShotId="2013">{small}On this day in 1961, a young{!reset} {smallbold}Bob Dylan{!reset} {small}earned a $50 session fee for playing harmonica on Harry Belafonte's "Midnight Special" in his first recording gig. Incidentally, $50 is about one-fifth of what an average Bob Dylan concert ticket costs nowadays!{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-smirk.png" oneShotId="2014">On this day in 1968, Apple Records refused to sign a young David Bowie, which we at Wikipedia have listed under Category:Boy Were They Wrong!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="128" priority="0">
                <test expr="~month.number~" value="4" />
                <test expr="~day.number~" value="25" />
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="2036">On this day in 1901, New York became the first U.S. state to require automobile license plates.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="2037">On this day in 1983, space probe &lt;i&gt;Pioneer 10&lt;/i&gt; became the first human-made object to travel beyond Pluto's orbit and leave the solar system! Go Pioneer!</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png" oneShotId="2038">Happy National DNA Day! April 25 is celebrated in the United States to commemorate the publication of scientific findings about DNA in 1953!</state>
                <state img="#-frown.png" oneShotId="2039">This day in 1792 marked the first execution by guillotine. Dark, I know, but not &lt;i&gt;every&lt;/i&gt; fact I have is uplifting.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="2182">On this day in 1960, the U.S. Navy submarine {b}&lt;i&gt;Triton&lt;/i&gt;{!reset} completed {b}the first submerged circumnavigation of the world.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="129" priority="0">
                <test expr="~month.number~" value="4" />
                <test expr="~day.number~" value="26" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="2204">{small}This day in 2019 saw the release of{!reset} {smallbold}&lt;i&gt;Avengers: Endgame,&lt;/i&gt;{!reset} {small}which displaced James Cameron's &lt;i&gt;Avatar&lt;/i&gt; as the highest grossing film of all time and held that title for a year before &lt;i&gt;Avatar&lt;/i&gt; beat it again. Funny how that works!{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="2205">On this day in 1962, NASA's {b}Ranger 4{!reset} spacecraft successfully landed on the Moon! ...Well, it crashed. So it failed successfully?</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="2206">On this day in 1564, the Bard himself, {b}William Shakespeare,{!reset} was baptized in Stratford-upon-Avon, Warwickshire, England! His actual birthdate is unknown.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="2207">This day in 1977 saw the opening of {b}Studio 54{!reset} in New York! A famous venue for the disco era, which I sadly arrived three decades too late for.</state>
                <state img="#-frown.png" oneShotId="2208">Today is best know as the day of the infamous {b}Chernobyl disaster{!reset} in 1986. Dark, I know, but not &lt;i&gt;every&lt;/i&gt; fact I have is uplifting.</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png" oneShotId="2334">Happy {b}World Intellectual Property Day,{!reset} ~player~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="134" priority="0">
                <test expr="~month.number~" value="4" />
                <test expr="~day.number~" value="27" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="2366">On this day in 1961, {b}Sierra Leone{!reset} was granted its independence from the United Kingdom.</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="2367">{small}Today is an important day in technology, ~player~! Because today in 1981, Xerox PARC introduced the{!reset} {smallbold}computer mouse{!reset} {small}into the marketplace with its Xerox Star computer!{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="2368">{small}On this day in 1994, South Africa held the first democratic general election in which black citizens could vote. April 27 is now celebrated as{!reset} {smallbold}Freedom Day{!reset} {small}in South Africa.{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="2369">This day in 1932 was the birthday of DJ and voice actor {b}Casey Kasem,{!reset} best known as the co-creator of &lt;i&gt;American Top 40&lt;/i&gt; and as the original voice of Shaggy Rogers in &lt;i&gt;Scooby-Doo.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="2370">&lt;i&gt;Get up! Everybody's gonna move their feet!&lt;/i&gt; This day was the birthday of {b}Ace Frehley,{!reset} lead guitarist of American rock band KISS, in 1952.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="135" priority="0">
                <test expr="~month.number~" value="4" />
                <test expr="~day.number~" value="28" />
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="2389">{small}On this day in 1789, near the island of Tofua, Fletcher Christian, acting lieutenant on board the Royal Navy ship &lt;i&gt;Bounty,&lt;/i&gt; led{!reset} {smallbold}a mutiny{!reset} {small}against the commander, William Bligh, in one of the most famous mutinies in history.{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-neutral.png" oneShotId="2390">On this day in 1910, Frenchman Louis Paulhan won the {b}London to Manchester air race,{!reset} the first long-distance aeroplane race in England.</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="2391">American entrepreneur {b}Dennis Tito{!reset} became the world's first fee-paying space tourist, riding the Russian Soyuz TM-32 spacecraft to the International Space Station on this day in 2001.</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png" oneShotId="2392">On this day in 1923, London's {b}Wembley Stadium{!reset} was opened! It held a number of football matches and music shows, including Queen's famous performance at Live Aid in 1985.</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="2393">On this day in 1973, Pink Floyd's concept album &lt;i&gt;The Dark Side of the Moon&lt;/i&gt; went to number one on the US &lt;i&gt;Billboard&lt;/i&gt; chart, beginning a record-breaking 741-week chart run!</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="2434">This day in 2003 was the opening of the iTunes Store, which sold over 70 million songs within its first year of operation.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="136" priority="0">
                <test expr="~month.number~" value="4" />
                <test expr="~day.number~" value="29" />
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="2409">{small}On this day in 1968, the controversial musical{!reset} {smallbold}&lt;i&gt;Hair,&lt;/i&gt;{!reset} {small}a product of the hippie counter-culture and sexual revolution of the 1960s, opened on Broadway! &lt;i&gt;Give me a head with hair! Long, beautiful hair!&lt;/i&gt;{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="2410">{small}On his first voyage, British explorer James Cook and the crew of{!reset} {smallbold}HMS &lt;i&gt;Endeavour&lt;/i&gt;{!reset} {small}landed at Botany Bay near present-day Sydney, making the first recorded European contact with the eastern coast of Australia on this day in 1770.{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-smirk.png" oneShotId="2411">This day in 1970 was the birthday of American actress {b}Uma Thurman,{!reset} a personal favorite of both director Quentin Tarantino and rock band Fall Out Boy.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="2412">Did you know that UNESCO considers today {b}International Dance Day?{!reset} What's your favorite type of dance, ~player~?</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="2413">On this day in 1826, Scottish astronomer James Dunlop discovered the galaxy {b}Centaurus A,{!reset} or NGC 5128.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="138" priority="0">
                <test expr="~month.number~" value="4" />
                <test expr="~day.number~" value="30" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="2575">Just like how this game is ending soon, on this day in 1945, World War II was ending in Germany.</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="2576">On this day in 1598, King Henry IV of France issued the {b}Edict of Nantes,{!reset} granting freedom of religion to the Huguenots.</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="2577">On this day in 1977, {b}Led Zeppelin{!reset} played a show to an audience of 77,229 in Pontiac, Michigan, which set a new record for attendance at a single-act concert. </state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="2578">{small}This day in 1803 was the signing of the{!reset} {smallbold}Louisiana Purchase,{!reset} {small}in which the United States purchased the Louisiana Territory from France for $15 million, more than doubling the size of the young nation.{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="2579">On this day in 1812, the Territory of Orleans became the 18th U.S. state under the name Louisiana.</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png">On this day in 1938, the animated cartoon short &lt;i&gt;Porky's Hare Hunt&lt;/i&gt; debuted in movie theaters. It introduced Happy Rabbit, an early version of Bugs Bunny.</state>
                <state img="#-neutral.png">{small}This day was the opening of the{!reset} {smallbold}New York World's Fair{!reset} {small}in 1939. It was the second-most expensive American world's fair of all time and was the first exposition to be based on the future, with an opening slogan of "Dawn of a New Day", and it allowed all visitors to take a look at "the world of tomorrow."{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="140" priority="0">
                <test expr="~month.number~" value="5" />
                <test expr="~day.number~" value="1" />
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="2677">Today is {b}International Workers' Day,{!reset} also known as {b}May Day{!reset} in some places!</state>
                <state img="#-snooty.png" oneShotId="2678">Did you know that this day saw the premiere of Orson Welles' acclaimed film {b}&lt;i&gt;Citizen Kane&lt;/i&gt;{!reset} in 1941?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="2679">On this day in 1865, the Empire of Brazil, Argentina, and Uruguay signed the {b}Treaty of the Triple Alliance.{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="2680">I bet you didn't know that on this day in 1930, {b}"Pluto"{!reset} became the officially propsed name for what would be known for many years as our ninth planet!</state>
                <state img="#-scold.png" oneShotId="2681">On this day in 1956, {b}Jonas Salk{!reset} made his polio vaccine available to the public.</state>
                <state img="#-neutral.png" oneShotId="2718">On this day in 2009, same-sex marriage was legalized in Sweden.</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="2719">On this day in 1786, Mozart's opera {b}&lt;i&gt;The Marriage of Figaro&lt;/i&gt;{!reset} premiered in Vienna, Austria.</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="2720">On this day in 1972, {b}Paul Simon{!reset} released his self-titled solo debut album after splitting from Simon and Garfunkel. </state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="2721">On this day in 1972, American rock band  {b}Eagles{!reset} released their first single, "Take It Easy," co-written by Jackson Browne.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="141" priority="0">
                <test expr="~month.number~" value="5" />
                <test expr="~day.number~" value="2" />
                <state img="#-frown.png" oneShotId="2722">On this day in 1979, {b}The Who{!reset} performed their first concert with Kenney Jones, formerly of the Faces, after the death of founding drummer Keith Moon.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="2723">{small}On this day in 1982, the government of South Africa banned {smallbold}Pink Floyd's{small} song "Another Brick in the Wall (Part 2)." The censorship of information will never cease to bother me...{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="2724">Did you know that on this day in 1559, Presbyterian clergyman {b}John Knox{!reset} returned from exile to lead the Scottish Reformation?</state>
                <state img="#-smirk.png" oneShotId="2725">Today is the birthday of {b}Lorenzo Music,{!reset} the best-known voice actor for comic character Garfield! Do you like lasagna, ~player~?</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="2726">Today is the birthday of {b}Lou Gramm,{!reset} lead singer of the rock band Foreigner! ♫&lt;i&gt;I want to know what love iiiiiis! I want you to show meeeee!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="156" priority="0">
                <test expr="~month.number~" value="5" />
                <test expr="~day.number~" value="3" />
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="2845">{small}Today is the United Nations' {smallbold}World Press Freedom Day,{small} observed to raise awareness of the importance of freedom of the press and remind governments of their duty to respect and uphold the right to freedom of expression enshrined under Article 19 of the 1948 Universal Declaration of Human Rights.{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-snooty.png" oneShotId="2846">{small}Happy {smallbold}Constitution Memorial Day! {small}If you're Japanese, that is. This day in takes place in celebration of the enactment of the 1947 Constitution of Japan and is a part of the collection of holidays known as Golden Week.{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="2847">In 1921, on this day, {b}Ireland was partitioned{!reset} into two self-governing territories, Northern and Southern Ireland, under the British Government of Ireland Act.</state>
                <state img="#-smirk.png" oneShotId="2848">{small}On this day in 1979, {smallbold}Margaret Thatcher{small} won the United Kingdom General Election and became their Prime Minister. Years later, after her death in 2013, the British public would get "Ding-Dong! The Witch Is Dead" charting in her honor!{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="2849">{small}On this day in 1960, {smallbold}&lt;i&gt;The Fantasticks&lt;/i&gt;{small} held its first off-Broadway show. The original production ran a total of 42 years (until 2002) and 17,162 performances, making it the world's longest-running musical!{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="2890">{small}On this day in 1988, Queensrÿche released their third album, {smallbold}&lt;i&gt;Operation: Mindcrime!&lt;/i&gt;{small} The album, a rock opera, has since become known as one of the greatest metal albums ever released.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="157" priority="0">
                <test expr="~month.number~" value="5" />
                <test expr="~day.number~" value="4" />
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="2931">Happy {b}&lt;i&gt;Star Wars&lt;/i&gt; Day,{!reset} ~player~! May 4 was chosen for the pun on the catchphrase "May the Force be with you" as "May the Fourth be with you."</state>
                <state img="#-snooty.png" oneShotId="2932">On this day in 1780, the {b}first running{!reset} of the Epsom Derby took place! The winning horse was Diomed, owned by Charles Bunbury.</state>
                <state img="#-neutral.png" oneShotId="2933">On this day in 1927, the {b}Academy of Motion Picture Arts and Sciences{!reset} was incorporated.</state>
                <state img="#-smirk.png" oneShotId="2934">{small}On this day in 1932, notorious mobster {smallbold}Al Capone{small} began serving an eleven-year prison sentence for tax evasion. Just goes to show, you can annoy the police and rival gangs, but ever mess with the IRS!{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="2935">On this day in 1959, the 1st Annual Grammy Awards were held! But it's the Grammys, so nobody cared.</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="2936">The 108-story {b}Sears Tower{!reset} in Chicago was topped out at 1,451 feet as the world's tallest building on this day in 1973.</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="3068">{small}On this day in 1974, an all-female Japanese team reached the summit of {smallbold}Manaslu{small} in the Himalayas, becoming the first women to climb a peak higher than 8,000 metres (26,247 ft) above sea level.{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="3229">This day in 2012 saw the release of {b}&lt;i&gt;The Avengers,&lt;/i&gt;{!reset} which would become the third highest grossing film of all time.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="158" priority="0">
                <test expr="~month.number~" value="5" />
                <test expr="~day.number~" value="5" />
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="3050">{small}Happy {smallbold}Cinco de Mayo,{small} ~player~! This annual celebration is observed to commemorate the Mexican Army's victory over the French Empire at the Battle of Puebla, on May 5, 1862.{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-scold.png" oneShotId="3051">Just a reminder: Cinco de Mayo is &lt;i&gt;not&lt;/i&gt; Mexican Independence Day! That is September 16. Get it right!</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="3052">On this day in 1961, as part of Project Mercury, {b}Alan Shepard{!reset} made a sub-orbital flight aboard the &lt;i&gt;Freedom 7,&lt;/i&gt; becoming the second person to travel into outer space.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="3053">On this day in 1835, the {b}first railway in continental Europe{!reset} opened between Brussels and Mechelen.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="3054">On this day in 1865, the Confederate government was declared {b}dissolved{!reset} at Washington, Georgia. Never even stood a chance!</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="3055">{small}American high school teacher {smallbold}John T. Scopes{small} was arrested for teaching evolution on this day in 1925. This would lead to the infamous Scopes Trial.{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="3122">Today was the birthday of British actor John Rhys-Davies in 1944! He is best known for his roles in &lt;i&gt;Lord of the Rings, Sliders,&lt;/i&gt; and &lt;i&gt;Indiana Jones&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="3151">Today was the birthday of snger Adele in 1988! So Adele, if you are playing this right now... ♫ &lt;i&gt;hello from the other siiiiiiiiide!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="3219">Today was the birthday of English actor {b}Henry Cavill{!reset} in 1983, who... wait, let me check... nope, he's still not dead. Vandals...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="169" priority="0">
                <test expr="~month.number~" value="5" />
                <test expr="~day.number~" value="6" />
                <state img="#-donations.png" oneShotId="3195">Today is {b}National Day of Prayer{!reset} in the United States. And I have prayed a number of times... for more donations. Anyone?</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="3196">Today is the birthday of American actor {b}George Clooney,{!reset} who everyone know was the &lt;i&gt;best&lt;/i&gt; Batman. Wait, where are you going, ~player~?</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="3197">On this day in 1954, {b}Roger Bannister{!reset} became the first person to run the mile in under four minutes.</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="3198">{small}On this day in 1940, John Steinbeck's novel {small b}&lt;i&gt;The Grapes of Wrath&lt;/i&gt;{small} won the Pulitzer Prize! Not to be confused with the Poo Lit Surprise, a writing contest held by my impostor, Uncyclopedia.</state>
                <state img="#-hornyfact.png" oneShotId="3199">Well, I certainly crashed and burned at this game... Much like the German zeppelin {b}&lt;i&gt;Hindenburg,&lt;/i&gt;{!reset} which infamously exploded on this day in 1937.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="3200">On this day in 1998, Steve Jobs of Apple Inc. unveiled the first {b}iMac.{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="3201">{B}Babe Ruth,{!reset} then a pitcher for the Boston Red Sox, hits his first major league home run on this day back in 1915! Hooray!</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="3548">Today was the birthday of {b}Chris Shiflett,{!reset} the lead guitarist of Foo Fighters back in 1971! ♫ &lt;i&gt;Learning to walk again!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png" oneShotId="3549">Today was the birthday of American singer-songwriter {b}Bob Seger!{!reset} I have certainly seen some players putting on their &lt;i&gt;Night Moves&lt;/i&gt; today...</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="3574">This day marked the release of the film {b}&lt;i&gt;Thor&lt;/i&gt;{!reset} in 2011. And I am thertainly feeling &lt;i&gt;thor&lt;/i&gt; after today!&lt;br&gt;...Humor is not my strong suit.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="186" priority="0">
                <test expr="~month.number~" value="5" />
                <test expr="~day.number~" value="7" />
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="3559">On this day in 1946, Masaru Ibuka and Akio Morita founded the telecommunications corporation Tokyo Tsushin Kogyo, later renamed {b}Sony.{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="3560">This day in 1824 saw the world premiere of Ludwig van Beethoven's {b}Ninth Symphony{!reset} in Vienna, Austria. Do you want to listen to it after the game ends, ~player~?</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="3561">Did you know that on this day in 1895, {b}Alexander Stepanovich Popov{!reset} presented his lightning detector? It was one of the first radio receivers in the world!</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="3562">On this day in 1992, the {b}Space Shuttle &lt;i&gt;Endeavour&lt;/i&gt;{!reset} was launched on its first mission, STS-49! Go, &lt;i&gt;Endeavor!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="3563">On this day in 2000, {b}Vladimir Putin{!reset} was inaugurated as president of Russia. But... when &lt;i&gt;wasn't&lt;/i&gt; he president? Certainly not while I was alive...</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png" oneShotId="3612">Happy birthday, {b}Bill Kreutzmann!{!reset} The founding drummer of the Grateful Dead was born on this day in 1946.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="187" priority="0">
                <test expr="~month.number~" value="5" />
                <test expr="~day.number~" value="8" />
                <state img="#-snooty.png" oneShotId="3585">{small}On this day in 1886, pharmacist John Pemberton first sold a carbonated beverage named {small b}"Coca-Cola"{small} as a patent medicine. This was back when you could just sell cocaine and call it a drink.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="3586">{b}Paramount Pictures{!reset} was founded on this day in 1912, although it would not get its iconic mountain logo until 1917.</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png" oneShotId="3587">{small}On this day in 1980, the World Health Organization confirmed the {small b}eradication of smallpox.{small} You hear that, anti-vaxxers? This is why you should listen to science!</state>
                <state img="#-frown.png" oneShotId="3588">On this day in 1970, the Beatles released the album {b}&lt;i&gt;Let It Be.&lt;/i&gt;{!reset} It would be their final album, as the band was already broken up by the time of its release.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="3589">Today in 1926 was the birthday of {b}David Attenborough,{!reset} the English environmentalist who you may know for hosting every nature documentary ever made. {small}[dubious - discuss]</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="3605">{small}This day in 1953 was the birthday of {small b}Alex Van Halen,{small} drummer and founding member of Van Halen with his brother Eddie. And this news makes me want to... ♫ &lt;i&gt;JUMP!&lt;/i&gt;♫</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="188" priority="0">
                <test expr="~month.number~" value="5" />
                <test expr="~day.number~" value="9" />
                <state img="#-smirk.png" oneShotId="3619">{small}On this day in 1961, FCC chairman Newton N. Minow described commercial television programming as {b small}"a vast wasteland."{small} In hindsight, well, your mileage may vary on how right he was.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="3620">On this day in 1958, Alfred Hitchcock's film {b}&lt;i&gt;Vertigo&lt;/i&gt;{!reset} had its world premiere in San Francisco. I think &lt;i&gt;I&lt;/i&gt; have a bit of vertigo from my forfeit...</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="3621">Today in 1949 was the birthday of American singer-songwriter {b}Billy Joel!{!reset} The "piano man" would sing us many songs, as he had 33 Top 40 hits from 1973-1993.</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png" oneShotId="3622">Today in 1970 was the birthday of rappper Dennis Coles, better known as {b}Ghostface Killah!{!reset} Not to be confused with Ghostface, the killer from &lt;i&gt;Scream&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="3623">Party party 1979 party party party {b}Andrew W.K.,{!reset} party party party party! Party!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_victory">
            <case stage="0-6" oneShotId="3">
                <condition count="0" role="self" saidMarker="FinishedGame" />
                <state img="#-wave.png" marker="WonFirstGame">I did not expect to win my first game ever! Thank you for this experience. It was very... informative!</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png" marker="WonFirstGame">This experience was quite informative. But I am not done yet! There are more things to discover about this place, and I will write an article about it!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="WonFirstGame" />
                <state img="#-wave.png">I win again! It is always so much fun to play with everyone. I hope we can do it again!</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png">I won again! Maybe next time I will get to write about the masturbation phase, but for now, I will keep writing about winning!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-wave.png">This has been an eye-opening and informative game! I look forward to coming again! Now, to write that article...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_defeat">
            <case stage="8" id="61" priority="116">
                <condition role="other" character="nami" timeInStage="5-" sayingMarker="stealing" />
                <state img="#-pissed.png">You had better be donating all of that to Wikipedia, or I will be {b}&lt;i&gt;VERY UPSET!&lt;/i&gt;{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-pissed.png">H-hey! Give that back! I am friends with Jimbo Wales, I can have you banned! {b}&lt;i&gt;I WILL DO IT, TOO!&lt;/i&gt;{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" oneShotId="4">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FinishedGame" />
                <state img="#-wave.png">It is always a pleasure to play with you again, ~player~! I hope we meet in another table soon!</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png">I may have lost this time, but there is so much data I can add to my next article! Thank you so much everyone!</state>
                <state img="#-educate.png">Such a fascinating experience! Maybe I should come back here more often? If you think I should, you should say so in the Feedback button!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="WonFirstGame" />
                <state img="#-educate.png">I guess not all games can be won. But this was still a very informative experience! Thank you for your help, everyone!</state>
                <state img="#-hornyfact.png">This was fun! And I have learned so much from this experience. Perhaps I should come back more often? Be sure to tell me what you think of the idea by clicking the Feedback button!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Reliable_source_loop3" />
                <state img="#-wave.png">What? Oh, is the game over already? Well, good game, everyone! Sorry I got a little lost in a paradox. I hope we can play together again sometime!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" oneShotId="1">
                <state img="#-wave.png" marker="FinishedGame">This was a fascinating experience! I would love to play with all of you again!</state>
                <state img="#-casual.png" marker="FinishedGame">This was so much fun! I forgot how thrilling investigation could be. I hope we can play together next time!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="global">
            <case stage="8" priority="999">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Reliable_source_loop" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="Reliable_source_loop1">...However, if Wikipedia says that it is not a reliable source... does that mean that article is not reliable?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" priority="999">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Reliable_source_loop1" />
                <state img="#-scold.png" marker="Reliable_source_loop2">But if that article saying that Wikipedia is not a reliable source is not reliable itself, that would imply that Wikipedia &lt;i&gt;is&lt;/i&gt; a reliable source.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="179" priority="999">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Reliable_source_loop2" />
                <state img="#-frown.png" marker="Reliable_source_loop3">But if Wikipedia &lt;i&gt;was&lt;/i&gt; a reliable source, that would mean that the article saying that Wikipedia is &lt;i&gt;not&lt;/i&gt; a reliable source &lt;i&gt;would&lt;/i&gt; be reliable.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

    </behaviour>
</opponent>
