<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<collectibles>
    <collectible id="noire_cookies" status="online" img="opponents/noire/collectibles/collectible-cookies01.png" thumbnail="opponents/noire/collectibles/thumbnail-cookies01.png">
        <title>Noire's cookies</title>
        <subtitle>Black Heart taste (dark chocolate)</subtitle>
        <text>"I can bake, of course. Anyone can do it; it's enough to follow a recipe. The only secret ingredient you need to use is your feelings toward the person you make the cookies for... D-Don't misunderstand me! I don't necessarily mean liking or love, or things like that! It can just be the feelings of... gratitude and such!"</text>
        <unlock>Win a game against Noire.</unlock>
        <hide-details>true</hide-details>
    </collectible>
    <collectible id="noire_chocolates" status="online" img="opponents/noire/collectibles/collectible-chocolates02.png" thumbnail="opponents/noire/collectibles/thumbnail-chocolates02.png">
        <title>Black Heart's chocolates</title>
        <subtitle>Handmade and heart-shaped</subtitle>
        <text>"You won again, even more convincingly than before. I'm glad you've become so strong. As a reward, accept these chocolates. I transformed into my goddess form before making them, because I wanted the higher stats to make them as delicious and pretty as possible... You do understand what I mean by their shape and by giving them to you on a day like this, so I don't have to say anything more... Right?"</text>
        <unlock>Win another game against Noire in her default La Victoire costume, either during the Valentine's Day event or on the "romantic" background, and avoid losing too many clothes.</unlock>
        <hide-details>true</hide-details>
    </collectible>
    <collectible id="noire_plushie" status="online" img="opponents/noire/collectibles/collectible-plushie03.png" thumbnail="opponents/noire/collectibles/thumbnail-plushie03.png">
        <title>Noire plushie</title>
        <subtitle>Nowagurumi</subtitle>
        <text>A gift to help you rest with a peace of mind when Noire herself cannot sleep next to you. Effectiveness confirmed by Uni.&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;

(Made by Plutia. She will happily present Noire with another one.)</text>
        <unlock>Tire Noire out and then let her witness something so unexciting that she falls asleep. Can be unlocked with Noire wearing (or rather no longer wearing) any costume.</unlock>
        <hide-details>true</hide-details>
        <counter>3</counter>
    </collectible>
    <collectible id="noire_pic_with_the_plushie" status="online" img="opponents/noire/collectibles/collectible-picture04.png" thumbnail="opponents/noire/collectibles/thumbnail-picture04.png">
        <title>Noire and the plushie</title>
        <subtitle>Only one of them has removable clothes</subtitle>
        <text>"You brought my plushie with you! That was cute, thank you! Hm? You want to take a picture of me sitting next to it? Okay, I may let you take one... as an exceptional one-time reward for how well you played today... How should I pose?&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;H-huh?! In just my sleeves, boots and thigh-highs?! You have some guts to ask a goddess for that! And some quite particular tastes! I do like cosplay, as you're the only one to know... but not that kind of cosplay! ...P-Probably not, at least!!...&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;W-Well... If you really want me to do it no matter what, then I will pose... just this once! But if you're to have a picture of me, I want it to be a good one, so be serious and take it properly!"</text>
        <unlock>Have a certain collectible unlocked, play a game on the classroom background and win against Noire (in her default La Victoire costume) without losing too many clothes.</unlock>
        <hide-details>true</hide-details>
    </collectible>
    <collectible id="noire_lingerie" status="online" img="opponents/noire/collectibles/collectible-lingerie05.png">
        <title>Noire's showdown lingerie</title>
        <subtitle>It's not like she wore it—and took it off—for you</subtitle>
        <text>Noire gave you her favorite lingerie set as a keepsake after she lost it in a game of strip poker. 

Maybe next time you meet in Lastation, she will wear a similar set of underwear, maybe a different one... And maybe she will even allow you to take it off her yourself? &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;(The lingerie is a secret memento of your time spent with a pure-hearted goddess. Do not think about wearing it. Probably, the size would not match anyway.)</text>
        <unlock>A secret collectible. Make Noire in her default La Victoire costume lose her lingerie and pose for you naked. (Hint: She may do it if she stays unclothed but still in the game for many rounds.)</unlock>
        <hidden>true</hidden>
        <hide-details>true</hide-details>
    </collectible>
    <collectible id="noire_bracelets" status="online" img="opponents/noire/collectibles/collectible-bracelets06.png" thumbnail="opponents/noire/collectibles/thumbnail-bracelets06.png">
        <title>Noire's Cool Girl Bracelets</title>
        <subtitle>Fitting her idol costume</subtitle>
        <text>Noire's own bracelets or maybe just very similar bracelets that she gave you after she lost to you once again in a game of strip poker.&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;"You know perfectly well what my bracelets look like. Just accept them already instead of making me pose in them like this for no reason."</text>
        <unlock>Convincingly win against Noire in her Cool Girl costume. Do not lose too many clothes.</unlock>
        <hide-details>true</hide-details>
        <wearable>true</wearable>
        <clothing name="bracelets" generic="armbands" position="arms" type="extra" img="opponents/noire/collectibles/thumbnail-bracelets06.png" plural="true" />
    </collectible>
</collectibles>
