<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<collectibles>
    <collectible id="roll_buster" status="testing" img="opponents/roll/collectible1-weaponget.png" thumbnail="opponents/roll/collectible1-weaponget.png">
        <title>Roll Buster</title>
        <subtitle>The buster in which Roll used to use, way back when...</subtitle>
        <text>Roll's buster from when she used to fight in those various events, such as the Marvel one, or the one adventure she had with her brother, in which Wily kidnapped all the other Robot Masters. 
Again.</text>
        <unlock>Win a game against Roll</unlock>
        <hide-details>true</hide-details>
    </collectible>
    <collectible id="roll_helmet" status="testing" img="opponents/roll/collectible2-hoperidesalone.png" thumbnail="opponents/roll/collectible2-hoperidesalone.png">
        <title>Joe's Helmet</title>
        <subtitle>The helmet of a hero long forgotten, long deceased.</subtitle>
        <text>His sacrifice will not be in vain, she'll make sure of it. Her brothers might not believe anymore, yet she knows there truly are still heroes left in man. She just needs to find them.</text>
        <unlock>Sometimes, Roll will spout references to an alternate universe in appropriate circumstances.</unlock>
        <hide-details>true</hide-details>
        <counter>5</counter>
    </collectible>
    <collectible id="roll_ruinedroast" status="testing" img="opponents/roll/collectible3-unforgettableluncheon.png" thumbnail="opponents/roll/collectible3-unforgettableluncheon.png">
        <title>Roll's Really Ruined Rump Roast</title>
        <subtitle>Probably should've turned that oven off...</subtitle>
        <text>Well, Roll, I made it. Despite your directions.
Ah, Dr. Light! I hope you’re prepared for an unforgettable luncheon!
Yes…
Oh ye gods! My roast is ruined! But what if… I were to purchase fast food and disguise it as my own cooking! Ohoho, delightfully devilish, Roll-chan!
Agh!
Dr. Light! I was just… stretching my servos on the windowsill! Routine maintenance, care to join me?
Why is there smoke coming out of your oven, Roll?
Uh… oh! That isn’t smoke! It’s steam! Steam from the steamed clams we’re having! Mmm! Steamed clams. 
Phew.
Dr. Light, I hope you’re ready for mouth-watering hamburgers!
I thought we were having steamed clams?
Oh, no, I said steamed hams! That’s what I call hamburgers.
You call hamburgers steamed hams?
It’s a software quirk.
Uh huh. Where in the software?
Uh, in the personality code.
Really. Well, I coded you, and I’ve never had you use the phrase ‘steamed hams’.
Oh, no, not in the source code, no, it’s a neural networking quirk.
I see. You know, these hamburgers are quite similar to the ones they have at Mega Burger.
Ohohoh, no. Patented Roll Burger, old robot recipe!
For steamed hams?
Yes!
Yes and you call them steamed hams despite the fact they are obviously grilled.
Ye-... uh… you don’t s-.... One thing I sh-.... Excuse me for one second.
Of course.
Ah, well, that was wonderful. A good time was had by all, I’m drained!
Yes I should b- GREAT ASIMOV WHAT IS HAPPENING IN THERE!?
Dr. Wily came back.
D-Dr. Wily came back!? At this time of year, at this time of day, in this part of the city, localized entirely within our kitchen!?
Yes!
Should we stop him?
No.
Roll! The lab is on fire!
No, Rock, it’s just a mad scientist.
Well, Roll, you are an odd robot, but I must say… you steam a good ham.
Ice Man! Splash Woman! Help!</text>
        <hidden>true</hidden>
    </collectible>
</collectibles>
