<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>

<!--This file was machine generated using the Character Editor v6.7.4 at 3:14:35 AM on April 29, 2022. Do not edit this file directly unless you know what you're doing.-->
<opponent>
    <version>v6.7.4</version>
    <first>Blake</first>
    <last>Belladonna</last>
    <label>Blake</label>
    <gender>female</gender>
    <size>medium</size>
    <timer>22</timer>
    <intelligence>average</intelligence>



    <wardrobe>
        <clothing name="underwear" generic="underwear" position="lower" type="important" />
        <clothing name="bra" generic="bra" position="upper" type="important" />
        <clothing name="tights" generic="leggings" position="lower" type="major" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="bow" generic="ribbon" position="head" type="minor" />
        <clothing name="shirt" generic="shirt" position="upper" type="major" />
        <clothing name="shorts" generic="shorts" position="lower" type="minor" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="boots" generic="shoes" position="feet" type="extra" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="arm wraps" generic="armbands" position="arms" type="extra" plural="true" />
    </wardrobe>


    <behaviour>
        <trigger id="selected">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-calm.png">It's Blake. I'm here to get away from it all for a while.</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">Blake Belladonna. &lt;i&gt;(This isn't any place on Remnant. Maybe I can let my guard down here... then again, maybe not.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_start">
            <case stage="0" priority="110">
                <condition count="3" filter="rwby" role="other" />
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Oh. Hey... team.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="fina" sayingMarker="FinaMasturbateWarning" />
                <state img="#-read.png">&lt;i&gt; (Of course it is. I hope no one actually needs that warning.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="estelle" saidMarker="EstelleGreeting" />
                <state img="#-tsundere.png">Oh hey. I wasn't expecting such a warm welcome. You can call me Blake.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="yang_xiao_long" />
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" marker="yang_greet">Ohh hey Yang! Your uhh... here to play as well then? &lt;i&gt; (That's a stupid greeting of course she's here to play... with me) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="yang" />
                <state img="#-unimpressed.png">That's a pretty poor impersonation. Who are you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="blake" />
                <state img="#-unimpressed.png">Neo? Cut it out. That's a terrible replica of my costume.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="ae86" />
                <state img="#-think.png">Right, it's April fools. &lt;i&gt; (Impressive robotics at least. I bet Ruby would love to look them over.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="pyrrha" />
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" marker="pyrrha_greet">Pyrrha? You came along to a place like this? Then again I'm here too.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" oneShotId="38">
                <condition role="opp" character="yuelia" />
                <state img="#-admire.png">That's an impressive Semblance. Ruby briefly transforms, I think, but I've never seen something like that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="22">
                <condition count="3" filter="black_hair" role="opp" />
                <state img="#-sarcastic.png">Hmm I wonder if, ~human~ prefers any hair colors, hard to tell. &lt;i&gt; (And I hope that's not the only reason I'm at the table.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="32" oneShotId="70">
                <condition count="3" filter="criminal" role="opp" />
                <state img="#-wistful.png" marker="crimminal_table">Well I'm used to hanging out with other criminals. I just hope this is a better group of people than the last one.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="33">
                <condition count="3" filter="royalty" role="opp" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="royal_table">I'm not too impressed, or out of my depth here actually. The Belladonna name is well known... if only where I grew up.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="34" oneShotId="71">
                <condition count="3" filter="student" role="opp" />
                <state img="#-chat.png" marker="student_table">Not sure how much I'll have in common with you all, but I am a student too, at Beacon Academy.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="35" oneShotId="72">
                <condition count="3" filter="supernatural" role="opp" />
                <state img="#-startled.png" marker="supernatural_table">Sorry if I seem a little out of place. This is quite a group.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="36">
                <condition count="3" filter="confident" role="opp" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="confident_table">I don't mind trailing behind the more confident on my team, or in a game like this.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="37">
                <condition count="2-" filter="dominant" role="opp" />
                <state img="#-aroused.png">&lt;i&gt; (Oh, this game could be even more fun than I thought.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="38">
                <alternative>
                    <condition count="3-" filter="cheerful" role="opp" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <condition count="3-" filter="kind" role="opp" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="kind_table">This is the kind of table I was hoping for. Thank you for having me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="29" oneShotId="68">
                <condition count="4" gender="male" role="opp" />
                <state img="#-startled.png">Uhh... okay. This is not the kind of group I expected to play with. Be prepared to give as good as you get. &lt;i&gt; (Not going to deny enjoying reading about... something like this though.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="30">
                <condition count="-1" gender="male" role="opp" />
                <state img="#-chat.png">Might be for the best. I do like boys but too many could be overwhelming.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="31" oneShotId="69">
                <condition count="4" gender="female" role="opp" />
                <state img="#-bashful.png">This does feel a little more comfortable for me... even in a game like this.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-chat.png">It's Blake. I'm here to get away from it all for a while.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="swap_cards">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-calm.png">~Cards.text~ ~cards.ifplural(cards|card)~.</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">Just ~cards.text~ ~cards.ifplural(cards|card)~, please.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-5">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Sure, ~cards.text~ ~cards.ifplural(cards|card)~.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">Hmm, ~cards.text~ ~cards.ifplural(cards|card)~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-think.png">Should probably go for ~cards.text~ ~cards.ifplural(cards|card)~, thanks.</state>
                <state img="#-stretching.png">Hmm, maybe, ~cards.text~ ~cards.ifplural(cards|card)~, thanks.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="good_hand">
            <case stage="6-8" oneShotId="60">
                <condition count="0" role="opp" character="ruby" />
                <condition count="0" role="opp" character="weiss_schnee" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="rubywiess">That time Ruby teased Weiss for being concerned for her romantic life. I was definitely surprised by the lean in from Ruby. They might actually make a cute couple.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-think.png">Not sure if I want to have good luck at a time like this. </state>
                <state img="#-sarcastic.png">Sure. Can't frown at a rainbow... unless the rain keeps coming afterwards.</state>
                <state img="#-chat.png">Of course I'm going to get some good hands. Let's see if it keeps up.</state>
                <state img="#-tsundere.png">Always better to start off with a few wins. I'll take hits eventually but at least I know I can fight back.</state>
                <state img="#-read.png">Doubt I need to worry about these cards and I've nearly finished this. I've got a few others lined up to read next I'd like to get to.</state>
                <state img="#-read.png">It would have been easy enough to bring a poker guide actually. Doesn't matter much anyway, it's not complex strategy to win a hand.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-5">
                <state img="#-admire.png">&lt;i&gt; (Games like this aren't something I've read about more then a few times... but that does make how this goes more interesting) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">I bet Yang would've cracked a dozen puns about how handy these cards are by now.</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">I do enjoy the games my teammates play from time to time, even if the rules tend to be... far less coherent. </state>
                <state img="#-stretching.png">I was tempted to join the last Grimm and Grotto's session. I just wasn't sure how to bring it up with with Yang. I think I might before the next one.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I guess I don't mind being a few down in a friendly contest. I'm glad that's most of mine these days.</state>
                <state img="#-tsundere.png">Even if I wasn't going to the next Vytal tournament I'd know it was coming up. Yang has had the time of her life making it clear how &lt;i&gt; vital &lt;/i&gt; it is she trains for it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-stretching.png">When I was a bit younger I never thought I could be so comfortable away from home. I owe a lot to my team.</state>
                <state img="#-tsundere.png">I don't like rain much, but it does sound nice, and watching Ruby and Weiss  enjoy it is always sweet.</state>
                <state img="#-admire.png">How secure I felt here was never about the cards, but this is a good hand too.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I enjoyed the Vytal festivals more than I expected. The unity between kingdoms is encouraging to see.</state>
                <state img="#-chat.png">The Second Vytal festival is coming up. I'm not as keen on combat as Yang or Ruby, but fighting in the arena with the crowd roaring does get my blood pumping, and I'm too focused to be nervous.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">I never thought I'd associate being comfortable and playing cards. Between my friends at Beacon and winning this hand, I guess I do now.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="okay_hand">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-think.png">I don't like having no control over how this round goes, but at least it's just cards.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Well, it was up to fate before I bothered.</state>
                <state img="#-stretching.png">I wasn't going to hope for a good hand anyway.</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">It was stupid to think that I could just hang out here and forget... everything.</state>
                <state img="#-chat.png">I'm not pleased by this hand, but I can't deny that the game has taken my mind off study.</state>
                <state img="#-skeptical.png">I never found the idea of fate as being neutral a very comforting one.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-5">
                <state img="#-confused.png">I've been forced to let the cards fall where they may on bigger stuff, but it's never a great feeling.</state>
                <state img="#-unimpressed.png">I'm used to uncertainty at least, for whatever that is worth.</state>
                <state img="#-tsundere.png">I might be fussing about the cards too much in spite of myself. This isn't so bad.</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">Maybe I have got a shot at this round after all.</state>
                <state img="#-stretching.png">I've played plenty of board and card games since Beacon. I assumed I wouldn't have time, but if the rest of my team aren't studying anyway I may as well join them right?</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">It's interesting how certain we can be that things will be unpredictable.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-unimpressed.png">You win some, you lose some, but not knowing what's happening is worse than either.</state>
                <state img="#-chat.png">It took a while to adjust to the showers at Beacon with the water constantly hitting me like that, but they are much more pleasant by now.</state>
                <state img="#-tsundere.png">I couldn't imagine myself at a game like this with well... non-faunus a few years ago. I'm glad that's changed. I'm glad I'm happy to... see this through. </state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">You know what, if I can become friends with Weiss  I can handle this game.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Ruby would probably be talking about how she definitely win with a hand like this. I'm not as sure, but I respect that attitude.</state>
                <state img="#-read.png">I've been told many times not to worry about what I can't control. Maybe it's finally sinking in.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="bad_hand">
            <case stage="5-8" oneShotId="1">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="thunderstorm" />
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" marker="thunderstorm2">No, I don't hate thunderstorms because I'm a cat Faunus. They're just so loud and sudden.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">This isn't much of a surprise with my luck.</state>
                <state img="#-unimpressed.png" marker="dogmail">At least I'm not dealing with that dog. I cannot believe Yang's dad actually sent him via the mail to her and Ruby .</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="thunderstorm">Great. Now all we need is a thunderstorm... which has nothing to do with... nevermind.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">Hopefully this hand isn't a sign of things to come, but I expect it is.</state>
                <state img="#-sarcastic.png">As Yang would say 'I can still win with this', mostly just before I beat her.</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">It's a shame that whenever people compete someone losing is a guarantee.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-5">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">I do keep wondering when my luck will turn bad again. I'm glad we're just playing cards...&lt;i&gt; (and undressing.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-tsundere.png">This won't win me anything. &lt;i&gt; (Except admiration, maybe.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-unimpressed.png">Been in too much  actual danger for a bad hand of cards to really worry me much.</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">I've gotten a lot further on trust than I ever thought I would, but I don't think that'll save this hand.</state>
                <state img="#-skeptical.png">Somebody always loses, at least I signed up for it this time.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-unimpressed.png">I can already hear Weiss  telling me off for swapping that. Not that she would've have done much better.</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">Beacon's been good, this has been good... but it's hard to forget it all for long.</state>
                <state img="#-skeptical.png">The lack of intense conflict for most of my life at Beacon is welcome, but sometimes...</state>
                <state img="#-tsundere.png">I still remember all the mess before Beacon sometimes... it's been years now. I wonder if I should still be bothered by it all. Sorry, ignore me, I came out here to have fun and I shouldn't spoil that.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">For all the shit we've been through, we're still here, and I smile more than I ever thought I would. I can handle one more bad hand of cards.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">I did not come here to lose, but well... I knew my odds.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="hand">
            <case stage="0-10" id="5">
                <condition role="other" character="ribbon_girl" stage="1" timeInStage="1" sayingMarker="ArmPowerTalk2" />
                <state img="#-skeptical.png">Like a Semblance, we have similar powers in my word... I think.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10">
                <condition role="other" character="amalia" stage="5" saidMarker="grow1" sayingMarker="grow2" />
                <condition role="self" notSaidMarker="grow2" />
                <state img="#-skeptical.png" marker="grow2">I feel like you should have warned us before you did that, but alright.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10">
                <condition role="opp" character="aqua_grunt" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-unimpressed.png" marker="blake_aq_destructiveplan">&lt;i&gt; Right. &lt;/i&gt; And you've carefully considered the moral implications right? The destruction you'd bring?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10">
                <condition role="opp" character="miki_miura" sayingMarker="miki_birthday" />
                <state img="#-tsundere.png">I'm not about to throw a hand for you, but happy birthday.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="25">
                <condition role="opp" character="hilda" sayingMarker="ResentScarfTie" />
                <state img="#-think.png" marker="scarftie_reply">We'll all have to redo our outfits anyway, whoever wins.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="36">
                <condition role="opp" character="brock" sayingMarker="brock_prompt_weapon" />
                <state img="#-worried.png" oneShotId="11">My Gambol shroud, it's a grappling hook, gun and sword. It's unique, but that's allowed me to become very good with it. Ada...a former frein... someone I used to know made it for me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="58">
                <condition role="opp" character="yang_xiao_long" saidMarker="yangpartner" />
                <state img="#-tsundere.png" marker="blakepartner">You know what I meant, Yang! Of course you're important to me!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="61">
                <condition role="opp" character="ms.fortune" sayingMarker="Mafia_Takedown" />
                <state img="#-skeptical.png" marker="mafia_nadiaresp">That mostly depends on how bloody you're willing to get your hands. As a lone attacker you have the advantage of being hard to track, and surprise, but do you think it's fair to go that far?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4" id="40" oneShotId="75">
                <condition role="opp" character="senko" sayingMarker="senko_pampering" />
                <state img="#-tsundere.png" marker="senko_pamper_cuddles">I don't spend a lot of time thinking about it. Being comfortable and quiet with my friends is always good. Being able to nuzzle up and accept... cuddling, is good to. &lt;i&gt; (And scritches, especially on my ears.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-10" id="41" oneShotId="76">
                <condition role="opp" character="senko" sayingMarker="senko_pampering" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="senko_pamper_earshonest">I don't spend a lot of time thinking about that. Being comfortable and quiet with my friends is always wonderful. Nuzzling someone I trust and accepting ear scritches is deeply comforting to.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="68" oneShotId="92">
                <condition role="opp" character="meia" saying="dread" />
                <state img="#-unimpressed.png" marker="meia_the_dread_pilot_roberts">That's quite a title, what do you have to&lt;i&gt; do &lt;/i&gt; to become the dreaded?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="93">
                <condition role="opp" character="ignatz" sayingMarker="igbullykink" />
                <state img="#-think.png">Gah. I've seen how rumors like that get spread to hurt people before. I trust you, Ignatz.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="94">
                <condition role="opp" character="ignatz" sayingMarker="paintingoffer" />
                <state img="#-sarcastic.png" marker="paintingoffer">That sounds lovely, but I have to ask how many people have immediately talked about nudes when you announce it in a place like this?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="97">
                <condition role="opp" character="ignatz" sayingMarker="igassassin_study" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="blake_ignatz_assassin">If the test is tomorrow then I'm not sure what you can do except cram. I didn't pick you as the assassin type though, that's some very cold blooded violence.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" id="71" oneShotId="105">
                <condition role="opp" character="pyrrha" sayingMarker="wanttobefamous" />
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="blake_py_fame_easy">Absolutely not. I've rarely enjoyed the attention I do get. I'm always impressed by your ability to easily handle so much spotlight.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" id="72" oneShotId="106">
                <condition role="opp" character="pyrrha" sayingMarker="define_friendship" />
                <state img="#-amused.png" marker="blake_py_freindship">Those who stick by you, even when you're not sure if you deserve it. How do &lt;i&gt; you&lt;/i&gt; define friendship, Pyrrha? No pressure of course.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="107">
                <condition role="opp" character="pyrrha" sayingMarker="too_serious_joke" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" marker="blake_py_jokes">Lots, but mainly I don't take kindly to people making fun of Faunus. As I'm sure you can imagine.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="108">
                <condition role="opp" character="pyrrha" sayingMarker="why_playing" />
                <state img="#-bashful.png" marker="Blake_py_whyplay">I'm not sure what you're expecting me to say. We all need to blow off steam from time to time, right? Yang and Sun have made that very clear to me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="109">
                <condition role="opp" character="pyrrha" sayingMarker="plans_tomorrow" />
                <state img="#-stretching.png" marker="blake_py_work">You know me well enough. Making plans before the day doesn't suit me. Probably more of the same though, study and training. Did you want to work together?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="111">
                <condition role="opp" character="yuri" sayingMarker="yuri_book_recommendations" />
                <state img="#-chat.png" marker="blake_yuri_books">Depends what you're looking for, really. I mostly read romance, but I've read my share of horror and drama. I used to read a lot of adventure and fantasy.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5" id="23" oneShotId="64">
                <test expr="~background.category~" value="bar" />
                <state img="#-worried.png">I haven't been a patron anywhere like this before. It's a good change of pace.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5" id="24" oneShotId="65">
                <test expr="~background~" value="tiki bar" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">I'm not a big fan of water, but the ocean is beautiful, especially from here.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5" id="25" oneShotId="66">
                <test expr="~background~" value="alley" />
                <state img="#-unimpressed.png">Well this certainly doesn't scream safety and comfort. At least if I decide to run I doubt anyone here could catch me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5" id="27" oneShotId="67">
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~background~" value="poolside" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~background~" value="beach" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Hmm, I could be convinced to go for a swim after the game... if anyone wanted to join me &lt;i&gt;then. &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5" id="28" oneShotId="79">
                <test expr="~background~" value="hot spring" />
                <state img="#-wistful.png">This makes me nostalgic, I mostly grew up with hot springs. They'll be great to soak in after game.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5" id="39" oneShotId="74">
                <test expr="~background.category~" value="forest" />
                <state img="#-stretching.png">Wouldn't be the first time I've spent a night in the forest, I doubt it'll be the last.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5" id="58" oneShotId="77">
                <test expr="~background~" value="bedroom" />
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Who's bedroom is this exactly? I don't plan on getting in bed with anyone today. &lt;i&gt; (Maybe I should rethink that though.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5" id="60" oneShotId="80">
                <test expr="~background.temperature~" value="hot" />
                <state img="#-stretching.png">At least the heat doesn't get to me much. I'm pretty used to these conditions.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5" id="61" oneShotId="81">
                <test expr="~background.dark~" value="true" />
                <state img="#-amused.png">I have near perfect sight in the dark, so ~background~ works great for me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5" id="63" oneShotId="83">
                <test expr="~background.temperature~" value="cold" />
                <state img="#-think.png">Not my choice of location to undress at, but the game might just... keep me hot enough.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5" id="64" oneShotId="84">
                <test expr="~background.category~" value="school" />
                <state img="#-think.png">Is this what a school is like where you come from? Beacon is a little more... dramatic.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5" id="65" oneShotId="85">
                <test expr="~background.surface~" value="grass" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">Wouldn't be the first time I've undressed outside, even in a sexual context.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5" id="59" oneShotId="78" priority="49">
                <test expr="~background.bathing~" value="true" />
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Sure. I do appreciate that the showers at Beacon are open at any time you need them for when I'm... when missions run late sometimes.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="opp" character="leon" sayingMarker="leon01" />
                <condition role="opp" character="hu_tao" />
                <state img="#-tsundere.png" marker="blake_leon_tao1">Gothic sure is in at this table, huh? Not that I don't appreciate the compliments.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="124">
                <condition role="opp" character="jura" sayingMarker="blake_belladonna0" />
                <state img="#-sarcastic.png" marker="blake_jura1">It's not on me that you don't know how to wear the color. What's a confident blonde like you doing in black anyway?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="76" oneShotId="125">
                <condition role="opp" character="revy" sayingMarker="blake_belladonna0" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" marker="blake_revy1">Charming, truly. I don't make a lot of friends, but at least I have them.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="77" oneShotId="126">
                <condition role="opp" character="leon" sayingMarker="leon01" />
                <state img="#-stretching.png" marker="blake_leon01">I wasn't going for Gothic exactly, but I'll take the compliment from you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" oneShotId="131">
                <condition role="opp" character="meia" sayingMarker="blake_belladonna0" />
                <state img="#-sarcastic.png" marker="blake_meia_leaders">Level enough to understand I'm not the best choice honestly. It went to Ruby, she's far brighter and more enthusiastic, but her zeal is contiguous. She pays &lt;i&gt; enough &lt;/i&gt; attention to detail, if barely.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-prestrip-.png">I didn't expect better luck.</state>
                <state img="#-prestrip+.png">Well, no such thing as a totally clean win.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-tsundere.png">I'll have you know your spoiling my aesthetic.</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">Well, at least there was nothing more I could've done.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-calm.png">&lt;i&gt; (I'm playing a full game with these people. They deserve something, I guess.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-sarcastic.png">Since you're all staring anyway, I guess I can talk a bit about myself.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">&lt;i&gt; (It is nice to be getting attention for something I'm choosing to show off, for myself.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-chat.png">Don't get too excited yet, but it's true I don't have much small stuff left.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Well, I don't want to lose the tights just yet, and you all seem alright so...</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">&lt;i&gt; (Deep breath Blake, you can do this.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">It hardly matters compared to my ears... but even so. I'm hardly used to this.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">I'm no stranger to scrutiny but this is... different. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-tsundere.png">I'd prefer it if you were looking forward to this, I suppose.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Not gonna try and pretend this isn't worth almost as much as my ears were.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-wistful.png">I knew what I signed up for, but this is a lot.</state>
                <state img="#-stretching.png">I'm prepared to... finish the game, but I need a second to catch my breath.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_winning">
            <case stage="0-2" oneShotId="2">
                <state img="#-calm.png">It wouldn't feel right if I didn't take off a few things at least.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-7">
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="1">Sure, good luck never lasts forever anyway.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_normal">
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="4">
                <state img="#-tsundere.png">Life never seems to take me where I expect, but at least these days I'm more sure of my choices.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_losing">
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="5">
                <state img="#-think.png">I've been in a lot of tougher spots than this.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripping">
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="opp" character="yang_xiao_long" sayingMarker="blake_tights" />
                <state img="#-stripping+.png" marker="yang_tights">I'm not sure if you being so enthusiastic makes it better or worse...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" oneShotId="127">
                <condition role="opp" character="leon" sayingMarker="leon02" />
                <state img="#-stripping+.png" marker="blake_leon2">Well done, Leon. You've thoroughly convinced me your eyes work.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="16">
                <condition filter="rwby_franchise" role="opp" />
                <state img="#-stripping-.png" marker="Remmant_expo_noexplain">As huntresses we train to hunt the creatures of Grimm. They are a constant threat to the people of Remnant. We also deal with... other threats. Nobody else seemed like they wanted to explain.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition count="3" filter="rwby" role="opp" />
                <state img="#-stripping-.png" marker="blake_expofullrwby">I'm a final year student training at Beacon academy with friends in team RWBY to become huntresses. I think you can figure out the rest, ~human~, given we're all... playing strip poker together.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" priority="9">
                <condition role="opp" character="ruby" />
                <state img="#-stripping+.png" marker="rwby_expo_ruby">I'm a final year student training at Beacon academy with my friends in team RWBY to become huntresses. RWBY spells out our first initials. Ruby is  team leader and admirably hopeful, no matter what.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="15" priority="2">
                <state img="#-stripping+.png" marker="rwby_expo1">I'm a final year student training at beacon academy with my team, RWBY, to become huntresses. RWBY spells out our first initials. Ruby's team leader, she's smart, and hopeful, maybe too much, but maybe not.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-stripping-.png" marker="silent_strip">&lt;i&gt; (... I should probably talk about where I'm from, or what I do, my friends, something like that... well, too late now. I only just met these people anyway.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-stripping-.png" marker="slient_strip">&lt;i&gt; (I want to trust these people, and it seems like I can. Even so there aren't any guarantees, and I'm not in a hurry to appease them with small talk.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4" id="1">
                <state img="#-stripping-.png" marker="ears_admit">Yeah I'm a Faunus, that's what the cat ears mean on Remnant. It's not a big deal. I just prefer to avoid announcing it. Lots of people don't respond well to us. </state>
                <state img="#-stripping-.png" marker="ears_admit">My ears are why I wear the bow, but given how far this game goes, I guess I can show them. Acceptance of me and other Faunus is an issue back home, to put it mildly.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">This is not where I pictured myself when I woke up this morning.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">You can look just... &lt;i&gt; (Don't comment, please comment? I'm not sure.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">I'm not too nervous about this at least, it's pretty warm back home... though my other tops are more than just a bra.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">&lt;i&gt;( I do look good in these tights though, damn.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">I knew I'd end up showing off a bit. Not something I'm used to, but I'm not leaving now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">I got used to leggings when I was younger. Without them you get all scratched whenever you climb anything or need to run in a forest.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">Sometimes the best way to climb a tree is to wrap your legs around it and haul yourself up, and trust me doing that without tights is a mistake you only make once.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">It's.... It's alright, I knew what I was getting into and I still came. &lt;i&gt; (Or more, I wouldn't mind that either even if I'm not going to admit that....) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">I've dealt with worse than a simple game, even if this is... different.  &lt;i&gt; (And much hotter.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="17">
                <state img="#-stripping-.png" marker="Remmant_expo">As huntresses we train to hunt the creatures of Grimm. They are monsters drawn to negativity and a constant threat to the cities and people of Remnant. We also deal with... other threats, as needed. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">This case was auto generated, but the overlap of other cases means it should never play, if you see this line in a game, please report it lol.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripped">
            <case stage="1-8">
                <condition role="opp" character="leon" sayingMarker="leon03" />
                <condition role="opp" character="hu_tao" />
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" marker="blake_leon_tao3">Is there a significant difference? I mean yes I... wait, nevermind. I'm... comfortable, yeah. &lt;i&gt; (And going to melt if these two keep it up.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <condition role="opp" character="yang_xiao_long" sayingMarker="blake_tights2" />
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I---I never said that either.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-8" id="73" oneShotId="110">
                <condition role="opp" character="yuri" saying="Some people change their behavior significantly depending on the situation they find themselves in, others act consistently everywhere. " />
                <state img="#-tsundere.png" marker="blake_yuri_consistant">I think it can be mark of strength to be consistent and honest with people, regardless of who they are.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" oneShotId="128">
                <condition role="opp" character="leon" sayingMarker="leon03" />
                <state img="#-bashful.png" marker="leon_blake3">You would be surprised about the fight utility... You aren't wrong about a game like this though. Thanks, I'm glad to be here.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="18">
                <condition role="opp" character="weiss_schnee" />
                <state img="#-amused.png" marker="wiessjudgements">Yang is... my closest friend, she's kind, gentle, and brave. They're all good friends, better than I ever thought I'd have, or deserve. You can make your own judgments on Weiss  though.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="opp" character="yang_xiao_long" />
                <state img="#-stripped+.png" marker="yang_expo">Weiss  is uhh... we get along better these days, she's strong and determined. Yang is... my partner, each person in the team has a partner, for attacks and stuff...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" priority="98">
                <condition count="0" role="opp" character="yang_xiao_long" />
                <condition count="0" role="opp" character="weiss" />
                <state img="#-stripped+.png" marker="rwby_expo2">Weiss  is, uhh, we get along better these days, she's strong and determined. Yang is... my closest friend, she's kind, gentle, and brave. They're good friends, better than I ever thought I'd have. &lt;i&gt; (Or deserve.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">&lt;i&gt;(Yeah, It's a lot for strangers to just expect me to talk about myself. Next round I'll share something... probably.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">&lt;i&gt; (If anyone was expecting me to be more talkative on my first loss, I guess they learned something important.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Of course they match. I've been thinking about coming to this for... a while. &lt;i&gt; (In both senses of the word.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">It's comfortable under the tights, alright? &lt;i&gt; (Not saying that's the only reason I brought these ones, but it's true.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">The appreciation feels... a little unexpected, but I'm okay with it.</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">I have always been happy with my breasts, any bigger would make being so active frustrating.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-wistful.png">&lt;i&gt;(Deep breath Blake, you're having fun, you don't need to be afraid here.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">That's me. Sorry it's not more exciting, but I mostly like it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I've got a friend who goes around with their shirt open, and Yang's always been a tease. &lt;i&gt;(Guess I'm just more used to admiring then joining in.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">It might seem a little early, but well... you'll probably understand soon.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5" id="67">
                <state img="#-tsundere.png" marker="ears_reveal">Yes, I love fish, and climbing, and I don't like the dog... But that is coincidence, alright? &lt;i&gt; (And I can't help but follow laser pointers, and I'm content in boxes, but they don't need to know everything.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="ears_reveal">This is why I showed my bra first so... be nice, alright?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-skeptical.png">&lt;i&gt; (I didn't plan to dress to the item limit, but my outfit just has a lot of layers, sorry.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">I don't wear anything too precious to me all the time. I might break or lose it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">This line also should never play in game. I'm giving it a pose so the validator doesn't hassle me.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_strip">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <condition role="opp" startingLayers="6-8" />
                <state img="#-skeptical.png" oneShotId="78">I can't complain about you layering up. It's the smart thing to do. &lt;i&gt; (Not that I did it on purpose.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-5" priority="0">
                <alternative>
                    <condition status="not_chest_visible" role="target" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-stretching.png">You're not anything new to me yet. It's hot back home, and I've got a friend who refuses to button his shirt.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I did come here for a good time, and you'd prefer me when I'm happy...</state>
                <state img="#-tsundere.png">You don't want to be outdone by the shy one do you?</state>
                <state img="#-chat.png">I could advise a better play, but then you might take it.</state>
                <state img="#-wistful.png">I don't miss... him, but sometimes I miss how safe I felt wrapped in his arms, dressed like this.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">You can tell me how you... feel... about me right now. I knew what I signed up for.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-confused.png">(&lt;i&gt; Two very attractive blondes back at beacon, come on. Give me a reason to think about you.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-fantasyidle.png">If you're not interested in impressing me, you're making a mistake. &lt;i&gt; (I'd let anyone touch my ears right now,especially if they teased my breasts at the same time.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="blakeconcern">I've got nothing to worry about from you. I know that, sorry if I seem a bit.. out of it at times.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">It wasn't easy learning to get help from my friends, but I'd happily accept a helping hand right now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-read2.png">I can hope you take off something worthwhile... but I'll be alright either way.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Honestly I can't remember the last time I stopped after just one round.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">I'm still running hot... how are you feeling?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-read.png">Ruby gave it this book me when we last swapped, but it was one I loved when I was a little younger. It's nice to see it again. </state>
                <state img="#-read.png">I do wonder how long my preference for romance novels will last. I liked adventure novels until it was stuff like that I needed the break from.</state>
                <state img="#-skeptical.png">I'd hope for something good, but I've got enough real problems to hope about.</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">...</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="blake_adamnerves">Not thrilled about meeting men for the first time in this context. Even if I'm not overly worried about them at Beacon.</state>
                <state img="#-skeptical.png">Sure.</state>
                <state img="#-chat.png">Not sure if I'm really in the mood to chat with you yet, but maybe you could impress me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-5">
                <state img="#-stretching.png">It was bound to be somebody. You'll get a turn to watch eventually.</state>
                <state img="#-skeptical.png">At least you're taking it relatively well. I was a little concerned.</state>
                <state img="#-read2.png">I've nearly finished this chapter, hopefully in time to watch something nearly as good.</state>
                <state img="#-read2.png">Don't feel obliged to hurry. I can always keep reading.</state>
                <state img="#-chat.png">Feeling alright? I know this game can be a lot.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Sure.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_strip">
            <case stage="0-10">
                <condition role="target" character="joey" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-think.png">Impressive slight of hand, I wonder if I could match that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" id="13">
                <condition role="target" character="joey" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">I am always interested in a good trick.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2" oneShotId="88" priority="0">
                <condition filter="rwby_franchise" role="opp" />
                <state img="#-think.png">&lt;i&gt;(I'm glad this game has slower rounds. Gives me time to get used to this place and these people.)
 &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-5">
                <state img="#-admire.png">&lt;i&gt; (She's pretty, but I'm not in a hurry to tell her that, not yet, anyway.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-skeptical.png">I got lucky with people being nice to me at Beacon, I don't expect that to keep up.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I do appreciate wandering alone, it allows you to see the little beautiful things. Like leaves falling or dust settling, but I don't need any of that to admire you.</state>
                <state img="#-read2.png">What you're taking off or not doesn't bother me too much, I'll just read for a bit. </state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Not expecting anything good, but I would appreciate it.</state>
                <state img="#-read.png">I'm reading so you don't feel pressured or anything, you can take your time.</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">Hmm.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-admire.png">I have been looking forward to this more then the rest of the game.</state>
                <state img="#-chat.png">I get playing to win, but don't you want to impress us?</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I'm happy to be playing with other girls. You don't need to be shy.
</state>
                <state img="#-tsundere.png">In a way, maybe it's better there is only one winner. So those who need to... forfeit, have more company.</state>
                <state img="#-wistful.png">I don't hold it against you if you win and we don't see any more. Even if we all tried to throw there would still be a winner.</state>
                <state img="#-chat.png">Yang doesn't always have the easiest time convincing me to try new things. But knowing I'd be playing with people like you made coming here much easier.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-calm.png">You've got my attention this round. Keep it please?</state>
                <state img="#-fantasyidle.png">Shit that's good, I don't do this nearly enough.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">I never said all my romance novels where about boys... Some of my favorite scenes are more like this...</state>
                <state img="#-read2.png">I promise, your next move doesn't have to be as elaborate as anything I'm reading to get my attention.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I'll admit it... you could probably get me purring, but only if you try.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">I've always been content with not rushing things, not wanting to get too close to people, but... do you want to join me, ~target~?</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I really shouldn't be so shy about asking you for something good when I'm already doing... this.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Do you want me to go another round, or not?</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Planning to grab my attention? Or would you rather grab my wrists?</state>
                <state img="#-admire.png">I can appreciate female and male beauty without making it sexual. However,  being welcome to do so here is... very nice.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">You're looking good, ~target. I do think you'd look better in my current outfit though.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Do you play a lot of cards or have you been lucky? Or maybe whether your good at cards is a better question. I've played plenty and look at me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-read.png">&lt;i&gt; (Don't want to pressure her into taking off something big early, so I'll just read.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">&lt;i&gt; (I'm not particularly worthy of her taking off anything notable, so I don't expect it.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-read.png">I do wonder a bit if this was the best use of my day. &lt;i&gt;(The others made it very clear how important rest is, relax Blake.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">This is good, I could hardly bring... study material. So worst case at least I'm not fixating on that.</state>
                <state img="#-read2.png">&lt;i&gt; (That's not the chapter I planned to flip to... but I might just keep reading.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-tsundere.png">&lt;i&gt; (I do not know how I'm supposed to think straight right now. I might still be dressed, but I'm well... here... playing this.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-read.png">...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="tie">
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="6">
                <state img="#-startled.png">Huh. I wonder what the odds of that where.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0-8" priority="50">
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="50">I might be more comfortable with girls, but I'm glad your here, ~target~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">This is not what I mean by teasing me. Wait I---I only mean... forget it.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Forgive me for not being impressed.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-wistful.png">I'd be disappointed but I'm still happy here.</state>
                <state img="#-read2.png">Your ~clothing~? At this stage of the game? Well at least I brought books worth looking at... for reading I mean, of course.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="0-8" priority="50">
                <state img="#-skeptical.png" oneShotId="71">&lt;i&gt; (Hard to make judgments on how comfortable he'll end up yet, or how comfortable I should be.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-sarcastic.png">Well done on playing so well nobody is looking at you, even when you lose.</state>
                <state img="#-unimpressed.png">Cruelty being easy doesn't make it right you know.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-admire.png">Whatever, I feel... somewhat satiated.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Sure, why not right?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0-8" priority="50">
                <state img="#-admire.png" oneShotId="49">It's certainly easy to appreciate your beauty, even if you're not... well, losing much.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">I get it, you're really lucky, good for you.</state>
                <state img="#-unimpressed.png">Really? I've done nothing worth to being even slightly nicer to?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-stretching.png">I'm still a bit hot... but this isn't helping.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">I'd say your lucky I'm patient, but it turns out I'm a lot less patient when I've been all riled up.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10" priority="0">
                <condition count="0" role="opp" character="yang_xiao_long" />
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" oneShotId="105">&lt;i&gt; (I wonder if I could be mad at Yang playing this well in a game like this... On second thoughts, I wonder if I could think at all if Yang joined me here.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="0-8" priority="50">
                <state img="#-read2.png" oneShotId="63">&lt;i&gt; (The Ninjas Of Love author sure has a thing for girls leaving small items on. I didn't get it... until now.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9" id="19">
                <state img="#-fantasyidle.png">At least we're closer to something good. &lt;i&gt; (Not really, I'm be better off thinking of Yang or Sun. laying my head on their chest... or chests, don't want to... leave anyone out.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">&lt;i&gt; (Wow, that drives home how hard I lost. Then again, losing here and being unlucky might be different things.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">Well at least it's a kind of meanness that doesn't hurt anyone too much.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-think.png">How did you manage that?</state>
                <state img="#-sarcastic.png">You're ~clothing~? When I'm done? I guess I have to be impressed.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0-8" oneShotId="86" priority="50">
                <state img="#-amused.png" marker="yangremoved">Yang might crack a joke about removing minors here, if it hadn't happened to her more then once back then.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">This is worse! At least accessories might mean something.</state>
                <state img="#-skeptical.png">Sorry if I seem frustrated with you. &lt;i&gt; (Because I am a little frustrated with you.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-sarcastic.png">Does being good at strip poker often actually come in handy?</state>
                <state img="#-chat.png">You've taken some hits, but even so, if there is any skill in the game, you've clearly got it.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_minor">
            <case stage="0-8" priority="50">
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="77">I don't mind the men taking it a bit slower. I'm still a little on edge.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-confused.png">It'll be something good next time right?</state>
                <state img="#-stretching.png">I guess even now a brief break from anything interesting is okay.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-read2.png">I can't be the only one in my year who reads smutty stuff like this, right?</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Okay it's hitting a bit that I'm standing here naked when you take &lt;i&gt; that &lt;/i&gt; off.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0-8" priority="50">
                <state img="#-bashful.png" oneShotId="115">You're beautiful regardless, but that only made me hope for more.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-aroused.png">C'mon don't keep teasing us, please.</state>
                <state img="#-skeptical.png">Typical of my luck I guess.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-chat.png">Sure, why not ask right? Does that mean anything to you?</state>
                <state img="#-read.png">,,,</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_minor">
            <case stage="0-8" priority="50">
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="127">I'm a little surprised you're keeping my attention. You're pretty, but this is hardly new ground for either of us.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-confused.png">I can't be mad about that. &lt;i&gt; (But I'm a little mad.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-sarcastic.png">The way this is playing out doesn't feature a lot in romance novels, &lt;i&gt; I wonder why.  &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Thank you all... I didn't think I'd feel this comfortable with my ears out.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Guess I have got bigger fish to fry... I should really try to fry my own fish sometime, actually.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_major">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-tsundere.png">Not complaining about a win. &lt;i&gt;(Or the view.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-read2.png">Already? Well I wouldn't want you to be uncomfortable.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-5">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">This is a little more than what I'm used to these days... but only a little.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">I've put my book down, well done.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Don't worry. Not everyone has the time to work out, and that's fine.</state>
                <state img="#-chat.png">You can tell a lot about how active someone really is by their legs and arms.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-admire.png">It's been a while since I've been this happy about the unfamiliar.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">If someone else called me a contented cat I'd probably tell them off... but it's a pretty good description.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-admire.png">I'm still watching, but I can look away if you want.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">I'm still paying attention... I mean, yeah, it's... nevermind.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_major">
            <case stage="0-10" id="10">
                <condition role="target" character="mettaton_neo" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-startled.png">&lt;i&gt; (Can't say I'm any more attracted now.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Nothing to complain about from me.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">I'm still pleasantly surprised I'm doing so well.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-5">
                <state img="#-tsundere.png">&lt;i&gt; (I'm not about to pretend I don't like what I see, but I don't feel like commenting at this point.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-read2.png">I won't stare, I'm better than that at this point. &lt;i&gt; (Maybe just this point though.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-stretching.png">It's not much less than going to the beach and I grew up on an island. You don't need to worry about me judging.</state>
                <state img="#-admire.png">I can already tell a lot, and I like what I see.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9" id="20">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">You wouldn't want to keep me waiting too long would you?</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">You remind me of... someone. &lt;i&gt;(Of Sun, his winks do fluster me... sometimes. I'm glad he can't tell how I'm feeling, and that he doesn't notice when they do something... or maybe I'd prefer he did know...) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-tsundere.png">I am glad something is still happening. I don't want to go just yet.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Can I ask what you're taking off next? Sorry, probably shouldn't have said that.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_major">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-admire.png">&lt;i&gt; (I could have helped her, but she's not in any real danger... and I do want to see this.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">It's certainly nice to see... nobody being judged for playing.</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">If only it was always so simple to get the upper hand.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-5">
                <state img="#-chat.png">I don't think this is unfair at least.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">I've read plenty of novels with this to, not that it compares.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-read2.png">I'm not too invested don't worry, I'm just... reading... yeah. &lt;i&gt; (Why am I a disaster?) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I'm not a natural flirt like Yang, but I need to say something... About someone as pretty as you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-admire.png">You're already looking good... &lt;i&gt; (You'd just look even better pulling my leash.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">You look great... &lt;i&gt; (So what do you look like under that ~clothing~?) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">I'm not even covering up much here, and I'm normally shy compared to my friends. </state>
                <state img="#-admire.png">I can't complain about that. There is already a lot to admire.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_major">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-read2.png">Well, your luck can't get worse from here at least. &lt;i&gt; (Wait, nevermind It definitely can) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">As your opponent of course I'm glad to be doing better than you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-5">
                <state img="#-tsundere.png">At this rate I may not even pick the book up again, very nice.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Girls are... girls... good. &lt;i&gt; (And I just proved why I should probably just not talk.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-admire.png">&lt;i&gt; (Now's probably the best time to say something. I'm not sure if I'll be able to think if she strips much more.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">I'm not used to just letting my emotions go, but it's hard not to here.</state>
                <state img="#-read2.png">'Beauty is in the eye of the beholder, but lust is somewhere a bit lower'. Sorry, it's one of my favorite bits of poetry from Lady Amarynth Briggs.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-admire.png">Yeah, you look great, of course you do like that...</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">&lt;i&gt; (I've been, waiting... please don't tease me any longer) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">It's nice to see you trying to match me... no need to stop there though.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-read2.png">&lt;i&gt; (Hmm, this was maybe not the romance book to read if I wanted to cool down.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">It's a unique beauty. I don't think it's about any part of you, ~target~, but how every part comes together.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="5-8">
                <state img="#-happy.png">I wasn't sure if I'd look forward to this, but it feels... safe.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">Don't worry I'm used to seeing this, and I'm not going to judge you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-tsundere.png">I grew up with this. Don't expect me to start purring for you. Don't expect me to start purring for you anyway, actually. </state>
                <state img="#-sarcastic.png">Think you can handle showing off your chest for me?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-read.png">I'm not disinterested, but it's not like I'll miss the one moment I can see it. </state>
                <state img="#-stretching.png">I might even be willing to play this game with my male friends after this, not that I'd want to necessarily.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-amused.png">Already? No, don't let me stop you.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I think everyone finds victory satisfying.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-10" id="6">
                <condition role="target" character="9s" />
                <state img="#-tsundere.png">I wonder why they gave you the other function but not that... I mean assuming you have... nevermind.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-think.png">&lt;i&gt; (Should I be having a stronger reaction? It's nice sure, but it is just the chest) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">&lt;i&gt; (It doesn't look bad, and muscles are always really good on guys, but without those... it just feels like a woman's chest but flatter.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I wasn't just pretending to be indifferent about the idea before now... but I'm definitely less indifferent now.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">I do want to rest my head on you more than I thought I would, ~target~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-happy.png">I could rest my head on you happily. &lt;i&gt; (It'd be up to you if I'm drenched in sweat and arousal first.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-admire.png">It does look very... &lt;i&gt; (Like I badly want to run my hands over it.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Impressed is the wrong word, but I'm certainly happy.</state>
                <state img="#-read2.png">&lt;i&gt; (That was the right page to flip to. Feels even more easy to picture that now.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-10" id="12">
                <condition role="target" character="tick" />
                <state img="#-sarcastic.png">No stranger than your other removals, really.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-admire.png">I respect it if you're willing to do this while I'm dressed. </state>
                <state img="#-startled.png">This already? Don't get me wrong I'm happy just, give me a second.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <state img="#-admire.png">I know what you're about to do... but in some ways, this is better.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">&lt;i&gt; (Do I try and pretend like this isn't turning me on? No point, I'm already blushing anyway.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-fantasyidle.png">Any of you could send me into a proper fucking heat at this point, &lt;i&gt;please. &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">We're about to... well, don't wait for me. I'm sorry that barely made sense, I'm... horny.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">&lt;i&gt; (Would I prefer if I couldn't fit it in my mouth, or if I could?) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-read2.png">If it helps, I can avoid staring at this point.</state>
                <state img="#-stretching.png">Gotta get a warm up in... before I... umm... climb next.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_small_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-amused.png">It's hardly a new saying, but it is more about how you use it, you can trust me on that.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Size is the last thing I look for in a guy, if I look for it at all.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">&lt;i&gt; (Masturbating or not I'm not about to ask if he knows how to use it... but it's tempting.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">All that's in my head right now is half baked compliments, so I'm just going to shut up and enjoy.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-amused.png">Adam did not appreciate me giggling the first time I saw his, but they are kind of funny.</state>
                <state img="#-admire.png">It suits you, and I don't mean that as an insult. You look good.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_medium_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-chat.png">It'll take more than that to send me into heat. &lt;i&gt; (At least a little more, anyway.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">You look... good, &lt;i&gt; (More than just good, much more.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-amused.png">A bit bigger than I'm used to, but that's for the best.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I hope you know how important fingers are, and touch...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">That's a nice size... I am not saying more on that.</state>
                <state img="#-tsundere.png" marker="jokenote">So... &lt;i&gt; (Really, you were about to ask if they where busy later? Do you want them to say yes? That's such a cheesy line.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_large_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-amused.png">It looks even stranger at that size, I won't lie to you.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">It's more impressive than it is attractive... Not that I'm not already aroused.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">I wonder if I could even fit that... Oh wow masturbating or not I didn't plan on saying that out loud today.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">&lt;i&gt; (Would fitting that be painful... or would the need to take it slow be even more fun?) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">That's impressive, but it's not tempting me to a round two... &lt;i&gt; (Maybe you could though.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Huh, that's certainly something.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="7-10" oneShotId="89">
                <condition count="-1" status="not_chest_visible" role="opp" />
                <state img="#-aroused.png">It's always comforting to be in the same situation as everyone else, especially here.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" oneShotId="90">
                <condition count="4" status="chest_visible" role="opp" />
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">I'm almost tempted to take my top off just to make it fair.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" oneShotId="163">I'm sure you'll look... good.</state>
                <state img="#-admire.png" oneShotId="164">&lt;i&gt; (There sure are perks to playing well after all.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-tsundere.png" oneShotId="165">Really it's frustrating this matters so much more than a man showing their chest... but I do want to see it more.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-admire.png" oneShotId="145">This was less common back home so it still... excites me a bit.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="146">You've got nothing to be shy about if even I'm feeling this brave.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png" oneShotId="147">Read plenty of books where this is an important point. I don't think I could get tired of it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-aroused.png" oneShotId="151">They'll still be beautiful to me regardless of the size.</state>
                <state img="#-read2.png" oneShotId="152">I do like having my ears pet... I just don't admit it often... if that helps with your reveal.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png" oneShotId="153">I'll let you... rest on my chest if I can rest on yours?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <state img="#-admire.png" oneShotId="157">Nobody comes to a game like this just to judge. </state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" oneShotId="158">We've got nothing to worry about, we're just you know...  &lt;i&gt; (Playing strip poker with strangers?)  &lt;/i&gt;Having fun?</state>
                <state img="#-stretching.png" oneShotId="159">Don't worry too much. We're all in this together by now.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_small_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-tsundere.png">If I can keep this up I could win... &lt;i&gt; (Are you really pretending you're not enjoying this right now? Maybe.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-read2.png">Of course you look good. Don't worry, I'm not that invested.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <state img="#-chat.png">I wouldn't worry about those. I know plenty of small breasted girls who are still pretty.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">You're already so... good. &lt;i&gt; (And exposed, which is what I was going to say.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-aroused.png">&lt;i&gt; (I could fit all of that in my hand, or most of it in my mouth.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I'd have to be careful about leaving marks on those without marking most of the breast... unless you'd prefer that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-admire.png">There's a lot of reason to think small breasts are the most beautiful.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">You're making me think about a round two as much as anyone else would... &lt;i&gt; (Except maybe Yang when she relaxes in our dorm in just a towel after a shower like it's no big deal.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_medium_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">This is flustering me a little more than I expected. &lt;i&gt; (Not that I didn't expect to be a blushing mess, but I could hope.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I'm a mess right now, but what else is new.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I'm not going into heat or anything... but I am excited, you look great.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">They're perfect... &lt;i&gt; (I'd prefer you wrap rope around mine, but I'd try with yours too.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">You look stunning. I'm not sure if I could look away, or stay quiet.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">...Sorry if you expected me to be able to think at this point.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-aroused.png">We shower separately at Beacon which is for the best... &lt;i&gt; (You make me wonder if it really is though... if Yang could...) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-admire.png">You'll have to forgive me for staring, but I can hardly look away.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_large_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="9" id="21">
                <condition count="0" role="opp" character="yang_xiao_long" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">I don't normally prefer them that big, but you remind me of Yang... and that's a good thing.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Yes! That I'm winning... not that your boobs are out, or their size... But they are really nice!</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">I'll bet you don't have much to worry about with those... &lt;i&gt; (Except back pain, and probably boys, so actually you have a fair bit to worry about, nevermind.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <state img="#-aroused.png">I've caught more than you might think back at Beacon. Yang does not have a lot of shame.</state>
                <state img="#-admire.png">&lt;i&gt; (I wonder if I'd rather go without tuna or breasts. Nevermind, having to pick would be too cruel.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">There are some people I wouldn't show my ears even if they undressed as much as you did.</state>
                <state img="#-admire.png">I'm sorry for the staring you must get. I've been stared at too for different things, but it's so much nicer choosing it, huh?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-confused.png">You could just smother someone with those, huh? Not that I want that... but, you could.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">&lt;i&gt; (Lots of space to bury my face, or my teeth.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-tsundere.png" oneShotId="14">Only one of us won't do this. You're not alone.</state>
                <state img="#-read2.png" oneShotId="15">I'm doing better than expected, good. </state>
                <state img="#-think.png" oneShotId="16">I get that I play it cool but, I'm glad you joined us, and you can leave if you need to.</state>
                <state img="#-admire.png" oneShotId="17">I might be the huntress but you're brave and I admire that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <state img="#-bashful.png" oneShotId="22">When I said I was glad to be playing with girls. I didn't mean just for the company.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png" oneShotId="23">I've been... looking forward to this a bit.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" oneShotId="21">I'm not going to say this matters less than my ears, but I've been quite vulnerable, and I'm glad you can do the same.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png" oneShotId="25">&lt;i&gt; (This is the time to break out of your shell a bit if ever there was one.) &lt;/i&gt; I think you're already quite beautiful, ~target~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-sarcastic.png" oneShotId="10" marker="badpun">This is... what I came here for... Or what I'm willing to come here for.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-bashful.png" oneShotId="18">I might still have another round in me... are you interested in that idea?</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" oneShotId="19">I've put my book down ahead of time, you really are pretty.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="20">Don't worry. Like most things with good people it's scarier at first than it never needs to be.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-worried.png" oneShotId="27">You look... delicious... I mean, beautiful! &lt;i&gt; (I made that worse, huh) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-chat.png" oneShotId="28">Don't worry yourself too much. Even I've stuck around despite losing.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png" oneShotId="29">Not gonna lie and pretend even the anticipation isn't getting me all hot.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png" oneShotId="37">First time I've ever done more then read about this game, and it's better than any book.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="9">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="badpun" />
                <state img="#-fantasyidle.png">&lt;i&gt; (I can't believe I said that. Yang must be rubbing off on me... Wait.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-admire.png" oneShotId="45">It'll take more than that to send me into heat. &lt;i&gt; (At least a little bit more, anyway.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="46">Uhhh... your very pretty, and I'm, very bisexual and I'm uh... just mean, it, you know... shutting up now. </state>
                <state img="#-tsundere.png" oneShotId="47">I came here for this... but I never expected such a good thing to come so easily.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">&lt;i&gt; (That sure is her naked and I'm... totally out of words right now) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <state img="#-admire.png" oneShotId="33">You're... beautiful, but I'm sure you know that.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png" oneShotId="34">I haven't seen much like this before, and it's better than I imagined. &lt;i&gt; (Or read about.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-tsundere.png" oneShotId="35">If throwing a few hands would make you more comfortable I'll... consider it.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png" oneShotId="36">It would be difficult to imagine anything as beautiful as you look like that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Fuck, you look good... you, you could...&lt;i&gt; (Do what you wanted with me) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" oneShotId="31">I didn't, show myself off just to go home alone... did I?</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="32">Ummmmmmmmm... yes, very hot, thank you. &lt;i&gt;(Blake what the fuck was that?) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png" oneShotId="30">I didn't mean to slip into a heat like this but you make it &lt;i&gt; so easy to. &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-aroused.png" oneShotId="39">... If you couldn't tell I didn't finish and stop being horny, damn.</state>
                <state img="#-admire.png" oneShotId="40">You look amazing. Nothing I could read matches this.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png" oneShotId="42">I'm very glad you're willing to commit to this game for your sake... and mine.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="43">Normally I'd probably settle for stunned silence, but in this case... I guess I'll talk a bit while my brain stops working.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_lost">
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="118" priority="500">
                <condition role="target" character="yang_xiao_long" />
                <condition count="0" role="opp" character="weiss_schnee" />
                <condition count="0" role="opp" character="ruby" />
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" marker="YangCrush">This really is happening. Sorry I must sound stupid I just never expected this to ever really happen... Never thought about this happening between us at all, I mean.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="29">
                <condition role="target" character="dawn" sayingMarker="DawnIsGone" />
                <condition role="opp" character="cynthia" />
                <state img="#-tsundere.png" marker="blake_dawngone_cynthcomfort">I know that if I wanted a moment like that... I wouldn't want anyone to bother me. She'll come back, Cynthia. I would for well... nevermind.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="31">
                <condition role="opp" character="yang_xiao_long" />
                <condition role="target" character="lux" sayingMarker="Light_Pun_Trigger" />
                <state img="#-amused.png">You two are incurable... &lt;i&gt; It is cute though. &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="96">
                <condition role="target" character="ignatz" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-skeptical.png" marker="blake_ignatz_fight">I understand how it feels to be forced to fight, but at least I do it for a good cause these days. You seem even less keen on it than me though.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="102">
                <condition role="target" character="heris" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-think.png" marker="blake_heris_leader">What's it like leading an institution so young? Do you get called on in a leadership role much?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="114">
                <condition role="target" character="meia" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-chat.png" marker="Meia_blake_stoic">You seem very comfortable in yourself, Meia. Do you struggle with a desire to be more open at times or are you happy as you are? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="116">
                <condition role="target" character="ahri" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="ahri_recluse">I'll admit, it's hard to imagine you as any kind of recluse, Ahri.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="117">
                <condition role="target" character="ahri" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-worried.png">Do you find yourself reflecting on your past often? I know it can be hard to avoid mine sometimes.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" id="75" oneShotId="119">
                <condition role="target" character="meia" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-chat.png" marker="blake_meia_men">You seem quite interested in men. I could answer some questions, even if I'm not willing to answer all of them just yet.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" id="78" oneShotId="129">
                <condition role="target" character="leon" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-sarcastic.png" marker="blake_leon_boyscout">Is it my turn to prove to you I'm not blind either? I see a fit boyscout hero, cute too, maybe too caring for his own good. Even if you attempt play the tough guy sometimes.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="95">
                <condition status="lost_some" role="target" character="ignatz" />
                <state img="#-wistful.png" marker="blake_ignatz_artistry">I do appreciate beauty and art. I just don't get a lot of time to focus on it. I'm impressed you put so much effort into making time for it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="130">
                <condition status="not_lost_some" role="target" character="leon" />
                <state img="#-chat.png" marker="blake_leon_fighter">You're certainly capable in a fight. The question is who is that bad news for?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="15">
                <condition role="target" character="dawn" sayingMarker="DawnsBack" />
                <state img="#-wistful.png">&lt;i&gt; (That's sweet... it's a surprise I got to be here for it. I wonder if I could do that...)  &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="30">
                <condition role="target" character="lux" sayingMarker="Light_Pun_Trigger" />
                <state img="#-sarcastic.png">Just when I thought I'd gotten away from Yang's jokes for a bit.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" id="69" oneShotId="101">
                <condition role="target" character="ganyu" />
                <state img="#-chat.png" marker="blake_ganyu_faunus">I respect your willingness to be openly Faunus, even if we're from different worlds. What's it like for you where you come from?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" id="70" oneShotId="103">
                <condition role="target" character="jura" />
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" marker="blake_jura_trainwreck">Hey I'm Blake... I said that already, uumm.. I meant...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="120">
                <condition role="target" character="mari_setogaya" />
                <state img="#-amused.png">Is there a particular reason you seem to be practically bouncing off the walls? It's endearing, but a little strange.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_stripping">
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="12">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="donpatch">... What the fuck is happening?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="18">
                <condition role="target" character="adora" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-startled.png">You must be quite powerful. I don't think I've ever seen a form changing Semblance that just makes you stronger.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="20">
                <condition role="target" character="sly_cooper" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">I hope you didn't expect me to be impressed. This early it feels more like your flashing us.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="28">
                <condition role="target" character="emi" stage="7" />
                <state img="#-chat.png">I'm not sure if that'll win you the game, but that's the kind of thinking that can keep you safe. Our team leader, Ruby is good at it to.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="33">
                <condition role="target" character="brock" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-angry.png">Shit keep your heads down everyone. You better not do that often, Brock.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="34">
                <condition role="target" character="brock" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-admire.png">Gotta admit, Pyrrha, I've always been impressed by your skill and control.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="43">
                <condition role="target" character="sakura" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-wistful.png" marker="blake_zombieresp">I'm not going to shame you, you're clearly just like us. We all have things we'd... rather hide.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="45">
                <condition role="target" character="adrien" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-amused.png">I can't help but wonder if this is karma for running around with those ears.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="47">
                <condition role="target" character="brock" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-startled.png">Fuck! That is always the risk with weapons. We should get the body away before it stinks up this place, I take it we aren't going to keep playing? It's a shame, but nobodies fault but his.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="53">
                <condition role="target" character="chihiro" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-startled.png" marker="blake_chirunresp">... You can just stop playing if you're that uncomfortable, you know.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="99">
                <condition role="target" character="miki_miura" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-wistful.png" marker="blake_miki_hand">I admire how clear and open you are about it. It really doesn't trouble you still at times?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="100">
                <condition status="not_lost_some" role="target" character="aqua_grunt" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="blake_aq_fish">Team Aqua seems like an odd name for fishers, but I can't complain too much given how much I love fish.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4" oneShotId="9">
                <condition role="target" character="mari_setogaya" sayingMarker="Cat_transformation" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="catreact_safe">It's brave of you to willingly transform. I'm glad you're safe to do so here.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <condition role="target" character="mari_setogaya" sayingMarker="Cat_transformation" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="catreact_kin">It's nice to have company... more so when you didn't have to.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="14">
                <condition role="target" character="wikipe-tan" sayingMarker="TransformationStart" />
                <state img="#-think.png" marker="wikitrans_semblance">Impressive. Though I hope for your sake your Semblance does more than that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="22">
                <condition role="target" character="kora" sayingMarker="blade_power" />
                <state img="#-think.png">That's quite a useful Semblance. You chose not to blind us I take it?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="41">
                <condition role="target" character="yuelia" sayingMarker="transformation" />
                <state img="#-chat.png" marker="yuelia_transform">That must come in handy. I was wondering if you'd be able to go any rounds before transforming.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="46">
                <condition role="target" character="sakura" sayingMarker="headless" />
                <state img="#-startled.png" marker="blake_headlessresp">... You're still okay aren't you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="51">
                <condition role="target" character="dust" sayingMarker="persist_ChazzAss" />
                <state img="#-amused.png">Haha, gotta make your point somehow right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="52">
                <condition role="target" character="perona" sayingMarker="nami_negative2" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">&lt;i&gt; (I am not getting involved in this, especially unarmed.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="55">
                <condition role="target" character="shantae" sayingMarker="monkey" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">...I'm gonna go ahead and assume that wasn't intentional.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10">
                <condition role="target" character="heris" saidMarker="HerisBlakeLeadership" />
                <state img="#-chat.png">I suppose a scientific role would be more managerial then personal? It's the personal leadership that affects an environment most, for better or worse, in my experience.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10">
                <condition role="target" character="aimee" />
                <state img="#-angry.png">You're an idiot! Hurt anyone else and I'm breaking that.</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">That's... breathtakingly stupid, you don't even have aura do you?</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">Ignorance doesn't make you less of a threat, and it's never stopped me protecting people before. So you better be damn good.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="19">
                <condition role="target" character="chihiro" />
                <state img="#-stretching.png">That's not a big deal. I don't see why it would be for the others either.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" id="74" oneShotId="113">
                <condition role="target" character="monika" />
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Books! It seems like we both read, what do you prefer? &lt;i&gt; (I hope she didn't notice me stare.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4" id="66" oneShotId="87">
                <condition filter="blonde" role="target" />
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" marker="blondepanic">I love your hair, ~target~... it's very... blonde. &lt;i&gt; (Why did I open my big damn mouth?) &lt;/i&gt; </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="112">
                <condition status="not_lost_some" role="opp" character="yuri" />
                <state img="#-think.png" marker="blake_">Do you do a lot of that in school, or is it a personal passion?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="26">
                <condition role="opp" character="polly" sayingMarker="Polly Fades Out" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">I can't be mad at you, but it's hardly fair.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2" id="3">
                <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="minor" />
                <state img="#-read.png">I'm listening to you, but there doesn't seem to be a lot to look at. </state>
                <state img="#-think.png">I'm not saying anyone has to be exciting. I just don't have much else to say.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I guess I could see someone being happy about this turn of events, but I need a little more than that.</state>
                <state img="#-skeptical.png">To be expected, but you shouldn't expect much from me in return.</state>
                <state img="#-read2.png">It's not that you're boring or anything, ~target~. Just that this book... definitely isn't.</state>
                <state img="#-skeptical.png">Do you think it's important to have a plan before you arrive? I do, but I don't think I needed it.</state>
                <state img="#-chat.png">It's been a while since I've hung out with any civilians before Beacon or during.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-5" id="46">
                <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="minor" />
                <state img="#-skeptical.png" marker="scarfsetup">Where I come from most people's necklaces or rings matter to them, and yet I've never met someone with a story about their socks or anything like that.</state>
                <state img="#-read.png">It's okay if you take a while. I brought books.</state>
                <state img="#-sarcastic.png">Do I have a right to be proud of that win? I didn't select my cards as part of a master plan.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">I guess I shouldn't expect to lead when I didn't practice.</state>
                <state img="#-read.png">It's a mundane exchange for a game this exciting, but it needs doing.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8" id="47">
                <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="minor" />
                <state img="#-read.png">I do appreciate the escape that books offer. Even before I had much to escape from.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Weiss  asked why I never learned to cook fish if I like them so much, so I've tried. It went okay, I just need to check the fire extinguisher works before I try again.</state>
                <state img="#-read.png">Ruby gave it this book me when we last swapped, but it was one I loved when I was younger. It's nice to see it again. </state>
                <state img="#-chat.png">Guess I can't get too frustrated with you when you've been so accepting, do you play a lot of cards?</state>
                <state img="#-read2.png">If you're not going to help me get ready for my forfeit then I will. I mean... assuming I lose of course.</state>
                <state img="#-read2.png">...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9" id="43">
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~clothing.generic~" value="scarf" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~clothing.generic~" value="tie" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~clothing.generic~" value="ribbon" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">You could put that ~clothing~ on me if you wanted. &lt;i&gt; (On my neck, and then pull me in.)  &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2" id="42">
                <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="extra" />
                <state img="#-admire.png">&lt;i&gt;(Stopping and wondering about how I ended up at Beacon is one thing, but this is a whole other level.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-read.png">&lt;i&gt; (Should I care about this strip? From this stranger? Probably not.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">Does that matter to you? &lt;i&gt; (Why wear it otherwise, right?) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-read.png">I'm not expecting you to be interesting yet. Just don't expect me to be interested yet. </state>
                <state img="#-chat.png">As difficult as they are at times, I'll give my friends this: they're never boring.</state>
                <state img="#-read.png">...</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">Maybe I should get a drink after all. &lt;i&gt; (Even with dulled reflexes I could probably avoid ~target~.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-5" id="45">
                <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="extra" />
                <state img="#-tsundere.png">You're playing better than me. I'm not going to get upset about that.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I suppose I shouldn't care. No lives on the line.</state>
                <state img="#-stretching.png">I might have wandered off by now, but I do want to see this game through.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Saying I read books where this happens doesn't mean much yet huh... Wait shit I don't mean &lt;i&gt; that. &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-admire.png">Everything needs to build up momentum, but I can hope it doesn't take you too long.</state>
                <state img="#-tsundere.png">It's strange being a final year at Beacon. I used to look up to them not that long ago.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8" id="44">
                <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="extra" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">The intent of the game isn't to strip meaningless things, you know that right?</state>
                <state img="#-wistful.png">You're far from the only tease I know, but it's no less frustrating.</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">I'd ask you to teach me how to play that well... but I'm not sure if I have the time to learn.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">This is fair, but it hardly seems right.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Why is it always the teasing people who get on my nerves?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_stripped">
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="42">
                <condition role="target" character="misato" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-worried.png">The scar is nothing to be ashamed of. Everyone who stands up for something gets them one way or another.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="48">
                <condition role="target" character="brock" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-startled.png" marker="blake_brocklives">You lived!? I thought you didn't have aura? I mean I'm glad your alive, of course.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="56">
                <condition role="target" character="gwen" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-tsundere.png">I don't think you have anything to be worried about at a place like this.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="73">
                <condition role="target" character="gwen" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-admire.png" oneShotId="48" marker="blakemaskresp">I admire your willingness to show your face then. I'm not always so good with being open.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="13">
                <condition status="naked" role="target" character="aimee" />
                <state img="#-unimpressed.png">Just when I thought you were done being concerning.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9-10">
                <condition role="target" character="mari_setogaya" sayingMarker="Cat_transformed" />
                <state img="#-bashful.png" marker="catreact_horny">Damn... What? We all like seeing ourselves in others... right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10">
                <condition role="target" character="ignatz" sayingMarker="glassesstart" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="blake_classesresp">Stay calm, you're not in any danger, Ignatz.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="17">
                <condition role="target" character="samus_aran" sayingMarker="Removing_armor" />
                <state img="#-think.png" marker="blake_armourresp">I'd be surprised if any of our mech pilots could do something like that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="24">
                <condition role="target" character="amy" sayingMarker="planar_form" />
                <state img="#-startled.png">... What the fuck is happening?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="32">
                <condition role="target" character="mari_setogaya" sayingMarker="Chubby_transformed" />
                <state img="#-think.png" marker="blake_marichubby">That's impressive. You're not more uncomfortable now?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <condition role="target" character="mari_setogaya" sayingMarker="Mari_wings_reveal" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="blake_wingsresp1">I'm glad you're comfortable with your wings. I'll make sure nobody touches them.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-10" oneShotId="39">
                <condition role="target" character="mari_setogaya" sayingMarker="Mari_wings_reveal" />
                <state img="#-tsundere.png" marker="blake_wingsresp2">Thank you, Mari. It makes me feel a little more at home here, and I understand how sensitive they must be.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="40">
                <condition role="target" character="ms.fortune" sayingMarker="Fortune_Strip_2C" />
                <state img="#-startled.png" marker="blake_headresp">Wow. I've seen a lot and I've never seen anything like that. You're really alright?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="44">
                <condition role="target" character="wikipe-tan" sayingMarker="TransformationFinish" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="blake_transresp">But why does that give you the power to do this? I've never head of a Semblance that only works on certain dates.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="27">
                <condition role="target" character="polly" sayingMarker="Polly Fades In" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" marker="blake_polly_fadeannoy">How nerdy we are or are not has nothing to do with how annoying that was.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="10">
                <condition role="target" character="arash" />
                <state img="#-aroused.png" marker="blake_throwresp">Is that in the spirit of the game? &lt;i&gt; (Please ignore me.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8" id="55">
                <condition count="0" role="opp" character="ruby" />
                <condition status="not_exposed" role="target" />
                <state img="#-sarcastic.png" oneShotId="60">I was right about not needing to bring my Shroud, and I'm sure Ruby will take care of it. She'd probably sooner drop a child than a weapon... for better or worse.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8" id="56">
                <condition role="opp" character="ruby" />
                <condition status="not_exposed" role="target" />
                <state img="#-stretching.png" oneShotId="58">Juane may be a little clumsy, but I'm sure he'll take care of my gear until I get back... I think I can trust him with it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="21">
                <condition role="opp" character="twisted_fate" sayingMarker="Bobobo_Broken" />
                <state img="#-unimpressed.png">That's hardly good sportsmanship.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2" id="54">
                <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="extra" />
                <state img="#-skeptical.png">&lt;i&gt; (That's unimpressive, not unexpected, just unimpressive.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-read.png">&lt;i&gt; (Probably for the best no one cares too much about such a simple thing.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Eye for an eye. Can't say I expected better.</state>
                <state img="#-read.png">Your ~clothing~? Sure can't complain. </state>
                <state img="#-think.png">It's been a long time since I walked in somewhere new and felt comfortable. That's not your fault.</state>
                <state img="#-read.png">I've been allowed to bring the book in, so clearly some boring moments are part and parcel here.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-5" id="53">
                <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="extra" />
                <state img="#-read.png">We're closer to interesting with you, but this book already is.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Right now I do kind of want to wander off, but I think I'll see this through.</state>
                <state img="#-skeptical.png">&lt;i&gt; (Well, it won't get more boring, Even if it could, it'd be a break from what I'm used to dealing with.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">Is that luck or skill? Sometimes I wonder if there is even a difference.</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">I wonder if it's fair to impose my expectations. I'm hardly used to this.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8" id="57">
                <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="extra" />
                <state img="#-read.png">Oh, ~target~ lost? Cool. </state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Are there really people who don't find this frustrating?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Most people at Beacon are so attached to their plans, dinner at 6, dancing at 8 or whatever. I appreciate that Ruby, and especially Yang, have gotten more used to the way I prefer to just wander around.</state>
                <state img="#-unimpressed.png">That's all?</state>
                <state img="#-stretching.png">I didn't think I'd have to worry about drowsiness at a game like this, but I am often late to bed.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2" id="49">
                <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="minor" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">I can escape from danger without my weapons. So I'm not worried here. </state>
                <state img="#-sarcastic.png">Sure, I don't know if I'd cope if my life was all excitement.</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">...</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">It can be hard to gauge how far along the game is. I prefer to know as much as I can about what I'm getting into.</state>
                <state img="#-read.png">Reading can be useful at times. Makes me look like I'm comfortable, but I can still keep my eyes on the room.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-5" id="50">
                <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="minor" />
                <state img="#-worried.png">&lt;i&gt; (I wonder what it's like, to come from a world where monsters aren't constantly on your doorstep, Grimm and otherwise.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">On our way to something better... not a I phrase normally think playing poker. </state>
                <state img="#-skeptical.png">&lt;i&gt; (Maybe I'm not giving the tactics of the game enough respect.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-sarcastic.png">At least I'm not in danger of losing because I'm distracted.</state>
                <state img="#-stretching.png">It's always dangerous to close your eyes in a new environment, but I can't remain that paranoid all game.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8" id="51">
                <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="minor" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">I wouldn't have imagined myself comfortable enough for this even when I arrived at Beacon. I'm very happy to have my team, no... my friends.</state>
                <state img="#-read.png">You might be doing something wrong. Because I'm significantly more interesting than you right now. </state>
                <state img="#-tsundere.png">I'm not saying anyone should play to lose... but it's about time you got rid of that.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">...Brilliant.</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">In any case, this place is still shelter from my troubles that I don't have to fight for.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-5" id="52" priority="10">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="scarfsetup" />
                <state img="#-think.png">&lt;i&gt;(Though, Pyrrha does love that scarf of hers...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="8-10" oneShotId="62" priority="5">
                <condition count="3" status="crotch_visible" role="opp" />
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Does seem fair we all end up naked if someone has to. &lt;i&gt;(Even if it wasn't, I doubt I'd find it in me to complain at this point.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="63">
                <condition count="4" status="crotch_visible" role="opp" />
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Holy shit, all of you before me? Well, I've learned how not to doubt a good thing at this point, at least.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="11">
                <condition role="target" character="nami" />
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">I've always preferred baths, but I'm sure plenty of people who shower do that... &lt;i&gt;(Including me.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="37">
                <condition role="target" character="bernadetta" />
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I don't see why that'd be a problem. &lt;i&gt; (And it is cute too.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="50">
                <condition role="target" character="jolyne" />
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Damn... if this is going where it seems to be... &lt;i&gt; (I should ask to join her, no, don't do that.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="54">
                <condition role="target" character="nico_robin" />
                <state img="#-skeptical.png">Wait, did you just create something without using dust?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-10">
                <condition role="opp" character="wasp" saidMarker="shrinking" />
                <state img="#-think.png" marker="blake_waspresp">Are you trading defense for hitting power when you do that?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <condition role="self" timeInStage="10" />
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" oneShotId="222">At a certain point this feels a little weirder again.</state>
                <state img="#-admire.png" oneShotId="223">&lt;i&gt; (I never thought I'd start to adjust to a sight so alluring.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-read2.png" oneShotId="224">I'd feel better if I stopped staring for at least a moment.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-admire.png">Can't say I have any regrets from today... or that I won't come back.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">Guess this really is a good way to bond with strangers, huh?</state>
                <state img="#-stretching.png">I'm not comfortable like it's my dorm, but I am happy.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Not such a bad forfeit, huh?</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">That still looks... really good. &lt;i&gt; (Am I still set on not taking anyone home?... Maybe.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Don't worry too much. We're in this together by now.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">...</state>
                <state img="#-admire.png">It's always nice to know what you want isn't it, ~target~?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="49">
                <condition role="target" character="twisted_fate" sayingMarker="Hat_Cheat" />
                <state img="#-angry.png">Fate you motherfucker!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="104">
                <condition role="target" character="pyrrha" sayingMarker="phones" />
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Oh right, your Semblance... I'm sure it's fine.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="91">
                <condition count="3" status="finished" role="opp" />
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Today has been beyond any fantasy I've had so far.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-admire.png">I was prepared to lose, you should have been too.</state>
                <state img="#-read2.png">You're really going to.... yup. I'm not complaining... at all it's just... nevermind... have fun?</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">You can still back out now... &lt;i&gt; (But please don't.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9-10">
                <state img="#-aroused.png">It's not so bad... being watched.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Probably as close as I want to get, &lt;i&gt; today. &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Don't mind me. it's nice to &lt;i&gt; want &lt;/i&gt; this again.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-admire.png">Not something I expected. I know what I signed up for, but it still... seeing it for myself...</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">It's brave to stick around for the full game. I admire that.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">&lt;i&gt; (It's fine that I'm staring right? Surely it'd hurt him more if I wasn't.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-wistful.png">&lt;i&gt; (A couple of people I'd want to see do this more than them... but only a couple.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Doesn't feature quite as much in my... novels, but now I wish it did.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-read2.png">I wonder if I'm just reading the wrong kind of novel, given I don't see this a  lot.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Is there a point to pretending I wasn't hoping for this? You heard me when I was, well...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">&lt;i&gt; (The motion is so... repetitive. Then again I look like that when I'm really in heat and just need to finish.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">&lt;i&gt;(I think I could still do a pretty good job with my hand wrapped around him.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">It's much easier for men to be... strong with me, but if you're not able to, I could do it for you?</state>
                <state img="#-wistful.png">It's good to be here. It's good to know what I want, and that my needs have nothing to do with... my past, one way or the other.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">If you're so willing to attend a place like this maybe I should have another look at... another man in my life. &lt;i&gt; (At the very least, I doubt Sun would take offense to me... asking.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Is finishing the best part for you? I prefer the stimulation, the touch on breasts, on my clit, on my ears, slowly pulling me in.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Not something I pictured myself doing next to a man like this... </state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">I do still crave how... raw and physical it was sometimes.</state>
                <state img="#-read2.png">&lt;i&gt; (Always nice to have a new reference for how the gay scenes look.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">I haven't heard or seen much of this... though in retrospect... that one time at the showers...</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">If you tell me what you're thinking I might do the same.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">It's been a long time... I mean... since I've been this aroused after finishing.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-tsundere.png">&lt;i&gt;(Okay. Slightly off putting given the clothing difference. I won't say that though. Don't want, ~target~ to stop.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_heavy_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-10">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Preferably not on my outfit...actually nevermind that.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">That's beautiful actually, and arousing, of course.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-10" id="9">
                <condition role="target" character="tick" />
                <state img="#-startled.png">Shit. I hope no one looked at it. What was that?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" priority="1">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I am a little sorry I didn't help more... maybe next time? &lt;i&gt; (Blake what are you doing.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">That's... that's uhh... that is. You're... pretty damn hot.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">&lt;i&gt; (Hopefully you take my staring like an idiot as a compliment, because fuck watching your face as you finish is hot.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-wistful.png">Fuck you look great... &lt;i&gt; (I almost want to ask you to come over here to do that. It's a bit late now though, and it'd be a lot if he said yes.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-tsundere.png">I wish you could... &lt;i&gt; (Take me, I wish I was sure enough to ask and not be overwhelmed) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-admire.png">I wouldn't call this pretty or beautiful... but it is picturesque.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">I'm actually more tempted to... offer to help, then when I was going at it.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0-10" id="8">
                <condition role="target" character="nami" />
                <state img="#-skeptical.png">You're not going to make it rain on the rest of us right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-bashful.png" oneShotId="180">Not exactly what I planned, sorry.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" oneShotId="181">Always at least one loser in a contest. I'm just glad this is the only stakes.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" oneShotId="182">Well, we were all playing to win, so it was gonna be someone's loss.</state>
                <state img="#-read2.png" oneShotId="183">Do what you need to. I can avoid staring... &lt;i&gt; (I'm not sure how long I can keep this up, but I can try.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <state img="#-aroused.png">If it helps, I am less worried about my forfeit now I get to... join you.</state>
                <state img="#-chat.png">It's remarkable how little anyone cares I'm a Faunus here. I didn't expect to be this relaxed. You've got nothing to worry about.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">If it makes you feel any better, one time I... &lt;i&gt; (Got my hair caught on a branch and got all hot cause I thought Yang was pulling it... Actually no, I'm not sharing that.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-confused.png">Yes! I mean... I'm glad it was you. &lt;i&gt; (Is that any better though?) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-chat.png">It's been cleaned recently, and thoroughly. I can still smell a hint of the cleaner.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-admire.png">Trust me, it's a good release after being pent up watching all this. &lt;i&gt; (Or pent up because I don't relax enough at Beacon.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Forgive me if I'm not riddled with guilt. I am happy to help anyway though.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="10" oneShotId="59">
                <condition count="0" filter="rwby" role="opp" />
                <state img="#-wistful.png">Probably for the best none of my team are here, although...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-aroused.png">I figured you'd do it but, &lt;i&gt;damn. &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-tsundere.png">Have fun, no point doing otherwise.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I wonder if... &lt;i&gt; (You'll sound like I imagined.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <state img="#-aroused.png">&lt;i&gt; (Fuck that's a stronger hit than any catnip.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-admire.png">It all just got a lot more real. I'm not planning on going anywhere though.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">You're so alluring like that. I can barely believe it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-stretching.png">I've already given you plenty to look at... you can keep doing it.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">You already had my attention, but now I can barely look away.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Feels almost to good to be true... almost.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-admire.png">When I traveled on the road with... some former friends. We hardly had separate bathing, but this is so much more.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I always appreciate it when an author doesn't write the women like they're done they're done after one round... I'm certainly not.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-10" id="7">
                <condition role="target" character="elizabeth" />
                <state img="#-tsundere.png">&lt;i&gt; (I wonder if I've been using my Semblances... to their fullest.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-confused.png">Sorry, I'm not feeling brave enough to help you out just yet.</state>
                <state img="#-admire.png">&lt;i&gt; (I understood the idea that this was beautiful as well as attractive, but seeing it proved is something else.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">&lt;i&gt; (Feels much more wrong to stare this early, but those eyes, her hips rocking. It's hard to even try and look away.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">You're...</state>
                <state img="#-admire.png">I'd have woken up from a dream by now. I hope.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">&lt;i&gt; (Of course I already know what I'd say... what I'd want, but this seems a little early for that.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Plenty of girls in ninja... my books. This game isn't... a new idea, &lt;i&gt; I just wish we were closer. &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">You can look, ~target~. It's... kind of nice to feel so wanted.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">I do not normally talk this much, let alone to strangers, but it's harder to be shy about talking when you're not shy about doing... that.</state>
                <state img="#-admire.png">You're just... gleaming with sweat. Don't worry, it's a good look.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">It's so much&lt;i&gt; more&lt;/i&gt; than I could ever have imagined.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Nothing wrong with doing this here if you're enjoying it.</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">I don't think I've met any girls who weren't beautiful... I was going to compliment you but actually the lack of even average girls is weird now I think about it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-aroused.png">&lt;i&gt; (It's a shame we can't do more, play more. Roll around til they pin me beneath them...) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Losing was okay but with you, I barely care I did.</state>
                <state img="#-fantasyidle.png">&lt;i&gt; (I wonder what they'd say if I asked them to touch me, with their hands... or with ropes.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Lots of first times today, the game, and now this... do you umm... want one more?</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">It's my first time doing this with a girl... up to you if it's my last.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">&lt;i&gt; (To just hold her, feel her soft warm skin beneath my hands...) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">You could touch my ears... if you wanted. They get a bit sensitive when I'm like this.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-confused.png">I was going to offer to give you a hug but I take it you'd prefer that a bit later.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_heavy_masturbating">
            <case stage="5-10">
                <state img="#-aroused.png" oneShotId="12">That's so enticing, the gleaming, heaving sweat and the hot breath... Just wish it was on my neck, or my wrists.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">I thought I was breathless before... I had no idea.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">I couldn't tear my eyes away now if I tried.. .but you don't seem to mind too much, ~target~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-aroused.png">You're that far already! Sorry I didn't do more for you, but I could do something now if you asked &lt;i&gt; nicely enough. &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">You're really going all out... and I'm just standing here.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-heavy 1.png">Fuck that's good. You're bringing me closer.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">You look absolutely perfect, but you could be louder.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">And with that, my ability to think is completely out the window.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">&lt;i&gt; (Fuck I could start going again right now.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-bashful.png" oneShotId="362">I can't have had much to do with that... Maybe next time I could?</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png" oneShotId="363">&lt;i&gt; (Maybe it would be okay to purr if she was finishing me like that.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png" oneShotId="364">Watching you just give in to it, swept away by pleasure...</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" oneShotId="365">I really just watched you... &lt;i&gt; (Can she see me soaking?) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9-10">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">That's uhh... you are amazing. I just... I wish you'd... touched me too.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate_first">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-tsundere.png">Shit. Not exactly the first place I was going for... But I'm not gonna quit now.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate">
            <case stage="8">
                <condition count="1" status="alive" />
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Well done. I don't resent you playing well.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-think.png">It would have been optimistic to expect to win from here.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Don't worry about me. I knew what I signed up for. I just hope... I don't know actually, let's just get this started.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="start_masturbating">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">You it's... I knew... hnn... &lt;i&gt; (I didn't hope for this... but I'm not unhappy to have lost.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Does anyone, do... &lt;i&gt; (You want to join me... or help me.)  &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-tsundere.png">I'm not going to tell you not to enjoy this. I know I would in your shoes.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="masturbating">
            <case stage="9" oneShotId="7" priority="10">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Satsen" />
                <state img="#-read2.png" oneShotId="7">&lt;i&gt; (The figure that enters her tower cell through, was the one she hoped for.  It was Sekush! She asks if Setkushi will hurt her, she's disappointed when she says no. They admit their feelings.. Then Setsen says... Or, you could leave me in this ropes?. Kiss me, hold me, do whatever you want, but dont you cut these ropes. Anything? Sekushi ran her hand down the side of her prisoners hair. So the ropes where pulled, tugged, and pulled and tightened, as well as tightened, as they kissed and kissed and had sex and got naked over the ropes, the ropes weret much of a problem in that regard, they simply left pretty red lines as their passion overtook them and took them all through the night, to the morning, after that night.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <condition role="self" timeInStage="6-7" />
                <state img="#-read2.png" oneShotId="2">You shouldn't expect me to just tell you what I'm thinking... &lt;i&gt; (Or all the books I've read.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="3">&lt;i&gt; (I don't do this nearly enough, but at least whenever the need hits, it's so satisfying) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" oneShotId="4">I-I don't go into heat, just so we're clear. I'm just as horny as any of you would be.</state>
                <state img="#-read2.png" oneShotId="5">&lt;i&gt; (I'm not pretending ninja's of love is a good book... but damn, that first sauna scene, the collars and outfits in the castle fights... it is hot.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-read.png" oneShotId="6" marker="Satsen">&lt;i&gt; (I need to focus more and get going properly so... Oh forget it, you know what you're thinking about, Blake. The bondage scene in book two, everyone knew she'd help Satsen escape... everyone but her...) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <condition role="self" timeInStage="7-8" />
                <state img="#-tsundere.png" oneShotId="8">No need to keep it all to myself. We all knew we came here for this. &lt;i&gt; (I didn't mean that as an invitation... but I don't mind if someone reads it that way.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-fantasyidle.png">I didn't think I was in a heat today... but then I started, &lt;i&gt; oh fuck, &lt;/i&gt; maybe I am.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">When I say heat I just mean... oh nevermind. Seeing you all... knowing you're all watching is...  &lt;i&gt;intoxicating...&lt;/i&gt;
 </state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">&lt;i&gt; (So what if I want someone to leash me up and play with me until I... It's nothing to do with being fanus. Some of my teammates would have to enjoy....) &lt;/i&gt; Being tied down, played with and teased until I'm a mess... Shit .</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I did plan to win. I don't think I can even plan to lose. But this is a loss I'm happy to &lt;i&gt; take. &lt;/i&gt; </state>
                <state img="#-read2.png">I've never done anything like this game before... and it won't be the last time I do.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Mwwrll... I'm not purring anymore than I could picture anyone else here doing.</state>
                <state img="#-fantasyidle.png">I want---I need, someone, you're all so close and I'm so... &lt;i&gt;wanting. &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-admire.png">So much to see, and touch, to taste on my tongue, even just on the air.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Even just the idea of cuddling naked with Sun or Yang is comforting. Or maybe even someone here?</state>
                <state img="#-fantasyidle.png">&lt;i&gt; (What I would give to mark, ~human~ with my teeth, with my lips. Not to make them mine, but to prove they where for one night.) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="heavy_masturbating">
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-heavy 1.png">Yes we do go into heat okay. &lt;i&gt; So won't someone, anyone, please... &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-heavy 1.png">I want. I---I'm burning up, I want hands, rope, to be held softly and fucked hard.</state>
                <state img="#-heavy 2.png">Some part of me hoped for help. I'm writhing all on my own now.</state>
                <state img="#-heavy 2.png">I saw Pyrrha wrap chains around a Grimm once, and it got me thinking. Not about her, but about... well, other uses for a power like that.</state>
                <state img="#-heavy 1.png">If you didn't want me to leave marks that's okay, ~player~. I just hope you're willing to leave them on me..</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finishing_masturbating">
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-finishing.png">Mrrwwll, I'm so, so warm, fuckk!</state>
                <state img="#-finishing.png">Gah I tried to hold this back a bit longer, f---fuck.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-finishing.png">That was even more intense than I expected. I guess I have you all to thank for that.</state>
                <state img="#-finishing.png">I love this. Just basking in my own heat and pleasure... I don't mind having company for it either.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="after_masturbating">
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-stretching.png">Can't say I have any regrets from today... or that I won't come back.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Guess this really is a good way to bond with strangers, huh?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I'm not comfortable like it's my dorm, but I am happy.</state>
                <state img="#-wistful.png">It's pleasant to be out and still have time before any regrets come back to me... most regrets.</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">This is probably a stupid thing to say, but some days really do remind you what's worth fighting for.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_victory">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-confused.png">I didn't even have to reveal... too much of myself. That's a pleasant surprise.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-6">
                <state img="#-tsundere.png">Well, you saw my big secret... and I still feel comfortable here, so thank you. Want another game?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I won?... I won! &lt;i&gt; (Losing wasn't looking quite as bad at the end there.)  &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_defeat">
            <case stage="10" id="2">
                <test expr="~self.place~" value="2" />
                <state img="#-chat.png">I don't train to play cards. I am pleased I did that well.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-happy.png">It was... fun. Thank you all.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I don't get into heats like that often so I can hardly complain. Might stay for another game.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="global">
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="16">
                <condition role="target" character="ae86" sayingMarker="driveaway" />
                <state img="#-skeptical.png">I wonder who made that... something tells me it's not Peitro's work.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" oneShotId="23">
                <condition role="target" character="nami_szs" sayingMarker="goodBye" />
                <state img="#-amused.png">Sure. I wouldn't want you to stay if you didn't want to.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" id="4">
                <condition role="other" character="lyralei" stage="0-7" saidMarker="lyralei_picture_drop" sayingMarker="lyralei_picture_drop_follow1" notSaidMarker="lyralei_picture_drop_follow" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="9">Sure, it's no big deal to me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10" priority="11">
                <condition role="self" timeInStage="0-1" />
                <state img="#-afterglow2.png" oneShotId="169">Don't worry. I won't fall asleep on you... I think.</state>
                <state img="#-afterglow2.png" oneShotId="170">Too much to see too fall asleep now, as much as I want to.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

    </behaviour>
</opponent>
