<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<collectibles>
    <collectible id="fischl_book" status="online" img="opponents/fischl/0-collectibea.png" thumbnail="opponents/fischl/Book_Flowers_for_Princess_Fischl.png">
        <title>Flowers for Princess Fischl</title>
        <subtitle>Fischl's favorite book</subtitle>
        <text>"This work originally came in a violet and black wooden box as a limited edition gift, but many hardcore fans of the series who wanted to collect the whole saga were enraged by the great amount of content versus the small number of copies printed. Due to this, Yae Publishing House would name this book "Volume 0" and sell it separately. Eventually, the original work, the boxed collector's edition, and Volume O would all come to be regarded as standard by fans."

-- Fischl's favorite book, and where she got her alias from. </text>
        <unlock>Win a game against Fischl.</unlock>
    </collectible>
    <collectible id="fischl_food" status="online" img="opponents/fischl/0-collectible.png" thumbnail="opponents/fischl/Item_Die_Heilige_Sinfonie.png">
        <title>Die Heilige Sinfonie</title>
        <subtitle>Fischl's favorite food</subtitle>
        <text>"Fischl's specialty. The exquisite presentation doth seem to communicate some incomprehensible enigma. When partaking, if one were to gaze upon Fischl, one might see her expectant gaze peek though the gaps of her fingers, which she is using to cover half her face... Is this also part of the mystery?"</text>
        <unlock>Lose a game against Fischl.</unlock>
    </collectible>
    <collectible id="fischl_bow" status="online" img="opponents/fischl/0-collectibow.png" thumbnail="opponents/fischl/bow.png">
        <title>Prinzessin der Verurteilung's Amethyst Bow</title>
        <subtitle>The bow belonging to the Princess of the Night</subtitle>
        <text>"The bow that belongs to Fischl von Luftschloss Narfidort, the Prinzessin der Verurteilung. When you wear it, are you confessing your loyalty to Fischl, or are you just another cosplayer like Amy's true self?"</text>
        <unlock>Win a game against Fischl without losing all of your clothing.</unlock>
        <wearable>true</wearable>
        <clothing name="bow" generic="ribbon" position="neck" type="extra" img="opponents/fischl/bow.png" />
    </collectible>
</collectibles>
