<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>

<!--This file was machine generated using the Character Editor v6.7.7 at 12:57:22 PM on July 18, 2022. Do not edit this file directly unless you know what you're doing.-->
<opponent>
    <version>v6.7.7</version>
    <first>Kaz</first>
    <last>Kaan</last>
    <label>Kaz</label>
    <gender>male</gender>
    <size>medium</size>
    <timer>26</timer>
    <intelligence>average</intelligence>

    <intelligence stage="3">good</intelligence>

    <nicknames>
        <nickname for="ms.fortune">Ms. Fortune</nickname>
    </nicknames>


    <wardrobe>
        <clothing name="underwear" generic="underwear" position="lower" type="important" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="pants" generic="pants" position="lower" type="major" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="socks" generic="socks" position="feet" type="minor" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="shirt" generic="shirt" position="upper" type="major" />
        <clothing name="blazer" generic="jacket" position="upper" type="minor" />
        <clothing name="shoes" generic="shoes" position="feet" type="extra" plural="true" />
    </wardrobe>


    <behaviour>
        <trigger id="selected">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="mari_setogaya" />
                <state img="#-aback.png" marker="MariS_selected">H-hang on! That's a demon!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-glad.png">Kaz Kaan. Neo Yokio's premier man of elegance. It's nice to meet you.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Kaz Kaan. Neo Yokio's most eligible bachelor and demon slayer. Pleased to meet you.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_selected">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition count="3" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I'm usually fashionably late to these things. Are we... waiting for more people still?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">So, do we wait for more people or is this it?</state>
                <state img="#-smile.png">Oh, guess I'm a bit early. Is this everyone?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition count="4" />
                <state img="#-glad.png">Looks like we're going to have a bit of a crowd to~background.time~.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Honestly, I'd feel kind of weird if it was just three people playing.</state>
                <state img="#-vibing.png">&lt;i&gt;Hmm hm hmmm...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition count="5" />
                <state img="#-showoff.png">Nothing like a full table to witness my victory!</state>
                <state img="#-surprise.png">It's gonna be lively with this many people. Guess that's what I'm here for.</state>
                <state img="#-pondering.png">The more the merrier, as they say. Think there's still room for my boys, Lexi and Gottlieb? Guess not.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_start">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="yuelia" />
                <condition role="opp" character="navi" />
                <condition count="4" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">Uh... so... ~player~... I take it you... like bugs?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="yuelia" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png">So we're just... ignoring the talking butterfly?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="navi" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png">So we're just... ignoring the talking firefly?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-smile.png">I'll warn you all, this isn't my first time playing strip poker. I've been to my fair share of ragers out in the Hamptons.</state>
                <state img="#-vibing.png">Embarrassment is temporary, but seeing people in their underwear is forever.</state>
                <state img="#-showoff.png">Don't be intimidated by my status as Neo Yokio's number one bachelor. Or maybe be intimidated. You're free to make your own decisions.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="swap_cards">
            <case stage="0-6" oneShotId="14">
                <condition role="other" character="samus_aran" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Samus_s0_3" />
                <state img="#-uppity.png" marker="Samus_s0_4">Ah-hem!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Let's go with ~cards.text~ and see what that brings me.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Hmm, I guess I need to exchange ~cards.ifPlural(these|this one)~ to have a chance.</state>
                <state img="#-serious.png">Let me exchange ~cards.text~, please.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="good_hand">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-glad.png">Man, it's not like me to have a good turn. Maybe luck is a lady.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">This isn't going to be much fun if the cards make it this easy for me.</state>
                <state img="#-pondering.png">Maybe I should have Charles get some champagne to celebrate my victory...</state>
                <state img="#-smile.png">This place has some nice vibes. Eclectic, busy, kind of like home.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" priority="0">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Beguilement&gt;=3" />
                <state img="#-glad.png">Not all luck goes sour, right? Sometimes things do work out... right? I am... seriously asking.</state>
                <state img="#-uppity.png">Okay... this seems good... but things aren't always as they seem.</state>
                <state img="#-blush.png">Dangit, got to keep my head in the game. I didn't even realize what I had there...</state>
                <state img="#-showoff.png">So, my stock is high right now, right? I'm not misreading the room... or being tricked?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" priority="0">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Elegance&gt;=3" />
                <state img="#-vibing.png">I'm feeling quite elegant to~background.time~ and it's all because of this lovely company.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Absolutely feeling this to~background.time~. Man, it was not a mistake hanging out with you guys.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Alright, when you see my cards just remember it's not a competition. Well, obviously this game is, but life isn't! Let's just be present here, you know?</state>
                <state img="#-nice.png">No matter how this turns out, this was definitely a Kaz Kaan table. It's undeniable.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" priority="0">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Communism&gt;=3" />
                <state img="#-aback.png">These are great cards, but somehow I don't feel very safe...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Focus Kaz. Remember your training... not that you've ever had any training.</state>
                <state img="#-surprise.png">So... weird vibes tonight... right?</state>
                <state img="#-uppity.png">Just play the game Kaz. Don't get distracted by strange thoughts.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" priority="0">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Melancholy&gt;=3" />
                <state img="#-melancholy.png">Shining hope gives way to darkest despair. Luck is an illusion cast by a vengeful and wack god...</state>
                <state img="#-melancholy.png">Why does lady luck taunt me with good fortune? She should cut me free, to fall into a pit of depravity and major embarrassment.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Whatever...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Why am I even trying? There's obviously a cosmic plot to keep me in a state of eternal wackness...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="okay_hand">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Wonder how this is gonna turn out...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="522">Charles, could you-- oh, right. No Charles here.</state>
                <state img="#-uppity.png">It's not very elegant to try too hard to win...</state>
                <state img="#-vibing.png">Yes, more vibes please...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" priority="0">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Beguilement&gt;=3" />
                <state img="#-uppity.png">I've a bit of a weakness for a pretty face. Don't think I don't know that might backfire in this sort of context.</state>
                <state img="#-blush.png">C'mon, Kaz, focus up. Don't let them get your head all foggy...</state>
                <state img="#-glad.png">Eh, this will be good enough. I'm kinda feeling myself right now anyways.</state>
                <state img="#-surprise.png">It's not going so bad, right? I can probably afford a slip up or two...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" priority="0">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Melancholy&gt;=3" />
                <state img="#-melancholy.png">A small blessing. A piece of driftwood in an endless ocean. This is better than I deserve, honestly.</state>
                <state img="#-melancholy.png">Drat. Well, this isn't so bad. I guess it's possible that maybe I still might lose this hand somehow.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">It will be what it will be. Who am I to struggle against fate? Against the gods, if there be gods that set fate against a mortal like me.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Would it be so bad just to stop trying? To give up and consign myself to my cringe-worthy fate?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" priority="0">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Elegance&gt;=3" />
                <state img="#-vibing.png">Why concern myself with luck? It's out of my hands. An unknowable fate is exciting.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Win or lose, we're all still having fun, right? </state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Even if I can't win, it was just nice to be able to chill with such an excellent crowd.</state>
                <state img="#-showoff.png">Can we keep the good times rolling? Even if just for a bit of extra time? Maybe we could work it out.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" priority="0">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Communism&gt;=3" />
                <state img="#-aback.png">I can't focus with all these weird vibes?</state>
                <state img="#-cross.png">Something is throwing off the chakra or the feng shui or something in here.</state>
                <state img="#-serious.png">If you're trying to throw me off my game, let me just say it's not going to work as well as you think!</state>
                <state img="#-blush.png">Is it hot? I feel like it's hot? Does that make sense? Does anything make sense?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="bad_hand">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-melancholy.png" marker="+Melancholy">Win, lose... we'll all be equal in the grave.</state>
                <state img="#-uppity.png" oneShotId="552">At least I don't have to worry about Arcangelo popping up and being a nuisance.</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">Maybe this is retribution for something I did in a past life...</state>
                <state img="#-uppity.png">I might need some good vibes to balance me out...</state>
                <state img="#-aback.png">Aww, man! I'm such an herb! I need, like, a do-over!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" priority="0">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Beguilement&gt;=3" />
                <state img="#-blush.png">Oops. So much for not getting distracted...</state>
                <state img="#-uppity.png">Ugh. Base feelings cloud the mind to reason... or something. </state>
                <state img="#-pondering.png">I mean, even if I lose I'm still popular, right?</state>
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="-Beguilement">... I'm getting the feeling that... I might be getting taken for a ride...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" priority="0">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Melancholy&gt;=3" />
                <state img="#-melancholy.png">Black clouds gather turning day into night. Turning sunshine into rain. The world is gray and so am I.</state>
                <state img="#-melancholy.png">Oh, great, it's wackness all the way down.</state>
                <state img="#-surprise.png">Giving up won't make me feel better and seeing this through won't make me feel worse.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">There's that familiar melancholy.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" priority="0">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Elegance&gt;=3" />
                <state img="#-vibing.png">If I lose this one, then I lost it for you.</state>
                <state img="#-surprise.png">Usually a little mistake like this would send me spiraling into a deep blue funk.</state>
                <state img="#-glad.png">Ah, shoot. This is so, I dunno, wack? Honestly, I'm feeling the vibe a bit too much right now to get bent out of shape about it.</state>
                <state img="#-pondering.png">Even a fall can be elegant.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" priority="0">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Communism&gt;=3" />
                <state img="#-speechless.png">Remember me for the man of elegance and fashion I was and not the muttering, sweaty mess I became...</state>
                <state img="#-aback.png">W-what? Good cards? In this economy?</state>
                <state img="#-cross.png">I appreciate your dedication to my misery, but at some point the courageousness has diminishing returns.</state>
                <state img="#-blush.png">Uh... maybe we should take a break? Is it time for snacks?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="hand">
            <case stage="0-8" id="77">
                <condition count="4-" />
                <condition role="other" character="nico_robin" stage="1-7" sayingMarker="place_of_origin" />
                <alternative>
                    <condition count="1" filter="one_piece" />
                    <condition role="other" character="nico_robin" stage="1-7" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-vibing.png">Neo Yokio is, of course, the greatest city in the world {small}probably{!reset}. We've got the finest dining, the most elegant clothes, and a demon situation that is totally under control thanks to me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="101" totalRounds="4-">
                <condition count="2-" filter="magic" var="mage" />
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" stage="0-5" sayingMarker="PromptMage" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Ha, no! I don't really "study" magic. I'm just a natural!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="78" totalRounds="2-">
                <condition role="other" character="nico_robin" stage="0-5" sayingMarker="flower_ability" />
                <state img="#-nice.png">Amazing. Now, is that &lt;i&gt;any&lt;/I&gt; part of your body?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="86" totalRounds="2-">
                <condition role="other" character="cagliostro" stage="3-7" sayingMarker="ChangePrompt" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I guess I could stand to be a little bit taller. Not too tall, though. I want to have good stature without being totally gangly.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="53">
                <condition role="other" character="dawn" stage="6" saidMarker="DawnNeedsAMoment" sayingMarker="DawnIsGone" notSaidMarker="DawnsBack" />
                <state img="#-blush.png">&lt;i&gt;Ahem&lt;/i&gt;... uh... bit awkward now...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="55">
                <condition role="other" character="amalia" stage="5" saidMarker="grow1" sayingMarker="grow2" />
                <state img="#-cross.png">Oh, come on... that's hardly fair...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="87">
                <condition role="other" character="senko" stage="1-4" sayingMarker="senko_pampering" />
                <state img="#-vibing.png">When I need pampering, I have Charles draw me a hot bath and play me the latest hits. That's the ideal right there.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="83" totalRounds="3-">
                <condition role="other" character="rouge" sayingMarker="magic_jewel_rumors" />
                <state img="#-glad.png">I don't know if this counts, but there is Damien Hirst sculpture For the Love of God. It's a platinum cast skull with over 8,000 flawless diamonds embedded in it. That's pretty unusual, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="82">
                <condition role="other" character="mari_setogaya" sayingMarker="Hope_you_are_having_fun" />
                <state img="#-uppity.png">I'm still not convinced you're not trying to lull me into a false sense of security, but it's not like it's totally killing the vibe...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" oneShotId="15">
                <condition role="other" character="samus_aran" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Samus_s0_4" />
                <state img="#-nice.png" marker="Samus_s0_5">Hi. I feel like we got off on the wrong foot. My name is Kaz Kaan, gentleman of peerless elegance.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="84">
                <condition role="other" character="reimu" sayingMarker="Reimu_GetRichQuick" />
                <state img="#-vibing.png" marker="+Communism">There's only one sure-fire get rich quick scheme, and that's to get born rich. It's fucked, but that's capitalism.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="88">
                <condition role="other" character="syrenne" sayingMarker="prompt_odd_jobs" />
                <state img="#-glad.png">If you know anything about demons, I have an exorcism I'm supposed to perform on some heiress later. It'd be nice if someone else could do it so I can play bocce ball with my boys instead.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="89">
                <condition role="other" character="syrenne" sayingMarker="prompt_magic" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png">Does it really take that long to learn? Huh. I've just always sort of been able to do it. It didn't occur to me there might be books about it...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="90">
                <condition role="other" character="syrenne" sayingMarker="prompt_mates" />
                <state img="#-glad.png">Heck, I'd invite Lexi and Gottlieb to play. It might be kinda weird for me, but they're both pretty open minded and they always make things fun.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="91">
                <condition role="other" character="syrenne" sayingMarker="prompt_tease" />
                <state img="#-uppity.png">Teasing is so grade school. Doesn't matter if you like the person or not, you're just being a herb.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="92">
                <condition role="other" character="syrenne" sayingMarker="prompt_bath" />
                <state img="#-nice.png">Baths are usually private relaxation time, but I wouldn't be totally opposed to present company joining me for a little private time.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="93">
                <condition role="other" character="syrenne" sayingMarker="prompt_talk" />
                <state img="#-vibing.png">Pillow talk, definitely. I want my girl in my ear so God doesn't have to hear all the nasty things she wants done to her.</state>
                <state img="#-cross.png">Yeah, I've had some real howlers in the sack before. There's nothing wrong with enthusiasm, but sometimes it's just too much.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="94">
                <condition role="other" character="syrenne" sayingMarker="prompt_story" />
                <state img="#-melancholy.png">Yeah, I usually keep it pretty light on the alcohol. I'm a total bummer as a drunk...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" oneShotId="1">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Elegance&gt;=5" />
                <state img="#-pondering.png" marker="Helena">
                    <text>All this taking off of clothes might actually be Helena Saint Tessero's kind of game. I wonder what she's up to nowadays?</text>
                    <markers>
                        <marker name="Elegance" op="+" value="1" />
                    </markers>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" oneShotId="2">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Melancholy&gt;=5" />
                <state img="#-melancholy.png" marker="Cathy">
                    <text>Feeling kind of blue, for some reason. Times like these I start thinking about my ex, Cathy, again. That makes me even bluer...</text>
                    <markers>
                        <marker name="Melancholy" op="+" value="1" />
                    </markers>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" oneShotId="3">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Beguilement&gt;=5" />
                <state img="#-blush.png" marker="Sailor">
                    <text>Woo, it's getting a little steamy in here. I hope I'm not getting drawn in again. I don't want another Sailor Pellegrino incident...</text>
                    <markers>
                        <marker name="Beguilement" op="+" value="1" />
                    </markers>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" oneShotId="4">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Communism&gt;=5" />
                <state img="#-speechless.png" marker="Mila">
                    <text>Is it weird I wore Mila Malevich's jumpsuit? I guess that old man did too... oh fuck that's even weirder...</text>
                    <markers>
                        <marker name="Communism" op="+" value="1" />
                    </markers>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="95">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Communism&gt;=3" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" oneShotId="569" marker="promptC_travel">Neo Yokio is full of fast cars and freedom, but I fly most everywhere on my butler. How does everyone else get around?</state>
                <state img="#-vibing.png" oneShotId="567" marker="promptC_panda">Alright, lightning round creative thinking exercise: you're dunked in your supposedly dead uncle's infinity pool and you emerge as an animal. What animal are you?</state>
                <state img="#-surprise.png" oneShotId="568" marker="promptC_homies">They say competition inspires innovation, but it can also breed contempt. The same people we compete with are sometimes those we have the most in common with. Don't you think?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="97">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Melancholy&gt;=3" />
                <state img="#-melancholy.png" oneShotId="576" marker="promptM_mood">You ever feel like life is trying to take you down just so it can sadistically kick you while you're down because everything is wack?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="583" marker="promptM_cheerup">Sometimes enjoying the finer things picks me up when I'm feeling melancholy. I dunno. What cheers you up?</state>
                <state img="#-melancholy.png" oneShotId="582" marker="promptM_exes">Anyone else have trouble getting over their exes or an ex? I could maybe use some insight...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="96">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Elegance&gt;=3" />
                <state img="#-vibing.png" oneShotId="590" marker="promptE_gotaway">Even when two people have a real connection, sometimes they just don't get together. You know what I mean? Who, to you, is the one who got away?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="618" marker="promptE_treatyourself">Karl Lagerfeld once said "vanity is the healthiest thing in life." Have you remembered to be vain?</state>
                <state img="#-nice.png" oneShotId="619" marker="promptE_celebrity">So, anybody got a celebrity crush? Someone famous they've dreamt about a romantic evening with? It's okay if the answer is me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="98" priority="0">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Beguilement&gt;=3" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="556" marker="promptB_catfish">Ever met someone who didn't turn out to be who they said they were? Like, a total smokeshow who is interesting and kind, but turns out to be... a real bonehead?</state>
                <state img="#-glad.png" oneShotId="557" marker="promptB_popmusic">So, what's popular in music these days? I picked up something of an aversion to pop stars, so I'm a bit out of the loop.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="560" marker="promptB_catperson">Your own preferences on animals aside, would you say you're more of a cat person person or a dog person person.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip">
            <case stage="0-2" id="32" priority="142">
                <condition role="other" character="polly" stage="3-5" sayingMarker="Polly_Kaz_WellDressed" />
                <state img="#-cross.png" marker="polly_resp0_DressA">Smack talk usually works better when you're actually doing well yourself.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="meia" stage="0-5" sayingMarker="kaz0" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="meia_resp0_1">It is kinda mind blowing to think about a cocktail party or designer brands on an alien planet. Outer space makes me think of eating freeze-dried ice cream and really horrible potatoes.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="meia_resp0_1">It's a bit wild to think about partying or shopping on an alien planet. I guess all those cheesy sci-fi movies prepared me for distant planets that are more... dusty and lawless.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5" id="33">
                <condition role="other" character="polly" stage="0-5" sayingMarker="Polly_Kaz_WellDressed" />
                <state img="#-uppity.png" marker="polly_resp0_DressB">That is... not a stereotype I'm familiar with.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5" id="34">
                <condition role="other" character="polly" stage="0-5" sayingMarker="Polly_Kaz_Charles" />
                <state img="#-uppity.png" marker="polly_resp0_Charles">Charles is equipped with state of the art statistical analysis software... that some would consider "cheating" in this context.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5" id="35">
                <condition role="other" character="polly" stage="0-5" sayingMarker="Polly_Kaz_FashionExpert" />
                <state img="#-cross.png" marker="polly_resp0_Expert">The suits I deal with are Armani and Chanel. Not that I expect you to appreciate that...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5" id="36">
                <condition role="other" character="polly" stage="0-5" sayingMarker="Polly_Kaz_RichKid" />
                <state img="#-angry.png" marker="polly_resp0_Rich">Believe me, Polly, you do &lt;i&gt;not&lt;/i&gt; wanna make this about class.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5" id="37">
                <condition role="other" character="polly" stage="0-5" sayingMarker="Polly_Kaz_Exorcise" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="polly_resp0_Exorcise">Do... do you have any basis for saying that? I don't see why I couldn't.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5" id="38">
                <condition role="other" character="polly" stage="0-5" sayingMarker="Polly_Kaz_Aunt" />
                <state img="#-aback.png" marker="polly_resp0_Aunt">Oh man! Aunt Agatha doesn't need to see, or hear, about any of this!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5" id="30">
                <condition role="other" character="fluttershy" saidMarker="Kaz_enchanted_reply" sayingMarker="Kaz_whereRU_from" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="fluttershy_respRU_1">Why, only the greatest city there is: Neo Yokio. City of elegance, hub of culture, height of fashion, and home to the rich and famous.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="revy" sayingMarker="kaz0" saying="Italian" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="revy_resp0_1">Since I doubt you're smoking MS cigarettes, I'm going to guess those pistols are Berettas.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Kaz_s0_1" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="yshtola_resp0_1">That's a bit reductive. I'm Neo Yokio's most eligible bachelor. I exemplify all it means to be a high-class gentleman. I'm a taste-maker. A trend-setter. Kaz Kaan is a brand unto itself.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Kaz_CapreseHazy1" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="bobobo_resp0_1">Why are you asking me? I didn't make the drink, I just promoted it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Kaz_s1_1" />
                <state img="#-vibing.png" marker="yshtola_resp1_1">A gentleman takes his losses on the cheek. Besides, it wouldn't do to be a poor sport with a lady about.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Kaz_s2_1" />
                <state img="#-glad.png" marker="yshtola_resp2_1">If you want to examine me, feel free. Kaz Kaan is an open book, happy to satisfy any curiosity you have about me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Kaz_s3_1" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="yshtola_resp3_1">Those aren't necessarily mutually exclusive, Y'shtola. I could probably show you what I mean if you'd admit you'd like me to.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Kaz_s4_1" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="yshtola_resp4_1">You wound me, Y'shtola. Don't we have a rapport by now? Are we not kindred spirits?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Kaz_s5_1" />
                <state img="#-blush.png" marker="yshtola_resp5_1">What I have under my underwear has very little to do with my ranking on the bachelor board!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Kaz_DamienHirstIsAnActualWeirdo1" />
                <state img="#-aback.png" marker="bobobo_resp1_1">That's a weirdly specific question about an event you weren't around for. How do you know about all of that?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Kaz_HealthyCompetition1" />
                <state img="#-frustrated.png" marker="bobobo_resp2_1">You can't be serious. I mean, you specifically can't be serious ever and especially not about this.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Kaz_IRippedThisJokeOff1" />
                <state img="#-cross.png" marker="bobobo_resp3_1">I don't need some dumb blonde guy pestering me about being homies everywhere I go, thank you very much.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Kaz_SuperEagle1" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="bobobo_resp4_1">Are you just saying random words and trying to pass it off as profound?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Kaz_Pink1" />
                <state img="#-aback.png" marker="bobobo_resp5_1">I don't know what you're expecting, but it sounds like you're going to be disappointed.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="heris" sayingMarker="HerisKazFashion" />
                <state img="#-vibing.png" marker="heris_resp0_1">Why, no occasion could be more special than chancing to meet you here, Ms. Heris. Regrettably, I am woefully underdressed for such an auspicious meeting.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="16">
                <condition role="other" character="estelle" sayingMarker="EstelleKazStart1" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="estelle_resp0_1">You've got a keen eye, Lady Estelle. The Kaan family is at the head of the magistocracy in Neo Yokio. Safe to say the city wouldn't be as great as if it weren't for my ancestors.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="17">
                <condition role="other" character="cynthia" sayingMarker="KazStrip01" />
                <state img="#-glad.png" marker="cynthia_resp0_1">You flatter me, Ms. Cynthia, but this ensemble is my casual, everyday look. Emphasizing comfort without sacrificing style. Kaz Kaan doesn't go out in anything less.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="18">
                <condition role="other" character="kyou" sayingMarker="kyou_kaz_01" />
                <state img="#-glad.png" marker="kyou_resp0_1">I think expanding one's horizons is very healthy, Ms. Fujibayashi. I know what the women of Neo Yokio think of me, but some outside opinions could help me improve my branding.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="19">
                <condition role="other" character="yuno_uno" sayingMarker="yuno_kaz_strip1a" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="yuno_resp1_1">Uh... as much as anyone else, I imagine? Good fun for a rainy day with the boys, if nothing else.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="miki_miura" sayingMarker="miki_kaz_wealthy" />
                <state img="#-melancholy.png" marker="miki_resp0_1">I understand completely, Ms. Miura. Discrimination on the basis of wealth is so gauche. One's money, or rather their family's money, doesn't make them a better or more worthy human...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="20">
                <condition role="other" character="jessie" sayingMarker="KazStrip01" />
                <state img="#-blush.png" marker="jessie_resp0_1">Ms. Maye! I, uh, I mean, thanks for the offer, but we hardly know each other. I just feel like it wouldn't be appropriate...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="21">
                <condition role="other" character="fina" sayingMarker="FinaKazStart1" />
                <state img="#-melancholy.png" marker="fina_resp0_1">That's... complicated. The magistocracy enjoys an elevated position, sure, but the other noble families have always held us in contempt. We have keep to proving ourselves, prove we're still &lt;i&gt;useful&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="22">
                <condition role="other" character="petra" sayingMarker="petra_kaz_strip0a" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="petra_resp0_1">Of course, Lady Macneary. My family rose through the ranks in Neo Yokio thanks to our ability to use magic. Nowadays there's less danger though, so we're more of a proper noble house now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="kora" sayingMarker="Kora_Kaz_1" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="kora_resp0_1">Of course, but the road to true elegance is different for everyone. Fashion must be true to oneself, honest and open. Being comfortable in your clothes always projects a sense of confidence.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="28">
                <condition role="other" character="chara_dreemurr" sayingMarker="ResponseCharaKazMustStrip1" />
                <state img="#-angry.png" marker="chara_resp0_1">Look, I'm not here to exorcise anyone. If you don't cause any trouble, I won't be forced to bust open a can of magical whoop-ass on you.</state>
                <state img="#-cross.png" marker="chara_resp0_1">Yeah, it doesn't take a trained demon slayer to pick you out of a crowd. Can we just mutually agree not to cause a scene? It's a bit gauche to mix business and pleasure.</state>
                <state img="#-serious.png" marker="chara_resp0_1">Don't try and start trouble with me, Chara. I'm not here to put down a... whatever you are. Besides, Aunt Agatha wouldn't appreciate me doing charity work.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="jura" sayingMarker="kaz0" />
                <state img="#-showoff.png" marker="jura_resp0_1">Miss Jura, men who know appearances are important are a dime a dozen. Men of true elegance are a rare breed, but among them Kaz Kaan reigns supreme.</state>
                <state img="#-vibing.png" marker="jura_resp0_1">It's not so strange for a man to try and look his best. Whether or not every man succeeds is a different story. I'll warn you: it wouldn't be fair to men everywhere to hold them to my high standards.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="revy" sayingMarker="kaz0" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="revy_resp0_1">Uh, Marlboro? I don't smoke, so I don't know any cigarette brands. Unless you mean the guns, in which case I &lt;i&gt;think&lt;/i&gt; they're Berettas.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="turandot" sayingMarker="kaz_0" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="turandot_resp0_1">My best pick-up line? I don't know, Princess. How can I be sure you're actually worth it?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="hu_tao" sayingMarker="tao01" />
                <state img="#-vibing.png" marker="hutao_resp0_1">Well, I consider myself a gentleman of elegance first and foremost, but I have been known to exorcise a demon or two. It's my duty to the public.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="hu_tao" sayingMarker="tao11" />
                <state img="#-smile.png" marker="hutao_resp1_1">I'm good in that department, thanks. I've already got a beautiful headstone picked out in the Kaan family plot. It's peaceful. Sometimes I like to visit and lay down on it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="hu_tao" sayingMarker="tao21" />
                <state img="#-vibing.png" marker="hutao_resp2_1">Death is not a parallel move. The key to dying well is living well, and the key to living well is surrounding yourself with the people and things you enjoy the most.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="hu_tao" sayingMarker="tao31" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="hutao_resp3_1">Ha, monotony? Never heard of her! Hardly any two days for me are the same for me. Things are usually pretty chill, but if I wait long enough something exciting is bound to happen.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="hu_tao" sayingMarker="tao41" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="hutao_resp4_1">I'm not one to turn down an experience like this. Good chance to meet some new people, the sort I'd never be able to meet with otherwise.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="99">
                <condition role="other" character="fluttershy" sayingMarker="Kaz_areYourDaysBusy" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="fluttershy_respDB_1">They can be. I never know when my aunt is going to call me for a job. I try to keep my schedule flexible so I can just chill with my boys, but when duty calls...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="100">
                <condition role="other" character="mari" sayingMarker="Kaz_PersonalityRead1" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="mario_resp0_1">You're not wrong, even if I do feel a little like a fish out of water, but an elegant man of taste makes his way no matter where he finds himself.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="105">
                <condition role="other" character="fluttershy" sayingMarker="Kaz_wellKeptHair" />
                <state img="#-blush.png" marker="fluttershy_respKH_1">Oh, you like it? Wow, uh, thanks! Usually people think it's weird. The upkeep isn't too much, but I do have to wax the strands every so often.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="turandot" sayingMarker="kaz_1" />
                <state img="#-vibing.png" marker="turandot_resp1_1">My aim is for the height of elegance. Understated luxury, a bold take on classical style, pioneering a new understanding of material and function, and above all being true to myself and my own vanity.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-5">
                <condition role="self" consecutiveLosses="3-" />
                <condition status="alive" />
                <state img="#-melancholy.png" oneShotId="639" marker="+Melancholy">Now my vibes are all messed up...</state>
                <state img="#-cross.png" oneShotId="636">Am I being punked? You can't possibly expect me to believe I'd lose like this again...</state>
                <state img="#-frustrated.png" oneShotId="638">Am I missing something here? You know, it's not so easy to pull the cashmere over my eyes...</state>
                <state img="#-melancholy.png" oneShotId="637" marker="+Melancholy">There is for sure a bout of melancholy at the end of all of this...</state>
                <state img="#-speechless.png" oneShotId="635">There's just no way! Don't I deserve, like, a do over at this point?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-5">
                <condition role="self" consecutiveLosses="2" />
                <state img="#-melancholy.png" marker="+Melancholy">Of course. Why not me again? </state>
                <state img="#-uppity.png">C'mon, Kaz, that was just bad luck. Don't psych yourself out...</state>
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">That's horrible! Does it really have to be me again?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-glad.png">Looks like it's time for me to get down to it. I guess this is where the fun begins.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">It wouldn't be a good look if I didn't lose at all! Gotta give the people what they want!</state>
                <state img="#-uppity.png">Yes, well, I figured I shouldn't just win outright. Best to make it an even spread, for appearance's sake.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_winning">
            <case stage="1-3">
                <state img="#-glad.png" oneShotId="60">Losing is all part of the fun. It's hardly exciting if I just stand here in my clothes the whole time.</state>
                <state img="#-surprise.png" oneShotId="61">Looks like you got me this time. Still, I'm doing better than I thought. Do you guys not get out much?</state>
                <state img="#-vibing.png" oneShotId="62">Looking around, I am a bit overdressed for this occasion. I could do with a dressing down.</state>
                <state img="#-pondering.png" oneShotId="63">Haven't had enough of Kaz Kaan yet? I guess I can understand.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-uppity.png" oneShotId="98">This is getting kind of dicey. It's not going to come right down to the wire, is it?</state>
                <state img="#-blush.png" oneShotId="99">Came this close to pulling it off too. That's a bummer...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_normal">
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-pondering.png">I can deal with another loss. It wouldn't look good if I played strip poker and only took off my shoes.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-4">
                <state img="#-pondering.png" oneShotId="106">It's not over yet. Maybe I could turn this around if I gave it a gentleman's try.</state>
                <state img="#-surprise.png" oneShotId="107">Okay, I could stand to be doing a little better. I thought I was being careful.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="108">C'est la vie...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-aback.png">Yeah... just like Freddie Miles' party.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_losing">
            <case stage="1-3">
                <state img="#-uppity.png" oneShotId="44">Can I just have a moment to say being overdressed for this is extremely gauche?</state>
                <state img="#-surprise.png" oneShotId="45">Seriously? This is killing my vibes...</state>
                <state img="#-melancholy.png" oneShotId="46">Oh well, there we go. I could've handled that better.</state>
                <state img="#-uppity.png" oneShotId="47">I feel like I'm being a perfectly good sport here and not getting any recognition for it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-aback.png" oneShotId="52">Oh, come on! It's one thing to lose, but another entirely to be losing!</state>
                <state img="#-melancholy.png" oneShotId="53">If they hear about this back home, I'm going to plummet off the Bachelor Board...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripping">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Kaz_s0_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="yshtola_resp0_2">Can't exactly be on the bachelor board if I'm not a bachelor, now can I?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Kaz_CapreseHazy2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="bobobo_resp0_2">It was invented by my friends, and I trust them. Lexy and Gottlieb don't have a dishonest bone between the two of them.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Kaz_s1_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="yshtola_resp1_2">Life is a swirling maelstrom of disappointment and betrayal. In this sweet oasis, I must drink deep of simple joys and raise the ship of my heart on the tides of companionship.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Kaz_s2_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="yshtola_resp2_2">Here, let me get this shirt off so you can get a closer look. I'd never stand in the way of the pursuit of higher knowledge, Miss Rhul. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Kaz_s3_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="yshtola_resp3_2">I must confess to being quite charmed by you, Y'shtola. This is certainly no arena for subtlety, and I would be terribly distraught if I missed my chance to make my impression on you. I'm just being true to myself, and by extension true to us.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Kaz_s4_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="yshtola_resp4_2">Why rush into getting to know each other? There's plenty of time for that over dinner or while flying over the city at night.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Kaz_s5_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="yshtola_resp5_2">You know, I'm starting to like you a little less...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Kaz_DamienHirstIsAnActualWeirdo2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="bobobo_resp1_2">Is that so?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Kaz_HealthyCompetition2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="bobobo_resp2_2">I don't think we have enough time to cover all of that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Kaz_IRippedThisJokeOff2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="bobobo_resp3_2">What is it to be homies? What is this fleeting, ephemeral sense of homieness one might feel for or think of another person? Are we really anything more than just two people passing briefly in this chaotic and uncaring swirl we call life?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Kaz_SuperEagle2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="bobobo_resp4_2">And now you're just saying completely random stuff to throw me off... it's kind of creepy. Would you knock it off?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Kaz_Pink2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="bobobo_resp5_2">I can't believe I have to say this, but don't freak out. Also, my name still isn't Ralph.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="opp" character="yshtola" saidMarker="BoKaz_s2_1" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="bobobo_resp2_2Y">Right. Real funny, Y'shtola. You can't actually be serious about that... can you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="kora" sayingMarker="Kora_Kaz_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="kora_resp0_2">Your friends just need to find their own brand. Find what feels right to them. Of course, one must keep in mind the appropriateness of seasonal attire. And they should avoid denim, and corduroy is right out. A good place to start is to pick out a sensible blazer, fitted if they can help it. Good clean lines are timeless, always a classic. Of course, formal drapery is always a daring look for an elegant man...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="heris" sayingMarker="HerisKazNormalWear" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="heris_resp0_2">My outfit is certainly what I'd call everyday wear. Do you like it, Miss Heris?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="23">
                <condition role="other" character="fina" sayingMarker="FinaKazContinue1" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png">I mean, in issues that really matter everyone gets a vote. Neo Yokio is still a democracy, whether you're rich or poor.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="24">
                <condition role="other" character="estelle" sayingMarker="EstelleKazContinue1" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="estelle_resp0_2">We're not "royal," but we are magical. That's how we got where we are in society. Unless you've got a mage in your ancestry, you've got no chance at using magic.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="25">
                <condition role="other" character="kyou" sayingMarker="kyou_kaz_02" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="kyou_resp0_2">I guess I don't want to come across as elitist. Behind the money and family legacy, I'm just a regular guy. Well, a magical regular guy. At any rate, I just want to be elegant without being snobby or bragging. Kaz Kaan's branding is inclusive, not exclusive.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="26">
                <condition role="other" character="jessie" sayingMarker="KazStrip02" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="jessie_resp0_2">Sounds like you're more interested in my family's money than you are in me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="27">
                <condition role="other" character="cynthia" sayingMarker="KazStrip02" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="cynthia_resp0_2">But my attire is what I do. I am a man of elegant taste. I seek the height of fashion. My personal brand is ever evolving and requires my constant attention. And not just close. I sample the finest of fine society.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="31">
                <condition role="other" character="fluttershy" sayingMarker="Kaz_whereRU_from2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="fluttershy_respRU_2">I wouldn't say I'm important. I mean, sure, I'm Neo Yokio's number one bachelor, one of it's most prolific influencers, and the best demon hunter around, but that doesn't make me "important." At least, that's what I think.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="39">
                <condition role="other" character="petra" sayingMarker="petra_kaz_strip0b" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="petra_resp0_2">Ah, nothing too special. Mostly I just shoot lightning from my hands and exorcise demons. I can {small}usually{!reset} tell when someone or something is a demon with it as well.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="turandot" sayingMarker="kaz_01" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="turandot_resp0_2">Damn, you're right, your highness. There's a lot I could learn from an impressive woman like yourself. Maybe we can have a chat later about it. I'll buy the cocktails if you'd do me the honor.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="hu_tao" sayingMarker="tao02" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="hutao_resp0_2">I had hoped to avoid work, but it's not like I'd just sit on my hands during an emergency. Besides, it'd be nice to take a job from a beauty like you for a change.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="hu_tao" sayingMarker="tao12" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="hutao_resp1_2">It's nothing extravagant. I wanted my resting place to be austere. Just a stone headstone from the family quarry and a stone slab covering the grave itself. My grave is, of course, already dug.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="hu_tao" sayingMarker="tao22" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="hutao_resp2_2">Personally, it wouldn't bother me at all. I'm sure other people would talk, but they'll talk no matter what. The only real question is what will they say.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="hu_tao" sayingMarker="tao32" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="hutao_resp3_2">I wouldn't be much of a gentleman if I allowed you to do that without returning the favor.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="hu_tao" sayingMarker="tao42" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="hutao_resp4_2">Ahem... well, there is a bit of a luxury in being an unknown, I'll admit.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="102">
                <condition role="other" character="fluttershy" sayingMarker="Kaz_good2BeResponsible" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="fluttershy_respDB_2">The whole family is depending on me to do my job and maintain our reputation in Neo Yokio. It can be a drag, but a gentleman knows that the most important part of a burden is that you carry it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-stripping.png">It's nice to see some new faces around here. Most gatherings in Neo Yokio I attend are just the same socialites each time.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">You know, usually I end up in these sort of games with people I know, like the other social elites of Neo Yokio and beyond.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">This is a weird way to meet new people, but it is pretty exciting. Usually this type of thing happens at parties full of people I already know, celebrities, and celebrities I already know.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-stripping.png">This is a Lemaire blazer. I can't just crumple it up and throw it on the floor. Clothing this refined requires care and caution. </state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Okay, I know what you're all thinking and yes this is a Lemaire blazer. I'm not just going to drop it on the floor and I'd like to keep it where I can see it.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">I don't mean to be rude, but just keep in mind that this is a Lemaire blazer. I'm not going to just toss it on the ground where someone could come along and take it, or worse: step on the seams!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-stripping.png">A gentleman must have a sport, mine is field hockey. I'd say it keeps me in pretty reasonable shape.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">As a man of elegance and bachelor, I spend a lot of my time playing field hockey with my team: The West Side Gentlemen. Keeps my mind sharp and my body in shape.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">You might be wondering how Neo Yokio's most eligible bachelor stays in shape. The answer: field hockey.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-stripping.png">I wouldn't be surprised if this all was some kind of ploy by my Aunt to get me to work. None of you are demons in disguise, are you?</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">This isn't, like, some kind of set-up by my Aunt, right? There are no demons around here? I don't mean to be rude, but I am a little suspicious.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Okay, I'm just gonna say it. This whole place is weird. Like, possible demon activity weird. I don't think you guys are possessed, at least in my professional opinion... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Wait, what underwear am I wearing today? It's not something inelegant, I hope.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">H-hold on a second. What underwear did I put on today? Oh man... please don't be... please!</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Am I wearing... uh, quick question! You guys wouldn't judge me if my underwear had little... uh... you know what, nevermind...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Well, I guess this is goodbye Ralph Lauren. You have served me admirably.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Ralph, you were my only ally in this fight. I can only hope your sacrifice won't be in vain.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">I can't believe Ralph failed me. Maybe I should pray to Coco Chanel...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripped">
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Kaz_s0_3" />
                <state img="#-glad.png" marker="yshtola_resp0_3">Being on the bachelor board is a great honor, but I'd much rather "take a lover" than keep my place on the board.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Kaz_CapreseHazy3" />
                <state img="#-frustrated.png" marker="bobobo_resp0_3">I think I'd rather try and explain how to make a caprese martini than dive into whatever this dumpster fire of trust issues you've got going on is.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Kaz_s1_3" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="yshtola_resp1_3">Knowing I'm in your thoughts will definitely keep my spirits up.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Kaz_s2_3" />
                <state img="#-showoff.png" marker="yshtola_resp2_3">We could study magic, or we could study a little anatomy. Either way, we could have a lot of fun.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Kaz_s3_3" />
                <state img="#-nice.png" marker="yshtola_resp3_3">Well, if you're gonna make me choose...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Kaz_s4_3" />
                <state img="#-uppity.png" marker="yshtola_resp4_3">Would it kill you to at least pretend you're impressed? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Kaz_s5_3" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="yshtola_resp5_3">Of all the times to humor me, you choose now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Kaz_DamienHirstIsAnActualWeirdo3" />
                <state img="#-serious.png" marker="bobobo_resp1_3">Right, and what exactly does any of that have to do with anything? Seriously!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Kaz_HealthyCompetition3" />
                <state img="#-smile.png" marker="bobobo_resp2_3">Well, one thing you have going for you is that self-confidence, even if it's a delusional sort.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Kaz_IRippedThisJokeOff3" />
                <state img="#-melancholy.png" marker="bobobo_resp3_3">
                    <text>Chocolate doesn't cure the wackness of the world, but it eases the pain momentarily.</text>
                    <markers>
                        <marker name="Melancholy" op="+" value="1" />
                    </markers>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Kaz_SuperEagle3" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="bobobo_resp4_3">And he's back. I guess the upshot is I'm so confused I keep forgetting I'm almost naked.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Kaz_Pink3" />
                <state img="#-blush.png" marker="bobobo_resp5_3">I don't know what to tell you. This is how all my boys do it. The modern gentleman is manscaped! We're not cavemen...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Kaz_s2_3" />
                <state img="#-cross.png" marker="bobobo_resp2_3Y">That is both an insult to me and the proud tradition of the Bachelor Board...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="29">
                <condition role="other" character="estelle" sayingMarker="EstelleKazEnd1" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="estelle_resp0_3">Well, not every mage is rich and famous. I've got a cousin who basically just races ATVs and lives in a pool house.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="heris" sayingMarker="HerisKazNormalWear2" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="heris_resp0_3">Oh man, I could sum that up in one word: comfort! Sometimes you gotta suffer for fashion, but I suffer well enough on my own most days.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="40">
                <condition role="other" character="fluttershy" sayingMarker="Kaz_whereRU_from3" />
                <state img="#-vibing.png" marker="fluttershy_respRU_3">Thank you, Fluttershy, but believe me when I say that the thrill is double for me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="hu_tao" sayingMarker="tao03" />
                <state img="#-vibing.png">Trust me; you never have to compromise with anything when it comes to me... wait, did you call me a dandy?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="hu_tao" sayingMarker="tao13" />
                <state img="#-vibing.png" marker="hutao_resp1_3">Thanks, but I'll pass. Death is the final mystery whose coming solution gives each new day a sense of importance. Besides, I want to stick around for as many new winter lines as I can.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="hu_tao" sayingMarker="tao23" />
                <state img="#-glad.png" marker="hutao_resp2_3">No offense, but I did peg you as the mischievous sort. Well, it wouldn't be the first time I was interested in a girl with... let's say "exciting" rumors around her.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="hu_tao" sayingMarker="tao33" />
                <state img="#-nice.png" marker="hutao_resp3_3">Consider this an open invitation to try.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="other" character="hu_tao" sayingMarker="tao43" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="hutao_resp4_3">From the way you've been talking, I get the feeling &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; might be the thing to follow me home.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="103">
                <condition role="other" character="fluttershy" sayingMarker="Kaz_familyGrateful4Efforts" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="fluttershy_respDB_3">If they are, they sure have a weird way of showing it...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="turandot" sayingMarker="kaz_1n" />
                <state img="#-vibing.png" marker="turandot_resp0_3">I serve at your pleasure, your majesty.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-pondering.png">At least I have my boys with me for those times. Lexi and Gottlieb always know how to make it a good time.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">No danger of running into exes or Arcangelo here. At least, I really hope not...</state>
                <state img="#-blush.png">Though, it is a bit weird doing this with strangers. Maybe I can get to know you guys a bit better before I lose another hand.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-cross.png">And although I trust you guys, could you just keep an eye out for me? There's no telling who else is skulking around looking for clothes and underwear to steal.</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">I caught wind that there's someone or &lt;i&gt;something&lt;/i&gt; going around jacking people's clothes. I'm not sure if it's true, but it'll be a cold day in hell when someone takes Kaz Kaan's clothes.</state>
                <state img="#-glad.png">I'm sure my sense of style has caught your eyes, but please don't think about taking my clothes. You can wear the clothes, sure, but the brand is personal to Kaz Kaan.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Hunting demons burns calories too, I admit, but field hockey is far more elegant than my job.</state>
                <state img="#-pondering.png">A man of elegance and fashion such as myself has to look after his figure, after all. Gotta look good even when you're not wearing anything, am I right?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">It doesn't hurt that I'm, you know, very good at field hockey. Best player in Neo Yokio if my record has anything to do with it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I've been duped before, and I don't plan on making that mistake again. I'll find out for sure if you're lying.</state>
                <state img="#-serious.png">Don't think you can fool me for long if you are a demon. One touch and I'll {small}probably{!reset} know.</state>
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">I mean, sure, I've been tricked before, but I absolutely learned my lesson! Double check everything and shun mainstream pop music!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5" id="15">
                <state img="#-glad.png">Ah, saved by Ralph Lauren. The only thing more inelegant than standing around in my underwear would be standing around in cheap underwear.</state>
                <state img="#-vibing.png">Good, some tasteful Ralph Lauren clean white briefs. Guess my reputation is safe.</state>
                <state img="#-cross.png">A man of elegance shouldn't go too far without luxury underwear. You never know what's gonna happen out there.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-blush.png">I prefer Armani suits to my birthday suit. I just want to be clear on that point.</state>
                <state img="#-blush.png">I hope this is all in good taste, for all of our sakes.</state>
                <state img="#-uppity.png">Go ahead. Boo. Cheer. Hiss. Karma has a way of catching up with that sort of thing.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_strip">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="Bobobo_s0_1">Bobobo, there's something about your personal branding that's... confusing.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="ignatz" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-smile.png" marker="Ignatz_s0_1">Guess I owe Gottlieb and apology. Other people really do wear glasses like that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="takatoshi" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-pondering.png" marker="Takatoshi_s0_1">You seem like a fairly sturdy guy, Takatoshi. What's your sport? Who do you play for?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="twisted_fate" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="TwistedFate_s0_1">Are you really able to use magic, Twisted Fate? I mean, card tricks are neat, I guess, but that's not actually magic. It's just sleight of hand... or illusion? Something like that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-serious.png" marker="Bobobo_s1_1">Bobobo, you can't just be completely unhinged each and every round. It's not a sustainable image! You're bound to crash and burn! To be unexpected, sometimes you must be expected.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-serious.png" marker="Bobobo_s2_1">And now you're gonna be naked, Bobobo. Honestly, what did you expect would happen? Do I even want to know?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="Bobobo_s3_1">Yeah... I'm pretty sure I know what's going to happen now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-glad.png" marker="Bobobo_s4_1">Guess this whole "stockpiling" tactic didn't work out for you in the long run. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-serious.png" marker="Bobobo_s5_1">I think it's time for you to face the music, Bobobo. No more hijinks, no more pranks, no more Don Patch.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Tough break, ~target~. I hope your personal brand can survive this.</state>
                <state img="#-glad.png">Too early to break out the champagne.</state>
                <state img="#-smile.png">I guess not every bad thing happens to me.</state>
                <state img="#-surprise.png">That's terrible, ~target~. Do you think some chocolate would cheer you up?</state>
                <state img="#-uppity.png">Man, I could be at Bergdorf's right now feeling out my next big look.</state>
                <state img="#-showoff.png">Only room for one bachelor at the top, ~target~.</state>
                <state img="#-vibing.png">For times like these, I find soothing ocean noises bring me serenity.</state>
                <state img="#-pondering.png">A man's personal branding should bring him luck. Maybe that's too hard for you to pull off, ~target~.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Oh man, ~target~! Don't tell me you're surprised!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Well, if I was dressed like ~target~, then I might be desperate to strip too.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_strip">
            <case stage="0-8" id="69">
                <condition role="other" character="cynthia" />
                <condition role="target" character="dawn" stage="6" sayingMarker="DawnsBack" />
                <state img="#-blush.png">Hoo-boy. She's back. Now what?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="5" />
                <test expr="~target.costume~" value="default" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="Yshtola_s5_1">I did like the overall look, Y'shtola, but unfortunately it's kind of fallen apart without all the individual pieces. I don't think the dress stands up on its own.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="8">
                <condition role="target" character="lucy" stage="4" sayingMarker="virgo" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png">Wish I could use my magic to summon Charles like that...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="104">
                <condition role="target" character="turandot" stage="2" sayingMarker="play_the_game" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="Turandot_respGame_1">Ice breakers? Huh, I'm game to answer {small}as long as it's not too embarrassing.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="pyrrha" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="Pyrrha_s0_1">So, a warrior and a celebrity? You must be a busy woman. The double life is tough, nevermind the double spotlight.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="kumatora" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="Kumatora_s0_1">Pink hair? Magic? Didn't think I'd run into another magistocrat here.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="dark_magician_girl" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-blush.png" marker="DMG_s0_1">Dark Magician Girl is a bit of a mouthful for a title. There's not a short version I could call you or maybe even a name?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="hatsune_miku" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="HatsuneMiku_s0_1">A pop star? Here? Can't say I'm familiar with your work, but if it's not mainstream I wonder how that could be. I'm always up on the underground pop scene.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="ms.fortune" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-glad.png" marker="MsFortune_s0_1">That's quite the striking look you have, Ms. Fortune. If it's not too forward to say, most girls dress to hide their scars, but yours seem to put a spotlight on them.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="samus_aran" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-cross.png" marker="Samus_s0_1">Whoever the pilot of this mecha butler is, looking at the chassis it's clear they must be pretty short. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="barbara" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="Barbara_s0_1">Seems like she's a singer. Here's to hoping this idol is who she says she is...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="noelle" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-glad.png" marker="Noelle_s0_1">A real flesh and blood maid! Don't see many of those anymore. I'm afraid in Neo Yokio, robots took your job.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="zoey" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-aback.png" marker="Zoey_s0_1">Zoey seems peaceful enough, but there's a part of me that's worried this is going to turn into an exorcism.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="fluttershy" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="Fluttershy_s0_1">Pink hair? Is it naturally pink? Somehow I don't think you're a magistocrat.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="nagisa" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="Nagisa_s0_1">This girl is so cute and shy. Not at all the kind of girl I expected to run into here. Not really the sort of girl I run into anywhere, actually...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-pondering.png" marker="Yshtola_s0_1">Maybe I'll get lucky and see where that tail begins...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-glad.png" marker="Yshtola_s1_1">Not a lot of girls like you in Neo Yokio, Y'shtola. Not a lot of girls like you anywhere I know of, to be honest.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-pondering.png" marker="Yshtola_s2_1">You strike me as a classy socialite, Y'shtola, much like myself. If you were from Neo Yokio, I'm sure we'd be very well acquainted by now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="Yshtola_s3_1">Uh-oh, Y'shtola. Maybe it isn't just black cats that bring bad luck!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="Yshtola_s4_1">Kinda feels like you're holding back on us, Y'shtola. Not feeling very daring?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="6" />
                <state img="#-nice.png" marker="Yshtola_s6_1">Time for you to cast a different kind of spell on us, Y'shtola.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="7" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="Yshtola_s7_1">If you're nervous, maybe it would help if we talked about something else? Take your mind off of it? You'll be naked before you even notice!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="mikan" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="Mikan_s0_1">Bandages? A Helenist? Here?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="fluttershy" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-pondering.png" marker="Fluttershy_s1_1">Gotta say, you've got a very distinct style. Very strong branding. I'm way into the butterfly motif. Very elegant.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="fluttershy" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="Fluttershy_s2_1">Looks like bad luck, Fluttershy. You're braver than most for sticking with this though.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="fluttershy" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="Fluttershy_s3_1">I hope I haven't been too forward with you, Fluttershy. It's just that you're quite beautiful and I really feel like something is clicking between us.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="fluttershy" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-nice.png" marker="Fluttershy_s4_1">If you're nervous, you could imagine for a moment that it's just you and me here as you strip, Fluttershy.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-glad.png">It may not be very gentlemanly to make a lady strip, but we also don't live in the 19th century anymore. At least, I don't.</state>
                <state img="#-vibing.png">Definitely getting some good vibes now.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Sorry about that, ~target~. I'll have Charles send you some chocolate to make up for it.</state>
                <state img="#-smile.png">This might seem good for me and bad for ~target~, but the universe has a way of evening things out.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Alright! Kaz Kaan, proving once again why he's the ichiban!</state>
                <state img="#-melancholy.png">Oh, man! I never get this lucky! I'm probably in for a real nasty surprise coming up.</state>
                <state img="#-glad.png">Sorry, ~target~. Guess we just can't get enough of you.</state>
                <state img="#-smile.png">Don't worry, ~target~. A man of elegance would never kiss and tell, or look and tell in this case.</state>
                <state img="#-pondering.png">Well... seeing ~target~ strip a little more would make my ~background.time~.</state>
                <state img="#-cross.png">I might be a gentleman, but I'm still a guy. No point in pretending I'm not trying to beat you here, ~target~.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="tie">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">Well, that was a waste of time. Looks like it's a do-over.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="2" sayingMarker="Yshtola_TheyMadeThisJokeInShrek2" />
                <state img="#-cross.png" marker="BoYsh_s2_2">Layers of insanity...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="7">
                <condition role="target" character="brock" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-cross.png">And that's why a rocket launcher is not a gentleman's weapon... okay, there's a lot more nuance to it than that, but you get my point.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition status="not_decent" role="target" />
                <state img="#-smile.png">Are you sure you don't need that to protect what decency you have left?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Uh-huh. I mean, you could have just left that on. It made you less... naked... somewhat.</state>
                <state img="#-surprise.png">Oh, I thought you were just gonna leave that on. No judgment either way, just saying.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-pondering.png">A man should accessorize. It's the little things that can really pull an ensemble together.</state>
                <state img="#-cross.png">I don't accessorize as much as I used to. I had a watch, but... oh, why get into it?</state>
                <state img="#-glad.png">Timepieces, hats, masks. These things have their place in fashion, even for men. </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition status="not_decent" role="target" />
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">So basically that was a big waste of time. I don't know if you noticed, ~name~, but that wasn't exactly stepping out of your formal clothes.</state>
                <state img="#-uppity.png">And for his next trick ~name~ will pointlessly drag out his loss.</state>
                <state img="#-cross.png">Bigger fish to fry, ~name~. For real.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Actually, I don't think that was really essential to your look. You could probably go without it, unless it has sentimental value.</state>
                <state img="#-surprise.png">Well... as a elegant man, I have to honestly say that maybe your ~clothing~ ~clothing.ifPlural(weren't|wasn't)~ pulling the look together after all.</state>
                <state img="#-cross.png">It's not that your ~clothing~ ~clothing.ifPlural(weren't|wasn't)~ nice or flattering, but I'd say this ensemble passes without it.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0-8" id="6">
                <condition role="target" character="nami" stage="0" saidMarker="perona0_resp_negative1" />
                <condition role="other" character="perona" saidMarker="nami_negative1" sayingMarker="nami_negative2" />
                <state img="#-angry.png" marker="NamPer_s0_2">Wait, what was that? A demon? Or something else?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="12">
                <condition role="target" character="florina" stage="0" saidMarker="fled" />
                <state img="#-serious.png">No! Wait! Don't run! As a gentleman, it's my sacred duty to assist you in times of stress and trouble!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="68">
                <condition role="target" character="yuelia" stage="0" sayingMarker="transformation" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png">... She's cute for a butterfly.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition status="not_decent" role="target" />
                <state img="#-nice.png">Aww, your ~clothing~? There was something kind of sexy about the fact that you still had it on despite, well, you know.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Okay, so ~target~ is literally going to leave nothing to the imagination. That's fair, that's fair.</state>
                <state img="#-surprise.png">Tsk, not the ~clothing~. That look was really working for you. I mean, it's held together mostly by the excessive nudity, but still!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-vibing.png">A lady must accessorize. The right accent makes the difference between a classy ensemble and a total dud.</state>
                <state img="#-pondering.png">I can appreciate a fashion conscious lady who accessorizes. Very elegant.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Do you consider yourself fashion conscious, ~target~? Seems like your outfit was carefully put together.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="3" />
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Yshtola_GoFoKaz" />
                <state img="#-glad.png" marker="YshBo_s2_3">Well, of course as an elegant gentleman I have only the most refined tastes; however, a gentleman would never think to rush a lady when she's getting undressed.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="nami" stage="1" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="NamPer_s0_2" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="NamPer_s0_3">
                    <text>Uh... I guess it was something else? I guess that's good. I'm feeling a bit of melancholy anyway; I don't wanna work...</text>
                    <markers>
                        <marker name="Melancholy" op="+" value="1" />
                    </markers>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="13">
                <condition role="target" character="ms.fortune" stage="3" sayingMarker="Fortune_Strip_2C" />
                <state img="#-aback.png">Gah! Head! Off! Fell! What?!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="63">
                <condition role="target" character="gruntilda" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-speechless.png">W... huh? She's a... hot witch?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="turandot" sayingMarker="kaz_dont" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="Turandot_postgame_dont">
                    <text>No, it wasn't for love. Look, I wasn't even supposed to be driving the car in the first place, but I wasn't the only unintended passenger...</text>
                    <markers>
                        <marker name="Communism" op="+" value="2" />
                    </markers>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition status="not_decent" role="target" />
                <state img="#-smile.png">Not entirely necessary to have taken that off, but it was fun to watch you strip.</state>
                <state img="#-blush.png" marker="+Beguilement">Uh, yeah, still sexy, ~target~.</state>
                <state img="#-pondering.png">All I'm saying is underwear models with big bangles or necklaces is a vibe.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-glad.png">Though, no bauble like your ~clothing~ could distract from your beauty, ~target~.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Although, with a body like yours they should be having you wear things to convince people to buy them.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">You seem to me a natural beauty, ~target~. Your ensemble is really held together by you, I'm afraid.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0-8" id="67">
                <condition role="other" character="chazz" stage="0-6" />
                <condition role="target" character="dust" stage="1" sayingMarker="persist_ChazzAss" />
                <state img="#-uppity.png">I am not here. I am somewhere else... far more elegant...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition status="not_decent" role="target" />
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">Yeah... of course... because your ~clothing~ ~clothing.ifPlural(was|were)~ what we were all distracted by...</state>
                <state img="#-cross.png">So I guess you just forgot you were wearing ~clothing.ifPlural(that|those)~, right, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-surprise.png">Uh, why take off ~clothing.ifPlural(that|those)~? Or, I mean, why take of ~clothing.ifPlural(that|those)~ &lt;i&gt;now&lt;/i&gt;?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Maybe I should have brought Charles with me. Aunt Agatha will be pissed if she calls and I'm not there to answer.</state>
                <state img="#-showoff.png">I think your style is a little lacking, ~target~. Maybe I could give you some pointers. Show you how a Neo Yokian dresses.</state>
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">Yeah, I'd get rid of the ~clothing~ too. It really confuses the color story you've got going on.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_minor">
            <case stage="0-8" id="75">
                <condition role="target" character="ignatz" stage="3" sayingMarker="glassesstart" notSaidMarker="bernadettathrowstart" />
                <condition role="target" character="ignatz" sayingMarker="glassesstart" notSaidMarker="artpunstart" />
                <condition role="target" character="ignatz" sayingMarker="glassesstart" notSaidMarker="igfluttershy_hug" />
                <condition role="target" character="ignatz" sayingMarker="glassesstart" notSaidMarker="artpunstart" />
                <condition role="target" character="ignatz" sayingMarker="glassesstart" notSaidMarker="igpetra_stripglasses2" />
                <test expr="~target.costume~" cmp="!=" value="ignatz_drawn_brawn" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Man, with rims that wide you think you'd notice right when they fell off.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition status="not_decent" role="target" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">Seriously. At this point, why even bother?</state>
                <state img="#-uppity.png">Yeah, well... I'm sure it's someone's fetish.</state>
                <state img="#-glad.png">Can we get back to the fun part of this game again?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-pondering.png">I am feeling a shopping trip coming on. I see Bergdorf's in my future.</state>
                <state img="#-cross.png">See, ~target~, now that your ~clothing~ ~clothing.ifPlural(are|is)~ gone you can see how it didn't really compliment your outfit. I mean, look at you. What's changed?</state>
                <state img="#-melancholy.png">Maybe we can hurry this along. I'm feeling a bout of melancholy coming on.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0-8" id="9">
                <condition role="target" character="sakura" stage="3" sayingMarker="headless" />
                <state img="#-speechless.png" marker="Sakura_s3_2">Excuse me &lt;i&gt;wwwwhat&lt;/i&gt;?!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="70">
                <condition role="target" character="shantae" stage="1" sayingMarker="monkey" />
                <state img="#-aback.png" marker="+Communism">Wwwwwwwwwwwwhat the...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="11">
                <condition role="target" character="sakura" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="Sakura_s2_2">Interesting... choice?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition status="not_decent" role="target" />
                <state img="#-glad.png">It's not much, but it's not like there's much left anyway.</state>
                <state img="#-smile.png">Taking off your ~clothing~ now? While you're... okay, damn. Maybe that's a bit kinky.</state>
                <state img="#-pondering.png">Since you kept ~clothing.ifPlural(that|those)~ on for this long, I figured ~clothing.ifPlural(it|they)~ might be sentimental. I guess that might be kinda silly...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-laughing.png">I really dig this whole taking things off slowly deal. Feels like some kind of exotic show.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Are you teasing us or just shy, ~target~? Either way, I find myself endeared to it...</state>
                <state img="#-glad.png">I guess it wouldn't be very elegant to tear off all your clothes at once. The slow approach is so much more... sensational.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_minor">
            <case stage="0-8" id="60">
                <condition role="target" character="sayaka" stage="2" />
                <alternative>
                    <condition role="target" character="sayaka" sayingMarker="familiar_aware" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <condition role="target" character="sayaka" sayingMarker="familiar_unaware" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-vibing.png">Never fear. Kaz Kaan is a renown demon slayer. A mischievous ghost is nothing I can't deal with. They'd be hard pressed to get one past me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="sakura" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-aback.png" marker="Sakura_s3_3">Well... at least she's more than just a head?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="sakura" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-blush.png" marker="Sakura_s2_3">So, she's seen past death's thin veil, only to return this plain of ignorant mortals. Cool. Cool, cool, cool...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition status="not_decent" role="target" />
                <state img="#-nice.png" marker="+Beguilement">So, I guess you just like putting on a show, ~target~.</state>
                <state img="#-blush.png">Huh... with all your clothes that would've been pretty underwhelming, but like this... damn.</state>
                <state img="#-vibing.png">Always a pleasure watching ~target~ strip, no matter how little she's wearing or how little she's taking off.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-blush.png">Uh, I hope I'm not being too forward. I don't usually play this sort of game with people I don't know at all.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">That's not weird for me to say, right? I guess we don't really know each other all that well.</state>
                <state img="#-surprise.png">I don't particularly mean anything by that. It's just odd being here like this with attractive strangers.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_major">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">They say clothes make the man, and I really get that. A person chooses what they wear, but their body is something they're born with.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Karl Lagerfeld once said "Don't dress to kill, dress to survive." You might've taken that to heart, ~target~, and brought a few more layers.</state>
                <state img="#-glad.png">I see you're transitioning to more of a summer fashion now. </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_major">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Who would've thought we'd end up like this? I don't even get that undressed in front of my boys!</state>
                <state img="#-pondering.png">If you're nervous, maybe just pretend your in the dressing room of a department store. That's not a weird place to be in your underwear.</state>
                <state img="#-showoff.png">Come on, ~target~. Don't be shy! This is probably the least embarrassing thing you will be doing today.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_major">
            <case stage="0-8" id="64">
                <condition role="target" character="nami_szs" stage="0" sayingMarker="goodBye" />
                <state img="#-smile.png">No shame in that, I suppose.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="72">
                <condition role="target" character="emi" stage="7" />
                <state img="#-glad.png">Well, those aren't clothes strictly speaking, but I'm not gonna stop you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Dang, your ~clothing~? This is gonna be a treat!</state>
                <state img="#-smile.png">Couldn't be happier to be put at a table with ~target~ than right now.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Wait, did I remember to ask you who you were wearing?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_major">
            <case stage="0-8" id="47">
                <condition role="target" character="mari_setogaya" stage="4" sayingMarker="Mari_wings_reveal" />
                <state img="#-uppity.png">Yeah, this doesn't exactly make me trust you...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="61">
                <condition role="target" character="gwen" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-vibing.png">A gentleman doesn't kiss and tell... not that I know who I would tell.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="73">
                <condition role="target" character="emi" stage="8" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png">You don't need, like, a chair or something, do you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-nice.png">I guess now I have to ask who you're &lt;i&gt;still&lt;/i&gt; wearing.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Yeah, forget being a runway model. Time for ~target~ to make the move to being an underwear model.</state>
                <state img="#-glad.png">As an elegant gentleman, I have to try not to stare too much. Doesn't keep me from admitting I'd like to.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-8" id="54">
                <condition role="target" character="brock" />
                <state img="#-aback.png">Uh... missile? Missile? Missile! &lt;i&gt;Missile!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-vibing.png" oneShotId="116">Nothing to be ashamed of, ~target~. We're here in the spirit of admiration. </state>
                <state img="#-showoff.png" oneShotId="117">Don't be shy, ~target~. The only real thing you have to be ashamed of is being bad at cards.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png" oneShotId="118">Just like being in the lockers before field hockey. Nothing but guys with no shirts slapping each other on the ass. It's not very elegant.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png" oneShotId="119">Come on, target! Don't be shy! I'm sure you don't have anything I haven't seen in the mirror!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" />
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="BoKaz_s0_3" />
                <state img="#-melancholy.png" marker="Bobobo_s0_3Y">It would be better if he &lt;i&gt;wasn't&lt;/i&gt; a raving lunatic...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="brock" />
                <condition role="opp" character="pyrrha" />
                <state img="#-speechless.png">Next time, let's leave the heavy weaponry at home.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" />
                <state img="#-cross.png" marker="Bobobo_s0_3">Y'know, the clothes weren't really what I was talking about...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="brock" />
                <state img="#-speechless.png">This was all very ill-advised.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-glad.png" oneShotId="125" marker="Elegance += 2">I'm just saying, there's no reason to be embarrassed. It's not very elegant, but we can't all pull it off as well as I can.</state>
                <state img="#-smile.png" oneShotId="126" marker="Elegance += 2">Not too shabby, ~target~. You must be popular with the women in whatever circle you run in.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="127" marker="+Elegance">Field hockey keeps me in this shape. I wonder what keeps you in yours, ~target~.</state>
                <state img="#-glad.png" oneShotId="124" marker="+Communism">I'm too much of a fashion icon to be seen walking around in public without my shirt on, but I'm sure you could pull it off ~target~.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-8" id="51">
                <condition role="target" character="tick" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">...Yeah, that's par for the course.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="81">
                <condition role="target" character="sly_cooper" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png">You don't usually wear pants? That's... somehow not the strangest thing about you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="1">Okay, so this is the part where it gets weird between us, ~target~. Between all of us, I guess.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="2">Not what I came here to see, but I did come here to win. Nothing elegant about losing a game like this.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="3">No reason this has to be weird... except for the part where I see your dick.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="4">It's looking less like the locker room and more like the showers...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_small_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-surprise.png" oneShotId="9" marker="Melancholy += 2">Oh... well... can we just move on without me having to make a comment?</state>
                <state img="#-surprise.png" oneShotId="10" marker="Communism += 2">Is it cold in here, or something? Well, I guess I'm in here and I know it's-- you know what, nevermind.</state>
                <state img="#-melancholy.png" oneShotId="11" marker="Melancholy += 2">Any comment I make here wouldn't be very nice, and that wouldn't be  very elegant of me.</state>
                <state img="#-melancholy.png" oneShotId="12" marker="Communism += 2">An elegant gentleman, when put in this position, would probably just give you a pat on the back. Just a metaphorical one since you're... you know.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_medium_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-surprise.png" oneShotId="18" marker="Beguilement += 2">So this is how you please the ladies, or the lads. Or both.</state>
                <state img="#-surprise.png" oneShotId="19" marker="Elegance += 2">I bet you don't leave anyone disappointed at night, or day. I don't know what your availability is.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="20" marker="Elegance += 2">We're friends now, right, ~target~? So we know there's no need to compare among friends.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="17" marker="Beguilement += 2">If anybody was unsure of you before, there's no way they're not keen on you now.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_large_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-uppity.png" oneShotId="26" marker="Melancholy += 2">I mean... it's not elegant.</state>
                <state img="#-aback.png" oneShotId="27" marker="Communism += 2">Oh man, no wonder you're okay with playing strip poker!</state>
                <state img="#-surprise.png" oneShotId="28" marker="Communism += 2">So... when they measure your inseam... is there any trouble with that?</state>
                <state img="#-frustrated.png" oneShotId="25" marker="Melancholy += 2">How do you not put that in designer briefs? You wouldn't put your best friend in a cramped locker; you'd put him in a hammock!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-8" id="43">
                <condition role="target" character="mari_setogaya" saidMarker="Chubby_Form_ON" sayingMarker="Chubby_transformation" />
                <state img="#-angry.png">H-hey! No funny business, demon!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="44">
                <condition role="target" character="mari_setogaya" saidMarker="Cat_Form_ON" sayingMarker="Cat_transformation" />
                <state img="#-angry.png">Damn it! I should have known better than to trust a fucking demon! Now she's going to...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="58">
                <condition role="target" character="polly" saidMarker="UnfinishedBusiness" sayingMarker="Polly Fades Out" />
                <state img="#-speechless.png">Huh? What? For real?!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="52">
                <condition role="target" character="kora" sayingMarker="blade_power" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png">Showing her breasts and a light show. Guess it's not the first time I've seen that happen.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-pondering.png" oneShotId="33">Gotta say, ~target~, I'm glad you're as bad at cards as you are.</state>
                <state img="#-smile.png" oneShotId="34">A gentleman wouldn't make fun or stare, but in certain situations...</state>
                <state img="#-glad.png" oneShotId="35">Well, I'm excited. Is anyone else excited? You, ~player~?</state>
                <state img="#-vibing.png" oneShotId="36">Now these are the best vibes a gentleman like me could ask for.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_small_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-blush.png" oneShotId="152" marker="Melancholy += 2">~Target~ is real cute. I mean, I thought so before, but now I think... I'm shutting up.</state>
                <state img="#-nice.png" oneShotId="153" marker="Beguilement += 2">I kind of want to tease ~target~ a bit, but that wouldn't be very elegant.</state>
                <state img="#-blush.png" oneShotId="154" marker="Melancholy += 2">Man... ~target~ is so cute, I mean- ~target~ is real cute, I mean- ~target~ is...</state>
                <state img="#-nice.png" oneShotId="162" marker="Beguilement += 2">I was wondering what color your nipples would be. There's no denying ~target~ is super cute.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_medium_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8" id="45">
                <condition role="target" character="mari_setogaya" saidMarker="Chubby_transformation" sayingMarker="Chubby_transformed" />
                <state img="#-aback.png" marker="+Beguilement">Oh wow... that's uh... uuuuh...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="46">
                <condition role="target" character="mari_setogaya" saidMarker="Cat_transformation" sayingMarker="Cat_transformed" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="+Beguilement">... Turning into a cat... girl? That's uh... new.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-blush.png" oneShotId="167" marker="Beguilement += 2">There's... not really an elegant way to compliment you on your... fine bosom.</state>
                <state img="#-nice.png" oneShotId="168" marker="Elegance += 2">No matter how elegant I am, I'm not immune to these carnal charms of yours...</state>
                <state img="#-blush.png" oneShotId="169" marker="Beguilement += 2">Dang, why was I born a mage and not a poet?</state>
                <state img="#-nice.png" oneShotId="170" marker="Elegance += 2">A man's curiosity is never sated, ~target~. Now that I know what they look like, I gotta wonder about how they feel...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_large_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8" id="59">
                <condition role="target" character="polly" saidMarker="UnfinishedBusiness" sayingMarker="Polly Fades In" />
                <state img="#-cross.png">Oh, ha ha. Yeah. Hilarious. Nice tits, by the way.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="huge_breasts" role="target" />
                <state img="#-speechless.png" oneShotId="177" marker="Communism += 2">That's-- those are... what ~clothing.ifPlural(was|were)~ your ~clothing~ made of?</state>
                <state img="#-speechless.png" oneShotId="178" marker="Communism += 2">S-so... like, all your tops are custom then, yeah?</state>
                <state img="#-aback.png" oneShotId="176" marker="Beguilement += 2">Never been with a woman with such, err... not that I meant that we should get together. I mean, we could?! Am I blathering? I feel like I'm blathering!</state>
                <state img="#-blush.png" oneShotId="175" marker="Beguilement += 2">I guess this confirms what we already knew: they're huge.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-blush.png" oneShotId="183" marker="Communism += 2">Uh... so... when you get fitted, do those... require alterations be made?</state>
                <state img="#-nice.png" oneShotId="184" marker="Elegance += 2">Most models don't have breasts like those. It's kind of a shame, really.</state>
                <state img="#-blush.png" oneShotId="185" marker="Communism += 2">I would never judge a lady on the size of her breasts... but a man of elegance knows world class when he sees it.</state>
                <state img="#-nice.png" oneShotId="186" marker="Elegance += 2">Ahem, well... I forgot what I was going to say. I guess I'll need your number so I can let you know when I finally remember.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-6 8">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Melancholy&gt;=3" />
                <state img="#-smile.png" oneShotId="525" marker="Melancholy=0">
                    <text>Well... maybe the world isn't all that wack after all.</text>
                    <markers>
                        <marker name="Elegance" op="+" value="2" />
                    </markers>
                </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-8" id="41">
                <condition role="target" character="sannytess" sayingMarker="COCK" />
                <state img="#-speechless.png" marker="Communism += 2">I was... &lt;i&gt;not&lt;/i&gt; expecting that... those? Uh...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-surprise.png" oneShotId="207">Sorry again. I know there's no way to make this elegant.</state>
                <state img="#-smile.png" oneShotId="208">To gaze upon the garden gates. It's more of a privilege than I expected.</state>
                <state img="#-blush.png" oneShotId="212">Man, I don't know if I'm nervous or excited, but my heart is going haywire.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="211">Now &lt;i&gt;this&lt;/i&gt; I gotta see. Makes the risk and embarrassment all worth it, if you ask me.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8" id="56">
                <condition role="target" character="amy" sayingMarker="planar_form" />
                <test expr="~target.persistent.strange_harmonies~" cmp="&gt;=" value="55" />
                <state img="#-speechless.png">Did... did I miss something?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="42">
                <condition role="target" character="sannytess" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="+Beguilement">... Well... different isn't bad.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6 8">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Melancholy&gt;=3" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" oneShotId="523" marker="Melancholy=0">
                    <text>Somehow the bitter unfairness of the world is melting away. Beauty was the cure all along.</text>
                    <markers>
                        <marker name="Elegance" op="+" value="2" />
                    </markers>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-nice.png" oneShotId="218" marker="Beguilement += 3">Forget elegance, this is exquisite. </state>
                <state img="#-nice.png" oneShotId="217" marker="Elegance += 3">A gentleman has to keep these sort of thoughts to himself, but I could be coerced if you asked nicely.</state>
                <state img="#-nice.png" oneShotId="219" marker="Elegance += 3">For you, I'll be a gentleman, unless you have other ideas.</state>
                <state img="#-nice.png" oneShotId="220" marker="Communism += 3">Some things would be worth giving up the fame of being a bachelor for...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_lost">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="aimee" stage="1-4" />
                <state img="#-blush.png" oneShotId="518">She's not going to start shooting again... is she?</state>
                <state img="#-melancholy.png" oneShotId="519">We're all gonna die...</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="520">Give me one second to come to grips with the fact that the cold embrace of death may come on suddenly and unjustly...</state>
                <state img="#-melancholy.png" oneShotId="521">Ugh... duck and cover, I guess.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="heris" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="Heris_s0_1">Well, Ms. Heris, feel free to get comfortable. You're not at work anymore, so why not put up your coat and relax a little with us.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="estelle" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-glad.png" marker="Estelle_s0_1">My apologies, Lady Estelle. As a gentleman, I wouldn't dare impugn your honor by playing poorly on purpose, but that also puts you in a precarious position. A real quandary for a gentleman...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="kora" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="Kora_s0_1">Man, she's pretty lively. I'm not sure I'm going to be able to keep up with you, Kora.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="cynthia" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-vibing.png" marker="Cynthia_s0_1">You've quite the sense of style, Cynthia. So dark and mature, like a fresh cup of coffee. Stimulating, deep, and powerful. Such a striking and complete display of personal branding.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="kyou" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="Kyou_s0_1">Gotta admire a girl with spirit like Ms. Fujibayashi. You strike me as a sportswoman, but which sport do you play?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="yuno_uno" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="Yuno_s0_1">Seems like a strange choice to build your personal brand around Uno, but you're so sincere about it there's no arguing that it isn't working for you...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="miki_miura" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-uppity.png" marker="Miki_s0_1">Ms. Miura, are you faithfully following your academy's dress code? Your tie is loose and your shirt is untucked. Speaking of the shirt, when did you get it pressed last? Seems awfully wrinkly...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="jessie" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="Jessie_s0_1">Animal print? Nowadays? A daring choice, but you're nothing if not daring, Ms. Maye... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="fina" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="Fina_s0_1">Very interesting clothes you have, Fina. The style is very foreign to me, but is this popular where you come from?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="petra" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-glad.png" marker="Petra_s0_1">I have to say, Petra, that I'm way into your vibe. I mean, I must sound like a total herb, but the branding you've developed has such a fresh aesthetic.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="chara_dreemurr" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-melancholy.png" marker="Chara_s0_1">Man, the hot ones are always some kind of monster... well, maybe not &lt;i&gt;all&lt;/i&gt; the hot ones, but still...</state>
                <state img="#-uppity.png" marker="Chara_s0_1">She's cute, but... damn if she's not evil...</state>
                <state img="#-cross.png" marker="Chara_s0_1">Right, a demon pretending to be a beautiful woman. I'm not going to fall for that... {small}again...{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="jura" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="Jura_s0_1">So, this is space fashion? It certainly isn't understated.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="Jura_s0_1">A dress from out of this world? Well, it's rather brave by Earth standards.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="meia" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-uppity.png" marker="Meia_s0_1">Okay, be honest with me, Meia. Are spandex bodysuits really the cutting edge of fashion on your planet? Just tell me the truth! I can handle it!</state>
                <state img="#-melancholy.png" marker="Meia_s0_1">Long has man dreamed of casting off his sublunary shackles and roaming free amongst the stars, but is it worth it? Why struggle if spandex bodysuits become fashion forward?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="revy" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-glad.png" marker="Revy_s0_1">Probably a bad idea to hit on the lady packing heat, right? No matter how hot she is?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="ahri" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-serious.png" marker="Ahri_s0_1">Look, I don't want to cause any trouble, but you're not a demon are you, Ahri? There's just... something about you...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="mari_setogaya" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-cross.png" marker="MariS_s0_1">Never had to exorcise a succubus before. I'd kind of like to keep it that way, if you catch my drift.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="hu_tao" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-glad.png" marker="HuTao_s0_1">It's refreshing to meet a like-minded, young professional here. I'm something of a funerary enthusiast myself, but we don't have to discuss your work if that's distasteful.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="hu_tao" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-uppity.png" marker="HuTao_s1_1">I'll admit, I'm a bit jealous of you, Hu Tao. I wish my family business was something as respectable as yours. Honestly, exorcism is so pass.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="hu_tao" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="HuTao_s2_1">So, how do the exorcists where you come from party? Black tie galas? Poolside cocktails? Craft beers with a live tiger?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="hu_tao" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-glad.png" marker="HuTao_s3_1">So, what's the night life like back home for you, Hu Tao? What does an evening out look like for you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="hu_tao" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="HuTao_s4_1">I must say, it has been a singular pleasure getting to know you, Hu Tao.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="mari" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="MariO_s0_1">This girl seems way too put together to be in a place like this...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="mari_setogaya" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-angry.png" marker="MariS_s1_1">I've still got my eye on you, just so you know. I still don't know what you're up to, but you won't get anything past me, alright?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="turandot" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-pondering.png" marker="Turandot_s0_1">This wouldn't be my first time entertaining a foreign dignitary, but entertaining royalty is a first.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" oneShotId="5">
                <condition filter="fancy" role="target" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="+Elegance">You seem to be quite elegant yourself, ~target~. I'm sure we could learn a lot for each other.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" oneShotId="6">
                <condition filter="insane" role="target" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="+Communism">~Target~ is a little... how do I put this nicely? Vibrant? Eccentric? Disturbed?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" oneShotId="7">
                <condition filter="seductive" role="target" />
                <state img="#-glad.png" marker="+Beguilement">~Target~ seems to me to be right at home here. Nothing wrong with that!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" oneShotId="8">
                <condition filter="gloomy" role="target" />
                <state img="#-melancholy.png" marker="+Melancholy">The energy in this group feels a bit off. It's putting a bit of a damper on my vibes.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" oneShotId="9">
                <condition filter="formal_attire" role="target" />
                <state img="#-vibing.png" marker="+Elegance">It's a real shame you'll have to strip, ~target~. I find your outfit quite tasteful.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" oneShotId="10">
                <condition filter="chuunibyou" role="target" />
                <state img="#-cross.png" marker="+Communism">Maybe as ~target~ strips off their clothes we can also start peeling away this persona they've got going on...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" oneShotId="11">
                <condition filter="perverted" role="target" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="+Beguilement">Gotta figure there would be people like ~target~ here.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" oneShotId="12">
                <condition filter="mean" role="target" />
                <state img="#-cross.png" marker="+Melancholy">You get out of the world the attitude you put in, ~target~. Your karma might not turn around unless you can put out some more positive vibes.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" oneShotId="13">
                <condition filter="shut_in" role="target" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="Elegance += 2">So, ~target~ is something of a recluse? Like, full hikikomori? What brought that on? Speaking out against society? Fed up with materialism? So mysterious...</state>
                <state img="#-smile.png" marker="Communism += 2">I guess ~target~ doesn't get out much. Welcome to the rest of the world. </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_stripping">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="1" saidMarker="Kaz_TurningPoint1" />
                <state img="#-vibing.png" marker="Bobobo_s1_2">See, now you're thinking straight. Now is the time to answer that call.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="2" saidMarker="Bobobo_ItStandsForPersonalProtectiveEEEEEE1" />
                <state img="#-uppity.png" marker="Bobobo_s2_2">You do realize for that to work you'd need to be standing there in more than just your underwear like a herb? I'm guessing you don't.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="3" saidMarker="Kaz_OpenBook1" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="Bobobo_s3_2">You're going to be wearing a third pair of underwear...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="4" sayingMarker="Kaz_DeoPatchio2" />
                <state img="#-aback.png" marker="Bobobo_s4_2">Ode to who's vape pen?!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="5" saidMarker="Kaz_CrocodileTears1" />
                <state img="#-uppity.png" marker="Bobobo_s5_2">Yeah, yeah, it'll take more than fake tears to trick me this time, Bobobo. Whatever you've got planned, I'm not about to let you get away with it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="0" saidMarker="kaz_resp0_1" />
                <state img="#-glad.png" marker="Yshtola_s0_2">Lady luck has never been very kind to me, so I might need some help from a different lady if I'm going to come out on top.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="1" saidMarker="kaz_resp1_1" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="Yshtola_s1_2">Well, I guess there is that, but there aren't really any girls who know about magic and stuff like that back home. It's nice to meet one who isn't my cousin, for once.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="2" saidMarker="kaz_resp2_1" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="Yshtola_s2_2">Still, seems like you're pretty important. Must be nice to have the ear of such powerful people.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="3" saidMarker="kaz_resp3_1" />
                <state img="#-nice.png" marker="Yshtola_s3_2">A fair point, a fair point. Well, then maybe this white cat is bringing me good fortune. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="4" saidMarker="kaz_resp4_1" />
                <state img="#-pondering.png" marker="Yshtola_s4_2">And yet you're here. There must be something inside you that desires to see and be seen in turn. A curiosity about the clandestine thoughts of your fellow man.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="5" saidMarker="kaz_resp5_1" />
                <state img="#-pondering.png" marker="Yshtola_s5_2">Well, remember: Coco Chanel once said, "Dress shabbily and they remember the dress; dress impeccably and they remember the woman." Believe me, we'll have a hard time forgetting you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="7" saidMarker="kaz_resp7_1" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="Yshtola_s7_2=demons">Ah, well, what to talk about? Uh... are there demons where you come from?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="Yshtola_s7_2=fashion">Okay, topics... uh, what's the fashion scene like in Eorzea?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="Yshtola_s7_2=chocolate">Alright, so maybe you can... tell me about... I dunno. Do you like chocolate?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="fluttershy" stage="0" saidMarker="Kaz_reply1" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="Fluttershy_s0_2">Ah, a magistocrat is me! I come from a long line of mages, and they passed down to me magical abilities and naturally pink hair! Looks like that's two things we have in common!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="mikan" stage="0" saidMarker="Mikan_Kaz_nurse" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="Mikan_s0_2">So, the bandages aren't a fashion statement? You're not protesting the wackness of a materialistic society?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="kora" stage="0" saidMarker="KazKora1" />
                <state img="#-melancholy.png" marker="Kora_s0_2">
                    <text>Be my best self? That's... a lot to ask for. All this pep and pressure is making me feel a bit melancholy...</text>
                    <markers>
                        <marker name="Melancholy" op="+" value="1" />
                    </markers>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="fina" stage="0" saidMarker="FinaKazReply1" />
                <state img="#-glad.png" marker="Fina_s0_2">And how does that work out for you? Standing out?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="estelle" stage="0" saidMarker="EstelleKazReply1" />
                <state img="#-vibing.png" marker="Estelle_s0_2">
                    <text>Well said, Lady Estelle. Let me just say, you shouldn't feel bothered by my losses at all. In fact, if I don't lose a hand at all I would consider it a terrible disappointment.</text>
                    <markers>
                        <marker name="Elegance" op="+" value="1" />
                    </markers>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="cynthia" stage="0" saidMarker="KazResponse01" />
                <state img="#-glad.png" marker="Cynthia_s0_2">Well, I can't blame anyone for trying, no matter how inept. It's flattering to me just to have your attention for a moment.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="fluttershy" stage="1" saidMarker="Kaz_style_reply" />
                <state img="#-vibing.png" marker="Fluttershy_s1_2">I agree completely. Both aesthetically and metaphorically, people have always been fascinated by the butterfly. Bursting forth from its cocoon, resplendent in beautiful colors.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="petra" stage="0" saidMarker="petra_kaz_self0a" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="Petra_s0_2">Oh, my bad. I'm so wack. If you're not up on your slang, that's dope. Sorry for being a tool.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="samus_aran" stage="0" saidMarker="Kaz_resp0a" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="Samus_s0_1">Never seen a model like this one. I wonder why the owner sent it here instead of coming themselves? Doesn't seem very sporting to me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="fluttershy" stage="2" saidMarker="Kaz_SelfBraverThanMost_reply" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="Fluttershy_s2_2">Well, talk about a trial by fire! If you really want to get over your shyness, I'm here rooting for you!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="mari" stage="0" saidMarker="Kaz_Look1" />
                <state img="#-blush.png" marker="MariO_s0_2">Augh, I'm such an herb. I didn't mean to stare, you're just... I dunno, not the sort of person I was expecting to see around here?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="mari_setogaya" stage="0" saidMarker="Kaz_snobbyRichKid" />
                <state img="#-angry.png" marker="MariS_s0_2">I am not! I mean, I &lt;i&gt;am&lt;/i&gt; an exorcist and demon hunter {small}by trade{!reset}. Look, I'm just saying you shouldn't try anything funny or I'll be all over you. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="fluttershy" stage="3" saidMarker="Kaz_SelfBraverThanMost_reply" />
                <state img="#-vibing.png" marker="Fluttershy_s3_2">Really? I figured you'd have mobs of guys crawling up the walls trying to ask you out, but that's for the best. Nobody wants that much attention.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="turandot" stage="2" sayingMarker="card_dont" />
                <state img="#-uppity.png" marker="Turandot_respGame_dont">Yeah, here's something: most people don't know I lost the Grand Prix on purpose. I can't, uh, really go into &lt;i&gt;why&lt;/i&gt;, but I totally would have won if I hadn't needed to... leave.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="turandot" stage="0" saidMarker="kaz_r0" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="Turandot_s0_2">Oh, servants? Plural? Meanwhile, my impoverished ass only has just the one butler to help me dress. Looks like I'll just have to stay humble.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="mari_setogaya" stage="1" saidMarker="Kaz_SelfNotPlanningAnything" />
                <state img="#-frustrated.png" marker="MariS_s1_2">That's the issue! I'm not dumb. I know if you fuck a succubus you &lt;i&gt;die&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="1">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-aback.png">Whoa! Oh man!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-frustrated.png" marker="Bobobo_s1_2a">Elegance requires a measure of restraint, such an overzealous play is just... hey, are you listening to me?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-aback.png" marker="Bobobo_s2_2a">Gah! Nosehairs? Again?!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-melancholy.png" marker="Bobobo_s3_2a">Exactly how many more of these does he has stored up?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-aback.png" marker="Bobobo_s4_2a">Whoa! Watch where you're swinging that... what?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-cross.png" marker="Bobobo_s5_2a">Yeah, that's right. Goodbye, Don Patch. You will not be sorely missed. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="6" />
                <state img="#-nice.png" marker="Yshtola_s6_2">Oh? Taking off your panties first? That's a bold choice, Ms. Rhul. Very bold indeed.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="4">
                <condition role="target" character="aimee" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-aback.png">W-what the fuck? What? What?!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="5">
                <condition role="target" character="aimee" stage="1-4" />
                <state img="#-aback.png" oneShotId="494">Oh fuck! Oh fuck! Oh fuck!</state>
                <state img="#-aback.png" oneShotId="495">Wait, no! Not this again!</state>
                <state img="#-aback.png" oneShotId="493">This chick is so fucked up! </state>
                <state img="#-aback.png" oneShotId="496">I don't wanna die!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="heris" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-vibing.png" marker="Heris_s0_2">It would delight me to no end to see you relax. As a gentleman, I will of course do anything I can to help.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="kyou" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-glad.png" marker="Kyou_s0_2">Oh, so a renaissance woman? How about tennis? Keeping up with women's tennis is a little hobby of mine, truth be told.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="jessie" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-uppity.png" marker="Jessie_s0_2">I am a gentleman of unparalleled elegance. When I look at someone, I look &lt;i&gt;respectfully.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="ahri" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-uppity.png" marker="Ahri_s0_2">I guess I'll have to trust you. It's not like I can verify for myself without looking a lot closer or placing my hands on you...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="hu_tao" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-aback.png" marker="HuTao_s0_2">W-whoa, what the?! A demon? A ghost? I didn't notice the- I mean, uh...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="hu_tao" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-frustrated.png" marker="HuTao_s1_2">I risk my social standing {small}and sometimes my life, I guess,{!reset} for the city, but none of my peers respect me for it. They called us rat-catchers then and Nouveau riche now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="hu_tao" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-vibing.png" marker="HuTao_s2_2">Perhaps I could interest you in something more low-key: light music, a bottle of red, and enough candlelight for two? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="hu_tao" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-pondering.png" marker="HuTao_s3_2">And follow up question: how does that change if I show up with champagne and chocolate?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="hu_tao" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-glad.png" marker="HuTao_s4_2">Though, I get the feeling we could get to know each other much, much better still. I get the feeling you'd be more than just a little interested in that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="80">
                <condition role="other" character="nami_szs" stage="0" sayingMarker="goodBye" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Not the game for everyone, understandably.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_stripped">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="4" />
                <condition role="opp" character="yshtola" stage="6-10" saidMarker="BoKaz_s3_2" />
                <state img="#-smile.png" marker="Bobobo_s3_3Y1">Actually you look like you could use a few extra pairs of underwear yourself.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="4" />
                <condition role="opp" character="yshtola" stage="0-5" saidMarker="BoKaz_s3_2" />
                <state img="#-frustrated.png" marker="Bobobo_s3_3Y2">This is insane! Is this even a legal move?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="74">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="5" />
                <condition role="other" character="twisted_fate" sayingMarker="Bobobo_Broken" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Should I bet worried that my reaction hasn't been to do that too?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="2" saidMarker="Kaz_TurningPoint2" />
                <state img="#-aback.png" marker="Bobobo_s1_3">W-wait, where were you keeping that thing?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="3" saidMarker="Bobobo_ItStandsForPersonalProtectiveEEEEEE2" />
                <state img="#-aback.png" marker="Bobobo_s2_3">That's... how are... why are you... I have so many questions.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="4" saidMarker="Kaz_OpenBook2" />
                <state img="#-smile.png" marker="Bobobo_s3_3">Yeah, I'm sure it's just luck. You'll get me with your surprise next time, Bobobo.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="5" sayingMarker="Kaz_DeoPatchio3" />
                <state img="#-angry.png" marker="Bobobo_s4_3">If that thing starts vaping, I think I'm going to completely lose my fucking mind.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="6" saidMarker="Kaz_CrocodileTears2" />
                <state img="#-cross.png" marker="Bobobo_s5_3">... On second thought, feel free to cover yourself up with something ridiculous again. Somehow... this is worse.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="1" saidMarker="kaz_resp0_2" />
                <state img="#-nice.png" marker="Yshtola_s0_3">Then maybe I can help you and you can satisfy my curiosity afterward. How does that sound?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="4" saidMarker="kaz_resp3_2" />
                <state img="#-blush.png" marker="Yshtola_s3_3">Oh! W-wait! It's not , like, offensive to refer to as a "cat," is it? I swear I didn't mean anything by it!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="2" saidMarker="kaz_resp1_2" />
                <state img="#-pondering.png" marker="Yshtola_s1_3">I've always got my boys and Charles for if I feel lonely, but it's hard to talk to them about hunting demons and such. There's really only Aunt Agatha, and to her magic is all business.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="3" saidMarker="kaz_resp2_2" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="Yshtola_s2_3">
                    <text>Yeah, well, I was tasked with watching over a foreign race car driver in order to avoid an international incident. I, uh, kind of lost her.</text>
                    <markers>
                        <marker name="Communism" op="+" value="1" />
                    </markers>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="5" saidMarker="kaz_resp4_2" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="Yshtola_s4_3">"Inexperienced" would not be a word I think would describe you. You seem intelligent. Worldly. Powerful. Elegant.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="6" saidMarker="kaz_resp5_2" />
                <state img="#-nice.png" marker="Yshtola_s5_3">I'll remember your dress for the way it slid off your shoulders, and you for the way you blushed sweetly all the while. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="7" saidMarker="kaz_resp6_2" />
                <state img="#-smile.png" marker="Yshtola_s6_3">
                    <text>Careful, Y'shtola. You're making it incredibly easy to imagine your fingers curling backwards...</text>
                    <markers>
                        <marker name="Elegance" op="+" value="1" />
                    </markers>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="8" saidMarker="kaz_resp7_2" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="Yshtola_s7_3">
                    <text>Okay, well, I caught none of that. How we feeling?</text>
                    <markers>
                        <marker name="Beguilement" op="+" value="2" />
                    </markers>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="8" sayingMarker="kaz_resp7_3==chocolate" />
                <state img="#-blush.png" marker="Yshtola_s7_3">
                    <text>No, no worries. I mean, wow... that was surprisingly informative. Okay, dark chocolate for Y'shtola, got it.</text>
                    <markers>
                        <marker name="Elegance" op="+" value="2" />
                    </markers>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="3" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="BoYsh_s2_2" />
                <state img="#-serious.png" marker="BoYsh_s2_3">I don't think there are any layers here. It's just one thick sheet of insanity all the way down with you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="estelle" stage="1" saidMarker="EstelleKazReplyContinue1" />
                <state img="#-nice.png" marker="Estelle_s0_3">Well, you may not feel sorry, but whatever other feelings my stripping makes you feel you should feel free to feel them. You feel me?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="heris" stage="1" saidMarker="HerisKazGentleman" />
                <state img="#-glad.png" marker="Heris_s0_3">Just don't ask me to make tea or anything. I'm not sure I could even heat up water without my butler's help.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="kyou" stage="1" saidMarker="kyou_kaz_s02" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="Kyou_s0_3">So... less a renaissance woman and more of a savant? Color me impressed...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="kora" stage="1" saidMarker="KazKora2" />
                <state img="#-vibing.png" marker="Kora_s0_3">Mm, yes. I can do me. Elegant and refined, just how I like it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="fluttershy" stage="2" saidMarker="Kaz_resplendentButterfly_reply" />
                <state img="#-nice.png" marker="Fluttershy_s1_3">
                    <text>And if it pleases you, I will watch in breathless anticipation as your chrysalis falls away to reveal the  full extent of your beauty.</text>
                    <markers>
                        <marker name="Elegance" op="+" value="1" />
                    </markers>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="mari_setogaya" stage="1" saidMarker="Kaz_AllOverMeWouldntMind" />
                <state img="#-speechless.png" marker="MariS_s0_3">
                    <text>No! I meant-what do you, what? I have experience with- I was not, I mean I have been, I mean &lt;i&gt;what's wrong with my hair?&lt;/i&gt;</text>
                    <markers>
                        <marker name="Communism" op="+" value="1" />
                    </markers>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="fluttershy" stage="3" saidMarker="Kaz_HopeYouGetWhatYouWant" />
                <state img="#-nice.png" marker="Fluttershy_s2_3">
                    <text>Well, if I can tempt you to be braver than you thought possible, I'm sure I'd be more than satisfied.</text>
                    <markers>
                        <marker name="Elegance" op="+" value="1" />
                    </markers>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="fluttershy" stage="4" saidMarker="Kaz_alreadyQuiteEmbarrassing" />
                <state img="#-pondering.png" marker="Fluttershy_s3_3">
                    <text>Hey, you get to this point and I think it's natural to be embarrassed, but hopefully it's also... exciting.</text>
                    <markers>
                        <marker name="Elegance" op="+" value="1" />
                    </markers>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-uppity.png" marker="Bobobo_s1_3a">Fine, whatever. Not like I care if you lose anyway...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-speechless.png" marker="Bobobo_s2_3a">W-wait? What? Another-&lt;i&gt;what&lt;/i&gt;?! Maybe I shouldn't be so surprised... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="Bobobo_s3_3a">And I'm just gonna go ahead and say it: that cannot be comfortable.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-speechless.png" marker="Bobobo_s4_3a">Just when I thought things were already as weird as they could be...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="6" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="Bobobo_s5_3a">And this just makes the three pairs of underwear thing even more unbelievable.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="aimee" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-speechless.png">Well, it was nice knowing you guys. Except you, Aimee. God... damn...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="aimee" stage="2-5" />
                <state img="#-speechless.png" oneShotId="501">I'm starting to think this isn't the greatest strip join in the multiverse...</state>
                <state img="#-speechless.png" oneShotId="501">Oh... good... still alive...</state>
                <state img="#-speechless.png" oneShotId="501">I have &lt;i&gt;zero&lt;/i&gt; faith in this chick.</state>
                <state img="#-speechless.png" oneShotId="501">Is it over?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="fluttershy" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-nice.png" marker="Fluttershy_s0_3">
                    <text>"Quite familiar?" Well, that would explain how you've got me so enchanted.</text>
                    <markers>
                        <marker name="Elegance" op="+" value="1" />
                    </markers>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="mikan" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-nice.png" marker="Mikan_s0_3">If not... then hello there. Kaz Kaan. Ultimate Man of Elegance. Pleased to meet you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="hu_tao" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="HuTao_s0_3">Sort of seems like you brought your work with you, actually. I'm not usually one to mix work and play, but I respect the grind.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="hu_tao" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="HuTao_s1_3">Ah, but who wants to listen to me complain? I'm sure it would bore you to hear about banishing demons from stuck up aristocrats and their valuables. I'd much rather hear about you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="samus_aran" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-speechless.png" marker="Samus_s0_3">
                    <text>H-huh? What the? But she's-and Charles's is, huh? What? T-that's not fair!</text>
                    <markers>
                        <marker name="Communism" op="+" value="1" />
                    </markers>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="hu_tao" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-glad.png" marker="HuTao_s2_3">Evidently, you get two exorcists like us in a room together and things are bound to get magical. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="hu_tao" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-nice.png" marker="HuTao_s3_3">Actually, forget about going out. I think we could have plenty of fun locked inside.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="hu_tao" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-nice.png" marker="HuTao_s4_3">I thought you might be hard to pin down, but now I'm certain I could pin you down and get you to tell me all kinds of secrets.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-8" id="65">
                <condition role="target" character="chihiro" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png">Chihiro? Hey! Wait! You dropped your... uh, what the?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8" id="10">
                <condition role="target" character="chihiro" />
                <state img="#-blush.png">Didn't see that coming. Not many guys can rock a skirt so effectively.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8" id="79" />
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-surprise.png" oneShotId="225">Tough luck, ~target~. I mean... &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; tough luck. The pits really. </state>
                <state img="#-cross.png" oneShotId="226">From this point on, elegance is out of the question for you, ~target~.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png" oneShotId="227">Well, look who's fallen out! Quite the inelegant fall, I'll say!</state>
                <state img="#-glad.png" oneShotId="228">Cheer up, ~target~. You had to have known this was going to happen. Don't tell me you're surprised.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="234">Yeah, well, good luck with that? What do you even say in this situation? Happy hunting? </state>
                <state img="#-glad.png" oneShotId="235">I guess you've got good material all around you.</state>
                <state img="#-cross.png" oneShotId="236">Don't look at me like that. I'm not gonna give you any advice! You're on your own now.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png" oneShotId="233">You're on your own now, ~target~. Don't expect any of us to help you out!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">This goes beyond locker rooms... or at least, I hope so.</state>
                <state img="#-glad.png">Treat your pal well, ~target~. There's no pleasure without him.</state>
                <state img="#-vibing.png">Best I can do ~target~ is send positive vibes your way.</state>
                <state img="#-blush.png">It's weird, but seeing another man do that does make you think about your own...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I'd be curious to know exactly what's on ~target~'s mind, but maybe I don't have to imagine.</state>
                <state img="#-glad.png">This doesn't have to be too weird, ~target~. It does have to be a little weird, I think, but I'm not gonna freak out if I see you looking over here. I should be flattered, really.</state>
                <state img="#-vibing.png">~Target~ is putting out some powerful vibes.</state>
                <state img="#-showoff.png">Gotta make the best of it, ~target~. That's the way to get through it.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_heavy_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-glad.png">C'mon, ~target~, I can tell you're holding back. How long can you hold it off?</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">A gentleman would give some warning before cumming all of a sudden. Food for thought, ~target~.</state>
                <state img="#-glad.png">Man, ~target~, you okay over there? Just let loose if it's time for it.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">~Target~ sure is giving it his all. Maybe he forgot we're all right here.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8" id="3">
                <condition role="target" character="twisted_fate" sayingMarker="Hat_Cheat" />
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">Hiding cards in your hat? That's not even a creative way to cheat! Man, I just lost so much respect for you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="62">
                <condition role="target" character="tick" />
                <state img="#-aback.png">Is he... okay?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-surprise.png" oneShotId="43">... Who cleans this place up?</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png" oneShotId="253">I guess you could say you're done beating around the bush!</state>
                <state img="#-pondering.png" oneShotId="254">A little release tends to lift me out of melancholy... on occasion.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="255">In the end, we're all just balls of carnal desires. Ticking like time bombs until we either find release or it's given to us.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0-8" id="71">
                <condition count="0" status="not_alive" />
                <condition role="target" character="lucy" sayingMarker="loke" />
                <state img="#-cross.png">Uh... hey, ghost guy. You missed the top button on your blazer. Do you wanna get that?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-smile.png" oneShotId="260">I'm not going to lie. I'm going to enjoy this.</state>
                <state img="#-glad.png" oneShotId="261">Man, I hope my karma for this is already paid up somehow.</state>
                <state img="#-smile.png" oneShotId="265">Coming here &lt;i&gt;was&lt;/i&gt; a good idea after all. Humiliation and all.</state>
                <state img="#-glad.png" oneShotId="264">~Target~ is out? Guess that means my luck hadn't run completely out today after all.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8" id="14">
                <condition role="target" character="nami" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="Melancholy += 3">Sorrows falling like rain, washing away vain hopes and rendering us clean, but heavy. Such is the burden of cleanliness. Of godliness. Of her, the goddess, dancing in the rain...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="57">
                <condition role="target" character="bernadetta" />
                <state img="#-uppity.png">... {small}Damn. That's really cute.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="nico_robin" />
                <state img="#-pondering.png">Huh... maybe I should have Charles order a chair in the shape of a big leg. It's very... avant-garde.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-nice.png" oneShotId="271">Remember that I'm an elegant man of class, and I'm honor bound to assist any lady who asks me.</state>
                <state img="#-nice.png" oneShotId="272">It's strange, but somehow seeing this in person is more... elegant.</state>
                <state img="#-nice.png" oneShotId="273">I'll be rooting for you, ~target~. Or, anything else you want me to do...</state>
                <state img="#-nice.png" oneShotId="270">I admire your tenacity for sticking it out, but believe me when I say I'm going to enjoy admiring you now even more. </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-glad.png">This is more than I could have hoped for...</state>
                <state img="#-nice.png">What's going through your head right now, ~target~? A guy's got to wonder.</state>
                <state img="#-pondering.png">You can look over here, ~target~. Can't help it if I'm your type.</state>
                <state img="#-glad.png">~Target~ is giving me goosebumps... among other things.</state>
                <state img="#-nice.png">Is that a hand in your pants, or are you just happy to see me?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">When ~target~ walked in, I could only dream of getting an eyeful like this.</state>
                <state img="#-blush.png">Can't say for sure how ~target~ is feeling, but I know how it's making me feel.</state>
                <state img="#-showoff.png">Girls go wild for the Ichiban. That's my burden to bear.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_heavy_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-nice.png">Oh, I know that look, ~target~. Never seen it from this far away though.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Gotta wonder if ~target~ even knows we're here anymore. </state>
                <state img="#-nice.png">Don't hold back on our account, ~target~. You'll enjoy it more than we possibly could.</state>
                <state img="#-pondering.png">A girl like ~target~ making a face like that. Do wonders never cease?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8" id="48">
                <condition role="target" character="mari_setogaya" saidMarker="Chubby_transformed" sayingMarker="Chubby_End" />
                <state img="#-blush.png">There's some joke in there about masturbation burning a lot of calories that I'm too... excited to make.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="49">
                <condition role="target" character="mari_setogaya" saidMarker="Cat_transformed" sayingMarker="Cat_End" />
                <state img="#-nice.png">Okay, there's &lt;i&gt;got&lt;/i&gt; to be a pussy joke in there that I'm not thinking of right now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="76">
                <condition role="target" character="caulifla" sayingMarker="finished" />
                <state img="#-blush.png">Man, if we play again, remind me to wear sunglasses. Sucks to have to miss any part of that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-blush.png" oneShotId="284">Damn, I should've taken notes...</state>
                <state img="#-nice.png" oneShotId="285">Damn shame we have to leave it at that...</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="282">Elegant, even in the throes of pleasure.</state>
                <state img="#-nice.png" oneShotId="283">So, ~target~, got any plans after this?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate_first">
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-speechless.png">W-wait, this can't be right? I'm out first? B-but, that's not very... damn it!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate">
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-aback.png">Crap, I messed up! How could I be such an herb?</state>
                <state img="#-aback.png">What the fuck? Seriously? How did this happen?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="start_masturbating">
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-uppity.png">Time for me to leave elegance behind me... for now. The only way to get through this is to enjoy it.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="masturbating">
            <case stage="7">
                <condition role="opp" character="nico_robin" stage="5-7" sayingMarker="mast_women_scene" />
                <state img="#-nice.png" marker="nico_resp_wscene">My imagination's not so good, but if you're that curious you could walk over and embrace me and I &lt;i&gt;promise&lt;/i&gt; you'll find out.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <condition role="opp" character="nico_robin" sayingMarker="mast_touch" />
                <state img="#-showoff.png" marker="nico_resp_touch">Well, Ms. Robin, if I recall you've got hands aplenty. Why not lay a few on me and see if we can't find that spot together?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Let's be real: not much of a penalty when it feels so nice.</state>
                <state img="#-glad.png">It's liberating to be so genuine with others, to not have to hide one's pleasure.</state>
                <state img="#-showoff.png">So, what's the hookup culture like around here?</state>
                <state img="#-smile.png">The heart pounding thrill really makes it better than usual...</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">It's a perfectly healthy way to relieve stress, of course, but we all know that's just an excuse.</state>
                <state img="#-glad.png">Man, the tension of the game really sets you up for when you lose.</state>
                <state img="#-showoff.png">Kaz Kaan: prolific lover. His secret? Endurance. Take a gander.</state>
                <state img="#-smile.png">Not the sort of intimacy I usually seek out, but it's sure something.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I'd rather a hottie was helping me out, but losers can't be choosers.</state>
                <state img="#-glad.png">Once you get into the rhythm, everything else stops mattering...</state>
                <state img="#-showoff.png">What? You think this is the first time I've gotten off in front of strangers? Man, the parties I've been to...</state>
                <state img="#-smile.png">If luck were really a lady, she wouldn't have tried to hard to get me naked like this. Then again, she might've not needed to try.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7" priority="0">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Cathy" />
                <state img="#-melancholy.png" oneShotId="443">A little release can chase those blues away...</state>
                <state img="#-pondering.png" oneShotId="444">Kinda reminds me of when Cathy blew me under the table at that poker game...</state>
                <state img="#-uppity.png" oneShotId="445">Hmm... Cathy...</state>
                <state img="#-melancholy.png" oneShotId="446">To never again know the touch of an old lover, but if I close my eyes...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="447">Trying to focus on this, but I can't stop thinking of Cathy... and her tight, fit body...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7" priority="0">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Helena" />
                <state img="#-vibing.png" oneShotId="453">Oh, Helena. Our parting was all to soon... but at least I hit that.</state>
                <state img="#-pondering.png" oneShotId="454">I wonder if Helena was ever wearing panties under that hospital gown...</state>
                <state img="#-nice.png" oneShotId="455">I think the real reason Helena's hospital gown caught on in the fashion world wasn't the statement, but because the fabric was pretty thin and you could totally see people's nipples.</state>
                <state img="#-vibing.png" oneShotId="456">Helena looked great in that Chanel suite, but she looked even better out of it and all wet...</state>
                <state img="#-nice.png" oneShotId="457">Man, I can't stop thinking about Helena St. Tessero. A classy uptown girl who moans when you grab her ass.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7" priority="0">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Sailor" />
                <state img="#-cross.png" oneShotId="468">She might've been a demon, but there's no denying Sailor was vibrant and beautiful. I still can't get over how she looked at the black and white ball.</state>
                <state img="#-pondering.png" oneShotId="469">Of course, I never made it with Sailor because she was a demon, but it's okay to &lt;i&gt;fantasize&lt;/i&gt; about her, right?</state>
                <state img="#-uppity.png" oneShotId="470">A pop star of infinite elegance... kneeling before me...</state>
                <state img="#-showoff.png" oneShotId="471">I'm just gonna say it. If that evening had gone well and I didn't know Sailor was a demon, we would've totally hooked up. Southern girls are freaky, right? Just imagine...</state>
                <state img="#-cross.png" oneShotId="472">No, no, I can't be thinking of Sailor Pellegrino right now. Yeah, she was hot and smelled nice and her skin was soft...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7" priority="0">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Mila" />
                <state img="#-blush.png" oneShotId="488">I guess I never thought about it... but Mila was pretty much naked under her racing suite the entire time I was watching her. How did I not notice?</state>
                <state img="#-pondering.png" oneShotId="489">Mila was real impressed with life in Neo Yokio, so I bet she'd be blown away by a Neo Yokian lover...</state>
                <state img="#-surprise.png" oneShotId="490">Mila was... actually quite beautiful. I can picture her now. Hair black as a night sky. Ruby red lips. Eyes full of... contempt for the free market...</state>
                <state img="#-showoff.png" oneShotId="491">Too bad Mila stripped for that fisherman to escape and not me. I hope she's still crazy, wherever she went off to.</state>
                <state img="#-pondering.png" oneShotId="492">Wait... so Mila was naked in that racing suite, and then Helena was practically naked in it, and then I wore it... is that gross or kinda hot? I can't seem to keep that straight right now.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="heavy_masturbating">
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-melancholy.png">Hoo... I'm getting... close...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Ah, damn... I don't think I can...</state>
                <state img="#-blush.png">Hanging on... by a thread. It's powerful...</state>
                <state img="#-melancholy.png">Just a bit more... it'll feel so good.</state>
                <state img="#-nice.png">My spine is all tingly. Anybody else feel that?</state>
                <state img="#-vibing.png">That's the stuff...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finishing_masturbating">
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-finishing.png">Aaaah... damn...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-blush.png">Yeah... well, if I said anything in the heat of the moment, that all stays here, okay? Great...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="after_masturbating">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">When I get back, I'm going to get Charles to make me some cocoa and chicken soup. I'll catch a cold standing around like this.</state>
                <state img="#-serious.png">Remember: vanity is one of the healthiest things in the world. This is, above all, a game about vanity.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="290">Okay, so obviously I have some unresolved romantic issues. That's hardly news to me, I guess.</state>
                <state img="#-vibing.png">Endorphins flowing, no need to worry about playing anymore. Life is good.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">There must be some place like this in Neo Yokio. I mean, if the Tiger Bar exists surely this wouldn't be all that weird comparatively.</state>
                <state img="#-melancholy.png">Ah, mental clarity. The one downside to release...</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Guess I didn't consider how long this whole thing might actually take.</state>
                <state img="#-uppity.png" oneShotId="553">Of course, no Charles here. Just when I need him too.</state>
                <state img="#-glad.png">I am a bit curious to see how this whole thing plays out. Morbidly curious.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Maybe this game is best played with strangers. In my experience, playing a game this raunchy with friends really makes casual conversation awkward for a little while.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_victory">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-showoff.png">All in a day's work for Kaz Kaan! It's nothing a gentleman of my caliber couldn't do!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_defeat">
            <case stage="8">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-toblerone.png" collectible="big_toblerone">Congratulations, ~player~! It's not much, but I got you a giant Toblerone!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-blush.png">Well, that was embarrassing. Whether it was luck or skill, you're the most elegant one here today.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

    </behaviour>
</opponent>
