<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<collectibles>
    <collectible id="allagan_tomestone_2" img="opponents/yshtola/op-rewardaar.png" thumbnail="opponents/yshtola/op-tomestone1.png">
        <title>Allagan Tomestone of Courtship</title>
        <subtitle>A mysterious piece of ancient technology that houses a pictograph.</subtitle>
        <text>The Allagan Empire may be long gone, but they left behind their technology. These things range from small data repositories to giant war machina. This one appears to have an image of Y'shtola loaded onto it, but it's not likely the Allagans are responsible for that.</text>
        <unlock>Finish a game with Y'shtola.</unlock>
        <hide-details>true</hide-details>
    </collectible>
    <collectible id="allagan_tomestone_1" img="opponents/yshtola/op-reward.png" thumbnail="opponents/yshtola/op-tomestone2.png">
        <title>Allagan Tomestone of Tumescence</title>
        <subtitle>A mysterious piece of ancient technology that houses a pictograph.</subtitle>
        <text>The Allagan Empire may be long gone, but they left behind their technology. Sometimes it is problematic, but other times it is very useful. This one appears to have an image loaded into it, but not one the Allagan's could have possibly generated themselves...</text>
        <unlock>Wtiness Y'shtola's Limit Break climax during a game.</unlock>
        <hide-details>true</hide-details>
    </collectible>
    <collectible id="allagan_tomestone_3" img="opponents/yshtola/op-rewardsecond.png" thumbnail="opponents/yshtola/op-tomestone5.png">
        <title>Allagan Tomestone of Vasodilation</title>
        <subtitle>A mysterious piece of ancient technology that houses a pictograph.</subtitle>
        <text>The Allagan Empire may be long gone, but they left behind their technology. The Allagans thrived in the Third Astral Era, but after internal turmoil their society was all but buried by an earthquake. This device is a small piece that managed to survive a long time, but the picture inside seems more recent.</text>
        <unlock>Win a game against Y'shtola seven times.</unlock>
        <hide-details>true</hide-details>
        <counter>7</counter>
    </collectible>
    <collectible id="seasonal_tomestone_v" img="opponents/yshtola/op-rewardvday.png" thumbnail="opponents/yshtola/op-tomestone3.png">
        <title>Seasonal Tomestone of Paramour</title>
        <subtitle>A festive piece of ancient technology that houses a pictograph.</subtitle>
        <text>A curious tomestone of unknown origins. It smells curiously of chocolate and roses. There appears to be an image loaded onto it to help you celebrate a special occasion.</text>
        <unlock>Finish a game with Y'shtola in her Valentine's Costume.</unlock>
        <hidden>true</hidden>
        <hide-details>true</hide-details>
    </collectible>
    <collectible id="seasonal_tomestone_e" img="opponents/yshtola/op-rewardeaster.png" thumbnail="opponents/yshtola/op-tomestone6.png">
        <title>Seasonal Tomestone of Oology</title>
        <subtitle>A festive piece of ancient technology that houses a pictograph.</subtitle>
        <text>A curious tomestone of unknown origins. It was inside of an egg you found. There appears to be an image loaded onto it to help you celebrate a special occasion.</text>
        <unlock>Finish a game with Y'shtola in her Easter Costume.</unlock>
        <hidden>true</hidden>
        <hide-details>true</hide-details>
    </collectible>
    <collectible id="seasonal_tomestone_h" img="opponents/yshtola/op-rewardhalloween.png" thumbnail="opponents/yshtola/op-tomestone4.png">
        <title>Seasonal Tomestone of Coruscation</title>
        <subtitle>A festive piece of ancient technology that houses a pictograph.</subtitle>
        <text>A curious tomestone of unknown origins. You can feel it thrumming with forbidden magic. There appears to be an image loaded onto it to help you celebrate a special occasion.</text>
        <unlock>Finish a game with Y'shtola in her Halloween Costume.</unlock>
        <hidden>true</hidden>
        <hide-details>true</hide-details>
    </collectible>
</collectibles>
