<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>

<!--This file was machine generated using the Character Editor v6.7.4 at 7:56:42 PM on April 28, 2022. Do not edit this file directly unless you know what you're doing.-->
<opponent>
    <version>v6.7.4</version>
    <first>Fernando</first>
    <last />
    <label>Fernando</label>
    <gender>male</gender>
    <size>large</size>
    <timer>60</timer>
    <intelligence>best</intelligence>



    <wardrobe>
        <clothing name="shorts" generic="shorts" position="lower" type="major" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="shirt" generic="shirt" position="upper" type="major" />
    </wardrobe>


    <behaviour>
        <trigger id="selected">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Hello, my sultry compatriots. What lusty trials shall we undertake this fine day?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Fernando... has arrived.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Is anyone here feeling... sexual?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_start">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-menace1.png">Though my sticky secretions come at no price, for just some small change I'll be yours for the night.</state>
                <state img="#-menace2.png">In games of lust, know this score: none can best a greasy manwhore.</state>
                <state img="#-menace3.png">Now then, who shall be my companion this evening?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="swap_cards">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-calm.png">These do not take my fancy.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">What sort of whore is bad at cards, I ask you?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I am compelled to make only one move.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Oh. Yes. Cards. Curious little slips of paper stock.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I do not play games, unless I am playing a game.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="hand">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <condition role="other" character="scm" stage="0-8" sayingMarker="scm_fernando" />
                <state img="#-bored.png" marker="scm_respQ_1">My lawyers say I no longer have to answer that question.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-seduce1.png">What awaits me? Pleasure or pain?</state>
                <state img="#-seduce2.png">Though your chances with cards is always slim, with a few dollars I shall heed your every whim.</state>
                <state img="#-seduce3.png">I urge you now to take a chance. Not with cards, but a manwhore in your pants.</state>
                <state img="#-seduce1.png">How does the anticipation leave you? Sweaty? Me too.</state>
                <state img="#-seduce2.png">The way you hold your hands is so very sublime, but witness what I can do with mine.</state>
                <state img="#-seduce3.png">Soon the cornucopia of our yearning nethers will unfurl into a feast of sticky secretions.</state>
                <state img="#-notseduce.png">Mmm, yoghurt.</state>
                <state img="#-seduce1.png">Let your eyes feast for free, but other hungers must exact a fee.</state>
                <state img="#-seduce2.png">We've all got a little manwhore in us.</state>
                <state img="#-seduce3.png">Why so tense? You must relax. Would it help if I ate your ass?</state>
                <state img="#-notseduce.png">Dairy good. Bone is strong.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="1">Just a little side-note, but if any of you need some cheap meds, I know a guy. The guy is me.</state>
                <state img="#-seduce1.png">Am I as nimble as a mountain goat? Hm, ha ha. Could anyone be so majestic?</state>
                <state img="#-seduce2.png">Yes. I can feel the love. So strong. So... irresponsible with its bodily fluids.</state>
                <state img="#-seduce3.png">Is my innuendo too subtle, or would you like it even &lt;i&gt;subtler&lt;/i&gt;?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="jura" sayingMarker="fernando0" />
                <state img="#-menace1.png" marker="jura_resp0_1">You fear that which you don't understand. Let my moans of perverse anguish wash over you and free your soul.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="meia" sayingMarker="fernando0" />
                <state img="#-menace2.png" marker="meia_resp0_1">But I still have so much to teach you. Have you ever heard the potent song of a manwhore such as I?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="revy" sayingMarker="fernando0" />
                <state img="#-menace3.png" marker="revy_resp0_1">Despite your rather hurtful words, I sense you too will perform absolutely sinful acts for the right price. My cries shall pry the truth from your supple lips.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="death" />
                <state img="#-notseduce.png" marker="death_resp0_1">I have not yet begun to stink.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="SolicitorCont" />
                <state img="#-solicitation.png" marker="Whoring1">Ah, my sexually curious interloper. What say you? Pass Fernando your tender, and he will treat you tender.</state>
                <state img="#-solicitation.png" marker="Whoring1">You have returned, my voyeuristic turtledove. For just a modest fee, Fernando will pleasure you for all to see.</state>
                <state img="#-solicitation.png" marker="Whoring1">You're back, my perverse admirer. Does Fernando's offer of untold pleasures entice you? Will you witness, nay, &lt;i&gt;experience&lt;/i&gt; me? It's, like, super cheap.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-seduce3.png">Oh my. You have successfully disarmed me. Or maybe, just maybe, you've actually armed me. Let's see if you can withstand my lustful moans.</state>
                <state img="#-seduce2.png">Yes, that's it. Make me the object of your sick lust. Can you contain your passions? What if I were to moan sensuously for you?</state>
                <state img="#-seduce1.png">You're well on your way to making Fernando your plaything. If you're not enticed to give me your money, perhaps a little moaning will change that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-seduce3.png">You still have your senses, I see. The only remedy for this is more musk and more moaaaaning.</state>
                <state img="#-seduce2.png">Why do you still struggle? Don't you want to give into pleasure? Come, let me drown you in my odor and sweet, sweet moans.</state>
                <state img="#-seduce1.png">I have yet to truly begin my seduction. If you dare to fully expose me, I assure you the stink of my musk will entrap you. Now, hear me moan.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripping">
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Whoring1" />
                <state img="#-stripnotalone.png" marker="Whoring2">Yes! With just a few measly dollars, our contract is sealed! Let the walls of pleasure come crumbling down! Let loose the flood of sweet, sweet sweat and other delectable emissions.</state>
                <state img="#-stripnotalone.png" marker="Whoring2">Let it be! Give in to your base desires! Let our flesh mingle like the tense coils of the lusty octopus! We shall be like two octopi! Lusty and flailing with tendrils... of passion!</state>
                <state img="#-stripnotalone.png" marker="Whoring2">Come my dear! Let me trap you in the cellar of my girthy ligaments. Let me lock you in the meat locker of my meaty meat. Pay me to fuck you... please.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-stripalone.png">&lt;i&gt;Hooooooh oooh ooooooooh oohoo oohoooooh...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-stripalone.png">&lt;i&gt;Hooooooh zoooooh ooooh oooooooh woooh...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-stripalone.png">&lt;i&gt;Hooooooh wooooooh hoooh woooh hoooooh...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-stripalone.png">&lt;i&gt;Hooooooh oh oh ooooh hoooh woooooh...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-stripalone.png">&lt;i&gt;Hooooooh oooooooh oooooh oooooh ooooooh...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-stripalone.png">&lt;i&gt;Hooooooh zoh wooooh woooh oooooh oooh hoooh...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-stripalone.png">&lt;i&gt;Hooooooh wooooh zooooooooooooooooooh hooooh ooooooh...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-stripalone.png">&lt;i&gt;Hooooooh oooooh... aaaaooooh ooooooh hoooh...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-stripalone.png">&lt;i&gt;Hooooooh noooooooh hoooh oooooh wooooooh...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-stripnotalone.png" marker="Solicitor">&lt;i&gt;Hooooooh oh woooh oh wooooh oooh oooooooooh zooooooooooooooh...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-stripalone.png">&lt;i&gt;Uuuuuuuuh ooooh uooooooh ooooh...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-stripalone.png">&lt;i&gt; Zooooooooooh... ooooooh.... oooooh... ooh... oh...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-stripalone.png">&lt;i&gt;Woooooo hooooo uooooh wuooooooooh...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-stripalone.png">&lt;i&gt;Huuuuuuuuuoooh huuuuh huuuuoooh ooooh uuuh...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-stripalone.png">&lt;i&gt;Wuuuuuuooooh ooooh oooh uuuuuuuooooh...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripped">
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Solicitor" />
                <state img="#-curious.png" marker="SolicitorCont">Seems like my moaning drew the attention of a lusty bystander. Just my type too: erogenous and flush with cash.</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png" marker="SolicitorCont">Did you see that? My moans drew in a potential customer from outside the arena. She seemed sturdy of bosom and heavy of purse, didn't she?</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png" marker="SolicitorCont">Oh my, seems a sweet dove has heard my sensuous call. I can tell she will open wide her wallet so that I might open wide her moist lips.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Whoring2" />
                <state img="#-solicitation.png" marker="Whoring3">Now is the summer of our- wait, a credit card? Uh, sorry, cash only. It's not a tax thing I just don't believe in plastic money... or chastity belts.</state>
                <state img="#-solicitation.png" marker="Whoring3">We will be as two sex- wait, a credit card? I don't have a card reader up my ass, so unless you get some cash you won't know what's actually up my ass.</state>
                <state img="#-solicitation.png" marker="Whoring3">Let the rough slapping of our- wait, a credit card? I, uh, only take cash. All the places I shop only take cash too, so it's just convenient. Seek ye out an ATM.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-seduce1.png">Still not completely bewitched by me, I see. No matter. Without my shirt, you will soon fall prey to my powerful musk.</state>
                <state img="#-seduce2.png">So, you withstood the erogenous waves of my moans. Impressive, but can you hold back when assailed with my natural musk?</state>
                <state img="#-seduce3.png">Still reeling from the vibrations of my passionate moans? I've left you perfectly vulnerable to my natural musk. Breathe in and drink deep...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-menace1.png">Do you feel it now? The desire to jump upon me? Why not give in? It costs less than a cup of coffee.</state>
                <state img="#-menace2.png">Now, run to me! Leap upon my body and have your way with it! As long as I get payment up front. Learned that lesson a long time ago.</state>
                <state img="#-menace3.png">Do you hear the sweet sound of my moans? Smell the dank dampness of my musk? Well, soon you will be rocked by the thrusting of my well trained hips.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="tie">
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Whoring5" />
                <state img="#-menace1.png">&lt;i&gt;Ooooh ooooooh waaaooooh ooooooooh ooooh...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-onetear.png">&lt;i&gt;Ooooh ooooooh waaaooooh ooooooooh ooooh...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-seduce1.png">A pittance? You tease.</state>
                <state img="#-moan1.png">Oh, ~target~ toys with our longing. How cruel. What pleasure! &lt;i&gt;Ooooooh wooooooh aaaoooh  uuuuoh...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-seduce2.png">The pain of withheld pleasure only brings more pleasure...</state>
                <state img="#-moan2.png">Not your ~clothing~! &lt;i&gt;Wooooooh zoooooh oooh aoooh wuuuuoooh...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-seduce3.png">Why not keep the ~clothing~ on during sex? You may think it unconventinal, but a manwhore delights in a challenge.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-menace1.png">A mere appetizer. You have whetted our appetite for your body, ~target~. We have received your lust.</state>
                <state img="#-notseduce.png">More.</state>
                <state img="#-menace2.png">By taking off so little, you have proven just how much of a slut you really are. What a filthy, pestilent sex crazed man you are.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">I must say, though, that time is money, so maybe we could limit the foreplay just a little bit...</state>
                <state img="#-menace3.png">We need no trinkets where we are headed, ~target~. Let us go, to the shores of tingling ecstasy.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-seduce1.png">These little things are a sure sign of wealth. I like a woman of means.</state>
                <state img="#-moan1.png">&lt;i&gt;Wooooh hooooh uuuaaooooooh.&lt;/i&gt; Sorry, this display of depraved reluctance drove me to moaning...</state>
                <state img="#-seduce2.png">Is there something you'd like Fernando to do with your ~clothing~?</state>
                <state img="#-moan2.png">Allow me to help make your display more sexual. &lt;i&gt;Uuuuuooooooh wooooooh zoooouuuuoooh...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-seduce3.png">Do you give me your ~clothing~ in exchange for my services? I can barter. I can barter hard...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-menace1.png">You serve us the deviled eggs of sexual foreplay. Bring forth the Denver omelet of your unbridled perversion.</state>
                <state img="#-notseduce.png">I lust.</state>
                <state img="#-menace2.png">This conservative display has only served to arouse me. Your message has been received, ~target~, but payment must still be levied.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">Oh, so you're not about to pay me. Got my hopes up for a moment there.</state>
                <state img="#-menace3.png">It is very important to remove any items that might get caught in my beard before initiating intercourse with me. Good thinking, ~target~.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-menace1.png">Do you dare, ~target~? Could you be so brazen? Could you be a manwhore too?</state>
                <state img="#-moan1.png">Your power is unbelievable, ~target~. I can only counter with my moaning. &lt;i&gt;Mmmoooooh ooooh uuoooaaoooh...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-menace2.png">You lusty fiend. You would execute the forbidden arts? Do not make me stop you.</state>
                <state img="#-moan2.png">Such lust. Such perversion. &lt;i&gt;Aaaooooooh uuuuuunnh haaaauuuuhn oooooouuuuh...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-menace3.png">He's mad! He's been driven crazy by his own lust!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_minor">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-curious.png">Oh, wait, this is a perfectly normal way to strip. Totally misread that. My bad.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Or maybe he's just stripping normally... yes, that appears to be the case.</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">Oh, ha ha! I totally misunderstood what you were doing ~target~. That was a close call.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Is that just your ~clothing~? Whoops, I thought you were doing something else. I apologize for going a bit crazy there.</state>
                <state img="#-notseduce.png">Wait what?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-menace1.png">She's been overtaken by the lusty spirit of the lobster. I must use the forbidden octopus stance to combat her lusty attack!</state>
                <state img="#-moan1.png">Careful! Do not look directly at ~target~! I will protect us with my moans! &lt;i&gt;Zooooh oooh uuuuuoooh wooooaah...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-menace2.png">Quick, everyone! Assume your mating stance and prepare for battle! ~Target~ means to subdue us all!</state>
                <state img="#-moan2.png">This lusty power! It's too much for mortals! I must use a special moan to save us all! &lt;i&gt;Oooooh ooooooooooh oooh oooooh oooooh....&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-menace3.png">The rest of you may want to stand back. Only the world's greatest manwhore could possible contend with the perversion ~target~ is about to unleash upon us.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_minor">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-curious.png">Wait, ha ha! She's just taking off her ~clothing~. That was almost very bad.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Actually, I guess there's actually no threat. ~Target~'s depravity is actually fairly average, at least from my experience.</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">Sorry, ~target~, I guess in a brief moment of delirium I mistook you for a wicked sexual she-beast. Oops.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Oh, silly me. She's just stripping normally. Apologies. I have seen some things.</state>
                <state img="#-notseduce.png">The danger has passed.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_major">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-bored.png">You are running out of places to hold your money. How will you pay Fernando?</state>
                <state img="#-menace1.png">Let me see what I will be pleasuring.</state>
                <state img="#-menace2.png">Unveil your sweaty flesh.</state>
                <state img="#-menace3.png">Yes. Reveal yourself to me. I do not bite... unless!</state>
                <state img="#-approval.png">Alright. That's how a manwhore does it!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_major">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-seduce1.png">Oh, darling ~target~. You should not have.</state>
                <state img="#-seduce2.png">~Target~ is ready for Fernando. I can tell.</state>
                <state img="#-seduce3.png">You cannot hide from Fernando. I have already discerned every curve of your body.</state>
                <state img="#-onetear.png">Yes. Beautiful. I dub thee a proper whore.</state>
                <state img="#-notseduce.png">Ery noice.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_major">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-bored.png">I am beginning to think ~target~ is not going to pay me to do &lt;i&gt;anything.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-menace1.png">Mm. Yes. Take off your ~clothing~, but do it slowly.</state>
                <state img="#-menace2.png">I would delight to view your glistening skin.</state>
                <state img="#-menace3.png">No piece of clothing can stop our love, ~target~. Not even your ~clothing~.</state>
                <state img="#-approval.png">Personally, I am having a fantastic time!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_major">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-seduce1.png">Why hide these treasures? This is how they should be viewed at all times.</state>
                <state img="#-seduce2.png">This bit of flesh could be pleasured by a manwhore of my caliber. Does this pique your curiosity?</state>
                <state img="#-seduce3.png">I can work with this. Oh yes, I can work with this.</state>
                <state img="#-onetear.png">Ah, I knew she was beautiful, but to see it unfurl... I am so moved.</state>
                <state img="#-notseduce.png">Toit.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-curious.png" oneShotId="173">Do not feel ashamed of your body. Whores come in all shapes and sizes. There are such varying tastes out there. Of course, I suit all tastes.</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">Yes. Let us inspect your nipples.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">Yes, bare yourself, but do not forget who the greatest manwhore is.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">Hm, my curiosity has waned. My keen manwhore senses have discerned exactly what sort of chest you have. Still, I must pay it the appropriate homage.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-approval.png" oneShotId="106">Sweet bod, bro.</state>
                <state img="#-approval.png" oneShotId="107">What a beach bod! A nudist beach bod!</state>
                <state img="#-onetear.png" oneShotId="108">Yes. It's beautiful. Embrace me now.</state>
                <state img="#-onetear.png" oneShotId="109">Though a manwhore that I be, your supple chest may embrace me once for free.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-menace1.png">Free your beast. </state>
                <state img="#-menace2.png">Let us see it. The monster that lives in your shorts.</state>
                <state img="#-menace1.png">What lusty beast lumbers this way?</state>
                <state img="#-menace3.png">I can feel the approach of a ponderous and throbbing creature.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_small_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-notseduce.png">Dick.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_medium_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-notseduce.png">Dick.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_large_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-notseduce.png">Dick.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-4" priority="1">
                <state img="#-seduce1.png" oneShotId="101">The world could use more manwhores like you.</state>
                <state img="#-seduce3.png" oneShotId="98">Oh, is that for me? I'd be more than happy to assist, if you could provide the funding.</state>
                <state img="#-seduce2.png" oneShotId="99">Oh dear, ~target~. Whatever shall we do about your unfurling lust?</state>
                <state img="#-seduce3.png" oneShotId="100">I'm so flattered, ~target~, but you still have to buy a ticket to ride the goat.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-curious.png" oneShotId="90">Yes, the breast. The fountain from which the life nourishing milk springs forth. And from such milk, delicious yoghurt can be made.</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png" oneShotId="91">Oh, bearing your chest? How very depraved of you. Trust me. I'm an expert in depravity.</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png" oneShotId="92">Ah. Yes. The boobs.</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png" oneShotId="93">Mmm, delightful. To savor the goodly sight of your burgeoning mammary glands.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-moan1.png" oneShotId="71">Your blossoming joy mounds have inspired me to poetry. Allow me to sing: &lt;i&gt;oooooh uuuooaooh  hoooooh zoooooh oooh...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-moan2.png" oneShotId="70">Such glorious nipples you have. I shall moan in their honor. &lt;i&gt;Wooooooah aaaauuuh ooooh hoooooh...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-moan1.png" oneShotId="84">Oh, this tender flesh. Like the supple folds of a walrus. I must moan a song in celebration. &lt;i&gt;Hoooooooh waaaaooooh ooooooh...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-moan2.png" oneShotId="85">Such beauty. I am in ecstasy. Unrelated, I shall now moan. &lt;i&gt;Zoooooooh oooooh wooooh oooh ooh oooooooh...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-seduce1.png" oneShotId="63">Will you unveil your... private cove of human pleasures?</state>
                <state img="#-seduce2.png" oneShotId="64">Will you show us your... secret moisture garden entrance?</state>
                <state img="#-seduce3.png" oneShotId="65">Will you reveal your... glistening lust chasm?</state>
                <state img="#-seduce1.png">Will you uncover your... beckoning sex pit?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-4" id="1">
                <condition role="target" character="sannytess" />
                <state img="#-curious.png">Ah, yes, the penis. I know it well.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-curious.png">Ah, yes. The vagina. I know it well.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_lost">
            <case stage="0-2 4" oneShotId="2">
                <condition filter="robot" role="target" />
                <state img="#-curious.png" oneShotId="191">Hm. Yes. I could seduce this robot.</state>
                <state img="#-onetear.png" oneShotId="202">I will teach this robot to love. It will bring peace to the world.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="213">Hmm, a sex robot. Truly, we live in a blessed time.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2 4">
                <condition filter="slutty" role="target" />
                <state img="#-seduce1.png" oneShotId="194">~Target~, your lust is particularly palpable. What say you? Does this loss entice you to employ Fernando?</state>
                <state img="#-seduce2.png" oneShotId="195">You want me, ~target~. It is clear to see. Do not hold back.</state>
                <state img="#-seduce3.png" oneShotId="193">Are you seduced now, ~target~? You seem very amenable to my swarthy charms.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2 4">
                <condition role="opp" character="magma_grunt" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-moan1.png" marker="Magma_s0_1">You might be a Magma Grunt, but I could make you Magma Moan &lt;i&gt;hooooh ooooouuuh oooh uuuuh oooooonh...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2 4">
                <condition role="opp" character="wikipe-tan" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-approval.png" marker="Wiki_s0_1">Hey, I've seen your website! I have a website too! You should check it out!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2 4">
                <condition role="opp" character="sex_toilet" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-menace3.png">Something perverse is afoot. What manner of manwhore technique is this?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2 4">
                <condition role="opp" character="ae86" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-menace2.png">If I do nothing else, I must seduce this car. Truly, a task worthy of a manwhore.</state>
                <state img="#-menace3.png">Can a manwhore seduce a car? No. At least, none except the world's greatest manwhore!</state>
                <state img="#-menace1.png">Must I... get into this car... sexually?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2 4">
                <condition role="opp" character="megamix" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-seduce1.png" marker="Mix_s0_1">Such an odorous monstrosity could only been born in deep in the labs of Pleasure Island. Have you come to destroy me, or seduce me?</state>
                <state img="#-seduce3.png" marker="Mix_s0_1">Some experiment freed from the depths of Pleasure Island? Is it here to destroy me or is it here to be seduced by me?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2 4" oneShotId="3">
                <condition filter="catfolk" role="opp" />
                <state img="#-curious.png" oneShotId="217">I am in awe of the wise cat people for both their combat prowess and their sexual deviancy.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2 4" oneShotId="4">
                <condition filter="innocent" role="opp" />
                <state img="#-seduce1.png" oneShotId="218">There is much I could teach you, ~target~. You've much to learn, and I've so much to give.</state>
                <state img="#-moan1.png">Your mind may not yet be prepared, ~target~. This special moan will awaken your libido. &lt;i&gt;Ooooh woooh ooooh uuuoooh ooooh...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state>
                    <alt-img stage="0-2 4">#-notseduce.png</alt-img>
                    <alt-img stage="3">#-moan1.png</alt-img>
                    <text>Tonight. You.</text>
                </state>
                <state img="#-menace3.png">Put your sexual goods on display. Fernando is not the only whore today.</state>
                <state img="#-menace2.png">The fruits of our labor, you shall bear. I'll see it all, every last hair.</state>
                <state img="#-menace1.png">Your sensual display has me wired. I hope mine will find me hired.</state>
                <state img="#-menace3.png">What do you know of carnal treasures? Does my trained hand need to teach you such pleasures?</state>
                <state img="#-menace2.png">The pain of losing hits you like a singing whip, but soon you come to pleasure's grip.</state>
                <state img="#-menace1.png">Do not fear my lusty calls. Close your eyes and imagine balls.</state>
                <state img="#-menace3.png">Your climax moment grows nearer still. Soon you'll need me to give you your fill.</state>
                <state img="#-menace2.png">Your luck condemns you to do nothing but watch, but Fernando can heal an aching crotch.</state>
                <state img="#-menace1.png">We shall hear your lusty cries. Your pleasurable fluids shall splash our eyes.</state>
                <state img="#-menace3.png">I could be your whore tonight. One small payment makes it right.</state>
                <state img="#-menace2.png">The crabs are gone. My junk is clean. Illicit drugs keep me lean.</state>
                <state img="#-menace1.png">When lady luck has left you dry, Fernando brings moisture to your thighs.</state>
                <state>
                    <alt-img stage="0-2 4">#-notseduce.png</alt-img>
                    <alt-img stage="3">#-moan1.png</alt-img>
                    <text>Hm.</text>
                </state>
                <state img="#-onetear.png">What a tragedy, ~target~. My throbbing heart weeps sensual tears of lust for you.</state>
                <state img="#-menace3.png">Walrus. Goat. Greasy beard. Come tonight, we shall get weird.</state>
                <state img="#-menace2.png">If you lack a lover's touch, Fernando's services can provide this much.</state>
                <state img="#-menace1.png">Lose the game to your desire. From wet ministrations, you shall tire.</state>
                <state img="#-menace3.png">For just a buck, you could use my rear. That will help me buy a new spear.</state>
                <state img="#-menace2.png">If our tongues would intertwine, then your hard tender must be mine.</state>
                <state img="#-menace1.png">Lusty feelings shall soon explode as you step closer to your glistening load.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_stripped">
            <case stage="0-2 4">
                <condition role="opp" character="bobobo" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-approval.png">Yes. Very whory.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2 4" oneShotId="1">
                <test expr="~clothing.generic~" value="shoes" />
                <state img="#-bored.png">I do not believe in footwear. I refuse to elaborate on this.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-2 4">
                <condition filter="no_genitals" role="target" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">... I can work with this.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-menace1.png" oneShotId="23">Time to take your perversion in your own hands. Feel it's weight. It's girth. It's testicles. Check for lumps. Stay healthy. Eat yoghurt. Hmm, your talk of yoghurt entices me.</state>
                <state img="#-menace2.png" oneShotId="24">Will you grab your pleasure snake by the throat and throttle it or wind your meaty hands around it and gently caress the life from it?</state>
                <state img="#-menace3.png" oneShotId="25">Now is not the time for regrets, ~target~. Close your eyes and imagine a moist chasm. Now open them, and notice Fernando.</state>
                <state img="#-menace3.png" oneShotId="26">Will the frustration of your loss translate into a grotesque display of human depravity? I think yes.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-seduce1.png" oneShotId="15">Slide a dollar to me, and I can take care of your masturbatory needs. And anything else that comes up. And at the two dollar level...</state>
                <state img="#-seduce2.png" oneShotId="16">To grind one's own pleasure sausage is cold and lonely. Why not buy my services so that the chorus of our moans can atomize the foundation of this place?</state>
                <state img="#-seduce3.png" oneShotId="17">Is Fernando not your type, ~target~? Your lusty gaze pierces right through me. If you want me, you know what you must do...</state>
                <state img="#-seduce3.png" oneShotId="18">It is admirable to make the most of your predicament, ~target~, but you know I could make so much more of it.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-seduce1.png">Do your coquettish hands travel the plains of your turgid manhood? Why travel alone? Fernando is here, for a small fee.</state>
                <state img="#-seduce2.png">Need assistance? Fernando is right here. Will you accept the charges? Yes, I'll hold.</state>
                <state img="#-seduce3.png">My natural musk is a powerful aphrodisiac. ~Target~, you may feel urges you have never even once considered.</state>
                <state img="#-menace1.png">The might of my wafting musk could drive you to the absolute pinnacle of human pleasure. Be warned, and be careful.</state>
                <state img="#-menace2.png">~Target~'s lusty cries have touched my soul. Such stimulation would send my throbbing arousal far enough to touch his soul.</state>
                <state img="#-menace3.png">Let your lust overcome you, ~target~. Money is temporary. The mark of Fernando is permanent.</state>
                <state img="#-notseduce.png">Smells of healthy goat in this place.</state>
                <state img="#-seduce1.png">Cum.</state>
                <state img="#-seduce2.png">Now's the time to unleash the fragrant sea beasts of your pleasure.</state>
                <state img="#-seduce3.png">Can you stand only to look at me? Not feel my caress? To have your fingers get tangled in my beard?</state>
                <state img="#-menace1.png">Your passion is impressive, ~target~. We should unite our genitals. The slapping of our flesh would change this place profoundly.</state>
                <state img="#-menace2.png">Do not hold back, ~target~. It takes this and more to seduce a trained manwhore.</state>
                <state img="#-menace3.png">Is this the extent of your perversion, ~target~? Show me depravity. Show me &lt;i&gt;depravity.&lt;/i&gt;Show me.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-2 4">
                <condition role="target" character="megamix" />
                <state img="#-onetear.png">~blank~</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-seduce1.png" oneShotId="5">What a beautiful climax. Like watching a glorious sunrise or two chimpanzees groom one another.</state>
                <state img="#-seduce2.png" oneShotId="3">Well jizzed, fellow whore.</state>
                <state img="#-seduce3.png" oneShotId="4">As a manwhore, I've unlocked all the secrets to pleasing the shaft, and then some, and them some more, and then I lost them all, and then some...</state>
                <state img="#-moan1.png" oneShotId="6">Yes. Let us synchronize our lusty moans. &lt;i&gt;Uuoooh wwoouh hoooh wuuuh...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-menace1.png" oneShotId="23">Do not pretend you are disappointed by this development, ~target~. Free your lust. Own your perversion.</state>
                <state img="#-menace2.png" oneShotId="24">~Target~ must tame the beast of their lust before it puts a collar on them. A dog collar. For dogs.</state>
                <state img="#-menace3.png" oneShotId="25">Does your heart pound, ~target~? Do your cheeks flush? Your bosoms ripen? Your crotch moisten? Do you require medical attention?</state>
                <state img="#-menace2.png" oneShotId="26">~Target~, you shall show us your filthy lust. Let the lust wash over you. And the filth. The filthy lust. Oh yes.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-seduce1.png" oneShotId="15">You need not say a word, ~target~. Drop a coin into my hand, and I will take care of the rest.</state>
                <state img="#-seduce2.png" oneShotId="16">Why masturbate when you and I could copulate? That's a fancy word for "have the sex."</state>
                <state img="#-seduce3.png" oneShotId="17">You could touch yourself, ~target~, or you could pay Fernando to do if for you. I have training in such things and I'm fully bonded.</state>
                <state img="#-seduce2.png" oneShotId="18">Will you make moist the flesh of your nethers while gazing upon me? Why not purchase my assistance, if you like me so much?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-seduce1.png">Do your lascivious hands meander the folds of your piping hot pie of womanhood? You know what goes great with pie? Milk.</state>
                <state img="#-seduce2.png">Need assistance? Fernando is right here. Will you accept the charges? Yes, I'll hold.</state>
                <state img="#-seduce3.png">My natural musk is a powerful aphrodisiac. ~Target~, you may feel urges you have never even once considered.</state>
                <state img="#-menace1.png">The might of my wafting musk could drive you to the absolute pinnacle of human pleasure. Be warned, and be careful.</state>
                <state img="#-menace2.png">~Target~'s lusty cries have touched my soul. Such stimulation would send my throbbing arousal far enough to touch her soul.</state>
                <state img="#-menace3.png">Let your lust overcome you, ~target~. Money is temporary. The mark of Fernando is permanent.</state>
                <state img="#-notseduce.png">Smells of healthy goat in this place.</state>
                <state img="#-seduce1.png">Cum.</state>
                <state img="#-seduce2.png">Now's the time to unleash the fragrant sea beasts of your pleasure.</state>
                <state img="#-seduce3.png">Can you stand only to look at me? Not feel my caress? To have your fingers get tangled in my beard?</state>
                <state img="#-menace1.png">Your passion is impressive, ~target~. We should unite our genitals. The slapping of our flesh would change this place profoundly.</state>
                <state img="#-menace2.png">Do not hold back, ~target~. It takes this and more to seduce a trained manwhore.</state>
                <state img="#-menace3.png">Is this the extent of your perversion, ~target~? Show me depravity. Show me &lt;i&gt;depravity.&lt;/i&gt;Show me.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-seduce1.png" oneShotId="5">You should sample my wares some time. I could show you a climax you'd never dreamed possible.</state>
                <state img="#-seduce2.png" oneShotId="3">That was well gushed, my good woman, but I could do it so much better.</state>
                <state img="#-seduce3.png" oneShotId="4">You lack the true skill of touch that a manwhore like me has cultivated over many years of depravity. </state>
                <state img="#-moan1.png" oneShotId="6">Let me add my own moaning the chorus of your climax. &lt;i&gt;Ooooooh oooooooooooooooouh aaaoooouuuh...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate_first">
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Whoring3" />
                <state img="#-losespecial.png" marker="Whoring4">Oh, you have returned. How fortuitous. My seed I shall not waste upon the ground, instead it shall find a home in you. Climb aboard, my sweaty angel.</state>
                <state img="#-losespecial.png" marker="Whoring4">Ah, your return could not have been more perfectly timed. Though I have lost the game I have won... five, six. seven dollars! Yes, this will buy many hot crabs!</state>
                <state img="#-losespecial.png" marker="Whoring4">Oh, seems like I have a job to do. I hope no one minds, for this kind lady has been generous with her money so I too must be generous with my... butt? Penis? Ah, yes, penis.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-curious.png">So, you may have picked up on this, but I exchange sex for money. Maybe consider this an audition. A free sample. Keep your wallets ready, okay?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate">
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Whoring3" />
                <state img="#-losespecial.png" marker="Whoring4">Oh, you have returned. How fortuitous. My seed I shall not waste upon the ground, instead it shall find a home in you. Climb aboard, my sweaty angel.</state>
                <state img="#-losespecial.png" marker="Whoring4">Ah, your return could not have been more perfectly timed. Though I have lost the game I have won... five, six. seven dollars! Yes, this will buy many hot crabs!</state>
                <state img="#-losespecial.png" marker="Whoring4">Oh, seems like I have a job to do. I hope no one minds, for this kind lady has been generous with her money so I too must be generous with my... butt? Penis? Ah, yes, penis.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-curious.png">So, you may have picked up on this, but I exchange sex for money. Maybe consider this an audition. A free sample. Keep your wallets ready, okay?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="start_masturbating">
            <case stage="2" addCharacterTags="tandem">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Whoring4" />
                <state img="#-coitus.png" marker="Whoring5">Now the ride begins. Hold tight to my rough locks, both for stability and because you cannot resist the pleasure. And have fun!</state>
                <state img="#-coitus.png" marker="Whoring5">You may wish to grip my hair to stay aloft of my fleshy girth. My hip technique is what some might consider... unnatural.</state>
                <state img="#-coitus.png" marker="Whoring5">Hold fast to my ebony locks and whiskers. The course, filthy roughage will elevate your libido beyond human limits. Also, for stability.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-menace1.png">Experience the amazing, lusty moans of a true manwhore.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="masturbating">
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Whoring5" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">Just as my Latin sex saber has opened wide your blushing, feminine crevice, so too shall the girth of my moans open your mind. &lt;i&gt;Hoooooh ooooh uuoooh...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-moan1.png">&lt;i&gt;Ooooooooh, oooooohn, ooooooh, oooh, ooooh...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="heavy_masturbating">
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-moan1.png">&lt;i&gt;Wooooooouuuoh oooouuooouh aaaaauuuoooohauuuhn...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finishing_masturbating">
            <case stage="3" priority="12">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Whoring5" />
                <state img="#-duofinale.png" marker="Whoring6" location="25%">&lt;i&gt;Oooooooh-mmph-hmpf!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" priority="11">
                <state img="#-finale.png">&lt;i&gt;Oooh...&lt;/i&gt; I need some yoghurt...</state>
                <state img="#-finale.png">&lt;i&gt;Oooh...&lt;/i&gt; the chafing...</state>
                <state img="#-finale.png">&lt;i&gt;Oooh...&lt;/i&gt; pleasure... or pain?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Whoring6" />
                <state img="#-duofinale.png" marker="Whoring7">Another satisfied customer. Your time has expired, so step aside and let another lusty patron take a ride.</state>
                <state img="#-duofinale.png" marker="Whoring7">Fernando can do that and so much more. Truly, I am the world's greatest manwhore. Go now, spread word that Fernando is here.</state>
                <state img="#-duofinale.png" marker="Whoring7">All in a day's work for Fernando. Now run along, my creamy patron. Tell the world what Fernando has done to you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-finale.png">So, do I have any takers? Or any givers? I can go both ways.</state>
                <state img="#-finale.png">Do not weep. Save your tears. For a truly touching performance, you need only render me a payment.</state>
                <state img="#-finale.png">Such a beautiful, natural high. I could show you more. Oh yes, I could show you so much more. Well, you know my price.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="after_masturbating">
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-bored.png">All this moaning has left me parched for milk.</state>
                <state img="#-seduce1.png">My virility can be restored at a moment's notice. I have just have to take a few... "pieces of technology from Manwhore industries."</state>
                <state img="#-seduce2.png">Sex is still very much on the table. I know my performance has left you all lusting uncontrollably.</state>
                <state img="#-seduce3.png">Do your loins ache for Fernando still? A foolish question. Of course they do.</state>
                <state img="#-seduce1.png">Yes. I am still here.</state>
                <state img="#-seduce2.png">If you've no interest in sex, could I interest you in our lord and savior Raptor Jesus?</state>
                <state img="#-seduce3.png">Climax makes my musk even more potent. Apologies for making you horny beyond normal human comprehension.</state>
                <state img="#-seduce1.png">Fernando can go all night, or day depending on your availability. I will have to consult my... Google Calendars.</state>
                <state img="#-seduce2.png">Feel free to check me out on Twitter. My user name is @AmazingPenis574. I have been recently... unbanned.</state>
                <state img="#-seduce3.png">Feel free to take me home. I can drive us there. I already know the way.</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">Does anyone here want to be in a sexually explicit music video?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_victory">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-bored.png">Is that really it? All your lust is spent? Crap. I'll have to find some other lonesome group to seduce.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_defeat">
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Whoring7" />
                <state img="#-unlock.png" location="75%" collectible="eskimo_brotherhood">Oh, poor ~player~. Your lust is not yet sp-&lt;i&gt;rrrrrrrrhk!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-seduce3.png">Oh, poor ~player~. Your lust is not yet spent. Come to Fernando. He will see to it you are not left out.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-seduce1.png">So, ~target~. Feeling frustrated? Sexually? Sexually frustrated? Everyone got off but you. Fernando can help, for a price...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="global">
            <case stage="3" priority="10">
                <condition role="self" notSaidMarker="Whoring5" />
                <state img="#-moan1.png">&lt;i&gt;Ooooooooh, oooooohn, ooooooh, oooh, ooooh...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-moan2.png">&lt;i&gt;Aaaaoooooohoohn, oooh, ooooooh, oooh...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-onetear.png">&lt;i&gt;Haoooooooh ooooooh ooooooooooh ooooohn ooooooooh ooooh...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-approval.png">&lt;i&gt;Zoooooh ooooh aaaoooh oooh uuuuoooh oooh...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-moan1.png">&lt;i&gt;Ooooaaaooooh uuuuh zooouuuh oooh hoooooooooh ooooh...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-moan2.png">&lt;i&gt;Mooooooh uuuuoooh woooooah ooooh zooooh oooooh oooh...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-onetear.png">&lt;i&gt;Uuuuuuaaaaahn ooooh uuuuuoh uuuoooh oooh uuuuuh...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-approval.png">&lt;i&gt;Wooooh uuuuh ooh uuoooh hooh hhhhhhuuuuuh oh...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-moan1.png">&lt;i&gt;Hhhooooo ooooh wooah wuuuoooooaah ooooh...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-moan2.png">&lt;i&gt;Oooouuuuh aaauuuuoh oooh woooouuuh uuuuuuh...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-onetear.png">&lt;i&gt;Uuoooooooh oooooooooh oooooooooooooooooooh oooh ooooooooh...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-approval.png">&lt;i&gt;Ooooh aaaooooh uuoooh wooooh zuooooooooh...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" priority="10">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Whoring5" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">Just as my Latin sex saber has opened wide your blushing, feminine crevice, so too shall the girth of my moans open your mind. &lt;i&gt;Hoooooh ooooh uuoooh...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-menace1.png">I have daddy issues.</state>
                <state img="#-menace2.png">They all gaze upon the moistened flesh of our union. Does their gaze spark your desire?</state>
                <state img="#-menace3.png">Yes, hold fast to me. The fear of falling only serves to heighten the pleasure of our furious torso dance.</state>
                <state img="#-seduce1.png">You have depths yet unexplored. Fernando will mark these on your map.</state>
                <state img="#-seduce2.png">Your body is a temple, and Fernando has just what every temple needs: &lt;i&gt;semen.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-seduce3.png">Please do not let go. I am very strong but at any moment your convulsions of pleasure you wrench you free of my damp flesh piston.</state>
                <state img="#-notseduce.png">Fernando can go for a long while. It is vital we keep these proceedings... moist.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">Yes. Let your hips do the talking. They tell no lies.</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">Your average man does not have thrusting techniques like mine. Not even the above-average man. No, these skills are known only to... the manwhores.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Am I talking to much? This place makes me feel oddly chatty. Shall I tell you tales of squid hunting?</state>
                <state img="#-menace1.png">This does not even come close to the most people Fernando has performed filthy intercourse in front of.</state>
                <state img="#-menace2.png">We have all the time we need to sample the hit tracks of my hip movements as well as all the deep tracks. That is not an innuendo, but it is also an innuendo.</state>
                <state img="#-menace3.png">Yes, it hurts when you pull my hair, but I crave that sharp sting.</state>
                <state img="#-seduce1.png">I call this move "deep cover" because I go in deep without any cover.</state>
                <state img="#-seduce2.png">Just a reminder that the safe word is "Ulotrichous."</state>
                <state img="#-seduce3.png">I call this move "factory reset."</state>
                <state img="#-notseduce.png">I must warn you, my ejaculation will be hot, gooey, and of a volume yet untold.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">How do you feel about... goats?</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">There is no pleasure without pain. There is no pain without pleasure. It's exactly like mashed potatoes.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">&lt;i&gt;Zooooh ooooh wooooaaooh oooh woo oooh...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-menace1.png">So, you in town for a convention or something?</state>
                <state img="#-menace2.png">Mm, yes, you needed this.</state>
                <state img="#-menace3.png">I'm moving onto the next lowest level of depravity. You are prepared for it's intensity.</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">&lt;i&gt;Woooaaah oooh ooh wooooh oooh ooh...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-notseduce.png">I hope you're not prone to sea-sickness because you're about to ride the towering waves of pleasure.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

    </behaviour>
</opponent>
