<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<collectibles>
    <collectible id="literally_a_green_onion" img="opponents/bobobo/donpatchsword.png" thumbnail="opponents/bobobo/donpatchsword.png">
        <title>Don Patch Sword</title>
        <subtitle>Don Patch's purportedly magic sword. Now that you're holding it, you're certain it's just a green onion.</subtitle>
        <text>Don Patch carries this ordinary vegetable into battle, and more often than not gets his ass handed to him as a result. It's supposed to be magic or at least a high-quality vegetable, but it's astonishingly mundane. But maybe in the hands of a Legendary Warrior...</text>
        <unlock>Lose a game against Don Patch.</unlock>
        <hide-details>true</hide-details>
    </collectible>
    <collectible id="streets" status="offline" img="opponents/bobobo/STREETS.png" thumbnail="opponents/bobobo/STREETS.png">
        <title>Streets Sign</title>
        <subtitle>You got the achievement, but you still don't know where that voice is coming from.</subtitle>
        <text>Just an ordinary street sign. You don't know where Bobobo got it, why he threw it at you like that, or where that voice was coming from? You'll likely never forget you time in the streets.</text>
        <unlock>Play on the streets with three characters from Street Fighter.</unlock>
        <hide-details>true</hide-details>
    </collectible>
    <collectible id="dengakumanplushie" img="opponents/bobobo/accent-dengakuman.png" thumbnail="opponents/bobobo/accent-dengakuman.png">
        <title>Dengakuman Plushie</title>
        <subtitle>A plush doll that looks just like Dengakuman!</subtitle>
        <text>Dengakuman is a former hair hunter, leader of fearsome Z-Block Headquarters. Z-Block was supposed to be the weakest of the Block Bases, but due to an accounting error they became the strongest. Now he's on Bobobo's side, and despite being an inaffectual fighter played a vital role in one fight...</text>
        <unlock>Beat Bobobo in a game.</unlock>
        <hide-details>true</hide-details>
    </collectible>
</collectibles>
