<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<metadata>
    <owner>mulan</owner>
    <noteworthy>
        <case name="Challenge" id="0" min="2" max="4">
            <description>Mulan challenges other players to reveal secrets if she or they lose. Please PM nmasp if you engage in this so I can make custom dialogue! (Any Hand with these conditions)</description>
            <trigger tag="good_hand" timeInStage="1" totalNaked="0" totalMasturbating="0" totalFinished="0" notSaidMarker="mulan_duel">
                <state img="challenge.png" marker="mulan_duel">Let's make this interesting. If one of you is the first naked, you reveal a secret. But if &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; get me naked first, &lt;i&gt;I’ll&lt;/i&gt; answer a question from &lt;i&gt;each&lt;/i&gt; of you. Fair?</state>
            </trigger>
        </case>
        <case name="Disguise?" id="0" min="2" max="2">
            <description>Mulan starts the game in disguise. Your character may have realized this by now, but can remark on the change here.</description>
            <trigger tag="stripped">
                <state img="stripped.png">I’d quote Sun Tzu about knowing yourself and keeping your opponents off-guard, but that seems a little too...</state>
                <state img="stripped.png">I’m not ashamed of being a woman, or anything. Sometimes it’s just good form to make a strong first impression. You'd best prepare yourselves.</state>
                <state img="stripped.png">You’ve gotten me out of my armor. Now I’m going to get you out of the rest of… your stuff. All of it, so get ready!</state>
            </trigger>
        </case>
        <case name="Dates" id="0" min="1" max="1">
            <description>During her first hand after losing her first item, "Ping" queries what types of people the party likes to date. [Any hand]</description>
            <trigger tag="good_hand" timeInStage="0">
                <state img="peace.png" marker="honorable_others">Uh, folks, what kind of things do &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; look for in a match? For me: a strong-minded person who speaks their mind, and is courageous, clever, and most importantly: honorable.</state>
            </trigger>
        </case>
        <case name="Mulan lost her duel" id="0" min="8" max="8">
            <description>Mulan is the first person naked, and will answer incoming questions. See Challenge. </description>
            <trigger tag="stripped" totalMasturbating="0" totalFinished="0">
                <state img="stripped.png">There’s no shame in an honest loss. Though, the next part… that can be a little shameful if I’m first to lose.</state>
            </trigger>
        </case>
        <case name="Fa_Ping" id="0" min="0" max="1">
            <description>Lowbrow joke about Fapping</description>
            <trigger tag="hand" totalRounds="9" priority="299">
                <state img="pinged.png" marker="fa_pp_ing">What's... Fapping? I think it's a joke at my expense. You know, Fa Ping. </state>
            </trigger>
        </case>
    </noteworthy>
    <hidden />
    <nextId>0</nextId>
</metadata>
