<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>

<!--This file was machine generated using the Character Editor v5.5 at 6:04:17  on February 24, 2020. Please do not edit it directly without preserving your improvements elsewhere or your changes may be lost the next time this file is generated.-->
<opponent>
    <version>v5.5</version>
    <first>Mary</first>
    <last>Calvin</last>
    <label>Mary</label>
    <gender>female</gender>
    <size>small</size>
    <timer>30</timer>
    <intelligence>good</intelligence>

    <intelligence stage="1">bad</intelligence>

    <intelligence stage="2">average</intelligence>

    <intelligence stage="7">best</intelligence>

    <tags>
        <tag>black_hair</tag>
        <tag>medium_hair</tag>
        <tag>messy_hair</tag>
        <tag>green_eyes</tag>
        <tag>pale-skinned</tag>
        <tag>short</tag>
        <tag>hairy</tag>
        <tag>pubic_hair</tag>
        <tag>small_breasts</tag>
        <tag>glasses</tag>
        <tag>exhibitionist</tag>
        <tag>nerdy</tag>
        <tag>sarcastic</tag>
        <tag>slutty</tag>
        <tag>smart</tag>
        <tag>witty</tag>
        <tag>bisexual</tag>
        <tag>single</tag>
        <tag>american</tag>
        <tag>original_character</tag>
        <tag>gamer</tag>
    </tags>
    <nicknames />

    <start />

    <wardrobe>
        <clothing name="boxers" position="lower" type="important" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="bra" position="upper" type="important" />
        <clothing name="pants" position="lower" type="major" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="shirt" position="upper" type="major" />
        <clothing name="hoodie" position="upper" type="minor" />
        <clothing name="tie" position="neck" type="extra" />
        <clothing name="crocs" position="feet" type="extra" plural="true" />
    </wardrobe>

    <poses />

    <behaviour>
        <trigger id="selected">
            <case stage="0" id="6" alsoPlaying="ae86">
                <state img="#-toughcrowd.png">Y'know what? Sure. I'll play a strip poker game against a freakin' car. At least it's playing some good beats.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Yo. Mary Calvin. Let's get weird.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">The name's Mary. I assume you already knew that, though.. </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_selected">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="mary" />
                <state img="#-headon.png">Damn it, if you're gonna make me play with a doppelganger, could you at least have picked one from a better point in my shitty fuckin' life?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_start">
            <case stage="0" id="5" alsoPlaying="yuelia">
                <state img="#-toughcrowd.png">Hey, uh, is... Is anyone else seeing the... Talking butterfly? Fuck, do I need to contact my pharmacist about this?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-absolutelyelementaryyoufuckingmoronyouabsolutefuckingbuffoonfuckyou.png">Let's keep the game clean. No cheating, no doping, no illegal blows.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="swap_cards">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <test expr="~cards~" value="5" />
                <state img="#-toughcrowd.png">There goes that hand. Get me a new one, dealer.</state>
                <state img="#-wah.png">What am I meant to do with &lt;i&gt;this&lt;/i&gt; shit? Get it out of my face, dealer!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <test expr="~cards~" value="0" />
                <state img="#-smug.png">What sort of jag-off would need new cards? Get real.</state>
                <state img="#-isthishappy.png">Hah! No cards here, dealer, I'm set for life!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-7">
                <state img="#-MINDBOOLETS.png">Get me ~cards.text~ ~cards.ifPlural(cards|card)~, stat!</state>
                <state img="#-elementary.png">No choice but ~cards.text~ ~cards.ifPlural(cards|card)~. That's how you win.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I ain't even gonna look - ~cards.text~, dealer.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-1">
                <state img="#-thissparksjoy.png">Get me ~cards.text~ ~cards.ifPlural(cards|card)~, stat!</state>
                <state img="#-absolutelyelementaryyoufuckingmoronyouabsolutefuckingbuffoonfuckyou.png">No choice but ~cards.text~ ~cards.ifPlural(cards|card)~. That's how you win.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I ain't even gonna look - ~cards.text~, dealer.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="good_hand">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-isthishappy.png">As expected, I'm &lt;i&gt;way&lt;/i&gt; too good at this game.</state>
                <state img="#-mendokuse.png" marker="bluff">What a shite hand, honestly. Like a whole pile of buffalo crap. An entire pile.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I usually prefer playing shit like this one-on-one, but beating multiple people at once can be fun.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-6">
                <state img="#-isthishappy.png">Y'know what? That's pretty dope.</state>
                <state img="#-isthishappy.png">Bangin'!</state>
                <state img="#-headon.png" marker="+sideeffects" weight="0.5">Gah! Fuck, give me a second to breathe... a'ight, I'm good.</state>
                <state img="#-idle.png">This whole strip poker thing is a bit weird. We might as well just roll dice and have the lowest roller strip.</state>
                <state img="#-isthishappy.png">Well, guess who has two thumbs, an outstanding warrant, and isn't gonna strip this round!</state>
                <state img="#-yeahigottime.png">Y'know, we can swap hands if you want, ~player~. Make things more exciting.</state>
                <state img="#-MINDBOOLETS.png">You do need pretty high IQ to be as good at poker as I am, y'know.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-mendokuse.png">Oh, fuck off, hands like these after I've already lost the one time I didn't t want to.</state>
                <state img="#-idle.png" marker="bluff">I guess these cards don't suck &lt;i&gt;too&lt;/i&gt; too bad.</state>
                <state img="#-thissparksjoy.png">Mama don't mind seein' that. Is it weird to call myself that?</state>
                <state img="#-mendokuse.png">Fuck, man. I honestly just want to get rid of this tie already.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-smug.png">End of the line, chumps. </state>
                <state img="#-isthishappy.png">Ha! This is far as you get, bros. Though, to be fair, this was already pretty far!</state>
                <state img="#-MINDBOOLETS.png">You absolute fools stand no chance against me now. Prepare to get fucked by the long cock of brain power and RNG!</state>
                <state img="#-isthishappy.png">This has been fun and all, but it's about time I show y'all your place.</state>
                <state img="#-MINDBOOLETS.png">I don't have a talent for many things in this world, but fuck me sideways if one of those things isn't playing pointless card games!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="okay_hand">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-toughcrowd.png">I'd say something about hoping this will be enough, but that's putting hope in statistics, and fuck that.</state>
                <state img="#-toughcrowd.png">Yo, is it too late to go back on the 'no cheating' thing? I'm pretty good at it.</state>
                <state img="#-yeahigottime.png">Like a pocket full of lint, this hand's just sort of here, serves no purpose and I wonder how it'd feel in my mouth.</state>
                <state img="#-idle.png">Let me just comment on the quality of the hand you're going to see in a moment anyway. That's a good use of my time.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-6">
                <state img="#-MINDBOOLETS.png">Every move I make is perfectly calculated. If only that meant jack shit in strip poker.</state>
                <state img="#-idle.png" oneShotId="12">Anyone know where the bathroom is? I don't need it now, but it's good to be prepared, less you wanna be touching cloth.</state>
                <state img="#-yourearealcomedianbro.png" oneShotId="28">Who invited all of us here, anyway? I think it was supposed to be ~player~, but I have no fucking clue who they are.</state>
                <state img="#-wah.png">Who is this dealer guy, anyway? Is it just me, or are they kind of... 'nondescript'?</state>
                <state img="#-idle.png" oneShotId="13">So what's your story, ~player~? No offense, but you look like some generic harem protag to me.</state>
                <state img="#-toughcrowd.png" oneShotId="14" marker="+sideeffects">Could someone crank the AC up? I'm sweating up a storm here.</state>
                <state img="#-yeahigottime.png">It's just another hand. Guess it never had the chance to be more than that.</state>
                <state img="#-idle.png">It doesn't make sense to complain about a hand like this, so why do I want to?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-toughcrowd.png" oneShotId="10" marker="sideeffects">Fuck, it's hard to breathe in here. The air's so damn stuffy...</state>
                <state img="#-toughcrowd.png">Why the hell are these cards so sweaty? Who the... Oh, wait, that's me. I'm the sweaty one. My bad.</state>
                <state img="#-isthishappy.png">Do you think this game was invented by men or by chicks? You'd think men, but you shouldn't underestimate the power of sluts!</state>
                <state img="#-mendokuse.png">So many different hands you can get in poker and I get this shit.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-mendokuse.png">I've got nothing to say here, tbh. This hand just kind of sucks right now. And blows.</state>
                <state img="#-toughcrowd.png">I'd say i still have an ace up my sleeve, but my sleeves are halfway across the room. How did they even get there?</state>
                <state img="#-MINDBOOLETS.png">Maybe if I focus hard enough, I can will a better hand into existence. It's worth a shot, ain't it?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="bad_hand">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-toughcrowd.png">Well, that's a pickle and a half. Maybe even three quarters of a second pickle.</state>
                <state img="#-thatdamnfinalchaosemerald.png">Damn it to fuck, I knew I should've looked at my cards!</state>
                <state img="#-mendokuse.png">Damn it, I like these shoes. Could someone fuck up real quick? Thanks.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-6">
                <state img="#-dread.png" marker="dread" weight="0.1">Well, that's not good.</state>
                <state img="#-buthow.png" weight="0.1">But.... how?</state>
                <state img="#-MINDBOOLETS.png">This shit hand is all part of a master plan you're too simple to see...! And so am I, apparently.</state>
                <state img="#-mendokuse.png">Well, at least whatever i lose will be fun to get rid of.</state>
                <state img="#-thatdamnfinalchaosemerald.png">Blast, foiled again! And by hubris, not even any meddling kids this time!</state>
                <state img="#-headon.png" oneShotId="15" marker="lasaga">My mind's been like... cheap lasagna lately. Delicious, but it falls apart when you probe it. Y'all have no idea how hard it is to wrangle this mind lasagna.</state>
                <state img="#-wah.png">Hey, dealer, put your hand out for me so i can &lt;i&gt;shit&lt;/i&gt; in it, since that's what you like doing to &lt;i&gt;me&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-thatdamnfinalchaosemerald.png">I have some powerful communications channels, dealer. Remember that.</state>
                <state img="#-yourearealcomedianbro.png">On with it already. We know what's coming.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-thatdamnfinalchaosemerald.png">Lady luck can &lt;i&gt;suck my dick&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-dread.png" marker="dread">Oh, isn't that just lovely?</state>
                <state img="#-buthow.png">But... There was no better move! That was it! That was my path to victory!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="hand">
            <case stage="0-7" id="13" alsoPlaying="shantae" totalRounds="3-" alsoPlayingSayingMarker="dance_first">
                <condition role="other" character="shantae" sayingMarker="dance_first" />
                <state img="#-yeahigottime.png">Damn it, Shantae, that's distracting. There's gotta be some rule against havin' hips that don't quit.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="9" alsoPlaying="revy" alsoPlayingSayingMarker="killing">
                <condition role="other" character="revy" sayingMarker="killing" />
                <state img="#-toughcrowd.png">I know better than to incriminate myself like that, Revy. But my, uh, hands aren't exactly clean, to say the least.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" oneShotId="1" totalRounds="0-1">
                <condition count="0" role="other" character="mary" />
                <state img="#-toughcrowd.png">...Have I been here before? Perhaps physically. Just play the game, game player.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="1" priority="101">
                <condition role="other" character="dust" sayingMarker="fidgetQA_snacks" />
                <state img="#-toughcrowd.png">Garlic toast. Makes my breath smell like shit, but they're delicious and ward off vampires. What else could you want, really?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="3">
                <condition role="other" character="amy" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Amy1" />
                <state img="#-isthishappy.png" marker="Amy_sicarius">Y'know, I always wanted a pet sicarius. The way they disguise themselves in the sand, waiting to strike... It's remarkable!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="4">
                <condition role="other" character="amy" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Amy1" />
                <state img="#-thissparksjoy.png" marker="Amy_conjunction">Hey, if we re talking language, probably a weird question, but - do you have a favorite conjunction? I personally love 'and'. No statement exists that can't be expanded upon ad-infinitum with and!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="5">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="litclub" />
                <condition role="other" character="sayori" />
                <state img="#-thissparksjoy.png" marker="sayori_preposition">As one writer to another, Sayori, I wonder- what s your number one preposition? i love 'around' - it has so many great uses in metaphor, and the word itself sounds like it just wraps right around you!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="6">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="litclub" />
                <condition role="other" character="natsuki" />
                <state img="#-thissparksjoy.png" marker="natsuki_pronoun">Yo, Natsuki! Do you have a favorite pronoun in writing? I love a good 'they'. Some snobs hate using it as a singular, but honestly, I welcome anything that gets rid of havin' to say 'he or she' all the time!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="9">
                <condition role="other" character="jessie" sayingMarker="JessieQA_LittleLies" />
                <state img="#-mendokuse.png" marker="JessieLies">Lying is fine so long as it's done to some benefit. Avoiding the truth because it hurts or because it's uncomfortable, however, s just weak.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="10">
                <condition role="other" character="jessie" sayingMarker="JessieQA_Million" />
                <state img="#-mendokuse.png" marker="JessieMillion">A million is nothing. Like spitting in the ocean of the world's wealth. I would do nothing I can't do now, because what else is there to do with that money/</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="11">
                <condition role="other" character="jessie" sayingMarker="JessieQA_Family" />
                <state img="#-toughcrowd.png" marker="JessieFamily">Have you heard the saying  blood runs thicker than water', Jessie? The full saying is actually 'the blood of the coven runs thicker than the water of the womb'. Take that as you will. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="12">
                <condition role="other" character="jessie" sayingMarker="JessieQA_Smokers" />
                <state img="#-toughcrowd.png" marker="JessieSmoke">I used to smoke reefers, though they just... Don't work anymore. It's a tough habit to break, though, so I've picked up menthols.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="13">
                <condition role="other" character="jessie" sayingMarker="JessieQA_Open" />
                <state img="#-idle.png" marker="JessieOpen">I mean, who cares? Sex is just sex, isn't it? Besides, long-term shit just seems like a hassle to me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="14">
                <condition role="other" character="jessie" sayingMarker="JessieQA_StupidMistakes" />
                <state img="#-idle.png" marker="JessieMistakes">I sill beat myself up over all the stupid shit &lt;i&gt;I've&lt;/i&gt; done,so why should others be exempt?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="15">
                <condition role="other" character="jessie" sayingMarker="JessieQA_DarkSecrets" />
                <state img="#-toughcrowd.png" marker="JesieSecrets">Plenty, Jessie, but you sound like you're asking with a lot more... innocence than would be advisable</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="19">
                <condition filter="ddlc" role="other" />
                <state img="#-isthishappy.png" marker="litclub">Oh, shit, you dorks are in a literature club? Sweet! Literature and the English language are like my... fifth and seventh favorite things to nerd out about!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="1" marker="imnotlooking">Y'know, there isn't really a point to bluffing or mind games. We make no bets, and can't change anything after we get our cards. So, I'll just not look at mine this round.</state>
                <state img="#-MINDBOOLETS.png" oneShotId="5">This game's pretty much pointless. I already pictured all of you naked the moment you walked in.</state>
                <state img="#-yeahigottime.png" oneShotId="6">Shit, how many cards did I just take? I kind of zoned the fuck out.</state>
                <state img="#-headon.png" oneShotId="7" marker="+sideeffects" weight="0.5">Fuck, anyone have a glass of water? My mouth feels feels like a country the US is gonna invade for oil. Like... sand. I mean it feels like it's full of sand.</state>
                <state img="#-headon.png" oneShotId="9" marker="+sideeffects" weight="0.3">God damn, I can barely see my damn cards... give me a minute.</state>
                <state img="#-headon.png" oneShotId="8" marker="+sideeffects" weight="0.3">I can barely keep my fucking eyes open - could someone slap me? Preferably on the ass?</state>
                <state img="#-headon.png" oneShotId="11" marker="+sideeffects">Can we really not get some fucking chairs? I think my leg's about to die on me.</state>
                <state img="#-headon.png" oneShotId="16" marker="+sideeffects">Jesus, I almost dropped my cards there!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" priority="0">
                <test expr="~background~" value="inventory" />
                <state img="#-idle.png" oneShotId="3" marker="privateroom">Have y'all noticed how we're just sort of... standing in the middle of the bar? There's a private room we could have used back there. With chairs.</state>
                <state img="#-idle.png" oneShotId="4">I wonder who the hell runs is this place. Or how they run it. Or get away with running it.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_winning">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-mendokuse.png">Ah, damn it. Here i was hopin' you fucknuts wouldn't make me ditch the crocs.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-mendokuse.png">Aw, fuck. This hoodie is my favorite part of this frickin' outfit.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-thissparksjoy.png">Thank fuck, this tie's been killing me all game! Screw style, this is not how i like to be choked.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-yeahigottime.png">I guess that's a'ight. Showin' off skin is part of the fun, innit?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-toughcrowd.png">Starting to get risky. I don't mind gettin' naked, but i got a reputation to maintain. A reputation of being good at card games.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Congrats, fuckboys. You'll be the first people in&lt;i&gt;years&lt;/i&gt; to see these.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-isthishappy.png">Hey, that's fine by me! Walking around in just my boxers feels way weirder than being butt-fuck naked anyway!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_normal">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-mendokuse.png" weight="9">Well, there goes the objectively cutest and best part of this fucking outfit, smh.</state>
                <state img="#-mendokuse.png">I'd keep my crocs on last, but I've been told 'posing them in every stage would be a bitch', whatever that's supposed to mean.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-toughcrowd.png">Sure. It's way too fucking hot in here for a hoodie, anyway.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-toughcrowd.png">Fine by me, fuckers. This tie's been killing me, and not in the good way.</state>
                <state img="#-toughcrowd.png" marker="notmytie">I don't know how the guy who owned this tie before handled it. It's like a semi-permanent noose.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-isthishappy.png">I guess this is the point where the game gets interesting to people. Maybe ~player~ will even stop skipping dialogue! </state>
                <state img="#-idle.png" weight="9">Y'know what? Shirts are a scam anyway. Same with bras.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-MINDBOOLETS.png">All part of a greater keikaku! Probably!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-isthishappy.png">Well, I don't mind this loss one bit! Bras are fuckin' gross! Hot on other chicks, sure, but gross to wear!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-toughcrowd.png">Well, that's my last advantage gone. Maybe I ought to have taken this game more seriously.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_losing">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-wah.png">What the fuck? why do y'all have so many layers? Ain't this place hot enough already?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-mendokuse.png">Fuck, and this hoodie is so goddamn comfy, too. Whatever, fuckboys.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-toughcrowd.png">I don't mind losing the tie, but man do I not like my odds.</state>
                <state img="#-toughcrowd.png" marker="notmytie">Maybe losing the tie is a good idea, anyway. It brought some shite luck to the last guy that owned it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-yeahigottime.png">I wouldn't have come here if I didn't want to get naked, but the rate at which I'm doing it is gettin' concerning.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-mendokuse.png">I'd get rid of the bra now, but fuck y'all, y'all haven't earned my tits yet. or, well, you kind of have, but I'm salty about that, too.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-headon.png">I'd start complaining about my position 'ere, but fuck has this bra been getting on my goddamn nerves already.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-MINDBOOLETS.png">Now y'all have gone done it! Prepare for an ass whooping, no holding back!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripping">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-strip.png">If you want to bitch about the crocs, bitch to yourself. I like 'em, and the haters can fuck off.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-strip.png">I tried to get one of those jackets with the little thumb-holes in the sleeves, but I couldn't find one on the account of it not being 2005.</state>
                <state img="#-strip.png">I wore a lot less than this back in the day 'cause I hated doing laundry. Still do, but at least I don't smell as bad.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-strip.png">Putting this thing back on sucks ass, but you know what they say, I'll fuck that bridge when I get to it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-strip.png">Ah, crap, a button fell off! Damn it to fuck!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-strip.png">Y'know, I'm not a fan of pants, anyway. Maybe I should just go back to shorts. Shorts are nice.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-strip.png">I'd say it's time to let my puppies out to breathe, but they're more like... kittens. Or baby hamsters. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-strip.png">There's almost a certain nostalgia to doing this. I can't really explain it, but it's there.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripped">
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-toughcrowd.png">They're easy to wear, easy to take off, comfortable and, fuck it, I think they look good.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-MINDBOOLETS.png">I'm more or less outta the small shit. I'd count my glasses like a proper bitch, but I can already barely see shit.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-idle.png">I still like that one, though, so if you're gonna jizz on it, ask permission first.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-headon.png">Hope the freakin' sight is worth it, 'cause I'll need a new shirt now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Something about standing here like this sure feels familiar. Can't for the life o' me say what.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-isthishappy.png">Well, here they are. Laugh at them if you want, I don't give a damn. Ain't like I chose them, though I probably would have!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-thissparksjoy.png">Ya know what, y'all? Whoever wins this, I didn't hate bein' here. That said I &lt;i&gt;am&lt;/i&gt; winning this.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_strip">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Plenty more losses to come, so get used to it, bucko.</state>
                <state img="#-idle.png">Don't pretend like you're not getting at least a chub when ya think about stripping for us.</state>
                <state img="#-thissparksjoy.png">Let's see what you got, hot shot..! Do people actually call each other that/</state>
                <state img="#-yourearealcomedianbro.png">Don't make a deal of it and just strip, bro.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-6 9">
                <state img="#-idle.png">Y'know, I've noticed there are way less dudes that hang around this joint than chicks. You'd expect the opposite, wouldn't you?</state>
                <state img="#-headon.png">Stop talking and get stripping, bro.</state>
                <state img="#-thissparksjoy.png">Oh, hey, it's that guy's turn to strip! That one guy! Him!</state>
                <state img="#-isthishappy.png">I'd say somethings like 'I was hoping you'd lose' but man, I do not give a shit.</state>
                <state img="#-MINDBOOLETS.png">Always one step behind, muchacho.</state>
                <state img="#-elementary.png">Here's a tip for next round: play the game better, forehead!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-toughcrowd.png">Lucky you, gettin'  to strip and all.</state>
                <state img="#-yourearealcomedianbro.png">How about you just strip and be done with it, bub?</state>
                <state img="#-thissparksjoy.png">Just think of stripping kind of like pulling off a scab. Who doesn't love doing that?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-idle.png">Don't complain about losin' when I'm here like this, bucko.</state>
                <state img="#-isthishappy.png">How 'bout you join the club, pal? It feels pretty damn nice, y'know. </state>
                <state img="#-MINDBOOLETS.png">I ain't playing around now, ~name~! There are only more losses to come!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Well, ~name~. Looks like it's your shot at helping me get going!</state>
                <state img="#-thissparksjoy.png">Got something good to show off, bro? I bet you do, seems like everyone here does!</state>
                <state img="#-idle.png">Could you skip to the part where you're naked already? Thanks.</state>
                <state img="#-MINDBOOLETS.png">I've already imagined you naked, dude, and I wasn't impressed. Care to change my opinion?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-MINDBOOLETS.png">I already finished, but I can still save all this in my spank bank for later, y'know!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_strip">
            <case stage="0-1">
                <state img="#-absolutelyelementaryyoufuckingmoronyouabsolutefuckingbuffoonfuckyou.png">An easy way to avoid a loss in poker is being better in poker than your opponent, or a bunch of purposefully mediocre AIs! You should give it a shot!</state>
                <state img="#-idle.png">Could you strip and move on? I kind of have shit to do. Not important shit, mind you, but neither is this.</state>
                <state img="#-MINDBOOLETS.png">I'd brag about outsmarting you, but I really just do the exact same thing every round so it's more like you outdumbed yourself.</state>
                <state img="#-toughcrowd.png">If you take off something nice, I'll give you... oral? I had something better lined up there but I forgot what it was mid-sentence.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-7 9">
                <state img="#-idle.png">Come on, ain't like you'd be here if you didn't want to strip. Who the hell would put themselves through that?</state>
                <state img="#-isthishappy.png">Seein' cute babes strip is what I came to do, so get the show goin'!</state>
                <state img="#-thissparksjoy.png">Remember, ~name~ - losing is fun!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Havin' to take off something in front of strangers is hardly the worst that could happen to a person. Sure, it's kind of up there, but not &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; high up there.</state>
                <state img="#-isthishappy.png">This better be good, 'cause my legs are falling asleep!</state>
                <state img="#-elementary.png">Remember, if poker's too hard for you, you can always try something more suited for your level of intelligence, like snakes and ladders!</state>
                <state img="#-thissparksjoy.png">Hey, kind of gay, but I do want to see you strip, ~name~. You're, like. Pretty and shit.</state>
                <state img="#-idle.png">We all knew what we were signin' up for coming here. Unless we didn't, which would be kind of fucked up, actually.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-yeahigottime.png">Y'know, I could definitely use some encouragement here. Encouragement in the form of a vagina in my face.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Whatever it is you take off, make it &lt;i&gt;sexy&lt;/i&gt;. You can do that with anything if you have the know-how.</state>
                <state img="#-yeahigottime.png">Spare coochie, ma'am?</state>
                <state img="#-MINDBOOLETS.png">Ah, just as I said before. All calculated. Now I get to flick the bean while watching you get naked!</state>
                <state img="#-thissparksjoy.png">Woop! Woop! That's the sound of... You needing to strip. I'm not exactly a wordsmith.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-idle.png">Man, how's this game still going, even? Did I really lose that fuckin' fast?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="tie">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-dread.png">Well isn't that neat - why don't you post a screenshot on reddit so people can go 'bruh in the comments and forget about it immediately?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0-9" id="3">
                <condition role="target" character="brock" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-headon.png">...Seriously? And you're supposed to be the pro, and I'm the clutz. I hope that damn rocket comes back to blow you the hell up, dude.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <state img="#-idle.png">That s pretty damn weak, but I guess ~clothing.ifPlural(|the)~ ~clothing~ could have some sexy uses.</state>
                <state img="#-idle.png">It's what most sane people would go for, so whatever. But I was counting on more crazy sluts being here.</state>
                <state img="#-mendokuse.png">Oh, please. You gotta be some kind of fruit to wear ~clothing~ like yours.</state>
                <state img="#-idle.png">I wonder why joints like this aren't more common. Y'know, aside from prudes like you making it a bore for everyone.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-toughcrowd.png">Oh, come on, at least do something fun with it!</state>
                <state img="#-headon.png">Shit, i guess I'm really working with nothin' here. This is gonna take a while.</state>
                <state img="#-toughcrowd.png">I wasn't exactly expecting the guys here to throw themselves at me, but I was hoping they'd at least show &lt;i&gt;some&lt;/i&gt; interest, y'know.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <state img="#-toughcrowd.png">Come to think of it, I've definitely seen a video of someone putting ~clothing.ifPlural(|something like your)~ ~clothing~ up their ass.</state>
                <state img="#-mendokuse.png">Eh. Whatever. Just stop holding the game up.</state>
                <state img="#-headon.png">Even that &lt;i&gt;asshole&lt;/i&gt; wouldn't pull shit like this.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-mendokuse.png">I wish I had taken my phone from my jacket. At least I have some JAVs downloaded on it.</state>
                <state img="#-wah.png">Do you get off on others not being able to get off? Is that a kink? Am I allowed to kinkshame that?</state>
                <state img="#-wah.png">I know you're mocking me, but if we're staying here until I get off, consider this a war of attrition.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0-9" id="11" target="yuelia" targetStage="0" targetSayingMarker="transformation">
                <state img="#-yeahigottime.png">Oh. You're a person. More logical, but... A bit less peculiar. I was wondering what counted for clothing on a butterfly.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <state img="#-idle.png">An item more worthless than an opinion online.</state>
                <state img="#-headon.png">You're going to drive me insane here, and not in the sexy way.</state>
                <state img="#-toughcrowd.png">Does this place work more like a strip club? Do I need to give you a fiver for you to take off something good, and, or, sit on my face?</state>
                <state img="#-idle.png">Where the hell is everyone else that hangs out at this bar, anyway. You'd think folks would jump at the chance to play this game with a bunch of smokeshows.</state>
                <state img="#-idle.png">Maybe if we actually cranked the temperature &lt;i&gt;up&lt;/i&gt;, it'd get you to strip something good.</state>
                <state img="#-mendokuse.png">Honestly, that would have gotten me plenty excited at some point in my life, I'm sure. Alas, now is not the past. Allegedly.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-mendokuse.png">That's really not doin' anything for me. Such hotness, wasted like the final drops of soda on the edges of a soda can.</state>
                <state img="#-headon.png">Fuck, guess I'm going back to my imagination. All sorts of things going into all sorts of orifices there.</state>
                <state img="#-thissparksjoy.png">So, this must be purgatory. I knew I should've paid off those damn indulgences. Curse you, Martin Luther!</state>
                <state img="#-idle.png">Could I get some sort of tiddy mag, at least? And by that, of course, I mean the gun kind of mag. Filled with tits. That I can shoot myself with.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <state img="#-toughcrowd.png">I bet they have cameras set up in this room. Good news is, whoever is watching this game has probably fallen asleep already.</state>
                <state img="#-wah.png">Anyway, could you hurry up, dealer? Some of us want to actually do something &lt;i&gt;interesting&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-yourearealcomedianbro.png">God, i could use a stiff drink. Or a joint.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-MINDBOOLETS.png">Perhaps you could be persuaded? Persuaded to not be such a bitch? No?</state>
                <state img="#-dread.png" marker="dread">Man, wouldn't it be lovely to just watch you get fucked.</state>
                <state img="#-idle.png">Fuck, my hand fell asleep, give me a moment.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <state img="#-idle.png">It's something, but everything is something by definition. Other than nothing. Nothing is nothing.</state>
                <state img="#-idle.png">Do they serve drinks here? They gotta serve drinks here. I don't have my ID with me, though, and I fucking &lt;i&gt;always&lt;/i&gt; get carded.</state>
                <state img="#-headon.png">God, do I not care about your ~clothing~. Nobody does.</state>
                <state img="#-mendokuse.png">Bro. Dude. Buddy. &lt;i&gt;Fuck you.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-headon.png">You're actually fuckin'  worthless, dude. Just go back to whatever hole you crawled out of with that shit.</state>
                <state img="#-toughcrowd.png">Just keep your shit away from my shit when you take it off, dude. I don't think you're gross, I just hate having my shit in with other peoples' 'cause then shit gets lost. Or stolen.</state>
                <state img="#-idle.png">Am I going to have to just take five here, dude? What the hell is this?</state>
                <state img="#-idle.png">To quote Chandler Bing -  could you &lt;i&gt;be&lt;/i&gt; any more of a gay bitch?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_minor">
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <state img="#-toughcrowd.png">Honestly, I'd make a better guy than you. I bet you my dick's bigger, too.</state>
                <state img="#-idle.png">Honestly, shit like your ~clothing~ just drags the game out. Like those torture devices that dragged people out by having horses pull them, but with strip poker, not people.</state>
                <state img="#-MINDBOOLETS.png">With every move like that, the size of your dick in my mind grows smaller and smaller. Keep that in mind.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-thatdamnfinalchaosemerald.png">Damn it, whose idea was it to play this damned game, anyway? It's just... just a buncha shit!</state>
                <state img="#-headon.png">I hate. Y'know, nothing in particular, I just hate.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0-9" id="12" target="shantae" targetStage="1" targetSayingMarker="monkey">
                <state img="#-isthishappy.png">Shit, you're just as cute as you were before like that! A shame you're so small, it'd feel wrong to do more than give you a head pat or somethin'.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-idle.png">Why the fuck are only a couple of us talking? ~Player~ hasn't said shit, neither has the dealer. It freaks me out.</state>
                <state img="#-idle.png">Oh. ~Clothing~. Daring today, aren' t we?</state>
                <state img="#-idle.png">I hope you're cancel culture's next target, ~name~. </state>
                <state img="#-idle.png">Is there a fire alarm nearby?  Don't want to pull it now, but I like knowing my options.</state>
                <state img="#-idle.png">Y'know, wearing something like your ~clothing~ is illegal in some countries. They're mostly shitholes, but countries never the less. </state>
                <state img="#-idle.png">Anyone have a ciggy I could borrow? I need one right about now.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_minor">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-headon.png">Fuck me, can we just get to something worthwhile today?</state>
                <state img="#-toughcrowd.png">I really don't get women. Or men. Or people. At least horses are easy.</state>
                <state img="#-thatdamnfinalchaosemerald.png">Degenerates like you belong... Well, here, frankly, but you should also be naked!</state>
                <state img="#-mendokuse.png">I wanna go home and watch some virtual camgirls or something. At least they won't let me down.</state>
                <state img="#-dread.png" marker="dread">You're pathetic.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_major">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-yeahigottime.png">Well, ain't that nice. We're making progress now.</state>
                <state img="#-MINDBOOLETS.png">How's it feel to be a cuck, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-MINDBOOLETS.png">Alas, my dear friend, your ~clothing~ ~clothing.ifPlural(are|is)~ forfeit!</state>
                <state img="#-idle.png">Psh. You weren't even pulling off your ~clothing~. I'd look way more handsome in that.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_major">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-toughcrowd.png">As long as we're moving forward. Which, in the sense of time, we're doing by default.</state>
                <state img="#-toughcrowd.png">I guess you look alright without all that. Better than with it, for sure.</state>
                <state img="#-isthishappy.png">This is how the order ought to be! Men undressing for the entertainment of chicks!</state>
                <state img="#-thissparksjoy.png">Maybe next time you could put some oomf in how ya take your shit off. magic Mike didn't get his job fumbling with a pair of trousers.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_major">
            <case stage="0-7" target="emi" targetStage="7">
                <state img="#-MINDBOOLETS.png">Most commendable, young Emi! But if I have to saw off my legs to beat you in turn, I'll do just that!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-yeahigottime.png">Fuck, man, this is actually getting me hot and bothered. That hasn't happened in a while now.</state>
                <state img="#-thissparksjoy.png">God, you're so fuckin' hot,~name~. It should not be legal to be that hot.</state>
                <state img="#-isthishappy.png">Aw, yeah, now we're talking! As opposed to before, where we were just awkwardly silent.</state>
                <state img="#-isthishappy.png">Nothing like a good striptease to get your cock up in the mornin'!</state>
                <state img="#-thissparksjoy.png">Could I get an autograph? Preferably on your ~clothing~?</state>
                <state img="#-isthishappy.png">Off comes the ~clothing~, out come the titties, up goes the boner and down go I!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_major">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-MINDBOOLETS.png">Y'know what comes next, right? Another defeat, and more boner fuel, that's what.</state>
                <state img="#-MINDBOOLETS.png">This ain't our final stop, ~name~. The final stop is Flavortown.</state>
                <state img="#-MINDBOOLETS.png">Fuck the game, all I'm strategizing now is how to steal your ~clothing~.</state>
                <state img="#-MINDBOOLETS.png">If you need help stripping next round, I'll be glad to do it. And the round after that. And after the game. And before it. </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-9" id="4" target="brock" targetStage="4">
                <state img="#-yourearealcomedianbro.png">Oh. I guess there it is, then.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-MINDBOOLETS.png">A greater step towards your demise! Demise in poker! Hah!</state>
                <state img="#-idle.png">Alright, place your bets, does ~name~ have abs, tummy or a gut? My bet is on a fupa.</state>
                <state img="#-idle.png">I'll only be impressed if your chest is as hairy as a... coconut. Yeah, those are pretty hairy.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition filter="chubby" role="target" />
                <state img="#-idle.png" oneShotId="22">Oh sure. It's normal for a guy to have a gut like that, but a chick? Nooo, that'd make her a fat cow. Well fuck you, I like cows</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition filter="muscular" role="target" />
                <state img="#-wah.png" oneShotId="23">I guess that's impressive, or something? Honestly, all that muscle just tells me you got nothin' to do other than lift.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-yourearealcomedianbro.png">Cool.</state>
                <state img="#-headon.png">Man, what a bore. At least show your ass or something, if you even have one.</state>
                <state img="#-toughcrowd.png">Can you roll your stomach? I'm just asking, 'cause I've seen people do it but whenever I try it I just... burp. </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-mendokuse.png">I'll be frank with you, I'd be more interested if you were hiding a coochie down there. Now if only I knew who Frank was.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Come on, bro. Some people do this sort of shit all the time in parks. They usually have trench coats, though.</state>
                <state img="#-toughcrowd.png">Unless you have some eldritch horror down there, you shouldn't make a big deal of it. You... Don't have an eldritch horror in your pants, do you?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_small_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-yeahigottime.png">It's weird, I somehow feel like you got a small dick by choice. That doesn't make sense, though, does it?</state>
                <state img="#-yeahigottime.png">Well, at least size doesn't matter for CBT, right?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_medium_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Nice cock, bro.</state>
                <state img="#-isthishappy.png">Hey, that's a penis! Good for you, champ!</state>
                <state img="#-isthishappy.png">I'd probably let you fuck me if I had nothing better to do. So there's that!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_large_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-wah.png">I guess it's big, but is that somethin' to be proud of? It's just genetics and, if you're a Chinese business man, ground-up rhino horn at work.</state>
                <state img="#-idle.png">Yeah. It's pretty big. But ya do know that at some point it does just become dead weight, right?</state>
                <state img="#-mendokuse.png">...Some time ago, that would have really gotten me going, but honestly looking at that thing just makes me a bit woozy now.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-idle.png">I guess it's kind of weird how breasts are a big deal to people. That includes myself, but if anything, any group I'm a part of is only made weirder for it.</state>
                <state img="#-thissparksjoy.png">Just so you know, I'm going to be staring directly at you from now on. It's the logical thing to do.</state>
                <state img="#-thissparksjoy.png">Come on now, everyone here wants to see 'em! if that ain't flattering, then iunno what is!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_small_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-isthishappy.png">Oh, fuck, those are adorable! I just wanna poke them and snuggle my nose into them, and pat you on the head for good measure!</state>
                <state img="#-yeahigottime.png">Hey, man. Flat is justice and all that. Plus, they give you more mobility to appreciate bigger busts.</state>
                <state img="#-isthishappy.png">Small tits are delicious, ~name~! Or so I've been told. I'll need a run a taste test to verify!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_medium_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-yeahigottime.png">Y'know, humans are kind of unique in that we have permanent breasts as a secondary sexual characteristic. They're not even well-designed! But they're still hot.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Breasts. Boobs. Bosoms. Bazongas. Lots of things to call them, but I'd rather just lick them.</state>
                <state img="#-MINDBOOLETS.png">Aaaand committed to memory! Good work, ~name~, that's all i needed.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_large_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-isthishappy.png">Talk about gazongas, ~name~! Makes me want to put my dick between 'em, and I don't even have one! Allegedly!</state>
                <state img="#-thissparksjoy.png">Those seem heavy. Mind if I hold them for you? &lt;i&gt;Fuck, that was smooth, Mary!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-MINDBOOLETS.png">Y'know, regular breast inspection is crucial to maintaining their health. As an uncertified medical practitioner, I volunteer.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-thissparksjoy.png">There are few parts on a woman that interest me more. Perhaps the brain. Or ass. Or... iunno, armpits.</state>
                <state img="#-MINDBOOLETS.png">Come on, ~name~, ain't like we haven't seen a coochie before! Well, except for ~player~, they don't seem like they have.</state>
                <state img="#-thissparksjoy.png">This is the end goal of the gay agenda and I am okay with it.</state>
                <state img="#-yeahigottime.png">Hey, if it helps, I too have a vagina. Crazy, i know.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-9" id="2" target="amy" targetSayingMarker="planar_form">
                <test expr="~target.persistent.strange_harmonies~" cmp="&gt;=" value="50" />
                <state img="#-yourearealcomedianbro.png">First time, Amy?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition filter="hairy" role="target" />
                <state img="#-toughcrowd.png">Yeah, I can't be fucked with shaving, either. At least there's demand for hairy coochie, too.</state>
                <state img="#-isthishappy.png">That's the kind of rug I'd like to rub a balloon on! The balloon is a euphemism. For... something!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition filter="shaved" role="target" />
                <state img="#-toughcrowd.png">I don't really bother with shaving. Plus, if my hand twitches when I'm doing somethin' like that, I'll end up with more holes than I'd want down there.</state>
                <state img="#-isthishappy.png">Picture perfect pussy! Speaking of, do you mind pictures?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-MINDBOOLETS.png">Welcome to the coochie gang, ~name~. Get it? coochie gang? Man, I'm a comedic genius ain't I?</state>
                <state img="#-isthishappy.png">Ain't that a precious sight! I'll be sure to cherish it forever and ever!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_lost">
            <case stage="0-9" oneShotId="2">
                <condition role="target" character="amy" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-toughcrowd.png" marker="Amy1">I hear you're a fan of spiders, Amy. So am I. Always wanted to have one as a pet, but I'd just end up killing it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" oneShotId="7">
                <condition filter="gamer" role="target" />
                <state img="#-isthishappy.png">Hey, a fellow gamer! I'd offer to play something together if my hand-eye coordination hadn't gone to complete shit!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" oneShotId="8">
                <condition filter="criminal" role="target" />
                <state img="#-toughcrowd.png">Shit, the feds are on your ass, too? Maybe we'd be better off getting out of dodge now. Things could get ugly.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition filter="blonde" role="target" />
                <state img="#-MINDBOOLETS.png" oneShotId="24">Y'know what they say about blondes - you're all pure evil! Well, I like me some evil!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition filter="school_uniform" role="target" />
                <state img="#-toughcrowd.png" oneShotId="25">I hope that uniform doesn't mean what it implies. The cops want my ass plenty already.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition filter="original_character" role="target" />
                <state img="#-toughcrowd.png" oneShotId="26">...I feel an odd bond with you, ~name~. Like we're.... similar somehow. It creeps me out.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition filter="insane" role="target" />
                <state img="#-headon.png" oneShotId="27">Jesus, you're insufferable. Was I ever &lt;i&gt;this&lt;/i&gt; bad?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_stripping">
            <case stage="0-9" oneShotId="17">
                <condition role="target" character="erufuda" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-idle.png">You seem nervous for just takin'  off a jacket. What, if you pull it off, will you die?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <test expr="~clothing~" value="socks" />
                <state img="#-yeahigottime.png">Shit. Yeah, sorry, I'm gonna be staring now.</state>
                <state img="#-yeahigottime.png">Alright, call me a weird, gay, crazy bitch, but I like feet. And I ain't ashamed to say it.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_stripped">
            <case stage="0-9" oneShotId="18">
                <condition role="target" character="erufuda" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-isthishappy.png">Hah! You're a big girl!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~clothing~" value="socks" />
                <state img="#-thissparksjoy.png">J-just. Wiggle your toes a bit. Please.</state>
                <state img="#-thissparksjoy.png">Y'know, I give some &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; good foot massages, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-idle.png">Don't act like you haven't been achin' for a wank, anyway.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Oh, please, it couldn't be more obvious how much you want to jerk your gherkin right now.</state>
                <state img="#-idle.png">Oh no, poor you, having to jerk off. I feel so sorry for you, you don't even freakin'  know.</state>
                <state img="#-yourearealcomedianbro.png">Come on, bro. You were gonna do this after the game, anyway.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-MINDBOOLETS.png">And just like that, another man falls to his carnal desires. Or something.</state>
                <state img="#-thissparksjoy.png">Gotta say, I am kinda curious to see how you do it. Dudes in porn always do it pretty much the same.</state>
                <state img="#-yourearealcomedianbro.png">Wait, is &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; how you're gonna do it? Weird.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-smug.png">I wonder how you learned to jerk off. Did you figure out how to just rub one out yourself?</state>
                <state img="#-isthishappy.png">Heh, you're really going to town there. Makes me wan to do the same!</state>
                <state img="#-thissparksjoy.png">Honestly, dicks look weird to me. I'm a bigger fan of those expressions you're making.</state>
                <state img="#-isthishappy.png">You should sit on your hand first, to make it seem like someone else is doing it. Or just finger yourself for best results.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Have you ever tried posh-wanking? I hear it makes the cleanup easier, but makes you feel even more pathetic.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" priority="0">
                <condition filter="large_penis" role="target" />
                <state img="#-mendokuse.png">It's kind of just nauseating to watch that thing flop around when you do that.</state>
                <state img="#-yourearealcomedianbro.png">Doesn't your arm get tired doing that? Mine would.</state>
                <state img="#-idle.png">I couldn't stand having a schlong that size. Like, I'd just trip over walking.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-isthishappy.png">And there went the goo!</state>
                <state img="#-thissparksjoy.png">Ahh, the sweet scent of callery pear. Oh, my mistake, it's just jizz.</state>
                <state img="#-isthishappy.png">Who would have thought you're a squirter, ~name~?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-MINDBOOLETS.png">Sorry, ~name~, but if you wanted to maintain modesty, you shoulda been better at this arbitrary card game!</state>
                <state img="#-thissparksjoy.png">Don't worry, ~name~. I'll make sure to stare.</state>
                <state img="#-MINDBOOLETS.png">A predictable loss. This was meant to be from the start.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-yeahigottime.png" oneShotId="21">I wish I had advice to give, but all my knowledge essentially comes from hentai.</state>
                <state img="#-isthishappy.png">Just focus on whoever you want to fuck the most, ~name~! I'll be sure to focus on you, after all!</state>
                <state img="#-MINDBOOLETS.png">Remember, ~name~ - we can all see where you're looking when you do it!</state>
                <state img="#-isthishappy.png">Is there a rule against recordings? Ah, whatever, no way this joint isn't packed with hidden cameras.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-isthishappy.png">Hah, if I close my eyes and listen to it... well, actually, it sounds like you're doing exactly what you're doing!</state>
                <state img="#-thissparksjoy.png">You're doing some good work there. some real fine, honest work.</state>
                <state img="#-isthishappy.png">Is someone gonna need to get the wet floor sign? This is a bar, they gotta have one.</state>
                <state img="#-yeahigottime.png">Shit, I hate sounding lame, but I wish I could look that good doing something like that.</state>
                <state img="#-isthishappy.png">So girls &lt;i&gt;do&lt;/i&gt; make those sounds IRL! Good to know!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="17">Alright, that was pretty good. I'd give that a solid 5/7.</state>
                <state img="#-isthishappy.png" oneShotId="18">Looked like you had fun there, ~name~. Good to know.</state>
                <state img="#-thissparksjoy.png" oneShotId="19">Not gonna lie, you looked hella cute like that. Like, hella.</state>
                <state img="#-yeahigottime.png" oneShotId="20">I wouldn't mind tasting all that. Wouldn't mind at all.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate_first">
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-mendokuse.png">Well, rules are rules. I bet some bullshit was involved, but eh. I'll get to it.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate">
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-yeahigottime.png">I should probably be more excited about this than I am. Jerking it surrounded by hotties should be a dream-come-true, y'know.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="start_masturbating">
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-isthishappy.png">I'll try and give a good show, but it might take a while for me to get going 's all I'm saying!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="masturbating">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-smug.png">I can usually keep going for a while like this. That's a positive, right?</state>
                <state img="#-toughcrowd.png">It used to be that I'd come a lot faster than this. That got a bit complicated, though.</state>
                <state img="#-isthishappy.png">This feels nice and all, but man, do my own fingers just not do the trick.</state>
                <state img="#-yeahigottime.png">I wouldn't say no to a bit of help, you know. The rules on that &lt;i&gt;are&lt;/i&gt; a bit wishy-washy here.</state>
                <state img="#-idle.png">I've never looked up how chicks are supposed to do this. I've seen a bunch of picks telling guys to lean back when they stroke themselves, but nothing on girls.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="heavy_masturbating">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-heavy1.png">Oh, shit! That's it! </state>
                <state img="#-heavy2.png">Eheh. I found the spot, now.</state>
                <state img="#-heavy3.png">God, yes! That's the stuff!</state>
                <state img="#-heavy1.png">Ooo, ooo, let's go!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finishing_masturbating">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-finish.png">Oh, fuck! Fuck, fuck, fuck - YEEEEEEEESSSSS!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-postworkout.png">Fuck! I actually freakin' came! i hadn't done that in... Fuck, I don't even know how long!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="after_masturbating">
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-idle.png">Fucks sake, I can't find where my tie went. I don't &lt;i&gt;like&lt;/i&gt; it, but I want it back!</state>
                <state img="#-headon.png" marker="+sideeffects">Man, doing all that made me... kind of woozy. ugh.</state>
                <state img="#-toughcrowd.png">...I'm actually starting to feel the cod now. Can we get dressed again yet?</state>
                <state img="#-idle.png">Does anyone remember how I got here? I hope I didn't drive. That would've been a terrible idea.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_victory">
            <case stage="1-7">
                <state img="#-MINDBOOLETS.png">Come back in ten billion years if you want to stand a chance against me, ~player~. 'Cause then we'll both be dead. Probably.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-MINDBOOLETS.png">Nothing but fucking net. I'd say you shouldn't cry about it, but I'd feel better if you did.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_defeat">
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-isthishappy.png">Alright, you got me. That was kind of a weird brand of fun. I might have to come back some time when I feel... uh, better.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="global">
            <case stage="0-9" id="7" alsoPlaying="mary" alsoPlayingStage="0-5" alsoPlayingSayingMarker="insanetrigger">
                <condition role="other" character="mary" saidMarker="sanity&gt;=15" sayingMarker="insanetrigger" />
                <state img="#-headon.png">Jesus Christ, as if just having &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; version of me here wasn't bad enough!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="8" alsoPlaying="mary" alsoPlayingStage="6" alsoPlayingSayingMarker="FUCK1">
                <condition role="other" character="mary" saidMarker="FUCKstart" sayingMarker="FUCK1" />
                <state img="#-headon.png">Gah! Fuck, this song's too damn catchy! Curse you, me! Or, shit, curse me, you! Damn it! You get the point!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

    </behaviour>
</opponent>
