<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>

<!--This file was machine generated using the Character Editor v6.7.7 at 12:58:15 AM on September 16, 2022. Do not edit this file directly unless you know what you're doing.-->
<opponent>
    <version>v6.7.7</version>
    <first>Mikan</first>
    <last>Tsumiki</last>
    <label>Mikan</label>
    <gender>female</gender>
    <size>large</size>
    <timer>15</timer>
    <intelligence>average</intelligence>



    <wardrobe>
        <clothing name="panties" generic="underwear" position="lower" type="important" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="bra" generic="bra" position="upper" type="important" />
        <clothing name="shirt and skirt" position="both" type="major" />
        <clothing name="shoes and socks" position="legs" type="minor" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="apron" generic="apron" position="upper" type="extra" />
    </wardrobe>


    <behaviour>
        <trigger id="selected">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="mari" sayingMarker="OppSelected_Mikan" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Ah, no, no, it's alright. I know how to properly apply them. A-And change or remove them if I need to. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Um, hello. Is this the right place for the game...?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_selected">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="mahiru" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png" marker="Mikan_Mahiru_start">M-M-Mahiru!? W-What are you doing here!?</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png" marker="Mikan_Mahiru_start">Eeeek! M-Mahiru!? I-I didn't know you were going to be here!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="chiaki" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png" marker="Mikan_Chiaki_opening">C-Chiaki? I-I didn't know you played games like this!</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="Mikan_Chiaki_opening">C-Chiaki...? W-What are you doing here? I-I um, y-you play games like this?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_start">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="trixie" sayingMarker="Mikan_Compliment" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png" marker="Mikan_Trixie_sudden">W-What!? A-Ah, I mean, um thank you! B-But this is all so sudden!</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png" marker="Mikan_Trixie_sudden">Huh!? Y-You're talking a-about me right? I-I mean, um, t-thank you! B-But this is all so s-sudden!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="chiaki" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="Mikan_chiaki_continue">(&lt;i&gt;Well, I guess it's okay if it's Chiaki...&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="Mikan_chiaki_continue">(&lt;i&gt;Would someone like Chiaki... get mad at me for playing a game like this?&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="45">
                <condition count="3" status="alive" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Um, not that I'm complaining, but... aren't we missing someone?</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Um, i-is it... emptier here? Ah! I-I'm sorry, I shouldn't complain about things that don't matter.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-worried.png">W-We're starting already? B-But I completely forgot to introduce myself!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="swap_cards">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <test expr="~cards~" value="0" />
                <state img="#-worried.png">Does someone like me deserve something this nice?</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I-It feels a bit odd to not exchange anything... Like I'm not participating.</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">Just... huh, ~cards~!?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <test expr="~cards~" value="1" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png">J-Just the one... I-If it's not a bother.</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">W-Will  just one be enough...?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-plead.png">Um, if it's alright with you, could I have ~cards~ cards, please?</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">Um, You can give me whatever cards you want. I-I don't mind.</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">B-But which ones should I take?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Um... o-okay.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="good_hand">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-worried.png">I-Is it really okay for me to receive something s-so valuable?</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">It's been a while since anyone gave me something so... so nice!</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">T-These are so good. It feels a little wrong for me to have them.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I-I don't know why you gave me something like this. B-But... thank you!</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">Thank you for giving me something so nice. Um, if you're ever injured, I could repay the favor!</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">(&lt;i&gt;Does the dealer feel bad for me?&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-stressing.png">I-I can't get too happy at this, o-or it'll just feel worse later!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-4">
                <state img="#-yell.png">Um, I'll try hard not to waste these good cards you gave me, dealer!</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">I'm terribly sorry for making you think about me. But... thank you.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">E-Even if they're just cards... getting something like this makes me f-feel happy.</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">Oh no, w-what if I waste something this precious. W-Won't the dealer get mad at me?</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">H-Having multiple of the same card is good... right?</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">(&lt;i&gt;Is it okay to let myself be happy about these?&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-stressing.png">Uuuu, what do I do? the thought of wasting these makes me so nervous!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-happy.png">I-I'm so happy! This is what I needed right now.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Hehe... I-I'm not sure what I did to make you think of me... B-But thank you...</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">Wow... I-I don't know what to say... T-Thank you.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Right, I-I need to think carefully. I-I don't want to waste these.</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">Can I really do this?</state>
                <state img="#-stressing.png">Uuuu, c-can I really trust this?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">(&lt;i&gt;Deep breaths... deep breaths.&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="okay_hand">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-sad.png">Sometimes... being average isn't so bad.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">T-These don't really stand out. B-But that doesn't bother me...</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">T-These aren't really the best. B-But I don't think they're the worst either... Maybe?</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">I-Is it alright to talk about my cards? O-Or is that considered cheating?</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Um, do I need to... do anything to get better cards?</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Um, don't look at me, I-I really don't have anything special...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-5">
                <state img="#-worried.png">I...I'm not really sure what to do with this.</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">I-Is it okay to ask for help? N-Never mind, I-I guess that wouldn't be fair.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">It's a little difficult to think about my cards right now, ehehe.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">W-With these cards... I-I don't know if I should be worried... or happy.</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">(&lt;i&gt;Should I try bluffing? No, that would be rude!&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Oh... um, are you guys, um... having fun?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-1">
                <state img="#-sad.png">I'm not really good at games, so I don't know how to use cards like these...</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">S-Someone better would probably know how to use these...</state>
                <state img="#-stressing.png">Oh no. W-What if I do something wrong with these!?</state>
                <state img="#-stressing.png">Uuuu, i-it makes me even more nervous when I can't make head or tails about my cards!</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Ah, I really wish I could ask someone for help with these. B-But that would probably be cheating.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">(&lt;i&gt;I have to be careful, I don't want to get my clothes dirty somehow&lt;/i&gt;.)</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">(&lt;i&gt;If I don't say anything, will there be an awkward silence!?&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">(&lt;i&gt;Are they looking at me?&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="bad_hand">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-sad.png">Oh no...</state>
                <state img="#-plead.png">I-I know someone like me has no right to say this. But if it were possible, I'd want a different hand...</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">I-I've been talking about myself so much... D-Do none of you really mind?</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">Is there no hope for me t-this time...?</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I-I guess I should start thinking of what to take off...</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I-I'm prepared for this... so it's okay...</state>
                <state img="#-stressing.png">Uuuu, I-I still need some time to prepare myself.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-5">
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Wait, I'm not ready! I-I-I dropped my cards!</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">Ahh! D-Did you give me these b-because you're mad at me?</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png" oneShotId="2">(&lt;i&gt;No one's doing anything to me here... Do they hate me? Or not care about me?&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-stressing.png">Ahh! Oh no no no no...!</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">O-Oh no! I-I'm going to trip! I-I know it!</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Ah! I-I promise I'm not trying to throw the game...</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I-I've gone this far... So going the rest shouldn't be so bad... right?</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">(&lt;i&gt;Why does this feel... right?&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">A-At this point... everything left feels... precious, ehehe.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="hand">
            <case stage="0-7" id="62" oneShotId="101">
                <condition role="other" character="nagisa" stage="6-7" sayingMarker="nagisa_beach_hiding_place" />
                <test expr="~nagisa.slot~" cmp="!=" value="4" />
                <test expr="~background~" value="beach" />
                <state img="#-fear.png">I-I didn't even think about that! Um... um... I-I'm really good at burying objects in sand... w-we could try that.</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">I-I should have thought about that beforehand. I-I'm sorry! Um... ah... W-We could try burying each other in the sand...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="47">
                <condition role="opp" character="miki_miura" />
                <condition role="opp" character="nagamimi" sayingMarker="nagamimi_miki_mikan_shutupResponse_Insult" />
                <state img="#-panic.png" marker="Mikan_Miki_Nagamimi_nofighting">N-Noooo! P-Please don't be violent!</state>
                <state img="#-stressing.png" marker="Mikan_Miki_Nagamimi_nofighting">I-I, I'm sorry for angering you two. P-Please don't fight!</state>
                <state img="#-yell.png" marker="Mikan_Miki_Nagamimi_nofighting">I-It's really not worth it to fight o-over someone like me! P-Please calm down!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="48">
                <condition role="opp" character="miki_miura" />
                <condition role="opp" character="nagamimi" sayingMarker="nagamimi_miki_mikan_shutupResponse_MikanKnight" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Miki_Nagamimi_worthit">Ah, no, no, I'm sure it's not like that! B-But, um, I-I don't think you w-would get anything out of helping me, Miki.</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png" marker="Mikan_Miki_Nagamimi_worthit">... Right. I-It's really not worth it to... get involved with someone like me, Miki</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="61" oneShotId="100">
                <condition status="masturbating" role="other" />
                <condition role="other" character="nagisa" stage="0-5" sayingMarker="nagisa_poem_prompt" />
                <test expr="~nagisa.slot~" value="1" />
                <state img="#-fear.png">P-Poems? N-No... I-I knew I forgot to study something before the game. I-I'm so sorry!</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">N-No... I-I don't know very many. I-I knew I should have read some before the game! I-I'm so sorry!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="59" oneShotId="99">
                <condition role="other" character="komi-san" stage="1" timeInStage="0" sayingMarker="jacket_off" />
                <state img="#-explain.png">W-Was that not enough f-for you? I-I understand...</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Um, d-did you think we would be mad with only your shoes. B-Because I-I'm fine with whatever you want!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="60" totalRounds="3-">
                <condition count="0" status="exposed" />
                <condition role="other" character="estelle" stage="0-3" sayingMarker="EstelleFocusPrompt" />
                <state img="#-fear.png">I-I'm sorry, I didn't think about this question. Um... uh, d-do medical encyclopedias count?</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">Uh... I-I'm sorry! I-I didn't make any note on how to answer a question like this. Ah... um... do medical encyclopedias count?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="55" oneShotId="96">
                <condition role="other" character="saki_zls" stage="6" timeInStage="0" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Y-You're not wearing two sets of makeup... which means you're an actual Zombie!? I-I guess you don't need that blanket then...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="9" totalRounds="10-">
                <condition role="other" character="jura" stage="0-6" sayingMarker="babies" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png" marker="Mikan_Jura_children">C-Children!? N-No... I-I'm definitely not ready yet... sorry.</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png" marker="Mikan_Jura_children2">N-No... I don't think I'm ready for children... But maybe if I found the right person...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="13" totalRounds="5-">
                <condition role="other" character="rainbow_dash" stage="0-7" sayingMarker="sports_question" />
                <state img="#-sad.png">N-No. I'm pretty slow, so I'm not very good at sports...</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">I-I'm not really good at much besides nursing... sorry.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="46" oneShotId="89" totalRounds="4-">
                <condition role="other" character="colress" stage="0" sayingMarker="ultrawormhole" />
                <state img="#-sad.png">I-I'm sorry. Outside of nursing, I'm really not all that knowledgeable</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Um, I'm sorry, but that's not really my field of expertise. O-Outside of nursing, I-I don't know much.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="48" oneShotId="90">
                <condition role="other" character="kora" stage="1-8" saidMarker="kora_beststory" sayingMarker="kora_gossip" />
                <state img="#-worried.png">U-Um... gossip? S-Sorry, i try not to listen in to other people's conversations. They might get mad at me.</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">Um, I'm really sorry, but I try not to listen to gossip. S-So I don't think I can help you...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="20" oneShotId="41">
                <condition role="other" character="senko" stage="1-4" sayingMarker="senko_pampering" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Senko_worth">Ah, no, no, you don't have to go to that effort for someone like me...</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Senko_work">Um, I don't mean to be rude... But I really don't think it would be... worth it to go to that effort for someone like me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="21" oneShotId="42">
                <condition role="other" character="senko" stage="3-7" sayingMarker="modern_amenities" />
                <state img="#-explain.png" marker="Mikan_Senko_medica"> T-There's so many modern advances in the medical field that I don't know what I'd do without. I-It's hard to know where to begin!</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png" marker="Mikan_Senko_medical">T-There have been so many modern medical advances. Heart treatments have improved, and the internet has made organizing patient's files easier. It's hard to choose just one!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="56" oneShotId="97">
                <condition role="other" character="kumatora" stage="3-9" sayingMarker="kumatora_ask_favfoods" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png">O-Oh... I'm just happy eating what everyone else is eating. B-But, if I had to choose... I-I've always enjoyed Mandarin Oranges!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="120">
                <condition role="other" character="scm" stage="0-8" sayingMarker="scm_mikan" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_SCM_blood">W-Why would blood make me uncomfortable? I-Isn't it...nice?</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_SCM_blood">B-Blood used to make me uncomfortable... But now, I find it kind of nice... is that weird?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-4" oneShotId="107">
                <condition count="1-" role="opp" character="chiaki" timeInStage="0" />
                <state img="#-worried.png">Um, Chiaki? D-Do... do you think I'm weird for playing something like this...?</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">Um, Chiaki? I-I'm really sorry for asking, b-but, do you think I'm... weird for playing something like this?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="15" totalRounds="3-">
                <condition role="other" character="meia" sayingMarker="earth_sightseeing" />
                <state img="#-explain.png" marker="Mikan_Meia_HPA">Y-You could try visiting Hope's Peak Academy. I-It's the most interesting place I've ever gone to.</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="Mikan_Meia_HPA2">I-I'm sorry... I don't go to very many places. M-Maybe you try visiting Hope's Peak academy? I-It's where I go to school. A-And, um, it's definitely interesting.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" oneShotId="40">
                <condition role="opp" character="fischl" sayingMarker="mikan_barbara" />
                <state img="#-fear.png" marker="Mikan_fischl_badmood">I-I'm sorry... D-Did I upset you? Y-You look like you're thinking about something that's p-put you in a bad mood.</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="Mikan_fischl_badmood">Y-Your face... D-Did I do something to put you in a bad mood...?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="43">
                <condition role="opp" character="miki_miura" saidMarker="Miki_Mikan_drugs" />
                <state img="#-explain.png" marker="Mikan_Miki_sickness">Ah, you're right. I wouldn't be able to prescribe you any medication without proper medical justification.</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png" marker="Mikan_Miki_sickness">Y-Yes, that's right. I couldn't give you a prescription without medical justification. And "school sickness" definitely wouldn't count.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="54">
                <condition role="opp" character="mari" sayingMarker="Mikan_Oranges" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="Mikan_Mari_mikan">I-I do, actually! I-I used to split them into pieces and eat a little bit at a time.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="Mikan_Mari_mikan">Y-Yes! When I was little I would split them into small pieces and e-eat them over time. S-So they would last longer.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="55">
                <condition role="opp" character="mari" sayingMarker="Mikan_StrongApproach" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Mari_repeat">Ehehe... Do, do you think you could say that again? Ehehe.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Mari_repeat">Ah, d-don't worry. I-It's really not a problem. B-But, um, do you think you could repeat that? Ehehe.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="56">
                <condition role="opp" character="mari" sayingMarker="Mikan_Work" />
                <state img="#-explain.png" marker="Mikan_Mari_infirmary">O-Oh, well, I actually run the infirmary in my school. I-In some ways... it is my class.</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png" marker="Mikan_Mari_infirmary">Well, actually I manage my school's infirmary. I-It takes up most of my days...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="57">
                <condition role="opp" character="mari" sayingMarker="Mikan_Expertise" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Mari_school">W-Well... yes. B-But the school I go to... T-They said it was made to develop those with a p-particular talents. Ah! I-if you ever get hurt I could give you a demonstration!</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Mari_school">U-Um, well, yes. B-But my school is pretty different from most. T-They said it was made to help those with a "particular talent" U-Um, if you're ever hurt, I could give you a demonstration! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7" oneShotId="58">
                <condition role="opp" character="mahiru" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Mahiru_picture">Ehehe, Mahiru. I-I don't think I would mind having my picture taken like this...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-4" oneShotId="59">
                <condition role="opp" character="mahiru" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">I-If only Hiyoko or Ibuki were here. I-It might have been fun to play a game like this with them!</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Um, it was strange at first... But p-playing a game like this with you has been fun, Mahiru! I-I wonder if Ibuki or Hiyoko would ever want to play... Ah! Only if you wouldn't mind</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-1" oneShotId="60">
                <condition role="opp" character="mahiru" />
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="Mikan_Mahiru_friendt">(&lt;i&gt;Oh no... what if I beat Mahiru and she gets mad at me?&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="Mikan_Mahiru_friend">M-Mahiru, um, if I win. W-Will you still want to be my friend?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-7" id="37" oneShotId="70">
                <condition count="1-5" role="opp" var="leader" />
                <test expr="~leader.place~" value="1" />
                <test expr="~self.place~" cmp="&gt;" value="1" />
                <state img="#-worried.png">T-This isn't one of those games where ~leader~ gets to order us around because ~leader.ifMale(he's|she's)~ leading, r-right?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">T-This isn't one of those games where we have to do whatever ~leader~ says because ~leader.ifMale(he's|she's)~ winning, r-right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="105">
                <condition role="opp" character="chiaki" />
                <state img="#-explain.png">I-In a strange way... T-This almost reminds me of when we all played video games together. D-Do you remember, Chiaki?</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">A-Ah! Do  you remember when we all played games together, Chiaki? T-This is kind of like that, r-right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" oneShotId="124">
                <test expr="~month.number~" value="5" />
                <test expr="~day.number~" value="12" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Um, I-It's actually my birthday today... Ah! N-Not that I e-expected any of you to get me a g-gift or something like that!</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">Um, T-Today is actually my birthday. S-Should I have brought cake o-or something like that?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7" oneShotId="125">
                <test expr="~month.number~" value="5" />
                <test expr="~day.number~" value="12" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">E-Even though this is a strange thing to do on my birthday, I-I'm still having a really fun time.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Um, thank you all for playing with me. T-This is actually the most fun I've had on birthday... in a really long time.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="94">
                <test expr="~background~" value="bedroom" />
                <alternative>
                    <condition count="0" gender="male" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <condition count="4-" gender="female" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">T-This is almost like a sleepover. I-I think... I've never actually been to one.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Ehehe, in a room like this, this is almost like a sleepover! I-I've never had one of those before...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="76">
                <test expr="~background~" value="alley" />
                <state img="#-panic.png">T-This is definitely the type of place you only see in crime documentaries! I-I don't want to get stabbed!</state>
                <state img="#-panic.png">O-Oh no, I feel like if I stay here I'll get kidnapped and never seen again! I-I don't want that to happen!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="3">
                <condition filter="weapon" />
                <state img="#-panic.png">W-W-Why would you bring a weapon! A-Are we in danger!?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5" oneShotId="4">
                <condition filter="weapon" />
                <state img="#-plead.png">P-Please be careful with that weapon! I-I wouldn't want anyone to get hurt.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="77">
                <condition filter="tattoo" role="opp" />
                <state img="#-explain.png" weight="20" collectible="Mikan's_Apron" collectible-value="+1">Um, while getting a tattoo is generally safe, there are still associated risks. Allergic reactions from the ink have been known to occur. A-And if the inking machine hasn't been cleaned, blood-borne diseases can be caught.</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png" weight="20" collectible="Mikan's_Apron" collectible-value="+1">W-While getting a tattoo isn't usually dangerous, there are some risks associated. You should take precautions before getting one. Familiarize yourself with the parlor to make sure you trust it. A-And always make sure your tattooist wears a fresh pair of gloves.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I-I almost got a tattoo once... N-Never mind, I-I don't want to talk about it...</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">T-Tattoos can be a little scary... A-Ah! not that I think you're a scary person or anything like that...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="78">
                <condition filter="pierced_nipples" role="opp" />
                <state img="#-explain.png" weight="20" collectible="Mikan's_Apron" collectible-value="+1">It's perfectly normal for skin around a new piercing to be red and tender for a few days afterward, but if it persists for longer, you should consult a doctor. Oh, but I guess you didn't need to know that if you already have a piercing.</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png" weight="20" collectible="Mikan's_Apron" collectible-value="+1">I-It's always smart to take care of your piercing. When it's new, always make sure to clean the skin around it, but don't move the piercing around too much. A-Ah, but I guess you don't need to know that if you already have a piercing.</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">Y-You're not going to want to give me a piercing as well, ri-right?</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">I-I, um, n-not that there's anything wrong with them... b-but you don't want to give me a piercing too, r-right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="93">
                <alternative>
                    <condition count="5-" gender="female" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Um, not that It's any problem to me... But... doesn't this game seem a little unbalanced?</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Not that I... would ever think to do anything as rude as complain. But... doesn't this seem a bit... unbalanced?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Um, something like this doesn't bother me. I-I'm really okay in a game with only women.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="18" oneShotId="121">
                <alternative>
                    <condition role="self" notSaidMarker="Mikan_medicalhelp02" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <condition role="self" notSaidMarker="Mikan_medicalhelp01" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-explain.png" marker="Mikan_medicalhelp01">I-I know a game like this can be stressful. So if anyone feels they need medical attention, please feel free to ask me.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="Mikan_medicalhelp02">If… If anyone starts to feel sick, I’m sure I can help. That’s what nurses are for, after all.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" priority="0">
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~background~" value="beach" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~background~" value="tiki bar" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-explain.png" oneShotId="108">Always remember to thoroughly apply sunscreen when on the beach. If you need help, it's always acceptable to ask someone to apply it for you!</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png" oneShotId="109">I-I think... something really important happened to me in a place like this. B-But I really can't remember what!</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png" oneShotId="110">I hope I don't start to tan... It reminds me too much of being burnt.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" oneShotId="111">I-I wonder if i should try and build a sand castle later. I would always try when I was little, but someone would always destroy it before I could finish.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" priority="0">
                <test expr="~background~" value="holiday lodge" />
                <state img="#-sad.png" oneShotId="100">I-I never liked winter... p-people get sick more. A-And I always trip more. B-But this place is nice...</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="101">I-I always loved Christmas movies as a kid. E-Everyone in them always looked so happy!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" priority="0">
                <test expr="~background~" value="library" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="104">L-Libraries are nice... When I run into a library, a-anybody chasing me just gives up. A-And nobody picks on me either.</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png" oneShotId="105">T-There are so many nice things to read in a library. I-I've always enjoyed technical books, l-like medical encyclopedias. B-But horror novels are also nice.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="33" priority="0">
                <test expr="~background~" value="mansion" />
                <state img="#-worried.png">U-Um, are you sure it's safe to play in a place like this? I-I wouldn't want to trip and damage anything.</state>
                <state img="#-yell.png">T-The owners of this mansion would probably get really mad if I broke something! I-I'll have to be extra careful!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="34" priority="0">
                <test expr="~background~" value="bedroom" />
                <state img="#-worried.png">W-Wait... W-Whose room is this. I-Is it yours, ~player~?</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">D-Did you invite me to your room to play strip poker, ~player~? I-I don't know if I'm ready for a step forward like that!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-stressing.png" oneShotId="36">Uuu, I'm sorry if I sound nervous. I just really want this to go well.</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png" oneShotId="37">Even t-though I-I'm not hurt anymore. I-I still wear these bandages because I find them... comforting. I-Is that weird?</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png" oneShotId="38">Um, i-if you ever have trouble sleeping, try avoiding stimulants before you sleep, a-and try some light stretches. L-Little things like that can help with your sleep quality.</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png" oneShotId="39">H-Has anyone read any good stories recently? I-I read a horror story I really enjoyed, hehe...</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png" oneShotId="40">Um... um, um I-I went to the trouble of memorizing 5,000 different poker strategies. B-But now that we're playing, I-I can't remember any of them! </state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" oneShotId="41">Hm... I wonder what sorts of drinks they have here. It's important to stay hydrated after all.</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png" oneShotId="42">U-Um, there may be lots of things I'm not good at. B-But I'll do anything. S-So please let me know if you'd ever like some help.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="35">U-Um, would anyone want me to buy them a drink? I-It would only be fair after you let me play this game with you.</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png" oneShotId="51">I-I have a... classmate, N-Nagito. I-I kind of wish I had his luck right now. Ah! B-But then I'd probably get kicked out!</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" oneShotId="62">H-Honestly... I feel a little lonely without some of my friends like Hiyoko, o-or Ibuki. N-Not to say I don't like playing with you a-all!</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" oneShotId="87">D-Do you think some music w-would make this a more pleasant time? T-There's a musician in my class a-at Hope's Peak. T-Though her music i-isn't what I'd call... ordinary.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-5">
                <state img="#-worried.png" oneShotId="34">W-We get our clothes back after the game, right? This isn't s-some type of trick?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">T-This game is really fun. I-I'm glad none of you mind playing it with me.</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">If you're ever feeling sick, please don't come to a game like this. You'll only feel worse, and you'll put others at risk. </state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">Ehehe, I-I'm usually out of a game like this pretty quickly. I-It's actually a little nice to play longer.</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">I-I went to the trouble of learning some poker tricks and strategies. B-But... right now, I-I really wish I could remember them.</state>
                <state img="#-stressing.png">U-Um, p-please let me know if I ever say anything weird or u-unnecessary. I-I wouldn't want to be a burden on all of you.</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">Please let me know if there's any way I could be helpful. Um, I'm not good at much, but I'll do anything! Um, besides dying, that is.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">♫ Bandage wrap... Bandage wrap... Bandage wrap. ♫</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">A classmate of mine... T-Teruteru, h-he enjoys games like these... a lot. B-But I kind of don't hope I see him here. I-Is that rude?</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png" oneShotId="99">I have a... friend named Junko. S-She's so confident... I think she'd look great playing a game like this...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">W-While I'm happy just to be here, um, there's a part of me which maybe... wants to... ah, strip more.</state>
                <state img="#-stressing.png">Um, should I be taking notes on the conversation? I-I don't want to forget anything and upset someone.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="cynthia" />
                <alternative>
                    <condition role="opp" character="cynthia" saying="My, you wouldn't happen to be a Pokémon center nurse, would you? It's very rare I see one of you this far away from a Pokémon center." />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <condition role="opp" character="cynthia" saying="I might be mistaken, but you've got that unmistakeable look of a Pokémon center nurse. I'm simply not used to seeing one in a place that's nowhere near a Pokémon center." />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Cynthia_nurse">Um, n-no... I'm sorry to disappoint... but I'm just a regular nurse... and I work in hospitals and not, um, a-a Pokemon center... sorry.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Cynthia_nurse">I'm afraid to say it... but I'm just a regular nurse, a-and not a... Pokemon center one. I-I do spend a lot of my time in hospitals though!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-1" id="66">
                <condition role="other" character="wikipe-tan" stage="1-8" saidMarker="MikanTeacher2" sayingMarker="Mikan_Curious_1" />
                <state img="#-explain.png" marker="Mikan_WPtan_yukizome">Oh um, h-her name was Chisa Yukizome!</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png" marker="Mikan_WPtan_yukizome">W-Well um, her name was Chisa Yukizome! H-have you heard of her before?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="neptune" stage="4-9" saidMarker="nep_mikan_outfit1" sayingMarker="nep_mikan_bandaging1" />
                <state img="#-stressing.png" marker="Mikan_Neptune_care">O-Of course not! I-I always make sure to give my patients the best care I can!</state>
                <state img="#-stressing.png" marker="Mikan_Neptune_care">N-Not if I can help it! I-I always try to give the  best s-service I can to a patient!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="jura" stage="0-6" sayingMarker="mikan0" />
                <state img="#-plead.png" marker="Mikan_Jura_panic">I-I may not be good at a lot of things, b-but I promise I'm good at nursing. I-I could never panic when a patient's life is my responsibility.</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">H-Huh? N-No, I can a-always control myself when a patient needs me!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="meia" stage="0-5" sayingMarker="mikan0" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Meia_help">U-Um, I would be happy to help... But, I-I think I may need some more information. W-What do you mean by "ship"? I-I've never really been on a boat before...</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Meia_both">U-Um, while I would love to help you... I-I don't know who would run my school's infirmary instead of me. S-So... is there any way I could do both...?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="revy" stage="0-7" sayingMarker="mikan0" />
                <state img="#-fear.png" marker="Mikan_revy_buy">Eeek! I'm sorry! I-I'll get to it right away! D-Do you also want some of my money?</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png" marker="Mikan_Revy_buy">A-Ahhh! Sorry, I-I'm sorry! I'll get right to it. W-Would you like me to buy you something as well?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="22">
                <condition role="opp" character="fluttershy" stage="0-6" sayingMarker="Mikan_are_you_ok" />
                <state img="#-explain.png" marker="Mikan_Fluttershy_notsick">I'm not feeling sick, i-if that's what you mean. I made sure to take my vitamins today, a-and I double-checked for any symptoms before coming.</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png" marker="Mikan_Fluttershy_notsick">Well... I'm not injured right now, if that's what you mean. B-But I brought some extra bandages just to be safe.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="23">
                <condition role="opp" character="fluttershy" stage="0-6" sayingMarker="Mikan_nurse_question" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Fluttershy_nursereason">W-Well... um, t-the sick and injured... they always need me. It's why... I could never leave the sick and injured alone.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Fluttershy_mursereason">W-Well, i-it's a little hard to say... but, sick or injured people... they depend on me absolutely. It's why... I have to be a nurse.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="magma_grunt" sayingMarker="mg_mikan_bullied" />
                <state img="#-fear.png" marker="Mikan_MG_pickon">I-I-I'm sorry for being a dweeb! P-Please don't pick on me here...!</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png" marker="Mikan_MG_pickon">I-I'm really sorry for being a dweeb. But please don't get violent...!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="magma_grunt" sayingMarker="mg_mikan_picked_last" />
                <state img="#-sad.png" marker="Mikan_MG_nursing">Y-You're right... I-I'm not good at much else besides nursing. I'm sorry...</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">I-It's true... I'm not very good at physical activities. I-I'm sorry... I'll try to be better.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="nagamimi" sayingMarker="nagamimi_mikan_insult2" />
                <state img="#-sad.png" marker="Mikan_Nagamimi_insulted2">I can't change it... T-This is the best it gets for someone like me...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="nagamimi" sayingMarker="nagamimi_mikan_insult3" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png" marker="Mikan_Nagamimi_insulted3">I-I'm not useless! I-I could help you when you're sick... O-Or act as a coat rack for you. O-Or even a footstool if you needed one!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="nagamimi" sayingMarker="nagamimi_mikan_insult4" />
                <state img="#-stressing.png" marker="Mikan_Nagamimi_insulted4">I-I'm sorry for being trash. P-Please don't remove me from the game...!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="nagamimi" sayingMarker="nagamimi_mikan_insult5" />
                <state img="#-stressing.png" marker="Mikan_Nagamimi_insulted5">N-None... I-I swear! I-I would never let a patient under my responsibility die like that!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="nagamimi" sayingMarker="nagamimi_mikan_insult11" />
                <state img="#-fear.png" marker="Mikan_nagamimi_insulted11">I-I'm sorry, I'm really sorry! I-I  don't have any gauze with me right now. W-Will bandages work for you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="nagamimi" sayingMarker="nagamimi_mikan_insult6" />
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="Mikan_Nagamimi_insulted6">H-Huh? I d-don't even think that's possible... Not while I'm... still alive, anyway.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="nagamimi" sayingMarker="nagamimi_mikan_insult7" />
                <state img="#-sad.png">I promise I'm not acting... I-I'm really sorry, b-but this is really... me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="nagamimi" sayingMarker="nagamimi_mikan_insult9" />
                <state img="#-fear.png">None! Really! I-I'm always extra careful when it comes to keeping a patient alive!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="nagamimi" sayingMarker="nagamimi_mikan_insult12" />
                <state img="#-worried.png">Huh? N-Not... not really. I-I'm sorry if that i-isn't what you wanted to hear...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="nagamimi" sayingMarker="nagamimi_mikan_insult13" />
                <state img="#-sad.png">I-I'm sorry... I, um, I didn't c-choose my hair looking like this... N-Not that I mean to disagree with you! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="nagamimi" sayingMarker="nagamimi_mikan_insult14" />
                <state img="#-explain.png">U-Um... my primary work isn't with children. But if it was, I-I promise I'd give them the best care possible!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="nagamimi" sayingMarker="nagamimi_mikan_insult10" />
                <state img="#-fear.png">H-huh? I-I'm really sorry, but I-I don't really understand what you mean...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="nagamimi" sayingMarker="nagamimi_mikan_insult1" />
                <state img="#-sad.png">I-I know. I'm kind of... used to it. S-So I don't... really mind if y-you wanted to do it to.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="nagamimi" sayingMarker="nagamimi_mikan_insult8" />
                <state img="#-worried.png">Huh? Maybe I could give you a demonstration? W-Would that help?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="mari" sayingMarker="Mikan_HiddenDepths1" />
                <state img="#-fear.png">W-What do you mean...? I'm not trying to h-hide anything... I swear!</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">Huh? I-I'm not trying to deceive you. T-This is how I really am. Please believe me!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="opp" character="mari" sayingMarker="Mikan_Attention1" />
                <state img="#-sad.png" marker="Mikan_Mari_distraction">I, um, I won't lie... having others notice me feels good... B-But please let me know if I'm taking away from the other players. I-I don't want to be a burden.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Mari_distraction">Um, while being noticed is definitely... nice. I-I wouldn't want to be a distraction from everyone else... I-If that's okay.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="critical_darling" sayingMarker="Mikan_NotForced1" />
                <state img="#-yell.png" marker="Mikan_CD_behere">N-N-No, I promise! I'm definitely not being forced into this. I-I really do want to be here!</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="Mikan_CD_behere">Um, I swear no one's forcing me to be here... S-Sorry if I'm being too nervous.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="24">
                <condition role="other" character="fina" sayingMarker="FinaMikanStart1" />
                <state img="#-explain.png" marker="Mikan_Fina_respone1">Um... e-everyone who goes to my school gets a title like that. I... don't know if I've met an... Ultimate Pirate yet though.</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png" marker="Mikan_Fina_response1">Um, e-everyone who attends t-the school I go to gets a title like mine. I-I hope I don't meet an Ultimate Pirate though...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="miki_miura" saidMarker="miki_mikan_bandage" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Miki_endure">I-It's nice to hear t-that someone else does the same thing... Ah! N-Not that I'd think we're on the same level. I-I didn't mean to put down what you've gone through... sorry.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Miki_endure">Hehe, i-it's nice to see I'm not the only one... Um, n-not to say we're on the same level. I-I can definitely see you've endured more than I have</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="tomoko" sayingMarker="MikanApron1" />
                <state img="#-sad.png" marker="Mikan_Tomoko_popular">M-Me? I-I don't think someone like me... can become popular no matter what I do...</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png" marker="Mikan_Tomoko_popular">... No matter what I do, I-I don't think someone like me could ever be popular with people.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" oneShotId="49">
                <condition role="opp" character="miki_miura" sayingMarker="miki_mikan_disabled" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Miki_help">D-Disabled students? Well, I'd love to help. B-But I'd need some more specifics of the lengths of the disability i-in order to.</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png" marker="Mikan_Miki_help">Oh, o-of course I'd love to help in any way I could. Do you have any specifics about the disability? It may help in providing the best care I can.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="noelle" saying="Please don't take offense, but is that red streak part of the design of your apron? If it's blood, I know a neat trick to get blood out of white apron, no matter how long it's been stained!" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Noelle_clean">Ah, no, no, it isn't blood. I-I always make sure my apron is properly sanitized.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Noelle_clean">O-Oh, don't worry, i-it's not blood. I wouldn't let my apron become so... unsanitary.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="heris" sayingMarker="HerisMikanDrive" />
                <state img="#-sad.png" marker="Mikan_Heris_reason">W-Well, when I was young, I'd get beat up a lot. S-Since there was no one to treat me, I-I started doing it myself. A-And soon I got good at it. That's it... really. </state>
                <state img="#-sad.png" marker="Mikan_Heris_reason">W-When I was a kid, I'd get hurt a lot. A-And since no was there to help, I-I started to treat myself. A-And soon I started to become good at it. T-That's all...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="barbara" sayingMarker="MikanApron1" />
                <state img="#-explain.png" marker="Mikan_Barbara_medical">W-Well, it's definitely a challenge at times. Especially with how long many injuries take to heal. B-But advances in medical technology are starting to make things easier!</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png" marker="Mikan_Barbara_medical">Well... yes, at times, it can be challenge. Many injuries and illnesses take a while to heal, and can leave irreversible damage. B-But the medical field is advancing every day!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="opp" character="fina" sayingMarker="FinaMikanStart2" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Fina_worse">Ah, no, no, you don't have to do anything. I-I'll try not to make the game worse for you anymore, s-sorry.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Fina_worse">Ahh! I-I'm sorry! I promise I'm enjoying myself. I-I'll try to calm down so I don't make the game worse for you!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="opp" character="miki_miura" saidMarker="miki_mikan_cutehelp" />
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="Mikan_Miki_unsure">Um, thank you very much, b-but I'm really not sure h-how you could help me do that. I-I'm sorry.</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="Mikan_Miki_unsure">U-Um Thank you... But I don't really know how you could help me with that... Sorry...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="yuri" sayingMarker="mikan_nursing" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Yuri_helpmany">Well...  I know it sounds a bit strange, b-but I'd like to do all of those. I-I want to help as many people as possible...</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Yuri_helpmany">I think I would like to do all of those, Yuri. N-Not at the same time of course... But I'd like to help as many people as possible.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="zoe" sayingMarker="MikanFanservice" />
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="Mikan_Zoe_past">Huh? W-Why? H-Have you seen me at a game like this before?</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="Mikan_Zoe_past">I-It doesn't surprise you? W-Why? H-have we met at a game like this i-in the past?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="zoe" sayingMarker="MikanTripping" />
                <state img="#-sad.png" marker="Mikan_Zoe_notrip">I-Is my tripping really that well known? I-I'm sorry, I'll try to be extra careful not to trip...</state>
                <state img="#-yell.png" marker="Mikan_Zoe_notrip">G-Got it! I-I'm sorry you had to see my tripping before, b-but I'll try really hard not to trip r-right now!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="zoe" sayingMarker="MikanReason" />
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="Mikan_Zoe_parents">Um, I'll definitely care for anyone who falls ill here... B-But there's no chance my parents show up, right?</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png" marker="Mikan_Zoe_parents">U-Um, while I'll definitely care for anyone who gets sick here... T-There really isn't a chance of my parents showing up, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="opp" character="cynthia" sayingMarker="MikanStrip11" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png">W-Well... I don't want to brag.  B-But I've always been good at... knowing when people are hurt. E-Even if they don't show it.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">W-Well... I don't think I'm better than most... But I've always been able to read people's facial expressions... a-and body signs. S-So I can tell when they're hurt, e-even if they don't know...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="opp" character="mari" sayingMarker="Mikan_Daring" />
                <state img="#-yell.png" marker="Mikan_Mari_more">A-Alright! Y-You've been so nice to me. I-I promise I'll take off more this time. I-It wouldn't be a problem at all!</state>
                <state img="#-yell.png" marker="Mikan_Mari_more">Um, okay! Since you've been so nice to me, I-I'll try to take off some more this time! I-It won't bother me at all.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="opp" character="mari" sayingMarker="Mikan_EyesOnYou" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Mari_enjoyable">U-Um... Thank you. Knowing someone like you is paying attention... I-It makes this more enjoyable. I-I'll definitely try to take off more this time.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="opp" character="mari" sayingMarker="Mikan_EyesOnYou" />
                <state img="#-horny.png">W-Wow... Hearing you say that... I'll definitely try to take off more this time... don't worry.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="nami" sayingMarker="mikan0" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Nami_friends">U-Um... okay! If it's no issue for you. T-Then I wouldn't mind... getting along.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Nami_friends">Oh, um, alright! I-If you really don't mind... Then I would be okay with being... friends.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="opp" character="nami" saying="Mikan, you're a little more, uhhh... &lt;i&gt;mellow&lt;/i&gt; than the other medical professionals I've met. But maybe a little too much... What would you do if there was a patient that needed your help, but was also very rude to you? Would you just leave them alone?" />
                <state img="#-yell.png" marker="Mikan_Nami_aid">O-Of course not! It's part of my duty as a nurse to give aid to anyone who needs it. N-No matter what they say or do to me.</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png" marker="Mikan_Nami_aid">N-No... I would still help them. E-Even if they're rude or hurtful to me... it's still part of my duties as a nurse to help anyone who needs it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="opp" character="nami" saying="Don't take this the wrong way, Mikan, but out of all the doctors and nurses I've met you're probably the most... timid. If you ever encountered someone who needed your help, but didn't want it, what would you do?" />
                <state img="#-sad.png" marker="Mikan_Nami_aid">Um, I know people have a right to refuse help... a-and I can't force anyone... B-But I would still have to everything I could to convince them they need the help...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="opp" character="nami" sayingMarker="mikan2" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png" marker="Mikan_Nami_really">R-Really!? I-Is it really okay to do that for someone like me?</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png" marker="Mikan_Nami_really">Huh!? A-Are you sure? I-Is it really okay to go to the effort on someone like me?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="leon" sayingMarker="leon01" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png" marker="Mikan_Leon_worry">W-What? Um, Y-Yes! Sorry if I worried you.</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png" marker="Mikan_Leon_worry">Hm? U-Um, Yes! I-I'm sorry if I alarmed you!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="opp" character="leon" sayingMarker="leon11" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Leon_job">Ehehe, thank you... B-But we're just doing our jobs... S-So it's nothing really...</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Leon_job">U-Um, t-thank you, Leon. W-We're just doing our duty as nurses... S-So it's really okay...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="opp" character="leon" sayingMarker="leon21" />
                <state img="#-explain.png">N-Nope, no sore spots. I-I know I'm wearing bandages. But I promise I am completely healthy</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">Um, everything's alright here. I-I know that I am wearing bandages. B-But I promise I'm not injured in anyway right now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="saki" sayingMarker="SakiMikanGreeting" />
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="Mikan_Saki_upset">Um, Saki? Are you alright? Y-You look like you're upset. I-Is it because of me?</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="Mikan_Saki_upset">S-Saki? I-I don't mean to pry. But, a-am I upsetting you at all? Y-You look like you're thinking about something which put you in a bad mood...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="opp" character="mari" sayingMarker="Mikan_TurnOn1" />
                <state img="#-horny.png" marker="Mikan_Mari_morepls">I-I didn't realize at first, B-But this does make feel good. Please... keep going.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png" marker="Mikan_Mari_morepls">Y-You're right... T-This does feel good. P-Please keep on going...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="opp" character="mari" saying="You really like this, don't you Mikan? Feeling my eyes on you, watching me take in all of your gorgeous curves and features... it's turning you on, isn't it?" />
                <state img="#-horny.png" marker="Mikan_Mari_morepls">Y-Yes... it is, i-it really is. I-I'd really like more...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="opp" character="mari" saying="My... this is turning you on, isn't it Mikan? Watching me drink in your sexy little body, knowing you have me wrapped around your finger..." />
                <state img="#-horny.png" marker="Mikan_Mari_morepls">I-is it really like that? Ehehe... T-Then I'd be happy to give you more...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-4" oneShotId="71">
                <condition role="opp" character="myriam" sayingMarker="mikan_strip_1" />
                <state img="#-stressing.png" marker="Mikan_Myriam_demonstration">I-I know I'm not very good at cards, b-but I promise I'm a good nurse! U-Um, I brought some extra bandages with me. I-I could give you a demonstration if you want!</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Myriam_demonstration">Um, I don't mean to be rude, but e-even if I'm bad at cards, I-I promise I'm not a bad nurse! U-Um, would you like a demonstration to prove it? I-I brought some extra bandages with me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-4">
                <condition role="opp" character="myriam" sayingMarker="mikan_strip_2" />
                <state img="#-yell.png" marker="Mikan_Myriam_actor">N-No, I-I'm not an actor! Um, do you want me to prove it to you! J-Just tell me what you want me to do, a-and I'll do it!</state>
                <state img="#-yell.png" marker="Mikan_Myriam_actor">Huh!? I-I promise I'm not an actor! Um, um, I can prove it to you! I-If you tell me what you're thinking of, I-I promise I can do it!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" oneShotId="73">
                <condition role="opp" character="miki_miura" saidMarker="miki_mikan_suzuhelp" />
                <state img="#-explain.png" marker="Mikan_Miki_morequestions">T-That's good. Creating a safe environment like that is very beneficial. To that end, I assume your school is aware and prepared for her condition? </state>
                <state img="#-explain.png" marker="Mikan_Miki_morequestions">S-Support like that can be very beneficial for creating a safe environment. Um, speaking of which, I assume your school is aware and prepared for her condition?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="opp" character="fina" sayingMarker="FinaMikanStart3" />
                <state img="#-explain.png" marker="Mikan_Fina_overwork">W-Well... most of the patients I've treated are members of my school. M-Many of them are artists, a-and they often overwork themselves until they collapse! I-it's quite a problem.</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png" marker="Mikan_Fina_overwork">U-Um, I've only really treated other students at my school. B-But it's not common for an artist, o-or an athlete to overwork themselves to the point of collapse. I-I've gotten good at treating them.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="kaz" sayingMarker="Mikan_s0_1" />
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="Mikan_Kaz_nurse">H-Helenist? U-Um no, I'm sorry b-but I'm just a nurse...</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="Mikan_Kaz_nurse">Um,  I'm really sorry, but I don't know what a H-Helenist is! I-I'm just a nurse...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="opp" character="cynthia" sayingMarker="MikanStrip21" />
                <state img="#-explain.png" marker="Mikan_Cynthia_book">O-Oh, well I-I haven't thought too much about it, but I've always enjoyed reading! E-Especially horror novels or medical novels!</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png" marker="Mikan_Cynthia_book">Hm, w-well... I suppose I've always liked reading when I'm not busy. E-Especially a good medical encyclopedia or horror novel!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="opp" character="heris" sayingMarker="HerisMikanStudent" />
                <state img="#-explain.png" marker="Mikan_Heris_interesting">H-Hope's Peak? I-It's not a... normal school. Um, you need to have some kind of... talent to enroll.</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png" marker="Mikan_Heris_interesting">H-Hope's Peak? I-It's an... interesting place! Y-You have to have some kind talent to enroll. So... i-it's never boring.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="wasp" saying="I feel better knowing we have a nurse here just in case! I hear the forfeits here can get kind of intense." />
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="Mikan_wasp_violent">N-Not that I'd ever turn down an opportunity to help. But... does that kind of thing usually get violent...?</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="Mikan_wasp_violent">Um, I'm always happy to help. But... do forfeits really usually get violent?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="fischl" sayingMarker="fischl_mikanmust01" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_fishy_school">Ah, n-no. I-I'm sorry to mislead you, but Hope's Peak Academy is the name of the school I attend.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_fishy_school">Oh, um, no. I-I apologize for disappointing you, but Hope's Peak Academy is just... the school I attend.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="jim" sayingMarker="Mikan0a" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Ah! Right now, I'm working as nurse in my school's infirmary. I-I haven't really thought about where I'll  go after I graduate...</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Oh... well right now I'm working as my school's nurse. But... I don't really know where I'll go afterward</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="fischl" sayingMarker="fischl_mikanmust02" />
                <state img="#-stressing.png" marker="Mikan_fishy_happy">Right, right, I'll try to be more happy... I-I'm sorry! I don't know if that's something I can do on the spot.</state>
                <state img="#-stressing.png" marker="Mikan_fishy_happy">Um... uh... I-I really want to be more happy. B-But I don't know if it's something I can do on the spot!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="kumatora" sayingMarker="mikan_greet" />
                <state img="#-sad.png" marker="Mikan_KT_hair">I-I... I didn't choose for it to look this way... </state>
                <state img="#-sad.png" marker="Mikan_KT_hair">I-I'm sorry... b-but my looking like this... it wasn't my choice.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="mari_setogaya" sayingMarker="Mikan_bandages_worry" />
                <state img="#-explain.png" marker="Mikan_MariS_comfort">O-Oh, um, don't worry! I'm not injured right now. I-It's just... comfortable to wear these.</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png" marker="Mikan_MariS_comfort">Oh, I-I sorry if I worried you, b-but I'm not hurt right now. I-It's just wearing these is... comforting.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="heris" sayingMarker="HerisMikanAttraction" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png" marker="Mikan_Heris_thanks">Y-You are!? I mean, u-um, oh... T-Thank you!</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png" marker="Mikan_Heris_thanks">H-Huh!? Y-You mean m-me? Um... ah, thank you!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="turandot" sayingMarker="mikan_0" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Turan_maid">Um... chambermaid...? I-I'm sorry, but I'm a nurse. B-But I-I could definitely be your maid if you wanted me to be!</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Turan_maid">I-I'm sorry, I'm actually a nurse, um, not a chambermaid. B-But if you wanted me to, I-I could definitely be your maid!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="opp" character="jim" sayingMarker="Mikan1a" />
                <state img="#-sad.png" marker="Mikan_Raynor_loop">W-Wow... I didn't even know that was possible. I-I'm sorry for being so unknowledgeable...</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png" marker="Mikan_Raynor_loop">S-Such a thing is... really possible? W-Wow, I-I'm sorry for being so... out of the loop.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="cagliostro" sayingMarker="MikanApron1" />
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="Mikan_Cagli_nomagic">I-I don't really know any... um, magic, and um, I-I'd really rather use methods I'm familiar with when people need help...</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="Mikan_Cagli_nomagic">Sorry, um, but I don't really know if I can do any magic, a-and it's better if I only use methods I know when people are in danger, r-right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="opp" character="cagliostro" sayingMarker="MikanShirt1" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png" marker="Mikan_Cagli_plead">"S-Slut"!? I-I'm not trying to anything like that! P-Please believe me!</state>
                <state img="#-panic.png" marker="Mikan_Cagli_plead">N-Noooo! I-I swear that's not what I'm trying to do! P-Please believe me!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="rarity_eg" saying="You seem to be quite nervous, dear. Is it because of what we have to do in this game? Don't feel forced to go through with it if you are not confortable with it." />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Rarity_right">Ah No, no, I-I'm alright with this... game. I-I just really want everything to... go right.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Rarity_right">N-No, I'm really okay playing this game. I-I'm just so nervous... about something going wrong...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="opp" character="rarity_eg" saying="As I mentioned earlier dear, no need to rush..." />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_rarity_more">R-Right, I'm sorry. B-But isn't it better... if I take off more?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-4" oneShotId="126">
                <condition role="opp" character="rarity_eg" saying="Look at her, she seems to keep getting more and more into the game as she loses clothes..." />
                <state img="#-explain.png">Ehehe... i-it is pretty fun.</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">Y-Yeah, maybe this is... more fun than I thought.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" oneShotId="128">
                <alternative>
                    <condition role="opp" character="jim" saying="I'm grateful for your willingness, Miss Tsumiki. And don't worry, I don't intend to put you on a battlefield - it's wounded civilians I've got in mind." />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <condition role="opp" character="jim" saying="If you're serious about this, Miss Tsumiki, then you've got my thanks. You don't gotta worry about dyin', by the way - I intend to have you helpin' civillians." />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Jim_battle">O-Oh good, I-I really do want to help, but I don't think I'd be much help on a battlefield.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Jim_battle">I-I'm glad, I want to help in any way I can, b-but I'm really no good in a fight...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="mary" sayingMarker="Mikan_health" />
                <state img="#-explain.png" marker="Mikan_Mary_healthrisk">U-Um, it shouldn't be a problem. I-I don't think this ~background~ is a health hazard.</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png" marker="Mikan_Mary_healthrisk">Um, I think I will be okay. T-This ~background~ shouldn't be a health risk, I think...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="stocking" sayingMarker="MikanStyle" />
                <state img="#-fear.png" marker="Mikan_Stocking_insult">Y-You're right, I-I'm sorry! I-I hope it wasn't too bad of an insult!</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png" marker="Mikan_Stocking_insult">I-I'm sorry! I-I didn't mean to make a mockery of your style!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="stocking" sayingMarker="MikanBandages" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Stocking_nurse">Um, I'm actually a nurse... s-so I take care of the bedridden.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Stocking_nurse">Um, I-I know I'm wearing bandages... b-but I swear I'm actually a nurse...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="dorothy" sayingMarker="doro01" />
                <state img="#-explain.png" marker="Mikan_Doro_temp">Oh, of course! I think I have a thermometer with me, j-just one second...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="opp" character="dorothy" sayingMarker="doro11" />
                <state img="#-sad.png" marker="Mikan_Doro_service">W-Well... yes, b-but I always make sure I care for my patients the best I can. I-I want them to be as satisfied as possible when they leave.</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png" marker="Mikan_Doro_service">I-I suppose... b-but I swear I always try to give my patients the best possible service. I-It wouldn't be right if they didn't feel satisfied when they left, after all...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" oneShotId="109">
                <condition role="opp" character="chiaki" />
                <state img="#-fear.png" marker="Mikan_Chiaki_watch">Um, um, y-you don't have to watch if you don't want to, Chiaki!</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Chiaki_watch">Um, t-this is a little strange when we... know each other, Chiaki. Y-You don't have to watch if you don't want to.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="stocking" />
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="Mikan_Stocking_outfit">I-I'm not a p-pervert! I-I swear! This is just, um, one of the better outfits I own...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" priority="10">
                <state img="#-worried.png">Um, I-I'm sorry! I-I know my strips have been disappointing. W-Would you be happier if I t-took off more clothes?</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Um, I know small items really aren't what you came here for... I-I'll try to take off something bigger this time, o-okay?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-1 3-4" oneShotId="24">
                <condition filter="danganronpa" role="other" />
                <state img="#-fear.png">Ahh! I-I didn't think I'd run into someone from Hope's Peak here. I-I'm sorry you have to see me like this!</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">W-W-What is someone from Hope's Peak doing here!?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4" id="51" totalRounds="0">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">A-Alright... A-At least no one can be mad at me...</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">O-Okay... Um, before I start... I-Is there a particular way I should do it? N-No?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_winning">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-sad.png">I knew my good luck would come to an end...</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">O-Oh right. I-It's my turn. I-I'm sorry, I almost forgot.</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">I don't know if I deserved to win anyway.</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">N-No one will be mad at me if I lose, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-4" id="5">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">E-Even though I lost... I-It's a bit of a relief. All that winning was making me n-nervous.</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">O-Oh... I lost. Well, there's still next time... Right?</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Y-Yeah... this is more what I'm used to...</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">W-Well... it was pretty nice while it lasted.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_normal">
            <case stage="0-1">
                <state img="#-sad.png">I knew this would happen sooner or later.</state>
                <state img="#-yell.png" oneShotId="1">I-I'll try my best... M-My very best, t-to not let you all down!</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I-I'm kind of nervous. I-I'll try not to mess anything up.</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">(&lt;i&gt;I want ~player~ to look at me. But would ~player.ifMale(he|she)~ even notice someone like me?&lt;/i&gt;) O-Oh, I'm sorry, I'll get to it.</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">O-Oh right, it's my turn. I-I'm sorry, I got distracted. I-I'll get right to it!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-4">
                <state img="#-explain.png">Um, there's no need to worry about me. I've done stuff like this before.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Hehe, I... I think I'm starting to enjoy this more...</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">S-Something like this... I-It really doesn't bother me...</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">W-When was the last time I did something like this?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_losing">
            <case stage="0-1">
                <state img="#-stressing.png">Um... I don't know if this will be enough to please everyone.</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">W-What? I-I didn't know my luck was so poor!</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">I-Is this some kind of trick... again?</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I-I'm just glad I get to choose what I take off...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-4">
                <state img="#-worried.png">I-Is this just bad luck? O-Or... N-No, none of y-you would do that to me... right?</state>
                <state img="#-stressing.png">I-I hope I don't trip!</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">Um, I-I hope seeing me go so many times doesn't get boring for all of you.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Um, I'll do this as many times as you ask. S-So don't worry...</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">O-Once you get used to it. I-It's really not so bad.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-4">
                <state img="#-sad.png">Uuu, I-It's not that I mind stripping in front of you all. But... I wouldn't mind some more time in between.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">O-Oh, I'm stripping again... Well, if you say so.</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">I guess I have poor luck as well...</state>
                <state img="#-stressing.png">I-I'll keep going! P-Please don't worry about me!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripping">
            <case stage="0" oneShotId="52">
                <condition role="opp" character="heris" />
                <alternative>
                    <condition role="opp" character="heris" sayingMarker="HerisMikanTreat" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <condition role="opp" character="heris" sayingMarker="HerisMikanTreatment" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-Stripping.png" marker="Mikan_Heris_better">Oh, um, t-thank you, Heris. Ever since I started attending Hope's Peak academy... things have started to get a lot better.</state>
                <state img="#-Stripping.png" marker="Mikan_Heris_better">I-I, um, thank you, Heris. T-Things have gotten better for me. O-Once I started attending Hope's Peak academy.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Mikan_Mari_distraction" />
                <condition role="opp" character="mari" stage="0" saidMarker="Mikan_Attention1" sayingMarker="Mikan_Attention2=1" notSaidMarker="Mikan_Attention2" />
                <state img="#-Stripping.png" marker="Mikan_Mari_really?">Y-You wouldn't mind? D-Do you  really mean that? S-Something like that... doesn't seem right.</state>
                <state img="#-Stripping.png" marker="Mikan_Mari_really?">A-Are you really sure you wouldn't mind? It doesn't seem right. I-I mean, wouldn't it be a problem for you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="mari" stage="0" saidMarker="Mikan_HiddenDepths1" sayingMarker="Mikan_HiddenDepths2=1" notSaidMarker="Mikan_HiddenDepths2" />
                <state img="#-Stripping.png" marker="Mikan_Mari_ready">S-Something about myself? I-I... I really don't know if I'm ready for something like that...</state>
                <state img="#-Stripping.png" marker="Mikan_Mari_ready">Um, I don't mean to doubt you, but... I don't know I'm ready to discover something new about myself...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="25">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Mikan_Fluttershy_notsick" />
                <condition role="other" character="fluttershy" stage="0-6" sayingMarker="Mikan_undressing_embarrassing" />
                <state img="#-Stripping.png">O-Oh... you really don't have to worry... I'm used to doing stuff like this.</state>
                <state img="#-Stripping.png">Ah, doing something like this... It's really no problem... at all for me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="26">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Mikan_Fluttershy_nursereason" />
                <condition role="other" character="fluttershy" stage="0-6" sayingMarker="Mikan_people_suffering" />
                <state img="#-Stripping.png" marker="Mikan_Fluttershy_care">U-Um... no, not any more than most places, I think. B-But even if there was, I-I'd still try to provide as much care as possible.</state>
                <state img="#-Stripping.png" marker="Mikan_Fluttershy_care">Well... no, I don't think there's more than most places. B-But even if there was, I-I'd still try to provide the best care I could...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="kyou" sayingMarker="kyou_mikan_slow" />
                <state img="#-Stripping.png">I-I, um, t-thank you... But, I don't want to ruin the game for everyone... S-So I'll try to be quicker next time...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="opp" character="kyou" sayingMarker="kyou_mikan_relax" />
                <state img="#-Stripping.png" marker="Mikan_Kyou_believe">D-Do... do you really mean that...? Ah! N-Not that I think you're lying... sorry.</state>
                <state img="#-Stripping.png" marker="Mikan_Kyou_believe">A-Are you sure...? N-Not that I'd ever doubt you... s-sorry.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="fina" sayingMarker="FinaMikanContinue1" />
                <state img="#-Stripping.png" marker="Mikan_Fina_talents">Y-Yes... E-Everyone who goes to Hope's Peak has some kind of talent. I-I've seen an Ultimate swordswomen, a-and even an ultimate princess.</state>
                <state img="#-Stripping.png" marker="Mikan_Fina_talents">Um, yes. Y-You need some kind of talent to attend Hope's Peak. M-My class has an Ultimate Mechanic, a-and even an ultimate princess.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="miki_miura" saidMarker="miki_mikan_endure2" />
                <state img="#-Stripping.png" marker="Mikan_Miki_sosorry">Ah, I-I'm sorry, i-it was terribly rude of me to compare like that... I-Is there anything you'd like me to do to make up for it?</state>
                <state img="#-Stripping.png" marker="Mikan_Miki_sosorry">Y-You're right. I-It was really rude of me to compare us like that. I-Is there anything I could do to apologize? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="cynthia" sayingMarker="MikanStrip02" />
                <state img="#-Stripping.png" marker="Mikan_Cynthia_care">W-Well... yes. B-But it's always worth it to provide the best care to everyone who needs it.</state>
                <state img="#-Stripping.png" marker="Mikan_Cynthia_care">W-Well, it does get a bit chaotic at t-times. B-But I need to provide care to everyone who needs it. S-So it's okay.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="critical_darling" sayingMarker="Mikan_NotForced2" />
                <state img="#-Stripping.png">W-Well... I think I understand that a little. M-Messing up... i-it can be a scary thought</state>
                <state img="#-Stripping.png">Y-Yeah... though, I-I think I get that a little. M-Messing up, i-it can be scary to think about.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="miki_miura" sayingMarker="Miki_Mikan_questionsorry" />
                <state img="#-Stripping.png" marker="Mikan_Miki_concerned">N-No... it's alright.  I-It makes me happy that you're concerned about the medical needs of your fellow students.</state>
                <state img="#-Stripping.png" marker="Mikan_Miki_concerned">Ah, p-please don't be upset. Just the fact you're concerned about the medical needs of those around you is a good thing...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="opp" character="mari" saying="Hehe, you're warming up to this pretty quickly, aren't you, Mikan? &lt;br&gt; I'm glad to see I was right... there's plenty of fun to be had beneath your shyness, hmm?" />
                <state img="#-Stripping.png">Ehehe... Y-You think so? Should... Should I try to be even more... fun?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="opp" character="mari" saying="It seems like you're already really warming up to this, Mikan. I knew you had it in you, hehe." />
                <state img="#-Stripping.png">Um, Thank you, Mari. H-Having you here has made this more fun... I-If you don't mind me saying.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="opp" character="mari" saying="My, my, Mikan... I'm glad to see I was right about you. You &lt;i&gt;can&lt;/i&gt; be pretty daring if you just let yourself relax, hmm? &lt;br&gt; You have such a nice figure, too... honestly, I'm a bit jealous, hehe." />
                <state img="#-Stripping.png">Y-You... Someone like you is jealous of m-me? Ehehe...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="opp" character="fina" sayingMarker="FinaMikanContinue2" />
                <state img="#-Stripping.png" marker="Mikan_Fina_keeptalk">N-No, please don't do that... Y-You can keep talking to me... I-If you want to, I mean.</state>
                <state img="#-Stripping.png" marker="Mikan_Fina_keeptalk">U-Um... please don't do that. I-It's really okay to keep talking to me. O-Only if you want to though.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="opp" character="leon" sayingMarker="leon12" />
                <state img="#-Stripping.png" marker="Mikan_Leon_Praised">H-Huhh? I-It still feels a bit weird to be praised, b-but... thank you, Leon.</state>
                <state img="#-Stripping.png" marker="Mikan_Leon_Praised">Ehh? U-Um, thank you, Leon. A-Although it still feels a bit weird to be praised.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="opp" character="cynthia" sayingMarker="MikanStrip12" />
                <state img="#-Stripping.png" marker="Mikan_Cynthia_time">W-Well... I-It's more useful for... smaller cases. L-Like when someone's not getting enough sleep, o-or a particular vitamin. For larger cases, I still need time and proper equipment.</state>
                <state img="#-Stripping.png" marker="Mikan_Cynthia_time">Um, well, I usually use it to help people with smaller cases. L-Like if their blood circulation is too low. For something, um, vital, I'd still need proper equipment and time... sorry.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="leon" sayingMarker="leon02" />
                <state img="#-Stripping.png">Y-Yeah... you're right. G-Getting worked up also won't make the game fun for others. I-I don't want them to be mad at me...</state>
                <state img="#-Stripping.png">Um... alright. I-I'll try and calm down. A-After all, getting upset will ruin the game for everyone else. I-I don't want to do that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="opp" character="leon" sayingMarker="leon22" />
                <state img="#-Stripping.png" marker="Mikan_Leon_look">O-Oh, I-I don't mind. Um, b-but are you sure you want to look at someone like me?</state>
                <state img="#-Stripping.png" marker="Mikan_Leon_look">O-Oh, well... if it's you, I don't mind. But, um, are you sure I'm the one you want to look at?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="opp" character="miki_miura" sayingMarker="miki_mikan_trust" />
                <state img="#-Stripping.png" marker="Mikan_Miki_believe">Huh... n-no one's ever said that to me before... M-Maybe I can believe you...</state>
                <state img="#-Stripping.png" marker="Mikan_Miki_believe">Huh... I-I don't think anyone's ever said that to me. Maybe... maybe it really is okay to believe you...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="opp" character="heris" sayingMarker="HerisMikanTalent" />
                <state img="#-Stripping.png" marker="Mikan_Heris_great">Er, well, I guess you could say that everyone there is a... prodigy. Ah! I-I'm sorry, I didn't mean to brag! I-I really don't think I'm anything special!</state>
                <state img="#-Stripping.png" marker="Mikan_Heris_great">Um, e-everyone there is some kind of... prodigy. Oh! I-I'm sorry for bragging! I-I promise I don't think I'm anything great!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="opp" character="fina" sayingMarker="FinaMikanContinue3" />
                <state img="#-Stripping.png">Life and death? N-No... I don't think it's that. I think they just get so caught up in their work, they forget about anything else.</state>
                <state img="#-Stripping.png">N-No, they're definitely not in any danger at Hope's Peak. I-I just think they become so absorbed in their work... that they neglect everything else.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="opp" character="cynthia" sayingMarker="MikanStrip22" />
                <state img="#-Stripping.png" marker="Mikan_Cynthia_slasher">Well... it's a little difficult to r-recommend one... But, I've always enjoyed ones where a scary killer chases down the characters. Um, s-slashers, I think they're called.</state>
                <state img="#-Stripping.png" marker="Mikan_Cynthia_slasher">U-Um, I don't know if you will like what I like... But I've always enjoyed stories where the characters are trying to escape a scary killer. Um, I think they're called slashers</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="kaz" sayingMarker="Mikan_s0_2" />
                <state img="#-fear.png">H-Huh? "Wackness"? I-I mean no. I'm just a nurse. I-I just want to help people!</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">Wait... "Wackness"? Um, I-I mean no, I'm only a nurse. I j-just want to help the sick and injured!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="jim" sayingMarker="Mikan_resp0b" />
                <state img="#-explain.png">O-Of course! I would need to know more details, but I'm always willing to help.</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">Sure! I'd need some specifics, but I'd never turn down an opportunity to help anyone who needs it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="yuri" sayingMarker="mikan_nursing2" />
                <state img="#-Stripping.png" marker="Mikan_Yuri_work">Yes... I-I would like to do that someday. T-Though right now, working in my school's infirmary i-is definitely keeping me occupied.</state>
                <state img="#-Stripping.png" marker="Mikan_Yuri_work">Y-Yes... that's my goal... someday. A-Although working in my school's i-infirmary is keeping me occupied for the moment...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="mari" sayingMarker="mikan_bandages" />
                <state img="#-explain.png" marker="Mikan_MariS_nonelastic">Ah! Don't worry, I use non-elastic bandages. They are not too constricting, while still being fairly secure. I-I also make sure to change them frequently.</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png" marker="Mikan_MariS_nonelastic">Well, actually I use non-elastic bandages because they aren't too constricting. Um, I also make sure to change them as frequently as necessary.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="opp" character="heris" sayingMarker="HerisMikanAttraction2" />
                <state img="#-Stripping.png" marker="Mikan_Heris_watch">Y-You mean it? I-It makes me happy that someone like you is watching me...</state>
                <state img="#-Stripping.png" marker="Mikan_Heris_watch">W-Wow... I really am happy someone like you wants to watch me...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="kumatora" sayingMarker="mikan_greet2" />
                <state img="#-Stripping.png" marker="Mikan_KT_stuck">O-Oh, it's alright. B-Back in school, they used to cut my hair... when they were bored. A-After a while, it just sort of, um, stuck...</state>
                <state img="#-Stripping.png" marker="Mikan_KT_stuck">I-I don't mind telling, Back in school, t-the other students would cut my hair for fun. I-I guess that, um, it just stuck after a while.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="opp" character="jim" sayingMarker="Mikan1b" />
                <state img="#-Stripping.png" marker="Mikan_Jim_makeup">I um, I still feel bad for making you feel... out of place, i-is there anything you want me to do to make up for it?</state>
                <state img="#-Stripping.png" marker="Mikan_Jim_makeup">I-It was still wrong to make you feel out of place like that. I-Is there anything I can do to make it up?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="rarity_eg" saying="I appretiate a lot what nurses doctors and all those type of people can do for us, it's just a shame their job outfits are always so... styleless..." />
                <state img="#-Stripping.png" marker="Mikan_Rarity_style">S-Styleless...? O-Oh I'm sorry, I wouldn't know much about that...</state>
                <state img="#-Stripping.png" marker="Mikan_Rarity_style">I-I'm sorry, I'm not very knowledgeable outside of nursing... so I don't know much about style.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="opp" character="rarity_eg" saying="Listen dear, I'm glad you are enjoying the game, just remember to conserve some class while you do this, or mean people could start calling you names for it." />
                <state img="#-Stripping.png" marker="Mikan_rarity_names">Huh? B-But everyone here seems... so nice. W-Would they really do that...?</state>
                <state img="#-Stripping.png" marker="Mikan_rarity_names">Um, n-not that I'm doubting you, b-but everyone here looks... so friendly. W-Would they really... call me names?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="turandot" sayingMarker="mikan_01" />
                <state img="#-fear.png" marker="Mikan_Turandot_backpeddle">R-Right, y-you're right, I-I'm sorry! I-I wouldn't be a very good maid a-anyway!</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png" marker="Mikan_Turandot_backpeddle">Ahhh! I-I'm sorry! I-I didn't mean to be rude! I-I'll just stay as a nurse.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="opp" character="neptune" sayingMarker="nep_mikan_bandaging2" />
                <state img="#-explain.png" marker="Mikan_Nep_hurt">Ehehe, I made a lot of mistakes when I was learning too. T-Thankfully I never hurt myself too bad when I practiced on myself.</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png" marker="Mikan_Nep_hurt">I-I also made mistakes when I was first learning. T-Though I only practiced on myself, s-so I never hurt anyone thankfully.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="dorothy" sayingMarker="doro02" />
                <state img="#-fear.png" marker="Mikan_Doro_stop"> Aaah! A-Are you feeling alright? S-Should we stop playing?</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="Mikan_Doro_stop">O-Oh no...! A-Are you sure you're feeling alright? Should we stop the game?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="opp" character="jim" sayingMarker="Mikan2b" />
                <state img="#-Stripping.png" marker="Mikan_Jim_healtnothurt">T-That's true! I-I'm supposed to heal, not hurt after all...</state>
                <state img="#-Stripping.png" marker="Mikan_Jim_healtnothurt">Y-You're right! I'm not supposed to do any harm after all.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="opp" character="dorothy" sayingMarker="doro12" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Doro_acting">Um, are you an actor of some kind? I-I could help you with the terminology if you want. I-I mean, if you're okay with my help...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-Stripping.png"> U-Um... I-I know just my a-apron isn't enough... But I’m not ready to take off more, s-sorry.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-Stripping.png"> I-I feel odd. Every loss brings m-me closer to… that. B-But I don’t feel as nervous a-as I thought I would...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-Stripping.png"> I-I should have expected this. I-I’m not very good at games… H-Honestly, I-I’m surprised it took this long...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-Stripping.png">I-I’m actually a little relieved to take this off. I-Is that w-weird?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-Stripping.png">Um, this i-isn't the first time I-I've done something like this. B-But something about it feels different... Better.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripped">
            <case stage="4" oneShotId="72">
                <condition role="other" character="myriam" stage="0-5" />
                <state img="#-after.png" marker="Mikan_Myriam_noone">A-Ah... M-My underwear. I-I'm sorry they don't look good. N-No one ever showed me what type I should get...</state>
                <state img="#-after.png" marker="Mikan_Myriam_noone">O-Oh... I'm terribly sorry about my underwear. I-I know they look bad, a-and I'm sorry. I-It's just... N-No one ever showed me what kind to get...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="opp" character="fluttershy" sayingMarker="Mikan_let_me_know_help" />
                <state img="#-after.png" marker="Mikan_Fluttershy_nodoubt">D-Do you really mean that...? Ah! N-Not that I'd ever doubt you, I-I'm sorry!</state>
                <state img="#-after.png" marker="Mikan_Fluttershy_nodoubt">A-Are you sure about that? Ah! I-I mean, I'm sorry for doubting you. P-Please forgive me!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="opp" character="fluttershy" sayingMarker="Mikan_hope_you_find_success" />
                <state img="#-after.png" marker="Mikan_Flutershy_illtry">Um, thank you, I try my hardest. P-Please let me know if you start to feel ill. I-I try my best to help you...</state>
                <state img="#-after.png" marker="Mikan_Fluttershy_illtry">I-I, well, thank you. I'll always try my hardest, A-Also, p-please let me know if you start to feel sick. I'll try my best to help you...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="opp" character="mari" sayingMarker="Mikan_HiddenDepths3" />
                <state img="#-after.png" marker="Mikan_Mari_worrystill">I-I'm sorry, b-but that's still making me nervous!</state>
                <state img="#-after.png" marker="Mikan_Mari_worrystill">I-I'm really sorry, but hearing that still makes me worry!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="opp" character="mari" sayingMarker="Mikan_Attention3" />
                <state img="#-after.png">Um... thank you, Mari. It's been a while since anyone said something so... nice to me. Um, do you think we could talk some more?</state>
                <state img="#-after.png">T-Thank you, Mari. I don't remember the last time someone said something so... nice to me. Um, if you don't mind, could we talk some more?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="opp" character="cynthia" sayingMarker="MikanStrip03" />
                <state img="#-sad.png" marker="Mikan_Cynthia_wellbeing">Um, I understand what you're saying... but the well-being of my patients has to come before my own...</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png" marker="Mikan_Cynthia_wellbeing">Y-Yes, I know that... But I have to consider the well-being of the patients over my own at times...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="opp" character="miki_miura" saidMarker="miki_mikan_selflove" />
                <state img="#-after.png" marker="Mikan_Miki_nodisappoint">R-Really, Miki? Do you mean that? T-Thank you, Miki, I'll try hard not to disappoint you!</state>
                <state img="#-after.png" marker="Mikan_Miki_nodisappoint">Y-You really mean that, Miki? Um, then thank you. I-I'll try really hard not to disappoint you!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="opp" character="fina" sayingMarker="FinaMikanEnd1" />
                <state img="#-after.png" marker="Mikan_Fina_princess">U-Um, I'm sorry! I really don't know how they decide who gets what title. Um, she does seem very... princess like though.</state>
                <state img="#-after.png" marker="Mikan_Fina_princess">I-I'm really sorry! B-But I really don't know how t-they decide on someone's title. Um, Sonia does very...princessy though.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="opp" character="mari" saying="Oh, you're taking off the skirt too, Mikan? &lt;br&gt; Not what I was expecting... but I definitely won't say no to seeing more of your fantastic figure!" />
                <state img="#-after.png" marker="Mikan_Mari_happy">I-I was a bit worried... B-But I also hoped you would like it. I-I'm really happy to see you did... ehehe.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="opp" character="mari" saying="&lt;i&gt;Two&lt;/i&gt; pieces, Mikan? I know I said it'd be nice to see you be a bit more daring, but... I didn't think you'd go that far! &lt;br&gt; You look &lt;i&gt;great&lt;/i&gt; like this, though. Just saying, hehe." />
                <state img="#-after.png" marker="Mikan_Mari_more">Ehehe... I'm so happy you liked it, Mari. I-If you keep saying stuff like that... I-I don't think I'd have a problem taking off even more...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="opp" character="mari" saying="Oh, the skirt too? My, now I &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; want to explore this hidden side of you, Mikan... we could have a lot of fun together, hehe. &lt;br&gt; Maybe I could help you relax even more... would you like that?" />
                <state img="#-after.png" marker="Mikan_mari_more2">U-Um... Um... I really think I would like that. D-Do you want me to do even more to s-start?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="opp" character="leon" sayingMarker="leon13" />
                <state img="#-after.png" marker="Mikan_Leon_nobother">A-Ah no, I definitely don't mind. Y-You can say stuff like that to me.</state>
                <state img="#-after.png" marker="Mikan_Leon_nobother">Oh, um, no, i-it's not a problem. Hearing stuff like that... doesn't bother me...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="opp" character="leon" sayingMarker="leon03" />
                <state img="#-after.png">A-Ah! I-I'm sorry! I-I should be the one offering those to you!</state>
                <state img="#-after.png">N-No, I-I'm sorry! I-It should be the other way around. I-I should be the one offering those to you!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="opp" character="leon" sayingMarker="leon23" />
                <state img="#-after.png" marker="Mikan_Leon_fall">Ehehe... um, thank you for saying something so nice... T-Though if I did fall... I-I promise I could treat my injuries.</state>
                <state img="#-after.png" marker="Mikan_Leon_fall">Ehe... t-that's really... nice, um thank you. B-But I promise i could care for my own injuries if I ever got hurt.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="opp" character="leon" sayingMarker="leon43" />
                <state img="#-after.png">R-Right... um, I'll try not to win next turn. A-Ah, but I promise I'm not a cheater!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="opp" character="miki_miura" sayingMarker="Miki_Mikan_Suzu" />
                <state img="#-worried.png">W-Well. It's not uncommon for cataplexy to be a symptom of narcolepsy. And while certain antidepressants can help, I don't think I'd be able to prescribe those myself. Do you mind telling me what you're currently doing to help her?</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">Hm, cataplexy is a common symptom of narcolepsy, There are treatments which decrease its severity, but I can't prescribe those myself without meeting her. Do you think you could tell me what your currently doing to help her cope?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="opp" character="cynthia" sayingMarker="MikanStrip13" />
                <state img="#-sad.png" marker="Mikan_Cynthia_muchelse">W-Well... I understand what you're saying... But nursing is what I really want to do... Besides, I'm not good at much else.</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png" marker="Mikan_Cynthia_muchelse">Well... t-that makes sense... But, nursing is what interests me the most. A-And besides, there isn't much else I'm good at.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="opp" character="fina" sayingMarker="FinaMikanEnd2" />
                <state img="#-after.png" marker="Mikan_Fina_thanks">U-Um, right... thank you very much.</state>
                <state img="#-after.png" marker="Mikan_Fina_thanks">Um, o-okay. Thank you...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="opp" character="heris" sayingMarker="HerisMikanBrag" />
                <state img="#-after.png" marker="Mikan_Heris_notmad">R-Really...? Y-You... You're not mad at me?</state>
                <state img="#-after.png" marker="Mikan_Heris_notmad">R-Really? Are you sure... Y-You aren't mad with me?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="opp" character="jim" sayingMarker="Mikan0c" />
                <state img="#-after.png" marker="Mikan_Jim_travel">A-A whole different planet!? U-Um, not that I'm unwilling to help... B-But how long is it going to travel there?</state>
                <state img="#-after.png" marker="Mikan_Jim_travel">H-Huh? I-It's on an entirely different planet!? O-Of course I still want to help, b-but how long is it going to take to go there?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="opp" character="kaz" sayingMarker="Mikan_s0_3" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Kaz_greeting">"Ultimate"...? I-I mean, um, It's nice to meet you too.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Kaz_greeting">"Ultimate"? ah, um, I mean it's nice to meat you as well!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="opp" character="heris" sayingMarker="HerisMikanAttraction3" />
                <state img="#-after.png" marker="Mikan_Heris_more">Ehehe... really? Um, if you'd like, I'd be happy to do more for you...</state>
                <state img="#-after.png" marker="Mikan_Heris_more">T-Thank you... Um, if you wanted me to, I-I'd really want to... do more for you, ehehe.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="opp" character="rarity_eg" saying="Do not worry dear, we are in no rush here..." />
                <state img="#-after.png">R-Right, um, thank you...!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="opp" character="rarity_eg" saying="Hold on, why are you also taking your skirt off?" />
                <state img="#-after.png" marker="Mikan_Rarity_surprise">Ehehe... d-did I surprise you?</state>
                <state img="#-after.png" marker="Mikan_Rarity_surprise">I-I'm sorry... you probably weren't expecting that...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="opp" character="rarity_eg" saying="I'm certain you wouldn't want to attract the &lt;i&gt;bad&lt;/i&gt; type of attention after all, right?" />
                <state img="#-after.png" marker="mikan_Rarity_class">No, no! I-I really wouldn't! I-I'll try to have more class next time, I-I mean it!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="opp" character="jim" sayingMarker="Mikan1c" />
                <state img="#-explain.png" marker="Mikan_Jim_anything">O-Oh no, please don't say that. I-I really do want to help you, a-and aside from dying, I'll do pretty much anything.</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png" marker="Mikan_Jim_anything">I-It's really not like that. I-I swear I want to help you, a-and I do anything you want! A-Aside from dying, of course...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="opp" character="kumatora" sayingMarker="mikan_greet3" />
                <state img="#-after.png" marker="Mikan_KT_forgot">I-I could never do that! B-Besides... L-Letting them do what they want... at least it's better than the alternative.</state>
                <state img="#-after.png" marker="Mikan_KT_forgot">I-I really don't think I could do that. E-Even if I could... letting them do what they want is at least better than being forgotten!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="opp" character="yuri" sayingMarker="mikan_nursing3" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Yuri_practice">I-I agree, especially since people think I'm... weird when I ask them if I could practice on them.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Yuri_practice">I-I agree, there's no substitute for the real thing. E-Especially since people think it's odd when I ask them to help me practice.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="opp" character="turandot" sayingMarker="mikan_1n" />
                <state img="#-panic.png" marker="Mikan_Turandot_beg">I-I'm, so, sooorrry! P-Please tell me if there's anything I-I can do to make it up to you!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="opp" character="neptune" sayingMarker="nep_mikan_bandaging3" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Nep_meaning">Oh of course! I-I'm pretty experienced, b-but more prac-- O-Oh, you probably didn't mean it like that, right?</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Nep_meaning">Um, alright! I've had a lot of practice, b-but more cou-- O-Oh wait, you didn't mean it like that, r-right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="opp" character="dorothy" sayingMarker="doro13" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Doro_often">W-What? I-I didn't realize that was the kind of... acting you do. Do you, um, do it often?</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Doro_often">O-Oh, that's the kind of acting you do? Sorry if this is um, too forward, but do you do it often? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-after.png">Please don’t hate me for taking so long to untie this! I’ll... I’ll be quicker next time, I swear!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-after.png">O-Oh, I’m sorry. You didn't want to hear me go on like that…</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-after.png">Just a little longer now…</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-after.png">O-Only because I-It’s a little tight since I-I bought the wrong size… again. T-That’s all...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-after.png">Ehehe, t-this is all of me… What do you think?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_strip">
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="137">
                <condition role="target" character="eichi" said="Oh, a nurse, huh... well, I suppose I have coverage if this awful body decides to be cruel to me..." />
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="Mikan_Eichi_illness">Um, ~target~? I-I'm sorry if this is overstepping, but I overheard what you said earlier... do you have some kind of illness?</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="Mikan_Eichi_illness">S-So, ~target~? I-I apologize if this is presumptuous, b-but I overheard you earlier, a-and... Do you have some kind of illness which would make playing this game unsafe?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="116">
                <condition filter="gay" role="target" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Um, I-I'm sorry, ~target~, I-I know I'm not what you're looking for. B-But, um, I hope we can still have a fun game together...</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Um, ~target~? I-I know I'm not exactly what you're... looking for. B-But I hope that doesn't mean we can't still enjoy this game...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-sad.png">I-It wouldn't be good if you got dirty... So be careful where you leave that afterward.</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">Huh... It's not me...? Ahhh! N-Not that I'm happy that you lost!</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">Um, I-I'm sorry that you lost. B-But, um, there's always next time, right?</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">Y-You... are you mad at me...?</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">Y-You're not the type to get violent when you're mad... r-right?</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Ah! I-I really want to hold on to your clothes... O-Only so they don't get dirty, I-I mean!</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">T-This game is pretty hard, r-right? Ah! N-Not that I think you're as bad as me!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-4">
                <state img="#-stressing.png">I-I can see it in your face! Y-You're mad at me right now!</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">I-I... I know winning is supposed to feel good. B-But I just feel more worried now!</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">E-Even though I won, I-I feel a bit... disappointed. I-I don't know why though...</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Y-You... you're doing... a great job? I'm sorry, that's probably not the right thing to say.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Are you finding this, um, fun?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I-I guess you're okay with stripping. O-Or you wouldn't have come to a game like this... Right?</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">S-Someone always has to lose... I think it's a little cruel.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I-I'd volunteer to go instead. But I don't have anything to take off. Ah! U-Unless you'd like me to take off my bandages?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_strip">
            <case stage="0-7" id="47">
                <condition role="target" character="mercy" stage="5" sayingMarker="SecretWeapon1" />
                <state img="#-fear.png">W-Weapon!? N-No! P-Please don't hurt me!</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">W-Weapon!? I-I'm sorry for whatever I did. P-Please don't hurt me!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="laevatein" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-worried.png">W-What do you mean by that...?</state>
                <state img="#-stressing.png">I hope you don't mean anything bad...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="127">
                <condition role="target" character="lucy" said="Do you have a cure for motion sickness? My friends Natsu and Wendy can't ride on moving vehicles without losing their lunch." />
                <state img="#-explain.png" marker="Mikan_Lucy_help">Um, that sounds rather extreme if it occurs every time. Though, if I could meet them I could prescribe some antihistamines which could help.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="26">
                <condition filter="gamer" role="target" />
                <state img="#-explain.png">I-I wonder if you could show me your games, ~name~. I-I had a friend who did that once.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I-I remember I had a friend who shared her games with me, ~target~. I-It was really fun!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="28">
                <condition filter="medic" role="target" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">Are you a nurse too, ~name~? Would you like to talk about your experience? I-I could tell mine as well.</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">I-I didn't expect to run into another medic here. It feels... kind of nice.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="118">
                <condition filter="lesbian" role="target" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png">O-Oh, you like... girls, ~name~? N-Not that that's a problem! I-In fact, I...! N-Never mind, b-but it really doesn't bother me.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Ah! I-I didn't realize you, um, liked... girls. Um, I-I hope you don't think that bothers me! It doesn't. Um actually, I also... well never mind. B-But it really doesn't bother me!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-sad.png">I-It's my fault you have to take something off... S-Should I strip instead?</state>
                <state img="#-stressing.png">(&lt;i&gt;Now she'll target me!&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">Um... ah, uh, P-Please forgive me for this!</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">P-Please don't hate me for this! I-I'll do anything you want in return.</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">Oh no... T-This is definitely the kind of thing w-which would put you into a bad mood, r-right, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Uh, y-you'll come back from this, I-I swear! A-Although, I'm sorry if I'm wrong!</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">I-If it makes you feel any better... I'm sorry I'm not in your place.</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">(&lt;i&gt;She hasn't said anything... But I'm sure she's mad at me!&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Oh, um, I'm sure it'll be me... next time.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-4">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I-I don't usually get to watch others strip... It's, um, a-a bit weird.</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">Um, are you mad at me for not losing instead of you...?</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">S-Someone had to lose. I-I'm sorry it wasn't me...</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">I-I really didn't mean for you to lose! P-Please believe me!</state>
                <state img="#-plead.png">Um, please make sure you know your limits. I-It wouldn't be good if you took off more than you're comfortable with.</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">I wonder if I should have prepared some interesting facts about clothes.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-worried.png">You didn't lose that one on purpose... Did you?</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">I-In a game like this, even losing can be fun. Ah! N-Not that I'm happy you lost...</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">U-Um, good luck next time, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Um, I-I think that by doing stuff like this... P-People will hate you less... I-Is that weird?</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">I-If this game feels like it's too much, I-I'm sure it's okay if you want to stop...</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">O-Oh... I won? S-So why don't I feel happy?</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">(&lt;i&gt;Am I jealous of ~target~?&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-worried.png">D-Do men usually wear clothes like that? N-Not that I have a problem with it.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Um, i-isn't it true that good things are better when they come in smaller pieces?</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">I-Is going slow like that what you're supposed to do...?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Y-You don't have to worry about me. I-I find even this fun to watch.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-5">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">O-Oh... I was hoping for a bit more... B-But this is fine too,</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">I-I'm not very good at this game... B-But a small item seems like a smart choice.</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">Y-You can take your time if you want... I-I don't think you need to rush if you don't want to.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">E-Everyone goes at different speeds. T-That's what makes this game fun, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">J-Just that...? I-It isn't much, but I won't complain.</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">Y-You... You don't have to worry about me being distracted...</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I-It's your choice, a-and I would never do something as rude as complain... B-But don't you think it would be more fun i-if you took off more?</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">D-Don't worry. I have enough to focus on even with just that.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="0-7" id="53" oneShotId="95">
                <test expr="~clothing~" value="tie" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">T-There's something about a tie that feels very... comfortable.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I-I really like your tie, ~target~. I-It makes me feel... comfortable for some reason.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-calm.png">It's alright if you want to take things at your pace. I-I don't mind.</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">Um, b-be careful not to drop something small like that. O-Or you may not find it...</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">Um, we should continue, right?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">W-Well... Let's move on.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-5">
                <state img="#-explain.png">D-Does it feel nice to take that off?</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">M-Maybe I should have worn something like that.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">W-We should continue, um, if it's alright with you, that is.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Um, if you can take off something small, t-then I'm sure you can take off something big when you need to...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-happy.png">I-I'll keep going, so just take off whatever you want.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">E-Even if you're just teasing me... It doesn't bother me when I'm doing this.</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">I-It's okay... It's really okay.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0-7" id="40" oneShotId="75">
                <condition status="crotch_visible" role="target" />
                <state img="#-sad.png">I-Is too much for you now? I-I'm sorry, ~name~ I-I didn't mean to pressure you.</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">O-Oh... Are you not enjoying this as much as you thought you were? I-I'm sorry if I made the game worse for you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Um, I think that will be enough for me right now.</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">I-I hope you're able to find that after the game. W-With everyone taking off their clothes. I-It should get pretty messy, right?</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">A-Ah, please feel free to throw that on me when you're done with it. I-it would definitely be cleaner than throwing it on the floor.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I-It's good you're not overdoing it, ehehe.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-5">
                <state img="#-explain.png">W-Wow, that really fits you. I-I could never pull off something like that.</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">Um, just because something isn't exciting, d-doesn't mean it isn't memorable, right?</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">D-Don't worry... I'll try not to complain about your choices... I-I don't want you to be mad at me.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Ah, I really wouldn't mind if you wanted to throw that on me for safe keeping. I-I promise I'll be careful with it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-sad.png">T-There are a lot of people who force themselves to do things they aren't comfortable with... S-So I think it's fine if you're only fine with taking off a small amount.</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">I-I've caused you so much trouble, ~name~. S-So whatever you take off won't bother me. I-It's only fair...</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Ehehe, I-I think it's a bit hard to pay attention while doing... this.</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">(&lt;i&gt;If it's only her ~clothing~, will the others still look at me?&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="0-7" id="17">
                <condition status="crotch_visible" role="target" />
                <state img="#-fear.png">Huh! But then... w-why didn't you... I-I don't understand this at all!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="30" oneShotId="110">
                <test expr="~clothing~" value="headphones" />
                <state img="#-explain.png" weight="20" collectible="Mikan's_Apron" collectible-value="+1">Ah! When using headphones, always remember to keep your volume around 70 dB, a-and anything over 85 dB can cause serious damage to the ear. S-So please don't use your headphones at max volume!</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png" weight="20" collectible="Mikan's_Apron" collectible-value="+1">Um, if you like to keep the volume loud on your headphones, keep track of your usage time. Significantly loud volumes can cause hearing damage in an hour or less!</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">A-Are you listening to anything in particular, ~name~? A-Ah, if my voice gets annoying, f-feel free to tune me out!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">W-Whenever I see someone wearing headphones... I-I can't help but wonder what they're listening to. I-Is that weird?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="31">
                <test expr="~clothing~" value="necklace" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="14">W-Wow... That necklace was so pretty! I-I would love to try one like that. A-Ah, not that I could wear it as well as you.</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png" oneShotId="15">I w-wonder how one would get a necklace like that. Ah! N-Not that I was thinking of taking yours!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="33" oneShotId="112">
                <test expr="~clothing~" value="shoes" />
                <state img="#-explain.png" weight="20" collectible="Mikan's_Apron" collectible-value="+1">Many people worry about their shoes' support, but for the average able-bodied person, it shouldn't be something to worry about. The foot has muscles to support itself after all.</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">A-Ah, I hope you're properly cleaning those. O-On average you should clean your shoes every two weeks. Though it differs depending on the type of shoe, and how much you wear them.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">B-Buying shoes isn't easy... I-I have to return mine a lot b-because I keep buying the wrong size...</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">D-Do you o-own a lot of shoes, ~name~? I-I only have these, a-and my school shoes. B-But I promise they're clean!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="35" oneShotId="111">
                <test expr="~clothing~" value="glasses" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">Glasses are actually one of my favorite medical inventions. I-It's hard to imagine a world without them!</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">S-Sometimes I feel that I need glasses. B-But I'm actually just clumsy.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">S-Sometimes people don't get glasses until long after they need them. I-It can be hard to convince them they need them sometimes.</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">W-While optometry isn't my preferred field, I-I ended up learning a lot about it after coming to Hope's Peak. T-There are a lot of glasses wearers there!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="42">
                <test expr="~clothing~" value="gloves" />
                <state img="#-explain.png">O-Oh, did you need those to keep your hands warm, ~name~? I-I brought some heating pads if you'd like.</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">Oh, i-if you were wearing gloves, ~target~, did you need them to stay warm? I-If you'd like, I-I brought along some heating pads.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Good things are better when they last longer... right?</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">Um, you could just throw ~clothing.ifPlural(those|that)~ on me if you'd like. I'm pretty useful you know! Hmhm.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">E-Even unimportant things can feel good... when you're having fun, right?</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">I-I know it may seem weird. But I've always preferred smaller things to bigger things...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-5">
                <state img="#-sad.png">I-I've never been good at picking out accessories. N-No one ever showed me how...</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Could I, um, Could I have a closer look at that? O-Only if you wouldn't mind.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I-I wonder if I could something like that... O-Of course, it looks much better on you, then me.</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">O-Oh, it looked really good on you. I-I'm sorry you had to take it off.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">♫Hm, hm, hm...♫</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">It, um, it feels a little strange that  you're t-taking such a small item off... When I've already... l-lost.</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">I-Is that all you're taking off? W-Well, Okay...</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">~Clothing.ifPlural(those|that)~ ~clothing.ifPlural(were|was)~ pretty. But, um, y-you still look nice without ~clothing.ifPlural(them|it)~.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I-Is that all you came here for...? Ah! I'm sorry! T-That must have come off as rude.</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">I suppose that was... unexpected. N-Not bad, just unexpected.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-explain.png">(&lt;i&gt;I wonder if ~name~ prefers a certain type of bandage.&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">I-I'm sorry you have to do this... B-But I-I'm pretty sure that's a smart choice...</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I...I,um, I can't think of anything to say. S-Sorry I didn't study more conversation topics.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-5">
                <state img="#-worried.png">Y-You're not worried about removing that in front of someone like me, are you?</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">H-have you ever played a game like this, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">~Clothing.ifPlural(are your|is your)~ dusty? A-Ah I-I guess it doesn't matter either way, s-sorry.</state>
                <state img="#-yell.png">I-I made sure to wash my hands before I came here. S-So please feel free to give that to me when you're done. O-Only if you want to, I-I mean!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_minor">
            <case stage="0-1" oneShotId="129">
                <condition role="self" notSaidMarker="Mikan_bbb_2" />
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="Mikan_aaa_1">(&lt;i&gt;Don't people think nurses are... sexy? D-Do they want that from me? B-But how would I do that&lt;/i&gt;!?)</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="Mikan_aaa_1">(&lt;i&gt;Aren't people attracted to Nurses? S-Should I try being... sexy then? B-But how would I even do that?&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-surprised.png">O-Oh! We're moving on!? I-I'm sorry, I got distracted.</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">L-Let me know if that ever gets damaged. Um, I'm not very good with clothes.. B-But I'm sure I could find someone talented at Hope's Peak to help!</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">W-Would you like to talk more after the game, ~name~? I-It could be about whatever you want. O-Or nothing at all. E-Either way is fine with me. </state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">(&lt;i&gt;I wonder if ~target~ could ever see me as a friend?&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-sad.png">I know I have no right to say this, but... I was hoping for a bit more...</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">W-Was that an odd thing to say? A-Are you mad at me, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">S-Sorry... it's hard to focus on the conversation when I'm... like this.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-worried.png">W-Won't everyone be upset with just that?</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Y-You're okay with stripping? Y-You don't want me to go instead? O-Or my money?</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">I-Is something like that, um, popular where you come from?</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">I-I uh, don't really know what kinds of clothes are popular... B-But I still think that looks nice!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-5">
                <state img="#-worried.png">(&lt;i&gt;I hope ~name~ is enjoying this...&lt;/i&gt;.)</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">I-I wonder if my classmates at H-Hope's Peak would enjoy this. I-I'm not really sure.</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">Um, ah... I-I'm sorry! I-I can't think of a good word to describe your ~clothing~.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">(&lt;i&gt;Is this something, ~name~ does often? I hope so.&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-sad.png">I-I promised I wouldn't complain, but...</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">A-Ah... well, I hope t-that will be enough to please e-everyone...</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I-Is that something you wanted to get rid of? S-Sorry I-If I'm wrong.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Ah, ~clothing.ifPlural(those were nice|that was a nice)~ B-But right now, I think you look better without it.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_minor">
            <case stage="0-7" id="12">
                <condition role="target" character="erufuda" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-sad.png">...</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">I-I don't mean to be rude, ~target~. But are taking weight loss seriously?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="komi-san" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">(&lt;i&gt;Is she so nervous that she can't decide!? I hope I didn't do anything.&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="38" oneShotId="74">
                <test expr="~clothing~" value="socks" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" weight="20" collectible="Mikan's_Apron" collectible-value="+1">Um, I know it sounds a bit tiresome, but if you're wearing your socks for prolonged hours, y-you should wash them after every wear. I-It's important to stay hygienic after all.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Um, like shirts, socks are closest to our bodies, so it's important to keep them clean. I-I'd recommend washing them after every use. I-It's important to stay clean after all.</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">S-Socks... I-I always end up losing mine. I-I'm sorry, I guess that's not what I should be talking about here. </state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">A-Ah, m-make sure you keep track of those. Socks are easy to lose, after all.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-1" oneShotId="130">
                <condition role="self" notSaidMarker="Mikan_aaa_1" />
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="Mikan_bbb_2">(&lt;i&gt;Don't people think nurses are... sexy? D-Do they want that from me? B-But how would I do that&lt;/i&gt;!?)</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="Mikan_bbb_2">(&lt;i&gt;Aren't people attracted to Nurses? S-Should I try being... sexy then? B-But how would I even do that?&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">M-Maybe we could talk some more after the game, ~name~. Ah! N-Not that I'd be so presumptuous to think w-we're actually friends!</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">S-Should we continue? I-I suppose it's up to you...</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">S-Sorry... Was that a weird thing to say?</state>
                <state img="#-stressing.png">(&lt;i&gt;I hope she doesn't hate me for saying that!&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-5" id="4">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Y-Yes... It's best to take it in small steps, right?</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">W-When I played something like this before... I'd have to strip e-even if I won. S-So thank you for not doing that.</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">T-Try not to trip... Ah! N-Not that I think you're as clumsy as me!</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">Ah, please feel free to throw that on me. I'll take anything you don't want. You can even call me a trashcan if you want!</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">Would holding on to that for you be against the rules? I-I don't want to get thrown out...</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">Um... uh... I-I really don't know what to say!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-sad.png">I... I don't mean to be rude, but I was hoping for a bit more...</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">U-Um, you still look pretty even w-without that, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Y-You... You're going to get naked too, r-right, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">O-Oh, you stripped? I was so distracted, I-I didn't even notice.</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">Ah! D-Don't worry. I-I'll make sure to pay attention this time.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_major">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I-If you want, I could look away. I-I really don't mind.</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">(&lt;i&gt;Everyone else is looking... But is it really okay for me to?&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-yell.png">I-I'm sorry its come this far. I-It's all my fault!</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">H-How much is too much?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-4">
                <state img="#-worried.png">Ah, t-that's a lot... I-I hope you're not to upset you're the one taking that much off instead of me.</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">R-Right in front of me...!?</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">You make it look so easy... I-Is it easy for you?</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Y-You knew about this part before you signed up, r-right?</state>
                <state img="#-stressing.png">(&lt;i&gt;Just think of it like an examination...&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Y-You... You look pretty good, ~name~. I-I hope you don't mind me saying.</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">I-I hope I'm ready for this...</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">G-Getting closer to the end. I-Isn't this a little scary for you?</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Um, do your best?</state>
                <state img="#-stressing.png">Uuu, I-I knew we'd get this far. B-But it still feels weird for it to actually be happening!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_major">
            <case stage="2-7" oneShotId="135">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Mikan_aaa_1" />
                <state img="#-explain.png">U-Um, if the patient will please remove their ~clothing~. (&lt;i&gt;Was that right?&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">I'll watch carefully... for any abnormalities during the procedure...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">If you require assistance, please let me know...</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I suppose... a more detailed look will have to wait until later...(&lt;i&gt;Did that sound okay?&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">You're definitely looking healthy!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">D-Do you want me to turn away? I w-wouldn't have any problem doing that.</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">W-What!? O-Oh, I-I was so nervous, I didn't notice you finished.</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">I... I didn't practice what I'm supposed to say for something like this!</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">T-That should have been easier for you by now... right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-5">
                <state img="#-explain.png">Ehehe. A game like this can be pretty fun, right?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">W-Wow... I-I think you look even better like that, ~name~. I-If you don't mind me saying.</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">Should... should I take something off in return?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-horny.png">I-I wonder if you prefer stripping yourself? O-Or watching others do it...</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Y-You're so close... I-I'm getting a little excited.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Ehehe... What are you planning next...?</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Ehehe... Do you want any help taking your clothes off next time...?</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">I-It's actually pretty fun being o-on the opposite side.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-stressing.png">Um, I promise I'll take off something just as good next time... I-I'm not lying!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_major">
            <case stage="0-7" id="10">
                <condition role="target" character="aimee" stage="0-2" />
                <state img="#-panic.png">Ahhh! W-What are you doing!?</state>
                <state img="#-panic.png">N-No... I-I don't want to be shot. P-Please don't hit me!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5" oneShotId="31">
                <test expr="~background~" value="armory" />
                <state img="#-plead.png">Please be careful when exposing so much skin around these weapons. I-It could be a safety hazard</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">D-Doing this around all these weapons... I-I makes me a bit scared.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-explain.png">I would recommend sanitizing that before wearing it again. Um, it's best to be safe.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Um, It probably feels a little weird to remove so much in front of us, r-right, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">O-Oh no... I-I don't want to be the reason you lose...</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">I-If you're going to put something like that on the floor... well, I just hope the floor has been properly cleaned..</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">The anticipation makes it more exciting... r-right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-worried.png">Y-You don't have many chances left... Um, I think you should try to be careful. N-Not that you should listen to me!</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">Y-You're removing your ~clothing~ before me!? I-I promise I'm not cheating!</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">Am I... ahead of you? Y-You're not trying to lose... Are you?</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">I-It feels a little strange seeing this... I-It's not really something I'm used to...</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">W-Wow, you're pretty good at this... I-I hope I'll be able to do the same.</state>
                <state img="#-stressing.png">Um... ah... I-I'm sorry! Y-You're trying so hard, but I can't even think of anything to say!</state>
                <state img="#-yell.png">U-Uh... T-Thank you for doing this. N-Not because I want to win, b-but because you look really... nice!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Heh... heheheheh. S-Sorry for laughing so suddenly. T-This just makes me so happy!</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">(&lt;i&gt;The way they look at her... Is it different from how they looked at me?&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Ehehe... I-I hope you don't mind the attention.</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">E-Everyone's going to look at you. A-Are you okay with something like that?</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Um, h-hang in there, r-right?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_major">
            <case stage="0-7" id="58">
                <condition role="target" character="samus_aran" stage="1" sayingMarker="Removing_armor" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">hawawa, what!?</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">How- what-, um. I-I don't get this at all!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="8">
                <condition role="target" character="yuri" stage="6" />
                <state img="#-sad.png">O-Oh ~target~... I'm sorry...</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">I-I didn't notice before... Y-Your... I'm sorry, ~target~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4" id="11">
                <condition role="target" character="aimee" stage="1-2" />
                <state img="#-plead.png">I-I know you seem to be very skilled. But please don't do that again. I-I don't want to see you hurt someone.</state>
                <state img="#-yell.png">U-Um. P-Please don't do something like that again! Y-You may hurt yourself!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="14">
                <condition role="target" character="natsuki" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-worried.png">(&lt;i&gt;Would it be ruder to tell her? Or not to?&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Um, ~target~? I-I can... n-never mind.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="54">
                <condition role="target" character="saki_zls" stage="6" />
                <state img="#-worried.png">Y-You're going to be freezing like that! Hold on, Let me see if I can find you a towel, o-or blanket, to stay warm.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="79">
                <condition filter="tanned" role="target" />
                <state img="#-explain.png" weight="20" collectible="Mikan's_Apron" collectible-value="+1">W-While there's nothing wrong with getting a tan, always make sure you're properly applying sunscreen!</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png" weight="20" collectible="Mikan's_Apron" collectible-value="+1">While getting a tan isn't harmful. Always make proper use of sunscreen! E-Excess exposure to UV light can leads to various forms of skin cancer.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-7" oneShotId="136">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Mikan_bbb_2" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">J-Just like that! The um, operation is proceeding smoothly.</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">Um, I believe I'll require a more... up-close observation. (&lt;i&gt;Was that too much?&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">N-Now just stand like that for a moment...</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">You're definitely looking healthy, ehehe!</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">If you require assistance, please let me know...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">That's a bit more then I was expecting. N-Not that it's a problem o-of course.</state>
                <state img="#-plead.png">Um, let me know if you feel too cold after that. I-It wouldn't be good if you caught a cold.</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">I-I'm ahead of you. So why... why aren't you mad at me...?</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">I-I hope the temperature is properly set here... I wouldn't want you catching a cold...</state>
                <state img="#-stressing.png">(&lt;i&gt;Right, I-I have to do it just like that. I-I can't mess up&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-4">
                <state img="#-explain.png">I-If you want, you could let me hold onto your ~clothing~. I-It's cleaner than leaving it on the floor, right?</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">S-Something like this... I-I think it'll get easier the more you do it, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">E-Everything's happening so quickly. I-I hope I can keep up.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I-It's weird... isn't a game like this one where p-people want to lose?</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">O-Only a little more to go... Ah! N-Not that I think that's a good thing.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">There's no hiding now...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-explain.png">Y-You don't have to listen to me. But I-I wouldn't mind if you took off more clothes like that.</state>
                <state img="#-yell.png">Don't overwork yourself! If you start to feel overwhelmed or stressed. Please let me know!</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">A-Are they going to compare us...?</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Ehehe, thank you, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">&lt;i&gt;(How much longer now?&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">N-Not that I'm doubting you, but... I-I really hope you can finish.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-worried.png">Um, w-would it be a problem if I l-looked?</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I-I'm more used to seeing this in a hospital. I-It's a little strange for me to see it... here.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">U-Um, thank you for doing this.</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">(&lt;i&gt;This is more than I thought I'd get.&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-5">
                <state img="#-explain.png">Um, I think you can learn a lot about a person's physical habits by looking at their chest.</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">I've been looking forward to this... I-Is that w-weird?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">T-This game can be pretty fun, right?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">(&lt;i&gt;I wonder if ~target~ has ever been injured...&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Ehehe... You can go now</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">A-A man's chest is nice... I-I don't get many chances to... appreciate them. </state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">I-I can't wait...</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">I'm sorry... if I'm pressuring you.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition filter="muscular" role="target" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="8">It makes me happy to see someone take such good care of their body.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="9">W-Wow... You really went a-above and beyond, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <condition filter="skinny" role="target" />
                <state img="#-plead.png">I-I don't mean to pry but have you been taking care of yourself? You look a bit underweight.</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">Hm... I could help you with your weight. O-Only if you wanted, I-I mean.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition filter="athletic" role="target" />
                <state img="#-explain.png" oneShotId="6">You're so toned... I-It's nice you take good care of your body.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Ehehe, y-you remind me of the athletes at Hope's Peak. I-It makes me happy to see.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="113">
                <condition filter="chubby" role="target" />
                <state img="#-explain.png">Um, ~target~? I-I know you didn't come here to hear this, but... i-if you ever feel like changing your diet, I-I'm sure I can help.</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">Um, t-this is kinda sudden, ~target~, b-but if you ever want help changing your diet, I-I'm sure I could refer you to someone who could help.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Huh, it looks different from an anatomy chart.</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">Um, i-it must feel a little odd with everyone looking at you... right?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">O-Oh good... You're looking healthy.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-5">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Ehehe, I-I'm sorry for laughing so suddenly. I-It's just... this is something I don't get to appreciate very often.</state>
                <state img="#-yell.png">U-Um! Thank you... for your hard work.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">(&lt;i&gt;I think touching it would feel, really, really nice.&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">D-Do you want me to get you something to cover up with? Ah! W-Wait, never mind. I-I was so nervous I forgot... you're supposed to be like this.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-horny.png">I-I wonder how it would it feel... Y-Your chest against mine...</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Ehehe... I wonder if you'd let me have a closer look...</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I-I'm really happy I chose to play, hehe.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">T-This reminds me of when I tripped and fell on top of Gundam. I-I don't think I've ever seen him so embarrassed like that.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">If it makes it easier for you, just think of this as a p-physical examination...</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">W-Wait! D-Don't do it so quickly. I-I-I'm not ready for this yet!</state>
                <state img="#-stressing.png">I-I should have prepared myself better!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-horny.png">I-I'll try to keep myself calm...</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">E-Everyone's eyes are on you now...</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Ah! I-It's coming out! I-I mean... n-never mind...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_small_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">O-Oh... don't feel bad. I-Its size... doesn't really matter to me.</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">Um, I-It could actually be more... comfortable like that. S-So, um, there's a silver lining at least.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-5" id="1">
                <state img="#-explain.png">Um, I know many people worry about their... size. But since size is primarily influenced by genetics. You can't do much about it. I-It's better to worry about other things.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I-It's not the size but how you use it, r-right?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Ehehe... I-I think it's cute. I-If that's alright with you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">D-Does it grow when y-you're, um, you know, aroused?</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">D-Don't feel bad, ~name~. I-I don't think there is anything wrong with you...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_medium_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-explain.png">S-Sometimes, I think b-being average i-isn't so bad...</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">(&lt;i&gt;Nothing to be afraid of.&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">Ah! D-Did it just move?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-5">
                <state img="#-sad.png">Ah, um... I-I'm not really sure what to say... I-I don't want you to be mad at me.</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">Ahh, I-Is it like that because of me...?</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I-It's so... normal looking. N-Not that I dislike it, of course.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-horny.png">T-This is... exactly what I needed, ehehe.</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">I-I think I've seen one that looks just like that before.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_large_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-sad.png">O-Oh... I don't mean to offend. But I think that would be a little much for me...</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">That's, um, that's certainly impressive...</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">U-Um... congratulations? I-Is that the right thing to say?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-5">
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Ahhh! T-To much! T-T-That's to much!</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">W-Wow. To see one that big. T-That's pretty rare.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Handling you... I-I think it would be a challenge... for most people, anyway...</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">I-I'm sorry for being rude... But I think that's a little much for me...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">W-While it is kind of... scary. I-I think I'd like to... try yours.</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">I-I, um, I like its shape if that m-makes sense.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">S-Should I be more excited...?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-7" id="34" oneShotId="63" totalRounds="0">
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Ahhh! I'm not ready for this! I-I'm not ready at all!</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I-I'm not really sure why you did that... But, um, I don't dislike it?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-7" id="7">
                <condition role="target" character="laevatein" />
                <state img="#-panic.png">Eeeek! N-No, S-Stay away from me! I-I don't wanna be burned again!</state>
                <state img="#-panic.png">Ahhh! I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry! Please don't burn meee!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-1">
                <state img="#-worried.png">I-It's been a long time since I've seen this... I-I hope I'm ready.</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">Eeek I-I have so much, a-and you... you're almost done! H-How did this happen!?</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">A-Are you sure... A-Are you ready for this?</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">Ah! I'm sure you don't have to worry about anyone touching you after, r-right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Sometimes... p-people can be adorable when they're embarrassed, right?</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">Ehehe... are you enjoying the attention?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">E-Everyone looking at you... I-It feels good, right?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Hehe, w-will you be joining me soon?</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Ahhh, this feeling, I know it well.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-5">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Hehe... Thank you very much for doing this.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Um... W-Would you like any help with that...?</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">My heart's pounding... I-I don't know if I'm nervous... or excited.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Ehehe, I-I guess it's finally time!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_small_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-sad.png">(&lt;i&gt;She probably doesn't have to worry about her bra being too tight.&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">Um, e-everyone here seems n-nice ... I don't think you should h-have to worry about your... size.</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">T-They really are small... D-Did I say that out loud? I-I'm so sorry! P-Please forgive me!</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">I-I know it's unusual... B-but I actually think they look nicer when they're smaller.</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">(&lt;i&gt;Would people look at me less if I looked like that?&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-5">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I hope y-you don't feel bad about your small chest... I-I don't think anyone here minds...</state>
                <state img="#-plead.png">Um, I know yours are smaller than mine. B-But I promise they're better. I-I'm not lying.</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">(&lt;i&gt;She probably doesn't have trouble finding the right size...&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">S-Sometimes I wonder what it would be like to have a smaller chest...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-horny.png">S-size, um, doesn't really matter to me. I-I think they look nice either way...</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Aww, they're so cute, ehehe. I-I really like them.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">D-Don't worry, ~name~. T-Touching them feels good no matter your size, ehehe.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_medium_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-explain.png">Um, i-if you're worried about your size... It's not uncommon for breasts to grow after puberty. At least until  your 20's. A-After that, um, sorry.</state>
                <state img="#-stressing.png">(&lt;i&gt;Don't annoy her, don't annoy her, don't annoy her...!&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">O-Oh, they're um, well shaped.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-5">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Um, I think Pekoyama's are a similar size. N-Not that I stare at her...</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">I-I'm more comfortable with a smaller size. N-Not to say yours are bad at all.</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">T-They're such a nice size... </state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">S-Sometimes... I wish mine looked more like that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-calm.png">T-They're so perfectly shaped... Y-You wouldn't let me touch them. Right, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">(&lt;i&gt;I think, ~name~ would sound cute if I touched those...&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">(&lt;i&gt;I wonder if ~target~ felt the same way I did.&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_large_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">That... That's a rather healthy size.</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">Many women with larger breasts often face back pain... Though this has also been correlated to other factors, such as an incorrect bra size.</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">Do... Do you ever feel people look at you differently, ~name~?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-5">
                <state img="#-stressing.png">I-I... I'm sorry for staring! Unless you want me to...</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">L-Let me know if you ever experience back pain. I-I should be able to help...</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Um, ~name~? W-What size b-bra do you wear? I-I'm not asking for any reason in particular...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">T-Those look a bit much for me... B-But I'm sure they'd make someone happy!</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">You... You must get a lot of attention with those...</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">I-I know I should look away. But I can't!</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I-It's not bad when you get used to it, r-right?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="5-7" oneShotId="106">
                <condition role="target" character="chiaki" />
                <condition role="self" notSaidMarker="Mikan_Chiaki_look" />
                <state img="#-horny.png" marker="Mikan_Chiaki_hornylook">(&lt;i&gt;Wow...I-I never realized... Has Chiaki always looked like that?&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png" marker="Mikan_Chiaki_hornylook">W-Wow... I guess I've never seen you like this, C-Chiaki, ehehe...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <condition role="target" character="chiaki" />
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="Mikan_Chiaki_look">D-Did you always look like that, Chiaki?</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Chiaki_look">I-I... huh. Have you always looked like that, Chiaki?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-sad.png">(&lt;i&gt;I wonder if this is easy for them...&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">O-Oh... They're... nice!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="103">
                <condition role="target" character="twilight" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I-I understand that, bu--- W-What are you doing?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-worried.png">T-This is the part people look forward to, right?</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">(&lt;i&gt;I've seen this before... It's okay.&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I-Ive seen something like this before. B-But it's still weird i-in a game like this.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-5">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I-I'm sorry it's gotten this far... W-Would you like me to go instead of you...?</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">Is it... wrong for me to be... excited? I-I don't want to upset you.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Ehehe, s-something about seeing this... I-It makes me feel better. I-Is that wrong?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-horny.png">I hope you enjoy doing this. T-That will make the game more fun for everyone... won't it?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">W-Wow... T-This is more then I ever expected...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">G-Go on... I-I'm sure you'll feel better after you do this.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-1">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I-Is this really fair? Shouldn't I have less...?</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">I-I'm sorry, ~name~. S-Someone like me should be going before you.</state>
                <state img="#-stressing.png">O-Oh no... I-I hope I'm ready for this!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-7" id="63" oneShotId="102">
                <condition role="target" character="twilight" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-fear.png">(&lt;i&gt;She's so open about it...!&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">I-Is it really okay to be so... open about it?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition filter="shaved" role="target" />
                <state img="#-explain.png" weight="20" collectible="Mikan's_Apron" collectible-value="+1">Um, while some consider shaving a matter of hygiene... there aren't actually any major hygiene benefits to shaving!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition filter="hairy" role="target" />
                <state img="#-explain.png" weight="20" collectible="Mikan's_Apron" collectible-value="+1">Pubic hair can actually provide protection. Of course it is possible to live without these protections.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="29" oneShotId="61" totalRounds="0">
                <state img="#-surprised.png">W-What!? D-Do you want us to look at you that much!?</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">Um, I'm sure you're enjoying this... B-But was that really... a good idea?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I-It feels a bit weird seeing this outside of a physical examination...</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">Ahhh! ~name~, I-I'm sorry I looked. I-I really am!</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">(&lt;i&gt;I definitely stared at it when I wasn't supposed to. B-But did, ~name~ notice?&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-5">
                <state img="#-explain.png">I-I don't mean to pry... But I hope you're taking proper care of that...</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Maybe... maybe I could take a closer look...? Only if you don't mind.</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">Um... Um. I-If I looked... Then it would only be fair if y-you looked at me back, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">U-Um, ~name~ might consider it rude if you stared at her... B-But if wanted, I-I wouldn't mind if you looked at me...</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Ehehe, I'm glad to see this if it means you'll be joining me soon!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-1">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">T-They've... always looked like that, right?</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">U-Um... It looks healthy.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_lost">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="heris" stage="1" saidMarker="HerisMikanMistakes" />
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="Mikan_Heris_pry">M-Mistakes...? What kind? Ah! Y-You don't have to tell me, I-I'm sorry for prying.</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="Mikan_Heris_pry">You've made mistakes? W-What kind? Ah! I'm sorry, it's not my place to ask. Y-You don't have to tell me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="fischl" stage="1" saidMarker="fischl_mikanjapan2" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="Mikan_Fishy_showaround">R-Really? I-I could show you around if you wanted! A-At least the part I live in. </state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="Mikan_Fishy_showaround">R-Really? I-If you wouldn't mind someone like me, I-I could show you around! A-At least the part I live in.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="heris" stage="2" saidMarker="HerisMikanSafe" />
                <state img="#-explain.png">E-Exactly... Wanting to keep others safe no matter what... It's part of why I wanted to become a nurse.</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">Yes... Wanting to help others no matter what... That's part of why I became a nurse in the first place.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="jim" stage="1" saidMarker="Mikan_resp0b" />
                <state img="#-fear.png">Um... uh... I-I'm sorry! I-I've made you uncomfortable. Y-You don't have to explain if you don't want to!</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">Um... ah, I-I'm sorry! I didn't mean to make you uncomfortable! Y-You don't have to explain if you don't want! I-I probably should have known in the first place!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="123">
                <condition role="target" character="neptune" stage="1" saidMarker="nep_mikan_outfit3" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Neptune_depricate">I-I'd love to... but would she really be okay with being with someone... like me?</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Neptune_depricate">T-That would be great... but would she really want to interact with someone like me?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="jim" stage="2" saidMarker="Mikan_resp1c" />
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="Mikan_Jim_prepare">I-I'm prepared this time, s-so I'm sure it'll go better, r-right?</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="Mikan_Jim_prepare">R-Right... I'm prepared this time, s-so it'll... probably go better...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="jim" stage="3" saidMarker="Mikan_resp2c" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Jim_right">Um! Y-You invented special engines which let you go to a special realm, a-and now you don't have to worry about losing things! D-Did I get that right?</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Jim_right">S-So, you have... special engines which let you travel through... another dimension? A-And now you don't have to worry about losing things. I-Is that right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="kumatora" stage="1" saidMarker="mikan_KTupset_resp" />
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="Mikan_KT_ramble">O-Oh, um, right! I-I'll try to calm down. I-I do want you to enjoy this. Um, n-not enjoy me in particular, t-though I wouldn't, um, mind that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="neptune" stage="2" saidMarker="nep_mikan_friend3" />
                <state img="#-fear.png" marker="Mikan_Nep_doubt">I-I don't want to doubt you, b-but what if they don't like who I am? W-Wouldn't they rather not be around me at all then?</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png" marker="Mikan_Nep_doubt">I-I'm sorry for doubting you, b-but what if they decide they'd rather not be around me at all then?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="jason" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Jason_familiar">Um, h-have I seen you before, ~target~? I-I don't mean to pry... But something about you looks really... familiar.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Jason_familiar">Um, ~target~ I-I'm sorry if I'm wrong... B-But have you done any acting before? I-I have this feeling... that I've seen you before.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="critical_darling" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_CD_Ibuki">U-Um, ~target~? W-Would you mind if I asked your name? I-It's just... I have a classmate, um, a friend who you remind me a lot of... Y-You two look like you make very similar... music.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_CD_Ibuki">Um, ~target~? W-What did you say your name was? I-I'm just curious because you remind me a lot of a... friend of mine. S-She also makes her own music...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="wikipe-tan" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_WPtan_teacher">Um, ~target~? A-Are you a teacher? S-Something about your clothes reminds me of one...</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_WPtan_teacher">Um, I'm s-sorry if this is an o-odd question, ~target~ But a-are you a teacher? Y-Your clothes... they remind me of o-one.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="bernadetta" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="Mikan_Bernie_health">U-Um... ~name~? You're looking pale. H-Have you been getting enough sleep? Or sunlight exposure?</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="Mikan_Bernie_health">Hm... ~name~? You seem... pale. I-I'm sorry for prying, but have you been getting enough sleep? Have you been getting a proper amount of sunlight exposure?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="mahiru" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Mahiru_camera">I-I see you brought you're camera, Mahiru. D-Did you come here to take pictures?</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png" marker="Mikan_Mahiru_camera">Ah! I-I guess it makes sense for the Ultimate Photographer to bring her camera with her. D-Did you come here to take pictures?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="heris" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="Mikan_Heris_doctor">U-Um, ~target~, i-if you don't mind me asking. A-Are you... a doctor?</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="Mikan_Heris_doctor">U-Um, ~target~ I-I'm sorry for asking, but would you be a... a doctor?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="ignatz" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="Mikan_Ignatz_health">Uuu, u-um, ~target~ I-I'm sorry to pry, b-but are taking care of yourself properly? I-I've met a lot of artists who overwork themselves, and neglect their health.</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="Mikan_Ignatz_health">Uuu, ~target~, I-I'm sorry if I'm being presumptuous, but you're not neglecting your health, right? I-I met many artists who get so focused on their work, they forget about their health completely!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="neptune" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="Mikan_Neptune_friend">Ehehe, I-I like your clothes, ~target~. I-It reminds me of a time when I played video games with a... friend.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="Mikan_Neptune_friend">Hehe, Y-Your clothes are... nice, ~target~. T-They remind me of a time when I played a game with a... friend.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="jim" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="Mikan_Jim_fights">Um, Mr. Raynor, I sorry for prying, but... h-have you been hurt in the past?</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="Mikan_Jim_fights">Um, I-I'm terribly sorry for asking this unprompted, Mr. Raynor. B-But have you been involved in any... fights before?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="saki_zls" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_SakiN_medical">Um, ~target~? Pardon me saying this, but... you're looking a little pale. A-Are you getting enough sleep? I-Is your blood circulation alright?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="kumatora" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_KT_name">"~Target~", t-that name... scares me a little...</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_KT_name">"~Target~", t-that's a bit of a scary name, i-isn't it?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="ganyu" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Um, ~name~? I-I'm sorry, y-you probably get this a lot... But, those horns, a-are they real?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="samus_aran" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Samus_robot">Um, I don't mean to be rude... But are some kind of, um... robot?</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Samus_robot">Um, I-I'm very sorry for asking... but, a-are you a robot?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="estelle" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-explain.png" marker="Mikan_Estelle_princess">W-Wow... I-I never thought I'd meet another princess.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="chiaki" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-explain.png" marker="Mikan_Chiaki_game">O-Oh, are you here to try out a-a new game, ~target~?</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png" marker="Mikan_Chiaki_game">O-Oh, I get it! Y-You... you're here to try a new game, r-right, ~target~?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="spooky" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Spooky_haunt">W-Wow... are you an actual ghost? H-Have you ever haunted anyone...?</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png" marker="Mikan_Spooky_haunt">W-Wow, I-I've never met an actual ghost before! U-um, have you ever haunted anyone before?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="polly" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Polly_boo">I don't think I've seen a ghost outside a movie. Um, you're not going to jump out and say something like, "boo" right?</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Polly_boo">Huh, I-I've never seen a ghost outside a movie before. Um, you're not going to jump out and try to scare me, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="38">
                <condition role="target" character="magma_grunt" saidMarker="mg_mikan_medical_assistance" />
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="Mikan_MG_shots">Huh...? Y-You don't like needles? B-But isn't getting shots fun?</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="Mikan_MG_shots">W-What? Y-You don't like shots? B-But getting shots can be fun. I-I brought some along just in case. S-So I could show it to you, if want...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="50">
                <condition role="target" character="fischl" saidMarker="fischl_mikancarry" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Fischl_particular">A-Ah...okay. I don't mean to pry, b-but were you thinking of s-someone in particular?</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Fischl_particular">Oh, um, alright. B-But if you don't mind me asking. W-Were you thinking of anyone in particular?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="yusuke" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Yusuke_dietprobe">Um, ~target~ I apologize if this is rude... But are you keeping a proper diet?</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Yusuke_dietprobe">~Target~, pardon me for asking, but have you been eating enough recently?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="53">
                <condition filter="fighter" role="target" />
                <state img="#-worried.png" oneShotId="5">D-Do you get into fights a lot, ~name~? Um,  you can come see me if you ever get hurt in one, okay?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5" oneShotId="13">
                <condition filter="fighter" role="target" />
                <state img="#-plead.png" oneShotId="3">I-I know I probably can't stop you from getting into fights... B-But please consider your health sometimes, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="2">
                <condition filter="musician" role="target" />
                <state img="#-explain.png">A-A friend of mine is also a musician! T-Though her music is... a little out there.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">There are so many unique styles of music at Hope's Peak. Y-You'd probably really like it, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="7">
                <condition filter="animal_ears" role="target" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">Aww, t-those are pretty cute ears, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">A-Are those ears, um, real? N-Not that it's a problem to me either way.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="8">
                <condition filter="armor" role="target" />
                <state img="#-worried.png">A-Armor...? A-Are you expecting a fight? P-Please don't involve me...</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Um, are you wearing that armor because you're expecting a fight? Um, if you are then I'll be sure to treat any injuries afterward!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="11">
                <condition filter="blade" role="target" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">W-What are you doing with that blade, ~name~!?</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">I-Is that real, ~Name~? A-Are we even allowed to bring stuff like that here?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="14">
                <condition filter="has_companion" role="target" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">O-Oh, you brought a friend, h-how nice!</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">(&lt;i&gt;I wonder if I could bring someone to this game like ~name~ does.&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="35">
                <condition filter="formal_attire" role="target" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Were we supposed to wear fancy clothes for this!? I-I didn't know!</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">(&lt;i&gt;When I compare myself to ~name~, I feel I should have worn something better...&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I d-don't know if I own anything as fancy as your clothes, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="25">
                <condition filter="gamer" role="target" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png">T-This probably isn't the type of game you're used to, ~name~, ehehe.</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">H-Have you ever played a game like this, ~name~?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="27">
                <condition filter="royalty" role="target" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Eeek! Y-You're royalty!? I-I'm sorry that I won instead of you. P-Please don't have me executed!</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I-It's hard to imagine someone royal p-playing a game like this... N-Not that I have a problem with it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="39">
                <condition filter="androgynous" role="target" />
                <state img="#-worried.png">(&lt;i&gt;I'm not really sure about ~name~. But if I say something, I might offend them.&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="80">
                <condition filter="high_heels" role="target" />
                <state img="#-worried.png">Uuuu, shoes like that make me nervous. I-I trip enough when I-I  wear flat shoes...</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">I-I can't help but feel nervous when I see your shoes, ~name~. I-I trip a lot, and that's when I'm wearing flat shoes. Ah! N-Not that I think your shoes are bad or anything.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="104">
                <condition filter="ghost" role="target" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I-I've always wondered how they make the ghosts in the movies... I-Is that weird?</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">I-I've always thought haunting people... actually sounded a bit fun, ehehe...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5" oneShotId="115">
                <condition filter="short" role="target" />
                <state img="#-plead.png">Um, I want you to know that I don't think you're any less capable because you're short. Ah! I-I'm sorry I shouldn't have said anything!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">(&lt;i&gt;~Name~ is so short... It's a little cute! But ~target.ifMale(he'd|she'd)~ probably get mad if I said that&lt;/i&gt;.)</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="122">
                <condition filter="tall" role="target" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Y-You're so tall, ~target~. I-It's a little intimidating...</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">I-I bet ~target~ could pick me up and throw me like a rag doll if ~target.ifMale(he|she)~ wanted to! P-Please don't!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="44">
                <condition role="target" consecutiveLosses="3" />
                <test expr="~target.biggestlead~" cmp="&gt;=" value="3" />
                <state img="#-sad.png">I-I'm sorry ~target~. S-Sometimes just don't work out...</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">Ah! I-I'm sorry, I want to say something. B-But I'm sure I'd just make you feel worse!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="67">
                <condition role="opp" character="miki_miura" saidMarker="miki_mikan_horror" />
                <state img="#-explain.png" marker="Mikan_miki_horrorreason">W-Well... H-Horror is nice. T-There's a lot of blood which nice. A-And the really mean characters usually die first... </state>
                <state img="#-explain.png" marker="Mikan_miki_horrorreason">Um, well. T-There's a lot to enjoy in horror. E-Everyone's scared and t-trying to escape being hunted down. I-I can kind of... relatable... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="49" oneShotId="91">
                <condition status="lost_all" role="target" />
                <condition count="0" status="not_alive" />
                <state img="#-sad.png">I'm sorry ~target~. S-Someone had to do it first... I-I just wish it had been me...</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">I-I'm really sorry, ~target~. I-I wish it had been me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="52">
                <condition role="target" consecutiveLosses="3" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png">J-Just... um... keep at it. Ah! N-Not that I want you to keep losing!</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">Um... please keep going. Ah! I mean please don't give up! N-Not that I want you to keep losing!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="50" oneShotId="92" totalRounds="0">
                <state img="#-surprised.png">A-Alright... I'll start-- W-Wait... it wasn't me?</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">H-Huh...? I didn't lose? A-Are you sure?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-plead.png">I-I'm sorry! P-Please don't be mad at me for winning instead of you!</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">Please forgive me. I-I didn't mean to make you lose...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_stripping">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="critical_darling" stage="0" saidMarker="Mikan_Ibuki1" />
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="Mikan_CD_huh">Ah, o-of course, I-I'm sorry, I-I should have thought about your outfit before say--  Huh? D-Did you say Ibuki?</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="Mikan_CD_huh">I-I'm sorry. I-It was pretty stupid for me to not have thought about your outfit before saying an-- Wait, um... d-did you say, Ibuki?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="46">
                <condition role="target" character="wikipe-tan" stage="0" saidMarker="MikanTeacher" />
                <state img="#-explain.png" marker="Mikan_WP_same">O-Oh, it's just... one of m-my teachers wore similar clothes before. S-Sorry for the mistake.</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png" marker="Mikan_WP_same">W-Well... it's just... I-I had a teacher who wore similar clothes once. I-I'm sorry for assuming you were the same...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="fischl" stage="0" saidMarker="fischl_mikanmondstadt" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Fischl_Japan">O-Oh, um, I was born, and live in Japan. Um, have you been there before...?</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Fischl_Japan">W-Well, um r-right now I live in Japan. I-I'm sorry if this is rude, b-but have you visited Japan before?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="bernadetta" stage="0" saidMarker="Mikan_Bernie_0A" />
                <state img="#-worried.png">I-I know you may feel fine, but not getting enough sunlight can be dangerous! Sunlight is essential to maintaining proper bone health. I-It may even affect your level of energy, or sleep...</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">I-I know you probably don't feel it, but you can really hurt yourself by not getting enough sunlight! N-Not getting enough will affect your energy level. And more importantly, can increase your risk of bone fractures, a-and muscle injuries.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="jim" stage="0" saidMarker="Mikan_resp0a" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png" marker="Mikan_Jim_war">A-A soldier!? A-Are you currently fighting? I-I didn't know there was a war going on!</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png" marker="Mikan_Jim_war">Y-You're a soldier!? I-I'm sorry, I didn't know! A-Are you currently... in service? I didn't know there was a war happening!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="86">
                <condition role="target" character="heris" stage="0" saidMarker="HerisMikanDoctor" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Heris_experience">W-Wow... that sounds complex. I-I don't have any experience with that kind of thing.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Heris_experience">O-Oh... I'm sorry I assumed when I didn't know... I-I don't really have any experience with that kind of field...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="88">
                <condition role="target" character="neptune" stage="0" saidMarker="nep_mikan_outfit1" />
                <state img="#-explain.png" marker="Mikan_Nep_nurse">R-Really? Are they also a nurse?</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png" marker="Mikan_Nep_nurse">R-Really? I'm happy to hear that. A-Are they a nurse as well?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="heris" stage="1" saidMarker="HerisMikanMistakes2" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Heris_suddenlyadvice">O-Oh. I understand being clumsy. But if you were working in a laboratory, I hope you used proper precautions.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Heris_suddenlyadvice">Ah, while I definitely understand being clumsy. I-If you were working in a lab... I hope you had safety measures beforehand...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="jim" stage="1" saidMarker="Mikan_resp1a" />
                <state img="#-explain.png" marker="Mikan_Jim_believe">O-Oh... no, i-it's okay. I-I was... a little caught off guard. B-But I really don't have any reason not to believe you...</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="Mikan_Jim_believe">H-Huh? N-No... I'm okay. I mean it did... surprise me a little. B-But I still believe you...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="kumatora" stage="0" saidMarker="MikanKT_name_resp" />
                <state img="#-fear.png" marker="Mikan_KT_beartiger">I-I'm sorry, y-you're right. B-Bears and tigers aren't scary... at all! ah! N-Not that I think of you as a b-bear or a t-tiger! I-I'm sorry!</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png" marker="Mikan_KT_beartiger">Y-You're right! I-I'm sorry! Those would be w-way scarier. B-Bears and tigers aren't scary at all! Ah! N-Not that I think of you as a bear o-or a tiger! I-I'm sorry!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="ganyu" stage="0" saidMarker="ganyumikanhorns" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Ganyu_grabpull">W-Well, it's just... aren't they... dangerous? I-I mean, w-what if someone tried to grab them? O-Or pull them?</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Ganyu_grabpull">Well, I just thought... have you ever had trouble with them? L-Like i-if someone tried to grab them o-or pull them?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="jim" stage="2" saidMarker="Mikan_resp2a" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Jim_interested">Um, right! I-I think some people in my school are very interested in that...</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">Y-Yes! Um, some of people at Hope's Peak seem very interested in that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="chiaki" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Chiaki_firsttime">I-I've actually played this game a few times before. Ah! I-I'm not very good though...</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Chiaki_firsttime">T-This actually isn't my first time playing something like this... Ah! I'm not very good at it though, s-sorry.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="samus_aran" saidMarker="Mikan_resp0a" />
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="Mikan_SamusA_sorry">I-I'm sorry... y-you must get that a lot. I-I should have thought before I spoke.</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="Mikan_SamusA_sorry">P-Please forgive me! I-I didn't think before I spoke. Y-You must be really tired of hearing that question by now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="heris" saidMarker="HerisMikanHealthcare" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Heris_forward">R-Really? W-Well, I don't think I would mind working with you... Ah! T-That was probably too forward, I-I'm sorry.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Heris_forward">O-Oh, well, I don't think working with you would be so bad... Um, ah, I'm sorry! I-I was probably being too forward there.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="neptune" saidMarker="nep_mikan_friend1" />
                <state img="#-sad.png" marker="Mikan_Neptune_annoy">W-Well... it's just that people tend to find me... annoying. I-I wouldn't want to annoy her...</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png" marker="Mikan_Neptune_annoy">Y-You're right... I-It's just that people usually say that I'm... annoying. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="37">
                <condition filter="scarred" role="target" />
                <state img="#-sad.png">Scars... I'm sorry you got hurt, ~name~</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">Y-You have scars... W-Was growing up not easy, ~name~?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="6">
                <condition filter="aggressive" role="target" />
                <state img="#-sad.png">(&lt;i&gt;~Name~ is kind of scary. I hope I don't make them mad.&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">Ahhh! A-Are you mad at me, ~name~!? P-Please don't hurt me!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="12">
                <condition filter="blonde" role="target" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I-I've always thought blonde hair looked really pretty. It, um, looks really good on you, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Blonde... is a nice color, ~name~. I-I've always thought it looked... fashionable.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="15">
                <condition filter="quiet" role="target" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Y-You really don't have to say much, ~name~. I promise it doesn't bother me.</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">Y-You don't talk a lot, ~name~. I-Is everything alright?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="16">
                <condition filter="confident" role="target" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Y-You're so confident, ~name~. I-It's a little scary.</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">You're so confident, ~name~. Do... Do you do this kind of thing a lot?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="21">
                <condition filter="drunk" role="target" />
                <state img="#-explain.png">Um, I don't mean to pry, but excessive intoxication can be detrimental to your health, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">(&lt;i&gt;I hope ~name~ is okay... People can be scary when they're drunk.&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="23">
                <condition filter="slutty" role="target" />
                <state img="#-worried.png">Um, don't you think you're being a little too much, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">(&lt;i&gt;What if ~name~ takes an interest in me!?&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="45">
                <condition filter="horror" role="target" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Ah! ~Name~, y-you look right out of a horror movie. W-Would you mind if I asked you some questions?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">W-Wow, ~name~, I-I really like your horror costume. Y-You must have put a lot of work into it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" oneShotId="82">
                <condition filter="assisted_strip" role="target" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Ahhh! P-Please don't strip me too! I-I'm not ready yet!</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">O-Oh no... P-Please don't strip me as well! I-I'm not ready for it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="68">
                <condition role="opp" character="jason" stage="0" saidMarker="RE_Mikan_Jason_familiar" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="Mikan_Jason_recognize">N-Now I realize! Y-You're dressed up as Jason, f-from Friday the 13th? I-It's a really well-made costume!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="Mikan_Jason_recognize">Ah! I-I understand now! Y-You came dressed as Jason. F-From Friday the 13th? I-It looks really good on you!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_stripped">
            <case stage="0-7" id="39">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <test expr="~clothing.generic~" value="shoes" />
                <test expr="~target.wearing(shoes)~" cmp="!=" value="~blank~" />
                <state img="#-fear.png">I-I don't get it! H-How did you even fit those in there!?</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">W-What? H-How did you have another pair on!? I-it doesn't make s-sense to me!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="critical_darling" stage="0" saidMarker="Mikan_Ibuki2" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_CD_itsthetruth">Ah, w-well, I know it sounds a little hard to believe. But my friend... h-her name is also Ibuki.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_CD_itsthetruth">Ah, i-it's nothing wrong. I-It's just... my f-friend's name is also Ibuki. I-I know it sounds a little strange, b-but I promise I'm not lying!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="fischl" stage="1" saidMarker="fischl_mikanjapan" />
                <state img="#-sad.png" marker="Mikan_Fischl_explainattempt">O-Oh... well Japan is... nice. I-It's pretty warm, e-except for the parts which get cold. I-It's not the biggest country. A-Although I haven't visited most of it. I-I'm sorry, I'm not doing a very good job at explaining this... </state>
                <state img="#-sad.png" marker="Mikan_Fischl_explainattempt">Um, well... J-Japan is... nice. T-There are a lot of animals. T-Though maybe not more than the average country... A-And it's... surrounded by the ocean. I-I'm sorry, I'm not doing a good job at explaining this...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="heris" stage="1" saidMarker="HerisMikanExperience" />
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="Mikan_Heris_mistake">H-Huh? Y-You... you're not mad at me?</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="Mikan_Heris_mistake">W-Wha...? I-I made a mistake, a-aren't you mad at me?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="heris" stage="2" saidMarker="HerisMikanAdvice" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="Mikan_Heris_safe">T-That's good... keeping others safe should always be a top concern.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="Mikan_Heris_safe">I-I'm happy to hear that. It should always be a top concern to keep others safe.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="jim" stage="1" saidMarker="Mikan_resp0b" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png" marker="Mikan_Jim_earthshock">W-Wait? T-This star system!? Y-You... you mean it isn't on Earth!?</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png" marker="Mikan_Jim_earthshock">Huh? I-I'm not sure I'm understanding you! Y-You mean it's not on Earth!?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="neptune" stage="1" saidMarker="nep_mikan_outfit2" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="Mikan_Nep_happy">W-Wow, really!? I-I'm still in school, b-but I'm really happy to hear that!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="Mikan_Nep_happy">R-Really!? T-That's so nice! Even though I'm still in school, h-hearing about others who want to help makes me really happy.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="sakura" stage="3" saidMarker="3UP" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">W-Wow... y-you're an actual zombie! T-That's amazing!</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">A-An... actual zombie... D-Do you know anymore?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="sakura" stage="3" saidMarker="3DN" />
                <state img="#-sad.png">O-Oh... I-It's just makeup... I-I should have known that...</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">O-Oh... right, it was just makeup. I-I'm sorry I didn't know that...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="jim" stage="2" saidMarker="Mikan_resp1b" />
                <state img="#-stressing.png" marker="Mikan_Jim_listen">Y-Yes! I-I promise I'll keep my eyes and ears open the entire time!</state>
                <state img="#-yell.png" marker="Mikan_Jim_listen">U-Um, you don't have to worry about me! I-I promise I'll listen to the entire thing!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="kumatora" stage="1" saidMarker="Mikan_KT_beartiger_resp" />
                <state img="#-sad.png" marker="Mikan_KT_upset">Um, alright. I-I'm sorry if I've upset you in anyway...</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png" marker="Mikan_KT_upset">Oh, o-of course, um, s-sorry if I've upset you at all. I really didn't mean to.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="heris" stage="3" saidMarker="HerisMikanHealthcare2" />
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="Mikan_Heris_think">Right, right, I'll um, I'll get started thinking about it, right away!</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="Mikan_Heris_think">O-Of course! I-I, I'll um get started thinking of a way as soon as I can!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="jim" stage="3" saidMarker="Mikan_resp2b" />
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="Mikan_Jim_note">Um... (&lt;i&gt;I should have brought my notepad.&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="Mikan_Jim_note">O-Okay...(&lt;i&gt;Why didn't I bring my notepad with me!?&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="neptune" stage="2" saidMarker="nep_mikan_friend2" />
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="Mikan_Nep_lost">Y-You really think so? B-But, I'm not really sure how...</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="Mikan_Nep_lost">Y-You're being honest? I-I'm sorry, but I really wouldn't know how...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="chiaki" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png" marker="Mikan_Chiaki_games">H-Huh? N-No, I-I couldn't do that! I-I'm not very good at games! A-And you know so much more!</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png" marker="Mikan_Chiaki_games">Huh? N-No... I don't think someone like me could do that! B-Besides, y-you know way more about games than I do...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="wikipe-tan" saidMarker="MikanTeacher2" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_WPtan_clumsy">A-Ah! No, um, nothing in particular. W-Well, actually, it would be good if I could learn how to be less clumsy.</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png" marker="Mikan_WPtan_clumsy">O-Oh no, um,  nothing in particular. Though, it would be nice if I could learn how to be less clumsy, b-but I don't know if you could teach me about that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="5">
                <alternative>
                    <condition count="0" filter="danganronpa" role="target" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <condition filter="school_uniform" role="target" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-explain.png">O-Oh! Hope's Peak has a school uniform too! B-But I'm not wearing it right now, sorry.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="9">
                <condition filter="skinny" role="target" />
                <state img="#-sad.png">(&lt;i&gt;I'm kind of worried about ~name~. I hope ~target.ifMale(he|she)~ is eating properly...&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Um, ~name~? I-I don't mean to pry, but do you have a proper diet? I-I wouldn't want you to become malnourished.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="10">
                <condition filter="tail" role="target" />
                <state img="#-worried.png">Are... Are you going to remove that tail? Unless... you can't for some reason?</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">(&lt;i&gt;If that tail isn't real... Then I hope it isn't attached to anywhere... bad.&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="19">
                <condition filter="mean" role="target" />
                <state img="#-stressing.png">(&lt;i&gt;I can't upset ~name~, I can't upset ~name~, I can't upset ~name~.&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">(&lt;i&gt;~Name~ looks like someone... who wouldn't leave me alone.&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="20">
                <condition filter="serious" role="target" />
                <state img="#-worried.png">Y-You're so serious, ~name~. You... You're not hiding anything, are you?</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">(&lt;i&gt;~Name~ is kind of scary. I wouldn't want to get on ~target.ifMale(his|her)~ bad side.&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="22">
                <condition filter="gloomy" role="target" />
                <state img="#-explain.png">U-Um, it's okay, ~name~. It's just one loss. I-I'm sure you can come back from it... really.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Um, don't feel bad, ~name~. W-Would you feel better if I lost the next round?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="84">
                <condition filter="clothing_destruction" role="target" />
                <state img="#-worried.png">O-Oh no... I-It looks like some of your clothing was destroyed. D-Do you want some of mine to replace it? A-Ah but I don't know if they would fit...</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">A-Ah... S-Some of your clothing was destroyed, I-I'm sorry. D-Do you want some of my money so you can buy new ones?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="114">
                <condition filter="athletic" role="target" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png">W-Wow, y-you must have worked hard for that. Um, your body I mean... sorry.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I-It always makes me happy to see someone taking care of... that. Um, I mean... your body, sorry...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="36" oneShotId="69">
                <condition status="exposed" role="target" />
                <condition count="1" status="exposed" />
                <test expr="~target.biggestlead~" cmp="&gt;=" value="3" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png">O-Oh... I'm sorry, ~name~. B-But, you can't win them all, right?</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Oh, I'm sorry, ~name~. L-Losing like that can't be fun. B-But... You'll get it next time, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="32">
                <test expr="~revealed.type~" value="major" />
                <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="major" />
                <state img="#-sad.png" oneShotId="19">Oh... Well, I-I guess it was good to come prepared.</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png" oneShotId="18">Huh, I-I was hoping... N-Never mind. I-It's good you came prepared.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="41" oneShotId="87">
                <condition count="1" status="exposed" />
                <state img="#-worried.png">D-Does showing off first make it h-harder or more fun for you? O-Or maybe both?</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">I-Isn't it kind of scary to show off first? O-Or maybe you like this sort of thing...?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-7" id="64">
                <condition role="target" character="chihiro" />
                <state img="#-fear.png">~Target~? W-Where are you going? I-I'm soooorrry! I-I didn't mean to scare you away!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-7" id="65">
                <condition role="target" character="chihiro" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Huh...? Y-You're not Chihiro... but, you look just like him?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="17">
                <condition filter="has_companion" role="target" />
                <state img="#-worried.png">Do... Do you both need to do it? O-Or are you going to help each other.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="18">
                <condition filter="quiet" role="target" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I-I guess it's hard to do something like this quietly...</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">I um, I don't really mind if you make some noise right now, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7" oneShotId="81">
                <condition filter="bondage_forfeit" role="target" />
                <state img="#-horny.png">~Target~ looks like ~target.ifMale(he's|she's)~ having so much fun like that. M-Maybe I should try that next time...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Ehehe... being tied up like that look's fun, ~target~. M-Maybe I should try it next time.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="83">
                <condition filter="kneeling_forfeit" role="target" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Ehehe... I-if I did it like, ~target~ did it... I think I'd be worried about falling over...</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I-I think if I did it like ~target~ is doing it... I think I'd fall on my face by mistake...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" oneShotId="85">
                <condition filter="uses_toy" role="target" />
                <state img="#-explain.png">M-Make sure you properly sanitize that before your next use, ~target~!</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">I-I hope that was properly sanitized before you used it! ~target~.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I-Is this, um, an easy thing for you to do?</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">Y-You're really going to...? O-Okay... if you're sure.</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">Y-You can close your eyes and think of something else if that helps you enjoy it.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I-I guess you've been looking forward to this, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-5">
                <state img="#-worried.png">(&lt;i&gt;Do I want, ~target~ to think of me?&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">(&lt;i&gt;A part of me... really, really wants to see this...&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">P-Please don't hesitate to look at me while doing this. It wouldn't bother me... at all.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I-I don't think I've seen a guy masturbate in front of me before...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Are you going to join me? I-I don't think I would mind the company.</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">Y-You should just do it a-as you normally would.(&lt;i&gt;I-I really want to see how, ~name~ usually does it.&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I-Is there anything I can do to make this better for you?</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">W-Want me do anything for you? I want you to enjoy this like I am, ehehe...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="117">
                <condition filter="gay" role="target" />
                <state img="#-worried.png">(&lt;i&gt;Would ~target~ get mad at me if I watched? What do I do?&lt;/i&gt;) Y-You're starting...?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-worried.png">I-Is it really okay for you to do something so... private, in the open like this.</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">Um, n-not that I'm doubting your competency. B-But try not to give yourself a cramp.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">J-Just, um, try to have fun? I-Is that right?</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">Don't grip too hard, o-or you may hurt your wrist, or fingers.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-5">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Um, would you mind if I, um, maybe watched a bit. O-Only if it's okay with you though...</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">I-It got erect so quickly!</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">(&lt;i&gt;Is it really okay for me to interested in stuff like this? Won't the others think I'm weird?&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Ehehe... this is the only place where I can see something like this...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-horny.png">W-Were you looking forward to this? I-I think I was... a little bit.</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">N-No need to rush... I-It'll feel better if you go slowly, right?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Ehehe... How long have you been waiting for this?</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Hehe, d-do you find nurses attractive, ~name~?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-horny.png">W-Wow... Are you starting to get into it?</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">Be careful not to strain yourself, okay?</state>
                <state img="#-stressing.png">(&lt;i&gt;Even if I don't look, I can hear. And that just makes me want to look!&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png" oneShotId="31">Does doing this... make you happy?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">K-Keep going...!</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">I-If you wear yourself out, I-I can see if I can find a cushion for you to rest on!</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">A-Are you like that because of m-me!?</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">Y-You don't... want any... help with that... right? I-I'm sorry! I-I shouldn't be saying stuff like that.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Ehehe... once you start to look... I-It's hard to look away...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-4">
                <state img="#-plead.png">I-It'll be okay... Even if it's a little awkward at the beginning. I-I'm sure you'll enjoy it by the end.</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">(&lt;i&gt;If ~name~ thought of me while doing this... would I like it?&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">(&lt;i&gt;The way his hand goes back and forth... It's hard to look away from.&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">(&lt;i&gt;The thought of ~name~ looking at me while he does this... It makes me want to join him&lt;/i&gt;.)</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-horny.png">(&lt;i&gt;I hope he's enjoying me...&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">P-Pace yourself... I-I think it'll feel better that way.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">W-Would you want to do... t-this with me instead, next time?</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Um, please don't feel bad about looking at me... It's what I'm here for, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-worried.png">A-Are we in s-sync, ~target~?</state>
                <state img="#-heavy-1.png">(&lt;i&gt;Would ~target~ want to do... it together with me?&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-heavy-1.png">(&lt;i&gt;The thought of ~target~ looking at me while doing this...&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">U-Um... ~target~... I-If you wanted to do... it with me. I-I'd really be okay doing anything you wanted! Ah! N-Not that I'd be so presumptuous to assume you wanted to do that with me.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Y-You look so... natural doing this, ~target~.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_heavy_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-fear.png">Ack! S-Something's coming soon. I-I can tell!</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Ehehe... he probably can't even hear us anymore...</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">If it's this fun to watch... T-Then it definitely must feel great to experience... right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-plead.png">I-I know you're almost there... B-But please don't be so rough. I-I don't want you to hurt yourself.</state>
                <state img="#-plead.png">P-Please be careful not to be too rough. I-I wouldn't want you to strain or bruise your wrist.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Y-Yes! H-He's so close...</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">D-Don't feel bad about getting a-any on me. I can clean myself later.</state>
                <state img="#-heavy-1.png">L-Let's do it together!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-explain.png">Ah! D-Do you want me to clean that up for you...?</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Looks like a, um, a healthy amount.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-5">
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Ahhh! T-That was more then I was expecting!</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">C-Congratulations... O-Or I'm sorry that you lost? I-I'm not really sure.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">O-Oh good... I-I was worried you'd get some on me...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-sad.png">(&lt;i&gt;I wonder how that would feel... On me.&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">(&lt;i&gt;Maybe next time... I could make him feel like that...&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Ehehe... T-That was definitely a lot... W-Were you pent up?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-sad.png">I-I understand that this can be an... uncomfortable experience. Don't force yourself if you're not enjoying it.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I-I'm sorry, ~name~. I-I hope this isn't too much trouble for you...</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">U-Um... You'll do great! Right?</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">T-take as long as you need to get started...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-5">
                <state img="#-stressing.png">W-Would it more rude to stare. O-Or not to? I-I'm not really sure!</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Um, I promise I won't stare... U-Unless you want me to...?</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">I-I'm sure you would hate me if I did anything weird. S-So I promise I won't!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Y-You're joining me...? As long as we're separate, it should be fine...</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">(&lt;i&gt;If she's joining me... Will I be forgotten!?&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Ehehe... having more company should be fun.</state>
                <state img="#-heavy-1.png">(&lt;i&gt;Would it feel even better if we did it together?&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="119">
                <condition filter="lesbian" role="target" />
                <state img="#-sad.png">(&lt;i&gt;~Target~ would want me to watch... so it's okay, right?&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-explain.png">Um, I think it would work best... If you s-started slow, and worked your way up. N-Not that you have to listen to me.</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">(&lt;i&gt;I know it's selfish and wrong, but part of me doesn't want them to look at her...&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">W-Would you want us all to turn around? I-It would make it feel more private. A-Ah, never mind. I-I really shouldn't speak for everyone.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-5">
                <state img="#-worried.png">A-Are you really okay... doing it in front of us?</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">T-This really seems like too much... But if, ~name~ is okay with it...</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">(&lt;i&gt;She got aroused so quickly! Was she looking forward to this that much?&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-stressing.png">I-I shouldn't be watching this... I-It should be the other way around!</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">Why... Why did you lose before me? Is something like that supposed to happen?</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">W-Would you find it... odd if I stared? O-Or would you... like it?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-explain.png">Rub slowly around the edge. T-That should h-help you warm up.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I-If you've gotten this far. Then you wouldn't mind if I watched... just a little bit, right?</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Ehehe, you'll probably sound pretty cute, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-horny.png">(&lt;i&gt;This isn't like an anatomy chart...&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">Um, d-does doing it so... publicly... change anything for you?</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">(&lt;i&gt;Those noises... Can ~target~ hear herself?&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Ehehe, a-are you thinking about anyone in particular, ~target~?</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">(&lt;i&gt;Is ~target~ looking at me? Does she like me like that?&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">I-I wasn't being weird! I-I swear, ~target~!</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I-It won't be long now...</state>
                <state img="#-yell.png">U-Um...! I-I know this probably isn't the easiest thing to do... So thank you!</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">Um, while my knowledge is mostly superficial. I-I do believe masturbation can have some stress-relieving effects.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">(&lt;i&gt;~Target~ probably doesn't want me to help, right?&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">Ah... uh... I-I'm sorry if I say anything weird, ~target~!</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Ehehe... watching this is really something special to me.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Ehehe, y-you look pretty cute doing that, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I-It's weird... I-I think it's more fun to watch you... T-Then it is to play...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-horny.png">(&lt;i&gt;She looks so happy...&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">Hehe, w-we actually do it pretty similarly.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I-I'm a little... jealous of, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I-I guess I won't have to wait long to join, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">I know how you feel, ~name~. I-It's good, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-worried.png">(&lt;i&gt;Should I say anything about how she's doing it? Or would that be weird...&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Um, I'm finding it kind of difficult to focus on the game while... t-this is happening.</state>
                <state img="#-stressing.png">Uuu! W-With the way I play. I-I'll definitely be joining her soon.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">(&lt;i&gt;Would ~name~ want me to join her?&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">(&lt;i&gt;Do I sound like that?&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-stressing.png">E-Even if she's doing it... Please don't forget about me, everyone.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">(&lt;i&gt;I hope... she's thinking of me...&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Ehehe... isn't this a weird game? I-I mean, losing should be less enjoyable than winning, right?</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I-I... I find it more fun doing it together... I-Is that weird?</state>
                <state img="#-heavy-1.png">(&lt;i&gt;Would ~target~ like it if we finished at the same time?&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Ehehe... H-Hearing you... I want to do it more!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_heavy_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-happy.png">W-Wow...people really lose control while doing this...</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Y-You're so into it... I guess being watched doesn't bother you, huh?</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">~Name~ is so close... I-I'm getting a little excited!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-horny.png">(&lt;i&gt;What if ~target~ said my name when she finished...&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">(&lt;i&gt;I can't look away... I really want see her face when she cums!&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-7" id="57" oneShotId="98">
                <condition role="target" character="ganyu" sayingMarker="fallingasleep" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png">O-Oh... she fell asleep. S-Should I get her a blanket?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Ehehe... She's actually pretty cute when she's asleep.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-horny.png">W-Wow...T-That must have felt great...</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">Um, just so you know. It's perfectly normal to feel tired after doing something like this.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">T-Thank you... for doing that for us.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-5">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Ehehe, your face... I-It looked really nice like that...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Maybe joining you could be... pretty fun..</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">Oh no... S-Should someone clean that up? S-Should I?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-horny.png">(&lt;i&gt;She looks pretty cute when she's worn out...&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Y-You definitely enjoyed that, right? I-I can see it on your face.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Hehe... Everyone should be able to experience pleasure like that, right?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate_first">
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-surprised.png">W-What? Already!? I-I-I.., I hope I'm ready for this.</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">I-I'm a little sad. But I can't say I'm surprised I'm going first...</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">I-I'm the first one? W-Won't everyone have to look at me then?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate">
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">O-Oh I-I guess it's my turn now. I-I... I hope you enjoy it.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I-I wonder if I'll enjoy this as much as you will...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="start_masturbating">
            <case stage="5" id="2">
                <state img="#-starting.png">U-Um, I-I really don't do this too often. So, um, I hope you can be patient with me.</state>
                <state img="#-starting.png">I-I made sure to wash my hands thoroughly before I came here. S-So, I'll be fine...</state>
                <state img="#-starting.png">Right... I'm sure I can do this right... definitely.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="masturbating">
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-calm.png">J-Just like that...</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png" oneShotId="125" weight="20" collectible="Mikan's_Apron" collectible-value="+1">W-While masturbation has no major health benefits, it can still be beneficial. It's the safest way to experience sexual pleasure, after all.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">S-Sorry if I make a mess...</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">A-Are you enjoying this...?</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">I-I'll try my best to be quiet. I-I don't want to upset you all.</state>
                <state img="#-heavy-1.png">I-I know this feeling...</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Ehehe... It's good to know even I can't mess this up.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I-It's much more fun to do this looking at people, and not... colored anatomy charts, ehehe...</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">I-Is there any way you want to see me do it? P-Please let me know...</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">P-Please feel free to watch. T-That's what I'm here for... right?</state>
                <state img="#-heavy-1.png">Should I spread my legs further for you?</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">D-Do you like it when I do it like this?</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">It's odd... I-I almost find it easier to do it in front of everyone...</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">I-I think I prefer using my hands to... other things I've had to use.</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">H-Huh? I-I sorry! It's hard to pay attention to the game right now!</state>
                <state img="#-heavy-1.png">Mhm! (&lt;i&gt;They're all looking at me...&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="heavy_masturbating">
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Keep watching me... please...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy-1.png">It's like... nothing else matters but this...</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I-Is all that noise... coming from me?</state>
                <state img="#-heavy-1.png">I-It's like I'm drowning in pleasure!</state>
                <state img="#-yell.png">P-Please don't forget this sight, everyone!</state>
                <state img="#-heavy-1.png">Ahh... I'm so close... J-Just a little more.</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">(&lt;i&gt;What will give them the best view?&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-heavy-1.png">(&lt;i&gt;Knowing they're all watching... It makes me want to go faster.&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">Do... Do you like it w-when I get excited?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finishing_masturbating">
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-finishing.png">Ahhh! I'm, I'm...!</state>
                <state img="#-finishing.png">Watch me, E-Everyone!!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="7" id="3">
                <state img="#-calm.png">W-Wow... That was exciting. W-Were you watching?</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">D-Did I really say stuff like that? I-I'm sorry, everyone!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="after_masturbating">
            <case stage="7" oneShotId="36">
                <condition count="0" filter="danganronpa" role="opp" />
                <state img="#-worried.png">(&lt;i&gt;What if my classmates wonder where I was? What could I even tell them? And if they do find out, what then. What if they want to come with next time!?&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-calm.png">&lt;i&gt;yawn&lt;/i&gt; T-That was more tiring then I thought it would be...</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">E-Even if I'm not playing... I-I'm sure watching could be just as fun...</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">W-Would anyone like to hear an interesting medical fact? I know a lot.</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">Ah! I wish I had something clean up with... Staying like this, i-it feels a little unsanitary.</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">A-Am I talking to much? I-It's really okay too tell me if I am...</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Doing it like that... was actually a bit stress reliving. D-Does that make sense?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">T-That was so fun... T-This place... It's like heaven to me.</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png">Ehehe... I-I'd gladly do that again if someone asked me...</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">M-Maybe I could just put my apron back on now? O-Or would that be too much.</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">A-As fun as that was... I-I really hope I didn't say anything... unsightly!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="29">I didn't know masturbation could be so fun! I haven't had the best experiences with it before...</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">T-This game was fun, but... I think I'll wait a bit before playing again. Um, you know what they say about too much of a good thing.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_victory">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-surprised.png" collectible="Mikan's_panties">W-What? I-I actually won? A-Are you sure...?</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png" collectible="Mikan's_panties">I-I won... B-But I'm feeling pretty tired...</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" collectible="Mikan's_panties">I-I really had a lot of fun! Thank you all for playing with me.</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png" collectible="Mikan's_panties">I don't remember the last time I got to relax like this. T-Thank you, everyone.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-awkward.png" collectible="Mikan's_panties">Huh? B-But I was so close to... N-Never mind...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_defeat">
            <case stage="7">
                <condition role="target" character="myriam" saying="If you are into playing doctor, Mikan, you can be my assistant for some experiment ideas. Is it okay I hang out with you? You should know what is safe." />
                <state img="#-explain.png" collectible="Mikan's_panties">Um... okay! I-I wouldn't mind helping you, so long as we're not harming anyone, o-of course.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <condition role="target" character="myriam" saying="Do you want to hang out together, Mikan? I won't bully you, unless that's your thing. You could be my bullying target practice in that case." />
                <state img="#-fear.png" collectible="Mikan's_panties">Um, sure! B-But the bullying isn't necessary, I-I mean, unless you want to.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7" id="16">
                <condition status="lost_all" role="target" />
                <test expr="~self.place~" value="2" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" collectible="Mikan's_panties">W-Wow, I-It was a lot closer than I thought it would be. </state>
                <state img="#-sad.png" collectible="Mikan's_panties">I-I, I knew I wasn't going to win, but it hurts k-knowing I was so close.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7" id="43">
                <test expr="~self.place~" value="2" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" collectible="Mikan's_panties">D-Don't worry. I-I don't need to win to be happy.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" collectible="Mikan's_panties">S-Second place... P-People don't get mad at you for coming in second, r-right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-calm.png" collectible="Mikan's_panties">Ehehe. E-Even if I lost... I still had a good time...</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png" collectible="Mikan's_panties">After this... I don't know if I really want to go home yet...</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" collectible="Mikan's_panties">I-I enjoyed this... If you like, I-I could prepare a fun trick for next time.</state>
                <state img="#-explain.png" collectible="Mikan's_panties">T-This was fun. I-I know! I should invite some of my f-friends next time.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="global">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="miki_miura" sayingMarker="miki_mikan_naga_coward" />
                <condition role="opp" character="nagamimi" />
                <state img="#-yell.png" marker="Mikan_Miki+Nagamimi_violent">P-Please wait! I-I know you're angry, Miki. B-But getting violent... i-it will only make things worse!</state>
                <state img="#-yell.png" marker="Mikan_Miki+Nagamimi_violent">P-Please wait a moment! I-I understand you're angry, Miki. B-But it won't help anything if you get violent!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="66">
                <condition role="target" character="miki_miura" />
                <condition role="opp" character="nagamimi" />
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="Mikan_Miki_Nagamimi_calm?">Ngh... I-I'm really, really sorry for making you two so angry. I-Is there anything I could do to help you calm down?</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="Mikan_Miki_Nagamimi_calm?">Uuuu... I-I know it's my fault you two are talking like this... I-Is there any way I could help you calm down?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="51">
                <condition role="opp" character="nagamimi" />
                <condition role="opp" character="miki_miura" sayingMarker="miki_naga_mikan_worthitrespond" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png" marker="Mikan_Miki_Magamimi_cute">Huh? Y-You think I'm cute? D-Do you think you could say that... again?</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png" marker="Mikan_Miki_Magamimi_cute">Wha-? Y-You really think that I'm cute? N-No one's said that to me before. Could you say it... again?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="64">
                <condition role="opp" character="miki_miura" />
                <condition role="opp" character="nagamimi" sayingMarker="nagamimi_miki_CowardResponse" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Miki_nagamimi_calm?">Um, s-see, Miki? W-We don't have to settle this with violence...</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Mikan_Miki_nagamimi_calm?">I-Is... Is everything calming down now? I-I guess we didn't need violence to settle this after all.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

    </behaviour>
</opponent>
