<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<collectibles>
    <collectible id="collectible_egg" status="online" img="opponents/cynthia/collectible_egg.png" thumbnail="opponents/cynthia/collectible_egg_thumbnail.png">
        <title>Pokemon Egg</title>
        <subtitle>An unhatched Pokémon egg</subtitle>
        <text>An unhatched Pokémon egg given to you by Sinnoh League Champion Cynthia after beating her in strip poker. You're not exactly sure what Pokémon would come out of this egg, or what to do to get it to hatch. Perhaps you should take it out for a walk? </text>
        <unlock>Win a game against Cynthia (except April Fool's outfit)</unlock>
        <hide-details>true</hide-details>
    </collectible>
    <collectible id="collectible_hidden_fates" status="online" img="opponents/cynthia/collectible_hidden_fates.png" thumbnail="opponents/cynthia/collectible_hidden_fates_thumbnail.png">
        <title>Cynthia Hidden Fates card</title>
        <subtitle>Hidden Fates card</subtitle>
        <text>Cynthia is the Sinnoh League Champion, and her ace Pokémon are her fearsome Garchomp, who's mere presence is capable of figuratively and literally shaking opposing Pokémon to the core, and her trusty Lucario, whose ability to read auras ensure that no secret lies unrevealed.</text>
        <unlock>Defeat Cynthia along with 3 female Pokémon characters</unlock>
        <hide-details>true</hide-details>
    </collectible>
    <collectible id="collectible_ultra_prism" status="online" img="opponents/cynthia/collectible_ultra_prism.png" thumbnail="opponents/cynthia/collectible_ultra_prism_thumbnail.png">
        <title>Cynthia Ultra Prism card</title>
        <subtitle>Ultra Prism card</subtitle>
        <text>Cynthia is the ideal Pokémon trainer, combining the cunning and ferocity expected in battles, yet remaining compassionate and caring to all Pokémon, not just her own. Wrap this all up with her natural ability to lead, and you can see how she has remained undefeated for as long as she has.</text>
        <unlock>Defeat Cynthia along with 2 male Pokémon characters</unlock>
        <hide-details>true</hide-details>
    </collectible>
    <collectible id="collectible_ultra_prism_alternate" status="online" img="opponents/cynthia/collectible_ultra_prism_alternate.png" thumbnail="opponents/cynthia/collectible_ultra_prism_alternate_thumbnail.png">
        <title>Cynthia Ultra Prism Alternate card</title>
        <subtitle>Ultra Prism Alternate</subtitle>
        <text>Cynthia's reputation as one of the strongest trainers is known all throughout the world, from Sinnoh to Alola, from Hoenn to Unova, a mere mention of her name can caused weak-willed trainers to lose their strength. Not even copious usage of Full Restores is enough to beat her. Just be thankful this is a strip poker game, rather than a Pokémon battle.</text>
        <unlock>Defeat Cynthia along with three 8-layered characters</unlock>
        <hide-details>true</hide-details>
    </collectible>
    <collectible id="collectible_piss_jar" status="online" img="opponents/cynthia/collectible_piss_jar.png" thumbnail="opponents/cynthia/collectible_piss_jar.png">
        <title>Jar of Cynthia's Piss</title>
        <subtitle>A jar filled with urine from the Sinnoh League Champion (read the description through the Collectible list for context)</subtitle>
        <text>After the game was over, Cynthia (the real one, not the slutty robot) had the Cynthia-bot whisked away by her Garchomp. Cynthia then made all the players and patrons in the Inventory swear to secrecy not to tell anyone about the actions and words of the Cynthia-bot, which they eagerly did, and all you could think about is how much of a sucker they are.
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Cynthia then approaches you and wants you to swear to secrecy too, but you counter that you will only do so for a favor. She replies that she will do anything within reason, to which you reveal that you want her to pee in a jar.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Cynthia is horrified and disgusted by your suggestion, but she recognizes that this must be done to uphold her reputation. You lead her out to a secluded spot, and hand her an empty jar that seemingly came out of nowhere. She pulls down her pants to her knees, then her pantyhose, then finally her panties, revealing her well-shaven crotch to you.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
She places the jar on the ground and squats over it, her smooth mound scrunching up against the glass opening. First came out a couple of drops, then a short flow, and finally a consistent stream of her warm urine came out of her piss hole, slowly but surely filling up the jar. After what felt like half a minute, the stream finally stops, and Cynthia wiggles her crotch to shake out the last couple of drops of her holy water.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
But you notice something odd: her mound appears to be flushed and damp. You then look at her face, and realizes that her disgusted expression had been replaced by one of mild arousal, and her face is a shade of light red. She pulls her pants back up, puts the lid in the jar, and reminds you to keep your part of the deal. You note that she appears to be giving you bedroom eyes, and she had a hint of arousal in her voice.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Before you could fully process what's happening, she leaves and goes along with her Garchomp. You pick up your prize from the ground, which was quite warm to the touch, and wonder just how much of the Cynthia-bot's claims might actually be true.</text>
        <unlock>Win a game against Cynthia in her April Fool's outfit</unlock>
        <hide-details>true</hide-details>
    </collectible>
</collectibles>
