<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<collectibles>
    <collectible id="collectible_egg" img="opponents/cynthia/collectible_egg.png" thumbnail="opponents/cynthia/collectible_egg_thumbnail.png">
        <title>Pokemon Egg</title>
        <subtitle>An unhatched Pokémon egg</subtitle>
        <text>An unhatched Pokémon egg given to you by Sinnoh League Champion Cynthia after beating her in strip poker. You're not exactly sure what Pokémon would come out of this egg, or what to do to get it to hatch. Perhaps you should take it out for a walk? </text>
        <unlock>Win a game against Cynthia</unlock>
        <hide-details>true</hide-details>
    </collectible>
    <collectible id="collectible_hidden_fates" img="opponents/cynthia/collectible_hidden_fates.png" thumbnail="opponents/cynthia/collectible_hidden_fates_thumbnail.png">
        <title>Cynthia Hidden Fates card</title>
        <subtitle>Hidden Fates card</subtitle>
        <text>Cynthia is the Sinnoh League Champion, and her ace Pokémon are her fearsome Garchomp, who's mere presence is capable of figuratively and literally shaking opposing Pokémon to the core, and her trusty Lucario, whose ability to read auras ensure that no secret lies unrevealed.</text>
        <unlock>Defeat Cynthia along with 3 female Pokémon characters</unlock>
        <hide-details>true</hide-details>
    </collectible>
    <collectible id="collectible_ultra_prism" img="opponents/cynthia/collectible_ultra_prism.png" thumbnail="opponents/cynthia/collectible_ultra_prism_thumbnail.png">
        <title>Cynthia Ultra Prism card</title>
        <subtitle>Ultra Prism card</subtitle>
        <text>Cynthia is the ideal Pokémon trainer, combining the cunning and ferocity expected in battles, yet remaining compassionate and caring to all Pokémon, not just her own. Wrap this all up with her natural ability to lead, and you can see how she has remained undefeated for as long as she has.</text>
        <unlock>Defeat Cynthia along with 2 male Pokémon characters</unlock>
        <hide-details>true</hide-details>
    </collectible>
    <collectible id="collectible_ultra_prism_alternate" img="opponents/cynthia/collectible_ultra_prism_alternate.png" thumbnail="opponents/cynthia/collectible_ultra_prism_alternate_thumbnail.png">
        <title>Cynthia Ultra Prism Alternate card</title>
        <subtitle>Ultra Prism Alternate</subtitle>
        <text>Cynthia's reputation as one of the strongest trainers is known all throughout the world, from Sinnoh to Alola, from Hoenn to Unova, a mere mention of her name can caused weak-willed trainers to lose their strength. Not even copious usage of Full Restores is enough to beat her. Just be thankful this is a strip poker game, rather than a Pokémon battle.</text>
        <unlock>Defeat Cynthia along with three 8-layered characters</unlock>
        <hide-details>true</hide-details>
    </collectible>
</collectibles>
