<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>

<!--This file was machine generated using the Character Editor v6.7.9.1 at 1:42:23 PM on December 16, 2022. Do not edit this file directly unless you know what you're doing.-->
<opponent>
    <version>v6.7.9.1</version>
    <first>Yunyun</first>
    <last>of the Crimson Demons</last>
    <label>Yunyun</label>
    <gender>female</gender>
    <size>large</size>
    <timer>20</timer>
    <intelligence>average</intelligence>



    <wardrobe>
        <clothing name="panties" generic="underwear" position="lower" type="important" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="top" generic="shirt" position="upper" type="major" />
        <clothing name="skirt" generic="skirt" position="lower" type="major" />
        <clothing name="socks" generic="socks" position="legs" type="minor" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="boots" generic="shoes" position="feet" type="extra" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="tie" generic="tie" position="neck" type="extra" />
        <clothing name="belt" generic="belt" position="waist" type="extra" />
    </wardrobe>


    <behaviour>
        <trigger id="selected">
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="yunyun_trick_or_friends" />
                <state img="#-Facade.png">... My name is Yunyun! Cute demon girl of the Crimson Demons! W-Wait, I'm not actually a demon! It's just a costume! Promise!</state>
                <state img="#-Excited.png">I am Yunyun and I must ask... Trick or Treat! And... Erm, please choose Treat...</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">My name is Yunyun! You notice something different about me today! And you'd be right! I'm using a new shampoo. Do I smell nice?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-Posing.png">... My name is Yunyun! An arch-wizard and... um, it's nice to meet you all! </state>
                <state img="#-Posing2.png">... My name is Yunyun! An arch-wizard and future Chief to the entirety of the Crimson Demons! Be careful for... &lt;i&gt;(Eris, this introduction is so embarrassing!!)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_selected">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="megumin" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png" marker="megumin_greeting">Megumin! You finally arrived! Uh, not that I knew you were coming or anything...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="darkness" />
                <state img="#-Crying.png">W-What are you doing here, Darkness?! Did you come to make friends too!?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_start">
            <case stage="0" priority="300">
                <condition count="0" filter="alternative_skin" role="other" />
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="yunyun_trick_or_friends" />
                <state img="#-Scared.png">Am I really the only one in costume?! This is like that time someone lied that it was go to school naked day…</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" />
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="yunyun_trick_or_friends" />
                <test expr="~kazuma.costume~" value="default" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png" marker="meguminkazuma_halloweencostume">Oh. Erm, I see neither of you are wearing Halloween costumes... I had hoped this would be something we could all do together...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" />
                <state img="#-Posing2.png" marker="meguminkazuma_intro">Ah, Kazuma, I'm sorry to interrupt your time with Megumin. But it is I, Yunyun! Fate has brought Megumin and I together once again!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="yunyun_trick_or_friends" />
                <state img="#-Facade.png" marker="kazuma_halloweencostume">Kazuma? You're here?! Please do not undress my cute Halloween outfit with your lecherous eyes!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" priority="100">
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" />
                <state img="#-Posing2.png" marker="megumin_intro">My lifelong rival Megumin! How odd to see you here! I guess since we're both here we might as well duel! Uh, please!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <state img="#-Shocked.png" marker="kazuma_intro">Kazuma! W-Where is Megumin? S-She told me to come here...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" priority="100">
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" />
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="yunyun_trick_or_friends" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png" marker="megumin_outfit">Megumin!? I... did not expect to see you here! &lt;i&gt;(Now I'm embarrassed by this outfit...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="yunyun_trick_or_friends" />
                <state img="#-Posing.png">Happy Halloween! I am here to protect anyone from scares, spooks and loneliness if they require!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition count="4-" filter="konosuba" />
                <state img="#-Happy2.png">I-It's... a-are we playing strip poker? D-did Kazuma get... g-get cursed again?</state>
                <state img="#-Crying.png">I-I c-can't believe we're all playing a game together! A-as f-friends, right? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Uh, wait! Has anyone seen a mage named Megumin? She's my rival! And she invited me here for a duel!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="swap_cards">
            <case stage="0" totalRounds="0" priority="200">
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" />
                <state img="#-Excited.png" marker="megumin_intro2">I challenge you to, um, whatever game we're playing!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" totalRounds="0" priority="200">
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" />
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <state img="#-Excited.png" marker="meguminkazuma_intro2">I, um, c-challenge you to whatever game we're playing! And Kazuma, you will watch, to record my victory once and for all!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" totalRounds="0" priority="200">
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" />
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="yunyun_trick_or_friends" />
                <state img="#-Facade.png" marker="meguminkazuma_intro2">You won't tell any of the other Crimson Demons about me wearing these silly demon horns. R-Right, Megumin? Right?!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" totalRounds="0">
                <state img="#-Shy.png">... I guess since I'm here I'll play... &lt;i&gt;(And hopefully make friends!)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="35">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="yunAaravi_0a" />
                <state img="#-Crying.png">W-Wait, why do I carry a straw like that around where I go?! Just you know, in case it's needed! For emergencies!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Shy.png">C-can we stop playing for just a second and all talk about our ambitions? No? O-okay!</state>
                <state img="#-Scared.png">I've got a bad feeling about ~cards.ifplural(these|this)~ ~cards~ ~cards.ifplural(cards|card)~... I've also got a bad feeling in general... </state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">C-can I have ~cards~ new ~cards.ifplural(cards|card)~? Sorry for being a nuisance!</state>
                <state img="#-Happy2.png">I'll swap ~cards.ifplural(these|this)~ ~cards~ ~cards.ifplural(cards|card)~... um, if I'm allowed to! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-Facade.png">I'm getting used to this!  ~cards.ifPlural(~cards.text~ new cards,|~cards.text~ new card,)~ dealer! W-wait, I didn't mean to sound pushy!</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Can I get ~cards.ifPlural(~cards.text~ new cards|~cards.text~ new card)~? You'll give me them? Really?</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Oh, um, can I get ~cards.ifPlural(~cards.text~ new cards|~cards.text~ new card)~? Wait, I'll keep these ones if you want me to! </state>
                <state img="#-Happy2.png">&lt;i&gt;(If I ask to swap these ~cards.ifPlural(~cards.text~ new cards|~cards.text~ new card)~, maybe people will think I'm smart!)&lt;/I&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-Excited.png">I'd like ~cards.ifPlural(~cards.text~ new cards|~cards.text~ new card)~ please. You can take your time dealer! No need to rush! I'm enjoying spending time with everyone and I want this game to last!</state>
                <state img="#-Sad.png">Hey, can I get ~cards.ifPlural(~cards.text~ new cards|~cards.text~ new card)~? And, um, how are you doing today dealer? Um, do you want to hang out after this game? No? Maybe some other time?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="good_hand">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <condition count="0" character="megumin" />
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="1">If you see my rival Megumin, please tell her that I did good this hand!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Posing.png">Careful! I've played countless games of poker by myself. And won &lt;i&gt;every time!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-Happy2.png">I guess I can use these cards... T-this hand is good, r-right?</state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png">An experienced Crimson Demon like me was destined to get these cards! Uh, wait, that was embarrassing to say! Forget that!</state>
                <state img="#-Stern.png">Let us make a little wager! If I win this hand, you all have to hang out with me after the game!</state>
                <state img="#-Excited.png">Wait, this hand is good! I'm not going to lose! I'm going to win! Yay!</state>
                <state img="#-Posing2.png">I got a good hand? Wait, I'm not surprised! I was o-one of the first of my class to g-graduate, after all!</state>
                <state img="#-Sad.png">If I win can I earn a Skill-Up potion? No? T-That's fine... I probably didn't deserve one anyway...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-Excited.png">I got a good hand! I got a good hand! This game is so fun!</state>
                <state img="#-Excited.png">This is a really lucky hand! Thanks so much, dealer!</state>
                <state img="#-Posing2.png">Hehe, what a hand! A Crimson Demon never loses! Uh, except for those times I lost before. Forget about those please!</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Wow, dealer! This hand is the nicest thing anyone has ever done for me!</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">I might win! That way, you can see my chest, and I can not lose!</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I... these cards are good, right... could you look? ...And stare less at my chest-- unless that means we're friends, then please stare! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-Excited.png">I got a good hand! I got a good hand! This game is so fun!</state>
                <state img="#-Excited.png">This is a really lucky hand! Thanks so much dealer!</state>
                <state img="#-Posing2.png">Hehe, what a hand! A Crimson Demon never loses! Uh, except for those times I lost before. Forget about those please!</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Wow, dealer! This hand is the nicest thing anyone has ever done for me!</state>
                <state img="#-Strip.png">This hand is-- &lt;i&gt;o-oh no... it's actually not bad...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-Excited.png">M-My hand isn't so bad but... OH! It's good! </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="okay_hand">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <condition role="self" hasHand="One Pair" />
                <state img="#-Sad.png" oneShotId="48">Well, at least I have a pair! Of cards that is. I wish I knew somebody who was like me...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Facade.png">I'm, uh, the future chief to the Crimson Demon Clan! That means you should r-respect me! P-please!</state>
                <state img="#-Sad.png">Please let this hand win! &lt;i&gt;(I really need the self-esteem boost right now!)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-Sad.png">This is an average hand... average like me I guess...</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">This hand is good enough... I'll be okay as long as I don't lose!</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">I've always wanted to play a game of strip poker with others! Well, I didn't imagine the strip or the poker part...</state>
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">I hope you haven't heard any rumors about me... I promise, whatever they are, they are untrue! Unless they are nice ones!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Oh... um, well I don't know what to even make of this hand. That's kind of exciting, r-right?</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">It'd be nice if we could &lt;i&gt;all&lt;/i&gt; win...</state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png">I'll win even with these cards! J-Just watch! But not too i-intently!</state>
                <state img="#-Posing.png">I-I can still win! M-maybe if you're distracted by my...</state>
                <state img="#-Posing.png">I-If I... I can still win! Even if my cards aren't the best! I-I know I'll... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Oh... um, well I don't know what to even make of this hand. That's kind of exciting, r-right?</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">It'd be nice if we could &lt;i&gt;all&lt;/i&gt; win...</state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png">I'll win even with these cards! J-Just watch! But not too i-intently!</state>
                <state img="#-Excited.png">This hand is great! I can feel it!</state>
                <state img="#-Excited.png">I know you must really like me, since you gave me such an okay hand!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="bad_hand">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Facade.png">This game isn't some kind of trick to get me &lt;i&gt;n-naked, &lt;/i&gt; right? Wait! I'm sorry for questioning you all! Don't hate me!</state>
                <state img="#-Scared.png">I don't deserve this awful hand! Why is everything so cruel?!</state>
                <state img="#-Scared.png">I hate this game! I mean not the game! It's just the c-cards! I mean, &lt;i&gt;sorry, sorry&lt;/i&gt;!</state>
                <state img="#-Stern.png">I'm a Crimson Demon! I should be doing better than this!</state>
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">What is wrong with me? Why do I keep getting bad hands? I'm an arch-wizard, I should be doing better than this!</state>
                <state img="#-Crying.png">A-are people purposely giving me bad cards!? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-6">
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Aw, I'll lose for sure with this terrible hand! But I'll get you all next time, so watch out!</state>
                <state img="#-Happy2.png">T-thanks for playing with me! Even if I lose this hand, I'm still having fun!</state>
                <state img="#-Scared.png">Every time I lose, I just get more determined to win! And every time I l-lose, um, I also get a bit more n-naked!</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Wait-- w-wait! C-can you please consider giving me another hand?</state>
                <state img="#-Scared.png">Please! I'll do anything to not lose this hand! I'll even take off my clothes! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-Crying.png">Aw, I'll lose for sure with this terrible hand! But I'll get you all next time so watch out! Wait, actually, I'll just be out!</state>
                <state img="#-Happy2.png">T-thanks for playing with me! Even if I lose this hand, I'm still having fun!</state>
                <state img="#-Stern.png">Y-you could have just asked me on a date... my standards for friends and... other things aren't so high...</state>
                <state img="#-Stern.png">I'm an expert wizard... so this feels awfully rude! </state>
                <state img="#-Scared.png">I... I'm so embarrassed... you can almost see my... b-but... oh no, I'm going to get the cards... &lt;i&gt;ahhhh&lt;/i&gt;!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="hand">
            <case stage="0-7" id="110" totalRounds="2-">
                <condition role="other" character="jessie" stage="0-2" sayingMarker="QA_Million_Yunyun" />
                <condition count="0" role="other" character="megumin" />
                <state img="#-Stern.png" marker="jessie_million2a">I'd first probably have to give some to my rival Megumin to pay off whatever debts she has fallen into.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="111" totalRounds="2-">
                <condition role="other" character="jessie" stage="0-2" sayingMarker="QA_Million_Yunyun" />
                <condition count="1-" role="other" character="megumin" />
                <state img="#-Happy2.png" oneShotId="121" marker="jessie_million2b">That's a good question. We &lt;i&gt;could&lt;/i&gt; use some new houses after a giant snake-like demon crushed half the village. Remember that, Megumin?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="77" priority="155">
                <condition role="other" character="saki_zls" stage="6" timeInStage="0" />
                <state img="#-Scared.png">A zombie... s-surely you could use another friend? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" priority="155">
                <condition role="other" character="sakura" stage="1" timeInStage="0" />
                <state img="#-Crying.png">&lt;i&gt;Friends!&lt;/i&gt;? Y-you're really going to be my friend, Ms. Sakura?! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="other" character="amy" stage="5" timeInStage="0" />
                <state img="#-Happy.png" marker="amy_friendship">You mean it? You really mean it? We can be friends!?!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" priority="155">
                <condition role="other" character="natsuki" stage="5" timeInStage="0" />
                <state img="#-Scared.png">Eh? R-right. We can't see your panties. N-not at all! A-anyone who says otherwise is just lying, like when someone lies and says they'll be your friend but really they just want something from you!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" priority="155">
                <condition role="other" character="natsuki" stage="5" timeInStage="1" />
                <state img="#-Sad.png">...I'm sorry, I... c-couldn't really see them because you were so proud of hiding them and I looked away...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="62" totalRounds="2-">
                <condition role="other" character="jessie" stage="0-2" sayingMarker="JessieQA_DarkSecrets" />
                <state img="#-Scared.png" marker="yy_j_darksecret">D-Dark secrets? N-no... I wish I did... i-if I'm being honest I'm a lot more boring than most Crimson Demons... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="63" totalRounds="2-">
                <condition role="other" character="jessie" stage="0-2" sayingMarker="JessieQA_LittleLies" />
                <state img="#-Sad.png" marker="yy_j_littlelie">L-Lies hurt a lot, especially the ones you tell yourself... like that people like and will love you... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="64" totalRounds="2-">
                <condition role="other" character="jessie" stage="0-2" sayingMarker="JessieQA_Smokers" />
                <state img="#-Shocked.png" marker="yy_j_smokers">Huh? I wouldn't have a problem with someone who smoked... it looks quite cool, and isn't it relaxing? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="65" totalRounds="2-">
                <condition role="other" character="jessie" stage="0-2" sayingMarker="JessieQA_Family" />
                <state img="#-Posing.png" marker="yy_j_family">I will be a paragon amongst my family! I will be the chief of the Crimson Demons and lead my family into the storied history of our people! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="66" totalRounds="2-">
                <condition role="other" character="jessie" stage="0-2" sayingMarker="JessieQA_Million" />
                <state img="#-Shocked.png" marker="yy_j_million">A million... dollars? How much is that in gold coins? If it's a lot, I'd probably donate it to my village in hopes that it could make life better for them! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="67" totalRounds="2-">
                <condition role="other" character="jessie" stage="0-2" sayingMarker="JessieQA_StupidMistakes" />
                <state img="#-Sad.png" marker="yy_j_mistakes">W-w-we all make mistakes... I certainly hope someone could forgive me for mine since I can forgive them for theirs!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="108" totalRounds="2-">
                <condition role="other" character="jessie" stage="0-2" sayingMarker="QA_DarkSecret_Yunyun" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png" marker="yy_darksecret2">Um... I don't have many friends among the Crimson Demons. I guess that's a secret...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="109" totalRounds="2-">
                <condition role="other" character="jessie" stage="0-2" sayingMarker="QA_Family_Yunyun" />
                <state img="#-Excited.png" marker="jessie_family2">My father is very supportive! And I count the rest of the Crimson Demons among my family! They are less supportive!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="112" totalRounds="2-">
                <condition role="other" character="jessie" stage="0-2" sayingMarker="JessieQA_Smokers" />
                <state img="#-Shocked.png" marker="jessie_smokers2">Oh, erm, my father told me to never fall to peer pressure. But I'll take one if you insist!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" id="113">
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" />
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="yunyun_trick_or_friends" />
                <state img="#-Facade.png" oneShotId="122" marker="megumin_costume">Do you enjoy Halloween too, Megumin? We should wear matching costumes sometime! Um, that's a thing rivals do, yes?</state>
                <state img="#-Stern.png" oneShotId="125" marker="megumin_trickortreat">I remember when we went Trick or Treating together, Megumin. And you ate all my candy...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="68">
                <condition role="other" character="jessie" stage="3-5" sayingMarker="JessieQA_Lights" />
                <state img="#-Scared.png" marker="yy_j_lights">I-I... I wouldn't have a preference if someone found me... s-so interesting as to... m-make love to me and care about me and love me... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="69">
                <condition role="other" character="jessie" stage="3-5" sayingMarker="JessieQA_SleptAround" />
                <state img="#-Sad.png" marker="yy_j_sleptar">I-I'd be more surprised if they didn't... I have never even been on a date... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="70">
                <condition role="other" character="jessie" stage="3-5" sayingMarker="JessieQA_Open" />
                <state img="#-Facade.png" marker="yy_j_o">I-I clearly would never be the exact match for something else someone wanted, so... it's possible that they might find other people... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="71">
                <condition role="other" character="jessie" stage="3-5" sayingMarker="JessieQA_Masturbate" />
                <state img="#-Facade.png" marker="yy_j_m">I... I know how to please myself pretty well... but I'd rather teach a partner... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="72">
                <condition role="other" character="jessie" stage="3-5" sayingMarker="JessieQA_Porn" />
                <state img="#-Scared.png" marker="yy_j_porn">What is... pornography? Is this like the dreams those succubi provide...? I have enjoyed once or twice. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="73">
                <condition role="other" character="jessie" stage="3-5" sayingMarker="JessieQA_SexNumber" />
                <state img="#-Aroused.png" marker="yy_j_number">Well... if I were in a relationship, as often as possible... even if it made me sore... and even if I had to do degrading things... just because it would mean that someone loved me. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="74">
                <condition role="other" character="jessie" stage="3-5" sayingMarker="JessieQA_SexPosition" />
                <state img="#-Aroused.png" marker="yy_j_position">W-well... one that could face someone would be nice... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="75">
                <condition role="other" character="jessie" stage="3-5" sayingMarker="JessieQA_Backdoor" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png" marker="yy_j_anal">I-I would take is a compliment if someone wanted to use... t-that much of me. I'd probably even enjoy it! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="other" character="rin" stage="4" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="rin_arms" />
                <state img="#-Posing2.png" oneShotId="126" marker="rin_magic">Oh, um, er... You should learn magic, Rin! It solves &lt;i&gt;everything&lt;/i&gt;!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-7" oneShotId="12">
                <condition role="other" character="tomoko" stage="0-2" />
                <state img="#-Shocked.png" oneShotId="73" marker="tomoko_pervertedcomments">&lt;i&gt;(Tomoko is staring at me with such strange eyes! Whatever lewd comments could she be thinking?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png" oneShotId="74" marker="tomoko_pervertedcomments">&lt;i&gt;(That strange short NEET continues to look at me. I hope I never find out whatever perverted comments she is thinking...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="5" totalRounds="0">
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" />
                <state img="#-Facade.png">I'll win and finally defeat you, Megumin! Once... I, uh, figure out how to play!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="jessie" sayingMarker="MeguminYunyunPair" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png" oneShotId="49" marker="MeguminYunyunPair_response">Well, erm, yes. Megumin and I are intertwined by fate and were born to be rivals. Though, erm, this game may be a bit awkward...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="jessie" sayingMarker="MeguminYunyunPair" />
                <state img="#-Crying.png" oneShotId="50">S-Sexual tension!? Absolutely not! B-But maybe? N-No! Just rivals!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="56">
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" sayingMarker="megumin_yunyun_moreMature" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png">N-No! N-Not everything I do is about you, Megumin! I w-was planning to come here anyway for personal reasons, if you must know! &lt;i&gt;(I was hoping to make some friends...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" id="103">
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" saidMarker="megumin_yunyun_embarrassingBirthmark" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png" oneShotId="108" marker="megumin_embarrassingbirthmark2">W-Well, technically my birthmark is on a less embarrassing area! B-But, um, let's stop talking about this before we accidentally tell the others too much...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" id="104">
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" saidMarker="megumin_yunyun_explosionProgression" />
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="110" marker="megumin_explosionprogression2">Oh! While I'll admit I still don't completely understand your... erm, passion towards the subject, I'm very happy you're progressing!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" id="105">
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" saidMarker="megumin_yunyun_adventuring" />
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="111" marker="megumin_adventuring2">O-Of course I've been keeping up! My adventures and life are filled with many trials. Most of which include extreme humiliation but I suppose that is the burden of an arch-mage.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" id="106">
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" saidMarker="megumin_yunyun_crimsonDemonWorld" />
                <state img="#-Stern.png" oneShotId="112" marker="megumin_crimsondemonword2">And yet you have garnered a reputation as the crazy explosion girl. I'd hardly call that good representation for our Clan! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="erufuda" sayingMarker="yunyun_mention_demon" />
                <state img="#-Crying.png">H-Huh! I don't even know what a fry is! Don't believe her, ~player~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="other" character="erufuda" sayingMarker="yunyun_wager" />
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">Er.. But wouldn't that defeat the point of working out? You've got me confused...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" totalRounds="0" priority="100">
                <state img="#-Scared.png">Wait, she's not here?! I'm s-sure she'll arrive eventually! She wouldn't trick me like this, right?! I'll just, uh, keep playing for now!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" id="9">
                <condition role="other" character="tomoko" />
                <state img="#-Happy2.png" oneShotId="51" marker="tomoko_popular">Tomoko, you talk a lot about being popular. May you share some of those secrets with me?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" id="30">
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" />
                <state img="#-Facade.png" oneShotId="52" marker="megumin_adventuring">So, erm, how is the adventuring with Kazuma and those others going? My adventuring has been... um, great! Though I'd change a few things...</state>
                <state img="#-Stern.png" oneShotId="53" marker="megumin_crimsondemonword">You have been spreading the word of the Crimson Demon gang right? I hope you haven't just been messing around with your new friends!</state>
                <state img="#-Shocked.png" oneShotId="54" marker="megumin_embarrassingbirthmark">Megumin, you do understand that in a game like this everyone may see your... embarrassing birthmark, right?</state>
                <state img="#-Happy2.png" oneShotId="55" marker="megumin_explosionprogression">If you wish Megumin, we may have a proper duel after this game! I am quite interested to see how you have progressed with explosion magic.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <condition role="other" character="emi" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png" oneShotId="56" marker="emi_running">I am also quite good at running, Emi! Mostly because I get quite nervous around new groups of adventurers and flee after battle. Oh, and I am often chased by giant monsters.</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="57" marker="emi_positiveupbeat">I do quite like your positive and upbeat attitude, Emi. I try to act the same, but it can be quite hard sometimes. </state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png" oneShotId="58" marker="emi_pushover">I see you are quite competitive, Emi. Well, the Crimson Demons are no pushovers! Just me...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="yunyun_trick_or_friends" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png" oneShotId="113">Do you like my costume? It’s cute, right? Erm, right?</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png" oneShotId="114">This is somehow more revealing than what I usually wear… Please try to avoid peeking at my panties...</state>
                <state img="#-Stern.png" oneShotId="115">For no particular reason, I wanted to make it clear that there is nothing shameful about an adult going Trick or Treating. It is just good fun! And you shouldn't judge anyone for doing so, especially not a young‑ish arch‑mage!</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="116">I feel less ridiculous wearing an extravagant outfit like this on Halloween. Erm, not that my normal outfit is &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; ridiculous…</state>
                <state img="#-Happy2.png" oneShotId="117">The Crimson Demons love celebrating Halloween! They’ll take any chance to be extravagant.</state>
                <state img="#-Sad.png" oneShotId="118">I do enjoy Trick or Treating. But everyone always seems to choose Trick on me…</state>
                <state img="#-Scared.png" oneShotId="119">This is the first time I've wore something other than my regular outfit in many years. That's a little gross now I think about it.</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png" oneShotId="120">I really hope I don't end up having to battle monsters in these clothes... I don't want to give any goblins an up-skirt. They're innocent and prude murderers.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="yunyun_trick_or_friends" />
                <state img="#-Facade.png">My father didn’t let me go Trick or Treating for a while as a kid. Mostly because the first time I went I got given a poisoned apple…</state>
                <state img="#-Sad.png">I love candy! Erm, sadly my father wouldn’t let me eat much due to potential cavities…</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">My favorite part of Halloween? Probably the pranks! Getting a bucket of water thrown at me or an egg, really makes me feel involved! &lt;i&gt;(It’s not often people take notice of me!)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-Posing.png">Remember to share any candy collected! Halloween is much more fun when you spend it with others! I think!</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Erm, I guess I'm losing my costume faster than I expected. It's a little embarrassing to go naked for Halloween..</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="13">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="konoFriend" />
                <state img="#-Scared.png">S-say... ~marker.konoFriend~, h-how about you tell me what to say a-and we can play again once we h-have a real conversation? J-just try to tell me somewhere l-like that Discord place...  </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="14">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="konoFriend2" />
                <state img="#-Scared.png">S-say... ~marker.konoFriend2~, h-how about you tell me what to say a-and we can play again once we h-have a real conversation? J-just try to tell me somewhere l-like that Discord place... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-3" id="60" oneShotId="16" priority="0">
                <condition count="2-4" filter="ginger" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png" marker="konosuba_ginger_lore">Orange hair is quite rare where I'm from... but it shows the mark of a truly powerful Crimson Demon!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-3" id="61" oneShotId="15" priority="0">
                <condition count="2-4" filter="blue_hair" />
                <state img="#-Stern.png" marker="konosuba_ginger_lore">You remind me of my... ah... &lt;i&gt;friend&lt;/i&gt; Aqua. Who is absolutely a real person and my friend. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" id="4" priority="0">
                <condition filter="enf" status="alive" role="opp" var="enfname" />
                <state img="#-Sad.png" oneShotId="59" set-intelligence="bad">&lt;i&gt;(~enfname~ seems really embarrassed... I feel so sorry for her! Do you think anyone would notice if I tried to throw this hand for her?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" id="11" priority="0">
                <condition filter="taken" status="alive" role="opp" var="romname" />
                <state img="#-Facade.png" oneShotId="60" set-intelligence="bad">Is it true that you are in a romantic relationship, ~romname~? That must be... wonderful... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" id="12" priority="0">
                <condition filter="pokemon" status="alive" role="opp" />
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="61" set-intelligence="bad">I'd quite like a Pokémon. It'd be nice to have an unconditional friend...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" id="13" priority="0">
                <condition filter="lonely" status="alive" role="opp" var="lonname" />
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="62" set-intelligence="bad">You seem quite lonely, ~lonname~. I could become your friend, if you wish? P-Please?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" id="14" priority="0">
                <condition filter="perverted" status="alive" role="opp" var="meanname" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png" oneShotId="63" set-intelligence="bad">Whilst you may be quite vulgar, ~meanname~... at least you are talking to me...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" id="16" priority="0">
                <condition filter="scantily-clad" status="alive" role="opp" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png" oneShotId="64" set-intelligence="bad">I see you are also wearing a "friend-making" outfit. I'm a little unsure if mine needs to be skimpier, as it's not worked so far...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" id="17" priority="0">
                <condition filter="nerdy" status="alive" role="opp" var="nerdname" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png" oneShotId="65" set-intelligence="bad">Are you one of those NEETs, ~nerdname~? Whilst I don't normally associate with that type, I would be happy to introduce you to the world of adventures! And maybe you could show me a video game or two...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" id="18" priority="0">
                <condition filter="adventurer" status="alive" role="opp" var="adname" />
                <condition count="0" filter="konosuba" role="opp" />
                <state img="#-Excited.png" oneShotId="66" set-intelligence="bad">A fellow adventurer? If you ever need help, I am available! I will even work for free!</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="67">What types of adventures have you gone on, ~adname~? We could exchange stories of our travels and... bond over them.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-3" id="79" oneShotId="17" priority="0">
                <condition count="2-4" filter="adventurer" />
                <state img="#-Aroused.png" marker="konosuba_adventurer_lore">There's quite a few adventurers here! We're going to be fast friends. My world has... actually... it's mostly adventurers, I think... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-3" id="80" oneShotId="18" priority="0">
                <condition count="2-4" filter="drill_hair" />
                <state img="#-Facade.png" marker="konosuba_drill_lore">I-I recognize a drill hair style anywhere... a-are we... d-do we have someone royal with us? A... a noble would make a powerful friend...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-3" id="81" oneShotId="19" priority="0">
                <condition count="2-4" filter="androgynous" />
                <state img="#-Shocked.png" marker="konosuba_androgynous_lore">Hm... are some of you elves? It's hard to determine your gender, just like home...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-3" id="82" oneShotId="20" priority="0">
                <condition count="2-4" filter="tattoo" />
                <state img="#-Posing.png" marker="konosuba_tattoo_lore">Where did you get your tattoos!? And are they magical? Some monks in Belzerg use them to channel magic... or look cool! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-3" id="83" oneShotId="21" priority="0">
                <condition count="2-4" filter="scarred" />
                <state img="#-Aroused.png" marker="konosuba_scarred_lore">Oh... you have such interesting birthmarks... o-or... perhaps those are scars. T-they're very cool to a Crimson Demon, though I have few of my own... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-3" id="84" oneShotId="22" priority="0">
                <condition count="2-4" filter="alien" />
                <state img="#-Facade.png" marker="konosuba_alien_lore">S-so... some of you are... v-very... &lt;i&gt;otherworldly...&lt;/i&gt; w-while there's many strange creatures in Belzerg, none like you...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-3" id="85" oneShotId="23" priority="0">
                <condition count="2-4" filter="catfolk" />
                <state img="#-Scared.png" marker="konosuba_catfolk_lore">Is someone forcing people here to wear one of those tails that goes in your butt and ears that go on your head or-- o-or are people just like that... sometimes...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-3" id="86" oneShotId="24" priority="0">
                <condition count="2-4" filter="monster" />
                <state img="#-Aroused.png" marker="konosuba_monster_lore">O-oh... normally monsters and people don't get along... but if we're all undressing, perhaps we're not all that different? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-3" id="87" oneShotId="25" priority="0">
                <condition count="2-4" filter="spirit" />
                <state img="#-Stern.png" marker="konosuba_spirit_lore">Some of you are spirits, aren't you? Well, don't possess people, though... if you go inside of me, you consent to being my friend! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-3" id="88" oneShotId="26" priority="0">
                <condition count="2-4" filter="deity" />
                <state img="#-Shocked.png" marker="konosuba_deity_lore">Oh... I just noticed... which pantheon are the deities here a part of? The Axis or Eris orders? One has a kindly water goddess with fanatical worshipers, while the Eris sect are... more reasonable.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-3" id="89" oneShotId="27" priority="0">
                <condition count="2-4" filter="witch" />
                <state img="#-Shocked.png" marker="konosuba_witch_lore">Some of you are Arch‑wizards too, aren't you...? I didn't realize it was such a common class outside of the Crimson Demons.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-3" id="90" oneShotId="28" priority="0">
                <condition count="2-4" filter="magical_girl" />
                <state img="#-Stern.png" marker="konosuba_meguca_lore">What's a magical girl? Can any of you actually do magic, or is someone doing it for you? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-3" id="91" oneShotId="29" priority="0">
                <condition count="2-4" filter="tsundere" />
                <state img="#-Crying.png" marker="konosuba_tsundere_lore">I don't know what it's like where you're from, but in Belzerg, w-we... we-- try to be straightforward... even... ridiculously so, for Crimson Demons...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-3" id="92" oneShotId="30" priority="0">
                <condition count="2-4" filter="book" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png" marker="konosuba_book_lore">So... have any of you enjoyed quality literature from your worlds...? Most books in Belzerg are training manuals or... erotic illustrations...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-3" id="94" oneShotId="32" priority="0">
                <condition count="2-4" filter="anime" />
                <state img="#-Excited.png" marker="konosuba_anime_lore">I'm glad to see that some of you look very similar to me-- or at least similar to the stories Kazuma describes! </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip">
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="meia_strip1s" />
                <condition role="other" character="meia" stage="0-5" sayingMarker="yunyun1" />
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">Eh? No... I just mean monsters, Meia. You know, horrible abominations worth experience points... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" priority="141">
                <condition role="other" character="bernadetta" stage="1-9" saidMarker="yunyunspy" />
                <state img="#-Facade.png">S-so, everyone! I-including my new friend Bernadetta-- u-um... Bernadetta, this is when you introduce y-yourself...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="revy" stage="0-7" sayingMarker="yunyun0" />
                <state img="#-Scared.png">N-no-- I-I cannot understand it either... I do not get... &lt;i&gt;positive&lt;/i&gt; attention. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="31">
                <condition role="other" character="emi" sayingMarker="emi_yunyun_name" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png" marker="emi_yunyun_name_response">Erm, I come from the Crimson Demon clan and this is a perfectly normal name there. You can, um, call me Yun for short if it's too weird for you!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="32">
                <condition role="other" character="emi" sayingMarker="emi_yunyun_school" />
                <state img="#-Facade.png" marker="emi_yunyun_school_response">I'm not a student! I'm an adventurer and quester! Um, this outfit was given to me by a friend. They told me it'd help me make friends... But it's a little revealing!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="neptune" sayingMarker="nep_yunyun_outfit1" />
                <state img="#-Facade.png">Oh! Um, I was actually given it by a companion! Is it &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; cute? Or are you just messing with me?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="neptune" sayingMarker="nep_yunyun_megumin1" />
                <state img="#-Posing2.png" font-size="smaller">Well, Megumin is many things to me. We grew up in the Crimson Demon village together and forged a close bond through the lunches I fed her. Obviously like all close relationships within the Crimson Demons, this blossomed into a powerful rivalship!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="neptune" sayingMarker="nep_yunyun_pasttime1" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Um, yes! I would enjoy spending time with friends! Erm, I have to spend a lot of my time leveling my magic powers though...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2" oneShotId="4">
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" sayingMarker="megumin_yunyun_cantEscape1" />
                <state img="#-Posing2.png" marker="yunyun_megumin_cantEscape1">I-I will so! You won't win this time, Megumin. It'll be you who has no dignity!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2" oneShotId="5">
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" sayingMarker="megumin_yunyun_rigged1" />
                <state img="#-Sad.png" marker="yunyun_megumin_rigged1">I have done no such things! You know I always play fair, unlike you!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2" oneShotId="6">
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" sayingMarker="megumin_yunyun_notADuel1" />
                <state img="#-Shocked.png" marker="yunyun_megumin_notADuel1">T-That doesn't mean I don't win! R-Right? T-Though I suppose to be fair we could play the game with just the two of us at some point...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" oneShotId="7">
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" sayingMarker="megumin_yunyun_friends1" />
                <state img="#-Sad.png" marker="yunyun_megumin_friends1">O-Of course... I-I have met many people in my travels...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" oneShotId="8">
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" sayingMarker="megumin_yunyun_chomusuke1" />
                <state img="#-Happy.png" marker="yunyun_megumin_chomusuke1">I am very glad! Please give &lt;i&gt;Kuro&lt;/i&gt; a treat on my behalf.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-6" oneShotId="9">
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" sayingMarker="megumin_yunyun_coldFeet1" />
                <state img="#-Facade.png" marker="yunyun_megumin_coldFeet1">N-No! It is just rather embarrassing, is all. Just please stop your teasing for one second, this is all quite a lot...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-6" oneShotId="10">
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" sayingMarker="megumin_yunyun_victoryWillBeMine1" />
                <state img="#-Posing.png" marker="yunyun_megumin_victoryWillBeMine1">A Crimson Demon never surrenders! May the best mage win!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-6" oneShotId="11">
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" sayingMarker="megumin_yunyun_undefeated1" />
                <state img="#-Scared.png" marker="yunyun_megumin_undefeated1">... I hate these games of emotions we play!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-6">
                <condition role="other" character="lucy" saying="Fairy" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png">I-I must have all the blood in my head-- it's like Lucy is being nice to me--! B-but that can't be so! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="other" character="komi-san" sayingMarker="yunyun_toughlove" />
                <state img="#-Excited.png">You can speak, or well, write freely around me, Komi-san! I am glad you are comfortable enough to share your thoughts!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="jessie" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png">I am not some kind of magician who will preform cheap tricks on demand... I am a dignified arch-mage who will bring glory to the Crimson Demon clan! Though if you ask nicely, I could create some pretty sparkles. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="jura" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Erm, while I may seem a little nervous, the truth is that I am a confident and powerful mage from the Crimson Demon clan. Who has never played a strip game before...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="revy" />
                <state img="#-Stern.png">It's the Crimson Demon clan! And I don't see how the size of my chest would assist me with my confidence.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="meia" />
                <state img="#-Excited.png">Oh! Of course Meia, thank you for asking! The Crimson Demon clan is an elite group of arch‑mages who protect the land from destruction!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="jessie" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Well, I adventure and quest. Slay monsters for experience and collect gold for my victories. Of course, I ensure to help the innocent along the way and spread the word of the Crimson Demon Clan...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <state img="#-Posing2.png">I-I am a Crimson Demon! I-I've faced hordes of horrific monsters! Fought tense battles where my very life was at the line! I-I can handle a little stripping!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <state img="#-Stern.png">I-I am not a pervert! N-Nor an exhibitionist! If you are wishing to personally experience my powerful magics, Kazuma, you are trying my patience!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <state img="#-Sad.png">If you k-keep this up, K-Kazuma, I will cast a devastating spell on you! Don't think just because you are Megumin's friend you can get away with such lewd comments towards a Crimson Demon!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png">O-Of course! I am not some overly innocent maiden. But I wear stockings for comfort and style. Not for any corrupted reasons!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">Y-You would guess correctly, K-Kazuma... Of course, this is the one thing you'd be knowledgeable about...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="komi-san" />
                <state img="#-Stern.png">E-eh? Y-you are a cat person, Ms. Komi-san? I-I have not yet met a monster that---</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="miko" />
                <state img="#-Sad.png">R-really? You truly think so? S-surely you are quite wonderful to know such secrets--</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="miko" />
                <state img="#-Posing.png">I am indeed a powerful Arch‑wizard! Top of my class! Future Chieftain of the Crimson Demons! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="miko" />
                <state img="#-Facade.png">S-surely... a-are you suggesting? B-but... I am but a maiden... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="saki_zls" />
                <state img="#-Sad.png">M-my my name is Yunyun--</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="saki_zls" />
                <state img="#-Crying.png">I-if you think it's nice now, w-wait until I lose more-- w-wait! I-is this a trick to get me to undress!? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="jim" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Oh! Yes, Mr Raynor. The Crimson Demons are a noble clan, who use their awesome magical powers to protect innocent nearby villages from horrendous and sometimes unspeakably twisted monsters. And, um, we also do a fireworks show once a year! You should visit and see!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="jim" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Erm, I suppose the name is quite comedic yes. But I must warn you Mr Raynor, that I &lt;i&gt;do&lt;/i&gt; possess great magical powers. One that would rival any demon! Except you know, the &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; bad ones.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="estelle" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png">O-Oh! Erm... Yes, I suppose. It's quite normal for my homeland. Very normal, er, like me...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" totalRounds="0">
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">Wait, I've got to do &lt;i&gt;what&lt;/i&gt; for losing?! No, wait, I'll strip! Just don't hate me!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_winning">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png" oneShotId="80">Well, I guess it is unfair if I never lose...</state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png" oneShotId="79">I feel really left out if you are all stripping and I'm not!</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png" oneShotId="78">Oh, I don't want to be the only one clothed! Or, I mean, I do but...</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png" oneShotId="77">I-I'm happy to stay dressed but... y-you'd rather see me undressed, w-wouldn't you? </state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png" oneShotId="76">I-I'd hate for you all to think I am unable to join the rest of you and appreciate the-- t-the game. </state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png" oneShotId="75">There is something fun about this, isn't there? I-it's quite different undressing for &lt;i&gt;friends...&lt;/i&gt;?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-6">
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="81">I, um, you guys are &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; nice so I'm fine with stripping...</state>
                <state img="#-Excited.png" oneShotId="83">Oh, this game is getting really really close! It's so exciting!</state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png" oneShotId="82">This is e-embarrassing but I wouldn't play this game if I didn't want to! Not that I &lt;i&gt;want&lt;/i&gt; to strip!</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="84">Since you're being so friendly, I hope I continue to earn your attention-- &lt;i&gt;affection&lt;/i&gt;-- ...by undressing. </state>
                <state img="#-Excited.png" oneShotId="85">Oh! I understand why this is so thrilling! Please! Let me enjoy this!</state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png" oneShotId="86">I-I'm having fun! N-not because I'm winning but because it's... f-fun. O-of course. </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_normal">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Shocked.png" oneShotId="87">I guess it's my turn... um, just don't stare! Or, um, you can if you want!</state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png" oneShotId="88">P-Please don't laugh! I promise you, there's nothing funny about me! Wait, I mean, I'm hilarious, okay?!</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png" oneShotId="89">Oh, um, it's only a small thing I have to remove, right? </state>
                <state img="#-Shocked.png" oneShotId="91">If... if you wish to stare, please give me compliments as well!</state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png" oneShotId="90">I-I know I'm... q-quite strange, but please... I-I'd rather you gawk in interest than amusement...</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png" oneShotId="92">It's better if I remove something large, is it not?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-6">
                <state img="#-Scared.png" oneShotId="93">Oh, um... if you are all seeing me like, uh, &lt;i&gt;this&lt;/i&gt;. Then we are automatically friends, right?</state>
                <state img="#-Excited.png" oneShotId="94">You know... even if you don't think of me as a friend. I see all of you as my friends! And that's all that matters!</state>
                <state img="#-Crying.png" oneShotId="97">I-I'm still going to win! I-I'm just going to be a little more n-naked as I do so!</state>
                <state img="#-Scared.png" oneShotId="95">I-I had never expected to be exposing myself to &lt;i&gt;friends&lt;/i&gt; but... I am happy to do so...</state>
                <state img="#-Excited.png" oneShotId="96">I'm glad we can bond over this moment. A-and as friends, we can look back and laugh at the time Yunyun met us and took off her clothes...</state>
                <state img="#-Crying.png" oneShotId="98">I-I don't intend to quit! I-I'm used to n-not being dignified, b-but if I win we have to be friends! T-that's victory for me!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_losing">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-Facade.png">I just want to remind you all that I could leave if I wanted to! And that means you should respect my resolve and like me for staying!</state>
                <state img="#-Stern.png">If anyone laughs, I'll make you regret it! I know magic! Believe me!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-6">
                <state img="#-Facade.png">Even if I'm losing badly... T-thank you for letting me p-play with you all!</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Well, um, that's a-another loss...</state>
                <state img="#-Scared.png">If I didn't know any better I'd say this game was just a ploy to see me naked! But you wouldn't do that, right? Right?!</state>
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">I might be constantly losing, but I still deserve respect! Even just a tiny tiny amount, please!</state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png">D-Don't worry about making me feel bad... I'm used to l-losing...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-3">
                <state img="#-Facade.png" oneShotId="99">I just want to remind you all that I could leave if I wanted to! And that means you should respect my resolve and like me for staying!</state>
                <state img="#-Stern.png" oneShotId="100">If anyone laughs, I'll make you regret it! I know magic! Believe me!</state>
                <state img="#-Crying.png" oneShotId="101">I keep losing! Are you guys bullying me?!</state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png" oneShotId="102">We're allowed to leave whenever we want, s-so p-please appreciate my resolve and resolve to be my friends!</state>
                <state img="#-Stern.png" oneShotId="103">I hope you know that I wore my favorite outfit today, so you should treat my next outfit as your favorite!</state>
                <state img="#-Crying.png" oneShotId="104">E-even if I keep losing, a-at least I'm &lt;i&gt;gaining&lt;/i&gt; friends...? </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripping">
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png">T-This is not the w-way I wished to do it!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png">P-Please do not bring up my bare butt right now!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png">I do not know what you are imagining but me and Megumin do not have that sort of relationship. Yes, of course we have shared a bath before that was just practicality.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png">Of course. We &lt;i&gt;are&lt;/i&gt; rivals after all...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png">W-Whatever do you mean, Kazuma?  We are arch‑rivals, destined by fate to forever challenge each other, if that is what you implying... W-Woah! J-Just lost balance...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png">S-She better not be looking at my bottom! W-We are not rivals with benefits, after all!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" id="95">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="yunyun_megumin_cantEscape1" />
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" stage="0-6" sayingMarker="megumin_yunyun_cantEscape2" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png">Y-you don't have to say that in front of... o-of everyone else...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-6" id="96">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="yunyun_megumin_coldFeet1" />
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" stage="0-6" sayingMarker="megumin_yunyun_coldFeet2" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png">I-I don't believe you! Y-you're-- you're just being mean to me like you always are... o-or are you actually being nice? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" id="99">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="yunyun_megumin_rigged1" />
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" stage="7-8" sayingMarker="megumin_yunyun_rigged2" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png">I-I'm not slandering Megumin! I-I... am just calling it like it is! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-6" id="100">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="yunyun_megumin_victoryWillBeMine1" />
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" stage="7-8" sayingMarker="megumin_yunyun_victoryWillBeMine2" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png">I-I- I'll show you! I'll show e-everyone! U-um... m-my e-everything! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" id="101">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="yunyun_megumin_notADuel1" />
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" stage="9-10" sayingMarker="megumin_yunyun_notADuel2" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png">That's so gener-- w-wait... w-would you be cheating me!? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-6" id="102">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="yunyun_megumin_undefeated1" />
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" stage="9-10" sayingMarker="megumin_yunyun_undefeated2" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png">M-Megumin, d-don't pretend like-- M-Megumin! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="revy" stage="0-7" sayingMarker="yunyun01" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png">Whatever flaws I have doubtless outweigh the virtues o-of my chest... which is a large target for girls I know... who slap them...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" priority="102">
                <condition role="other" character="neptune" saidMarker="nep_yunyun_megumin1" sayingMarker="nep_yunyun_megumin2" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png">Y-yes! O-of course! G-great friends. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" priority="102">
                <condition role="other" character="neptune" saidMarker="nep_yunyun_outfit1" sayingMarker="nep_yunyun_outfit2" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png">O-okay... w-when are you going to say "not...?" </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" priority="102">
                <condition role="other" character="neptune" saidMarker="nep_yunyun_pasttime1" sayingMarker="nep_yunyun_pasttime2" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png">R-really? I am a powerful-- p-powerful Arch‑wizard! I have many forms of magic, all might... b-but also some weaker spells, too.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="97">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="yunyun_megumin_friends1" />
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" sayingMarker="megumin_yunyun_friends2" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png">N-no! I'm-- I'm not bad at lying! I'm amazing at lying-- I mean, I don't lie... M-Megumin!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-3" id="98">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="yunyun_megumin_chomusuke1" />
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" sayingMarker="megumin_yunyun_chomusuke2" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png">...K‑Kuro is... is my... M‑Megumin! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" />
                <condition role="self" notSaidMarker="Megumin_Winning1C" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png" marker="Megumin_StripLosing1B">I just realized this game is going to end with at least one of us getting completely, um, naked...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="jura" sayingMarker="yunyun01" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png" marker="jura_response01">I'm... usually not the center of attention, Jura. I tend to blend into the background...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="revy" sayingMarker="yunyun01" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png" oneShotId="68" marker="revy_yunyun01">Well, my large chest hasn't seemed to get me very much attention in the past. My rival has always teased me for their large size...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6">
                <condition role="other" character="komi-san" sayingMarker="yunyun_friend_facade" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png">W-Well, y-you know... Um...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="meia" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png">We live in the Crimson Demon Village, where we are taught our magics from a young age, making us the most potent magical users! As long as we spend our points &lt;i&gt;wisely&lt;/i&gt;..</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="jessie" />
                <state img="#-Stern.png">Well, most of my magical spells are quite dangerous! They aren't to be cast lightly. I only use them when absolutely necessary! Or, um, if I need to look impressive during an intro...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png">I-If you keep acting like this, Kazuma, I will be forced to tell Megumin!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png">K-Kazuma! I have no clue why Megumin continues to carry around with someone as... direct as you!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png" font-size="small">L-Look, Kazuma, I am not a delicate girl. There were times when first practicing magic I accidentally destroyed parts of my own clothing... Which, while rather embarrassing, has prepared me for a game like this.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png">I don't quite understand. What do you get, Kazuma?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png">I do not wish to stand out. Colorful colors may attract unwanted attention of monsters or other enemies.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png">W-Wait, who would d-do such a thing-, Woah! I, erm, was caught off guard.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png">S-So lewd, Kazuma! I am a-already taking my skirt off, what else do you want?! And I am {b}not{!reset} an exhibitionist!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="komi-san" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png">O-okay! Okay! I'll undress! P-please do not use such a disappointed gaze upon me! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="bernadetta" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png">I-I-I'm so &lt;i&gt;grateful&lt;/i&gt; you're l-letting them give me attention, Bernadetta--</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="bernadetta" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png">B-Bernie, let me use you for sup--support!! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="lucy" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png">...You say that, Lucy, but nobody wants to be my friend anyway...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="miko" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png">W-would I have friends? I... I see no downside in this, Prince Miko, even if I don't necessarily think you're a real prince...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="miko" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png">Y-yes... b-but... I-I would hardly say I'm &lt;i&gt;young&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="miko" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png">A wife...? I suppose... that would not be so bad... Who would this person be? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="saki_zls" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png">I-I just want to make friends! Like you! I wouldn't be desperate and lonely if we were friends! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="jim" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png">A-Apologies for any overreaction. I'm just rather proud of my family and clan despite, er, our oddities.</state>
                <state img="#-Strip.png">Oh! Er... I thought you were making fun of me. A lot of people make jokes about the Crimson Demons... But we're really a force of good in my world!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="jim" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png">Well, yes! It was lonely- I mean, lovely growing up there! And the people there treat... most with a lot of respect.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="estelle" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png">I wouldn't say I'm &lt;i&gt;looking&lt;/i&gt; for friends. I mean, if one appeared I would not say no, of course... But...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="estelle" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png">Well... My magic is mostly based around light and utility. I try and keep a wide variety of skills so I can be useful in any situation...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="estelle" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png">N-No, no... I've got t-this! C-Catch me, someone!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="other" character="estelle" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png">E-Er... Y-Yes... But such is the challenging life of an arch‑mage!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="erufuda" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png">This is quite casual dress where I come from, Erufuda. And I've been told these clothes are quite helpful for gaining allies...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" cmp="!=" value="yunyun_trick_or_friends" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png">I wear this outfit because I was told it'd help me make friends... It's working, right?</state>
                <state img="#-Strip.png">These clothes are a little... embarrassing. But a trustworthy source told me they'd help make friends! It doesn't seem to have happened yet...</state>
                <state img="#-Strip.png">Don't judge me for my clothes! This is my friend-making outfit! My friend D-Dust told me it'd help!</state>
                <state img="#-Strip.png">I was told that this outfit would help me make friends? It's not, um, working. It's just really embarrassing me...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="yunyun_trick_or_friends" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png">I, erm, know this outfit is a bit... revealing. But I heard most people dress like this on Halloween...</state>
                <state img="#-Strip.png">While these clothes are... a little tight. I also think they look cute!</state>
                <state img="#-Strip.png">Um, so you know... the horns aren't real...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-Strip.png">Erm, well... I guess even a Crimson Demon can't win every time... &lt;i&gt;(Even if Megumin wins every duel we have...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-Strip.png">I'm not lonely! I am just really really self-sufficient!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-Strip.png">I'll take off my boots and get comfortable, I guess. Or at least &lt;i&gt;try&lt;/i&gt; and get comfortable... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-Strip.png">Oh no, oh no, oh no! Don't fall over! People will remember and mock you forever!</state>
                <state img="#-Strip.png">A-A-Ah! N-no, don't fall over, Yunyun! Who would ever respect someone who did that!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-Strip.png">I-I'm not insecure! About my body, that is...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-Strip.png">You can do this, Yunyun! You are a Crimson Demon!</state>
                <state img="#-Strip.png">Crimson Demons should care little about nudity! But, um, they do care about losing...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-Strip.png">O-oh, Eris! T-This is all I have l-left! Er, uh, don't laugh at me! I-I'll do it!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">I shouldn't say this! I'm sorry for the bug!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripped">
            <case stage="6">
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" />
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <state img="#-Stern.png">T-This is not a competition I care about winning!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" />
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <state img="#-Posing.png">D-Do not tell me what to do, Kazuma! B-But I suppose, that is the game... Look quickly for this shall only be brief!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" />
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png">D-Do y-you really think so?  Wait, don't make such comments about our bottoms!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" />
                <state img="#-Stern.png">We are &lt;i&gt;rivals&lt;/i&gt;, Kazuma. Do you not understand what that means?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" />
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Well, erm, yes. You could call it that. I will never stop my challenges until I win!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png">W-Why thank you, Kazuma... I suppose you are more than just a perverted creepy layabout who has no potential for anything productive in his life.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" />
                <state img="#-Stern.png">N-No? That is not how rivals interact! Though I suppose many of the great rivals of our history have battled with great sexual tension. T-They call such relationships "rivals with benefits"... T-That is n-not the case with me and M-Megumin however!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" />
                <state img="#-Sad.png">Y-You are &lt;i&gt;very&lt;/i&gt; rude, Kazuma. You should consider your allies carefully, Megumin.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="bernadetta" />
                <test expr="~self.position~" value="left" />
                <test expr="~self.distance~" value="1" />
                <state img="#-Crying.png">N-no! Y-you didn't! I-I'm sorry! I just want to be friends! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="jura" stage="0-6" sayingMarker="yunyun1s" />
                <state img="#-Crying.png">M-Ms. Jura! Nobody wants to be my friend! I-in your advanced age, surely you've had dozens-- no-- &lt;i&gt;hundreds&lt;/i&gt; of friends! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="revy" stage="0-7" sayingMarker="yunyun1s" />
                <state img="#-Crying.png">T-Take me to your world, then! I-I would happily be popular! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" />
                <condition role="self" notSaidMarker="Megumin_Winning1C" />
                <state img="#-Crying.png" marker="Megumin_StripLosing1C">W-Well, it won't be me! N-Not that I want &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; to get naked Megumin! W-Why don't we play a game of chess instead?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="meia" sayingMarker="yunyun1s" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png" oneShotId="69" marker="meia_strip1s">Eek! Sorry! I just get very excited while talking about my homeland. Well, there's a lot of demons and monsters around which people need protecting from! There's all sorts of sinister magic around.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7" oneShotId="33">
                <condition role="other" character="komi-san" saidMarker="yunyun_friend_facade" />
                <state img="#-Happy.png">I understand what you are trying to say Shouko and I do appreciate your words. But I do enjoy pleasing other people!  And while my words may be seen as fake, I promise that my feelings are very true and eventually I hope I can find someone who will appreciate that. I suppose maybe I do go a bit overboard though...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="jessie" />
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Well, I &lt;i&gt;could&lt;/i&gt; do those things. Though they sound relatively weak. My magical spells are used to protect myself and others.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <state img="#-Crying.png">S-Stop looking at my large bottom! I usually put clothes over that!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <state img="#-Crying.png">W-What are you talking about?! While I am mildly comfortable with nudity, that does not mean I wish to show all my nude body!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <state img="#-Crying.png">I am neither of those things! I am just playing the game as it is supposed to be played. I'm curious as to how the other players feel about your crude comments, Kazuma...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <state img="#-Stern.png">I am sure ~player~ is an upstanding person, unlike you! R-Right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">If people wish to imagine such things with my feet... Then, I suppose I will allow it. And maybe oblige them if they agree to go questing with me afterwards...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <state img="#-Happy2.png">T-Thank you Kazuma. It is good to know you can show restraint when needed...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="komi-san" />
                <state img="#-Posing.png">S-see! I did it! Please, please be my friend! </state>
                <state img="#-Posing2.png">I-I did it! And you didn't have to threaten me! P-please be my friend!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="bernadetta" />
                <state img="#-Scared.png">S-see! She's-- she's s-so generous she doesn't even have to say anything! And because she didn't say she's &lt;i&gt;not&lt;/i&gt; my friend, it means she is!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="bernadetta" />
                <state img="#-Crying.png">B-b-but I could've used it! I want you to be my f-f-friend! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="lucy" />
                <state img="#-Crying.png">W-wait! Lucy! A-are you trying to be my friend!? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="miko" />
                <state img="#-Crying.png">N-no! Y-you're making fun of me, Miko! This is like the time Kazuma pretended to be dying to get me to do lewd things-- &lt;i&gt;j-just&lt;/i&gt; like this game!!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="miko" />
                <state img="#-Scared.png">I-I-I just said that! A-are you really listening to me? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="miko" />
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">A... hm. I do know many of those... perhaps this would be to my benefit!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="saki_zls" />
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">Why would anyone want to lay low my self-esteem when it's already so-- I-I mean, certainly! W-whatever you say, Saki! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="estelle" />
                <state img="#-Happy.png">You think? That's encouraging to hear! I thought it was maybe a bit... Sultry. But I suppose not!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="estelle" />
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">Huh? Estelle? Are you quite alright? You seem distracted...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="estelle" />
                <state img="#-Sad.png">L-Look... I just don't want to share the EXP. That's all! Promise!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <condition role="other" character="estelle" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Um... They do pop out from time to time... It's created some awkward situations...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="yunyun_trick_or_friends" />
                <state img="#-Facade.png">Oh, erm, I guess I didn't take much off. But that's because a Crimson Demon must use every advantage they have! Or else they'll lose repeatedly over and over to their rival!</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">If anyone can think of a good Halloween pun for me to say after stripping, please tell me...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="yunyun_trick_or_friends" />
                <state img="#-Facade.png">I spent ages putting this cute outfit on and now I have to remove it so suddenly... A waste of time... &lt;i&gt;(Like me...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="yunyun_trick_or_friends" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Do you like the colours? I thought they were quite thematic... J-Just don't look too much...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <condition count="1-4" filter="shaved" gender="female" status="crotch_visible" />
                <condition count="0" filter="hairy" gender="female" status="not_naked" />
                <state img="#-Facade.png">I-I understand that it is important not to become too hairy... b-but I have never in my life removed all of the hair from my womanhood... I-I imagine this depletes power...</state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png">I-I did not know we were expected to remove hair from our... womanhood b-before the game... o-or I would have! I...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-Facade.png">I'm s-sorry for being so w-weird... I'm sure you'd rather play with a different member of the  Crimson Demons...</state>
                <state img="#-Sad.png">There's my belt. It... uh, doesn't hold anything up. So it's mostly useless. &lt;i&gt;(Like me...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-Excited.png">T-this is so e-embarrassing! B-but even if my chances of winning may be virtually nothing... as long as they aren't &lt;i&gt;absolutely&lt;/i&gt; nothing, I'll never give up! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">The tie is just a fashion accessory! Losing it won't stop me from winning! It'll just make me one step closer to losing! Wait, that's bad!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-Sad.png">I hope I get better cards next round... I deserve that at least...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">This game kind of reminds me of my many duels with Megumin... And it's just as embarrassing!</state>
                <state img="#-Posing2.png">Hmph, okay! I'm done losing now! Promise! You better watch out because I'm going to use all the training I've had as a Crimson Demon!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-Shy.png">I-I thought these p-panties were c-cute okay! They a-are, right?</state>
                <state img="#-Excited.png">Y-You can stare... But only if you consider me a friend! And if you look, you're automatically a friend!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-Sad.png">A-are these okay? I know they are p-probably t-too big...</state>
                <state img="#-Crying.png">You might think this is embarrassing! But for someone like me who is experienced in the art of humiliation, it's just another day! Wait, that's a bad thing!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_strip">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">Oh... ~player~ lost? That's good. Really good. Not because I want to see him naked! Just because, uh, uh... Never mind!</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">&lt;i&gt;(I want everyone to be my friend... but I really really want ~player~ to be my friend for some reason!)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">Why does ~player~ make me feel weird? Wait, did I say that aloud?! &lt;i&gt;So embarrassing... &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-Scared.png">You know... you don't talk much, ~player~. I've always thought my type of guy would be quiet and reserved... W-wait, w-why am I telling you this?!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-Happy.png">~Player~... I... hope that you getting to watch me was something you enjoyed, for am I about to enjoy you stripping tremendously...!</state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png">W-well, you have seen my fingers enter myself... t-this means we are certainly &lt;i&gt;at least&lt;/i&gt; friends, i-is it not? </state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I... wish to observe you, ~name~! It will help with my ritual of self-pleasing... </state>
                <state img="#-Happy2.png">Y-you don't have to say anything, ~player~, I-I can tell you have more favor for me than most... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-Happy.png">T-Thanks for spending time with me, ~player~... you're making this game really fun...</state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png">H-Hey, ~player~? Is it okay if I tell everyone you're my friend? Not in a weird way! Promise!</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">Oh... you've got to strip, ~player~? I-Is it okay if I watch?!</state>
                <state img="#-Happy2.png">Even though you don't talk to me,  ~player~, that's still nicer than how most people treat me!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Sad.png">Even if you lose, all that matters is that you tried! Why does nobody ever tell me that?</state>
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">... You've got to strip, right? That was a question, not a demand! Sorry!</state>
                <state img="#-Crying.png">I, um, this game is kind of lewd... isn't it? Not that I care! I'm very calm and comfortable, okay?!</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Wait, I didn't lose?! That's a nice feeling...</state>
                <state img="#-Sad.png">I know I should be happy I won... But I'm a little sad someone else lost...</state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png">I know I'm supposed to give a victory speech like most other Crimson Demons would... but that'd be so embarrassing...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">If you don't want to strip, I won't make you! I... I'd like it if you did though! Wait, not for perverted reasons! P-Promise!</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Y-You can strip too! If we're both embarrassed that means we can understand each other better, right?!</state>
                <state img="#-Happy2.png">Even if you lost, I really hope you're still enjoying yourself, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-Scared.png" oneShotId="105">YunYun just WonWon! Wait, that was the worst thing I ever said!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I-I would rather enjoy it if you continued to undress, but only because it would give us an experience to bond over, much like if we... became intimate. </state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">If you wish to undress faster, you would be able to more deeply understand my embarrassment... which would bring us closer!</state>
                <state img="#-Happy2.png">~Name~, are you... do you enjoy what I'm doing to myself? I hope you find it pleasing... </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_strip">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="futaba" stage="2" />
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" />
                <state img="#-Posing2.png">Megumin, Futaba would make a fine Crimson Demon! And unlike you, she has some curves to her! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="futaba" stage="5" />
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">Kazuma... now that Futaba's about to undress, is... is she one of those girls that you call... a lollypop?  </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" priority="405">
                <condition role="target" character="natsuki" stage="5" timeInStage="0" />
                <state img="#-Scared.png">I-I knew you didn't want us to look so I didn't! T-That's all, Natsuki! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="futaba" stage="0" />
                <condition count="2-3" filter="phantom_thieves" />
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">Futaba, you brought some friends... how did you make them in the first place? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" totalRounds="0">
                <condition role="target" character="natsuki" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Scared.png">I... I have played this before but... i-is this the best way to make friends? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="kizuna" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Ms. Kizuna Ai! You are friends with everyone, yes, won't you be my friend? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="kizuna" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-Crying.png">H-how are you so free spirited about this! Y-you are even more of a model Crimson Demon than I am! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="kizuna" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Kizuna! A-are you just doing this because you are joking around with me, like a good friend would? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="kizuna" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-Scared.png">We can already see everything... I can't tell if that makes this better or worse... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="streaming-chan" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Scared.png">S-Streaming-chan i-is... does anyone in your chat actually like me? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="streaming-chan" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-Happy.png">So... can I call you Nicole? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="streaming-chan" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-Sad.png">Nicole-- um... you seem like you don't have too many friends... but I guess you're talking to a lot of them... h-how would I get started? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="streaming-chan" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-Posing.png">Support Streaming-chan, chat! ...&lt;i&gt;(Am I doing this right?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="sakura" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Excited.png">You and I are dressed quite similarly! Even though we serve different sources of power, doubtless we can make... g-good friends! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="sakura" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-Sad.png">S-Sakura, you-- you don't have to lose, I-I could d-do whatever you need to do instead! F-for my friend! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="sakura" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-Scared.png">I get the sense that something is bad about to happen... bad things happen to me quite a lot, so... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="sakura" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-Crying.png">S-Sakura, even if you're a zombie, I'll be your friend! L-Lots of people have undead friends! Y-you can even bite me a little! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="sakura" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-Scared.png">D-do you want help? I don't want my first friend to break apart... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="amy" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Happy2.png">I-I know this is rather... d-do you also find yourself not having too many friends? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="amy" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-Happy2.png">So... um... c-could we... do something after this game? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="amy" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-Crying.png">A-A-Amy! Please?! I-I'll teach you magic, or just take you out for food, o-o-or any of a number of things, truly! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="amy" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png">...C-can I at least &lt;i&gt;say&lt;/i&gt; you're my friend? I-I do promise I'll be nice and do whatever it takes...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="amy" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-Sad.png">Amy... be on your guard! Others mean to distract you! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="futaba" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">Futaba, are you one of those people from Kazuma's world that doesn't go outside much...? A NEET? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="futaba" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Futaba... do you often play lewd games of this nature...? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="futaba" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">It's really important for a Crimson Demon trainee to have lots of accessories! Where should we start? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="futaba" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Fret not, Futaba. &lt;i&gt;I&lt;/i&gt; clearly appreciate the application of your... &lt;i&gt;thights.&lt;/i&gt; Did I say it right? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="futaba" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">It'll be your chest next, won't it? I'm sure they are rather... impressive. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="futaba" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">Futaba, I am reminded of a statement Kazuma once made... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="natsuki" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">Natsuki, if you don't want to, I'd hardly expect a schoolgirl to need to undress... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="natsuki" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">Oh, you're staying? But... I thought you had planned to leave... besides, didn't you take off two things last turn? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="natsuki" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Oh! I see. Did you learn so many words from the "Manga" you were talking about? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="natsuki" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-Stern.png">You know, Natsuki, we'll have to get you a &lt;i&gt;lot&lt;/i&gt; more accessories. You have to use them to store magical power...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <condition role="target" character="natsuki" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png">...Might I suggest your skirt, next? It's what I'd do... but I've got more to hide than you do, I think... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-9">
                <condition role="target" character="natsuki" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png">...Might I suggest your skirt, next? It's what I did... t-though perhaps I have more to hide than you do--</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="natsuki" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png">I... think I understand! A fruit is the sign of a mature woman! It's my underwear, which has no patterns, that's the immature pair... r-right? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="natsuki" stage="6" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png">You know... Natsuki, maybe you should try being an acolyte or some sort of paladin...! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="natsuki" stage="7" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Don't worry, Natsuki... it can be like a fabled girls trip to a hot spring...! I've never gone, but I assume everyone's naked...? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <condition role="target" character="ringo_ando" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Posing.png" marker="Ringo_ribbon1">S-So, Ringo! I see you too are a practitioner of magic! You know, I actually know a lot of high level spells! I‑I could teach you some if you wanted...!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-Happy2.png">&lt;i&gt;(I want everyone to be my friend... but I really really want ~player~ to be my friend for some reason!)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">Oh... ~player~ lost? That's good. Really good. Not because I want to see her naked! Just because, uh, uh... Never mind!</state>
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">Why does ~player~ make me feel weird? Wait, did I say that aloud?! &lt;i&gt;So embarrassing...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-Happy.png">T-Thanks for spending time with me, ~player~... you're making this game really fun...</state>
                <state img="#-Scared.png">H-Hey, ~player~? Is it okay if I tell everyone you're my friend? Not in a weird way! Promise!</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">Oh... you've got to strip, ~player~. I-Is it okay if I watch?!</state>
                <state img="#-Happy2.png">Even though you don't talk to me,  ~player~, that's still nicer than how most people treat me!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-Happy.png">~Player~... I... hope that you getting to watch me was something you enjoyed, for am I about to enjoy you stripping tremendously...!</state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png">W-well, you have seen my fingers enter myself... t-this means we are certainly &lt;i&gt;at least&lt;/i&gt; friends, i-is it not? </state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I... wish to observe you, ~name~! It will help with my ritual of self-pleasing... </state>
                <state img="#-Happy2.png">Y-you don't have to say anything, ~player~, I-I can tell you have more favor for me than most... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">I, um, this game is kind of lewd... isn't it? Not that I care! I'm very calm and comfortable, okay?!</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">... You've got to strip, right? That was a question, not a demand! Sorry!</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Even if you lose, all that matters is that you tried! Why does nobody ever tell me that?</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Wait, I didn't lose?! That's a nice feeling...</state>
                <state img="#-Sad.png">I know I should be happy I won... But I'm a little sad someone else lost...</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">I know I'm supposed to give a victory speech like most other Crimson Demons would... but that'd be so embarrassing...</state>
                <state img="#-Scared.png">W-wait! Did... am I finding this appealing-- b-but of course I am! I mean... not ~name~ losing... &lt;i&gt;oh no.&lt;/i&gt;  </state>
                <state img="#-Scared.png">I... I'm just amazed it wasn't me...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-Shy.png">I-if you want, you can certainly take off more... after all, you can already see me and my...</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">I hope you are still enjoying yourself! I know I am... e-enjoying myself-- b-because I'm... n-not because you lost... p-please forgive me!</state>
                <state img="#-Excited.png">We are closer than ever to bonding-- w-what other conclusion could you come to...? </state>
                <state img="#-Excited.png">A triumph from behind! Even a Crimson Demon can celebrate such a victory! </state>
                <state img="#-Crying.png">B-but... this makes it look like... like I'm masturbating to you! A-and... I-I-I am but I don't want to make people think I'm &lt;i&gt;weird&lt;/i&gt;! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-Scared.png">You know, winning this game feels really good! Wait, I'm sorry for boasting! I'm humble!</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Y-You can strip too! If we're both embarrassed that means we can understand each other better, right?!</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Even if you lost, I really hope you're still enjoying yourself, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-Scared.png">YunYun just WonWon! Wait, that was the worst thing I ever said!</state>
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">~Name~ lost! And not me! Oh...</state>
                <state img="#-Sad.png">Oh... ~name~... if I knew you'd be losing... </state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png">Oh... ~name~, do you need a friend at this trying time? </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="tie">
            <case stage="0-1">
                <state img="#-Scared.png">A tie... but... I'm still wearing a tie, does this mean something bad? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-3">
                <state img="#-Stern.png">A tie! But I already took mine off! What are you bothering me, for! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">A tie... surely this momentous occasion means we can all become friends, yes? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-Crying.png">A tie! Surely this means we can all put something on! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">Oh... how rare! </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Excited.png">I've always wanted to play a game like this with friends. It's okay if I pretend we're all friends, right?!</state>
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">This is my first time playing a game like this... does it always go so... slow?</state>
                <state img="#-Posing.png">You should all know that I'm the Greatest Genius of the Crimson Magic Clan! Or, um, the s-second Greatest G-Genius...</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">You know, I'm not dumb, o-okay? I know when people are lying to me! I just... like to pretend they aren't...</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Just because you know I'm going to lose doesn't mean it's f-fair to keep the game going when you don't have to... </state>
                <state img="#-Stern.png">Are you trying to drag the game out, ~name~? A-are you sure? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-Happy2.png">Oh, I see! You're trying to... present yourself as a gentleman! I understand you're doing this because you're treating me like a lady... right?</state>
                <state img="#-Excited.png">I am enjoying the game more the longer it goes... so don't speed up, ~name~, it just means more time together!</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">You're very clever, ~name~, using your ~clothing~ to draw out the game... quite brilliant. Very smart. </state>
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">O-Oh! You're finally removing your ~clothing~...? I-is this like one of those tales where a knight bestows an icon of favor on his lady-wizard of choice...? </state>
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">You're-- p-please tell me you're doing this to stare at me, aren't you? </state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png">I... I lost really terribly, didn't I? T-this makes it easy to plan to protect me, and not leave me alone to fend for myself naked, yes? ...R-right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-Happy2.png">It might not be much but it's the thought that counts! Thanks for stripping for us! Please like me!</state>
                <state img="#-Excited.png">Keep taking off small things like that! The longer this game lasts the better!</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">That's a really smart move, ~name~! I guess you've got to use all the advantages you have!</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">That's really great that you still had your ~clothing~! </state>
                <state img="#-Happy2.png">O-oh. His ~clothing~... s-sure...</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Would it be impressive to you if I told you I could also wear ~clothing.ifPlural(some|a)~ ~clothing~ like yours, ~name~?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Sad.png">That's all? Wait, I'm not complaining! Sorry!</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Um, I'll keep playing if you all still want me here...</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">I had a fun idea for a game! Every time you lose, you must give the winner a compliment. Why don't we start playing now?</state>
                <state img="#-Scared.png">The Cursed ~Clothing~ of ~Name~! It makes it impossible for anyone to think of Yunyun as a friend!  </state>
                <state img="#-Scared.png">This reminds me of home, and how nobody paid attention to me either... o-oh... I-I see. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-Facade.png">Can we keep playing now? Please! I'm having fun!</state>
                <state img="#-Scared.png">You know... I don't often get to play games like these with other people. I've always wanted to and I just really want to say- Wait, what? Next hand? Already?!</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Oh. You've still got a lot left, ~name~? Heh, you're... um... making me kind of nervous!</state>
                <state img="#-Sad.png">You're taking that off just now? Oh no! I'm totally going to lose!</state>
                <state img="#-Sad.png">Please strip more off! I could really use a win!</state>
                <state img="#-Scared.png">~Name~? P-please! I'm almost naked-- e-even if we aren't friends, please have mercy!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-Facade.png">We can keep going, right? I'm having an &lt;i&gt;excellent&lt;/i&gt; time. I-I can't imagine this going any better!</state>
                <state img="#-Scared.png">I-if I might, I want to say that I rather enjoyed this experience, and even though it's humiliating perhaps-- eh? N-nobody was listening, were they?</state>
                <state img="#-Sad.png">You're... not really giving me a lot to look at, ~name~... but I suppose th‑that's what happens when you lose... </state>
                <state img="#-Scared.png">For reasons I can't quite explain... n‑never mind... w-wait... nobody was listening anyway, were they? </state>
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">It can't be that ~name~'s ~clothing~ has my groin so soaked... c-can it? </state>
                <state img="#-Crying.png">N-no-- w-wait-- a-am I enjoying being humiliated so? T-that cannot be! </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0-9" totalRounds="1-">
                <condition role="target" character="natsuki" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Scared.png">A-All I meant was that... a-as someone a little older that you should enjoy your youth while you have it! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" totalRounds="0">
                <condition role="target" character="natsuki" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Sad.png">...Don't tell me that you're a poor girl trying to earn attention for yourself this way...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="streaming-chan" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Posing2.png">Well! Hello-- &lt;i&gt;Chat!&lt;/i&gt; It is I, Yunyun! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="streaming-chan" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-Happy2.png">I... I can? Really?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="sakura" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Happy2.png">I quite like your dress... you are a bard, aren't you? But where is your instrument of power...? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="amy" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-Facade.png">B-b-but-- you said that--</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="amy" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-Sad.png">M-maybe I could teach you a spell to help you concentrate? Those are really important... and help build towards the climax of a really big spell...!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="futaba" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-Happy.png">I see, do you think it's an excellent way to make companions? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="natsuki" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-Facade.png">&lt;i&gt;T-they also... l-look really cool, d-don't they?&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Shy.png">I've always wanted to play a game like this with friends. It's okay if I pretend we're all friends, right?!</state>
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">This is my first time playing a game like this... does it always go so... slow?</state>
                <state img="#-Posing2.png">You should all know that I'm the Greatest Genius of the Crimson Magic Clan! Or, um, the s-second Greatest G-Genius...</state>
                <state img="#-Sad.png">You know, I'm not dumb okay! I know when people are lying to me! I just... like to pretend they aren't...</state>
                <state img="#-Excited.png">Well done, ~name~! This way, you won't expend more mana than you need to and end up collapsed on the floor!</state>
                <state img="#-Posing.png">You need not waste additional resources! Prepare your greatest powers as ~name~ reveals her true might hidden by her ~clothing~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-Excited.png">Y-you must really like me if you want me to keep watching you... s-since it's just your ~clothing~. </state>
                <state img="#-Happy2.png">You're really trying to show off, aren't you, ~name~? T-that's what Kazuma c-calls a strip tease, r-right?</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">W-wow! I can't believe you're working so hard... you must be... r-really enjoying watching me like this, aren't you?</state>
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">Oh... ~name~... you've... you'd be a great friend to have, considering how good you are at cards... </state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">I-Is... a-are you just trying to get a better look at me... I-I've heard someone say that people like a look inside like this...</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">D-does this view please you, ~name~? B-because you've certainly overwhelmed me--</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-Excited.png">It might not be much but it's the thought that counts! Thanks for stripping for us! Please like me!</state>
                <state img="#-Happy2.png">Keep taking off small things like that! The longer this game lasts the better!</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">That's a really smart move, ~name~! I guess you've got to use all the advantages you have!</state>
                <state img="#-Posing2.png">I understand that your ~clothing~ was only holding back your power! Do not worry, as y-your f-friend, I, Yunyun, will match your strength!</state>
                <state img="#-Sad.png">~Clothing~ ~clothing.ifPlural(make|makes)~ the adventurer... wait-- um... n-not what I meant!  </state>
                <state img="#-Excited.png">Quite impressive, ~name~! I'm sure you'll look excellent without your ~clothing~... n-not that you didn't before! </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="streaming-chan" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-Scared.png">Was-- was t-the point of that...?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="streaming-chan" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-Crying.png">B-B-But... i-if I always do that... t-then! C-come on! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="sakura" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-Crying.png">Y-you are so nice... (&lt;i&gt;A friend! A friend! I'm going to make a real friend!&lt;/i&gt;)!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="amy" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-Scared.png">...I really thought we were going to connect--</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="amy" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-Scared.png">E-eh? I-I wasn't making fun of you-- I j‑j‑just... s-should I have said a repair spell instead? A-Amy? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="futaba" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-Happy2.png">I think we've... a similar sense of fashion. If we're both naked at the end of this... m-maybe we could try to dress you up? That's what friends do, isn't it? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="natsuki" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-Crying.png">W-what did I say wrong? Y-you're so petite and cute, s-surely you can forgive me for mistaking you for a young girl! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="natsuki" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-Posing.png">An excellent play, Natsuki! You're... d-definitely mastering the magic of this game! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="3">
                <condition status="crotch_visible" role="target" />
                <state img="#-Crying.png">W-Wait, why didn't you take that off first? I'm so confused!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Facade.png">That's all? Wait, I'm not complaining! Sorry!</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Um, I'll keep playing if you all still want me here...</state>
                <state img="#-Scared.png">Y-you know, instead of taking off small items, maybe we could just say something nice to each other instead? Please? A-and instead of big things we could promise to get to know each other better? N-no? O-okay.</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Um... you... must not want me to leave if you're trying to extend the game... this makes sense. </state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png">You... you really only meant to take that off. Truly, you're waiting until later to show us your power? Surely?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-Excited.png">Can we keep playing now? Please! I'm having fun!</state>
                <state img="#-Scared.png">You know... I don't often get to play games like these with other people. I've always wanted to and I just really want to say- Wait, what? Next hand? Already?!</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Oh. You've still got a lot left, ~name~? Heh, you're... um... making me kind of nervous!</state>
                <state img="#-Sad.png">You're taking that off just now? Oh no! I'm totally going to lose!</state>
                <state img="#-Sad.png">Please strip more off! I could really use a win!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-Excited.png">A-after this, I'd be happy to go shopping for ~clothing~ with you, ~name~! T-that's what friends do, right?</state>
                <state img="#-Scared.png">I... I lost very badly, didn't I? Y-you could always beat me if we played together! </state>
                <state img="#-Sad.png">I-it's really not &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; embarrassing! I'm hardly ashamed at all-- a-and I know a lot about-- </state>
                <state img="#-Sad.png">Nwgh. </state>
                <state img="#-Scared.png">I-I... y-you don't think I'm weird because I enjoyed you taking off your ~clothing~, do you? I promise! I'm completely normal for a girl who had to masturbate in front of strangers in hopes of making friends...!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Happy2.png">Are you really okay with &lt;i&gt;stripping&lt;/i&gt; in front of someone like me? Really?! T-Thanks so much!</state>
                <state img="#-Sad.png">If it's really embarrassing, you can just pretend I'm not here... I'm used to it.</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">This game is heating up, huh? Can you please agree with me?</state>
                <state img="#-Happy2.png">T-thank you, ~name~! If your ~clothing~ were an item at a magic shop, I would doubtless acquire it for myself! </state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">...I am grateful that your ~clothing~ ~clothing.ifPlural(were|was)~ not some kind of ancient magic item... but I am also saddened ~clothing.ifPlural(they were|it was)~ not... </state>
                <state img="#-Excited.png">Without your ~clothing~, you will reveal your full power, will you not? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-Shy.png">I think I've seen ~clothing~ like that... but I've never seen someone take it off... until now. </state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png">Is... this at all embarrassing for you, I think you're rather shameless-- s-so you shouldn't have shame and &lt;i&gt;should&lt;/i&gt; take it off!</state>
                <state img="#-Excited.png">Oh... ~name~, i-is your ~clothing~ magical? Or just you... i-is that flirting? </state>
                <state img="#-Posing.png">If you gave me your ~clothing~, ~name~, I'd be failing at exposing myself...</state>
                <state img="#-Posing2.png">People seem to love watching me make a fool of myself! So, behold! It is I, Yunyun, on full display though ~name~ is only removing his ~clothing~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Well, ~name~, you're running out of small items. Right? Or do you have a bunch hidden?!</state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png">This isn't too embarrassing for you, right? I mean, it's barely anything... Wait, I'm not being condescending!</state>
                <state img="#-Excited.png">The more time we all get to spend together the better!</state>
                <state img="#-Scared.png">Eh? His ~clothing~? B-but... I didn't know I'd see something like that before my wedding night... if I ever got married...</state>
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">Oh... I think ~clothing~ like that is usually worn by adventurers who arrive from Kazuma's world... before they acclimate...  </state>
                <state img="#-Crying.png">I-If you want, ~name~, I can take that from you! I'd wear it every day! </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_minor">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Shy.png">You're enjoying this game, right? I hope I'm not ruining it...</state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png">Wow. This game is making me &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; hungry! Anyone else want to go for food afterwards? Just, you know, for practical reasons. &lt;i&gt;I'll pay!&lt;/i&gt; </state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">Well, at least we all see &lt;i&gt;something&lt;/i&gt;. Um, not that I'm lewd! I'm not!</state>
                <state img="#-Scared.png">I'm only used to seeing boys with bare chests when their clothes are destroyed by monsters or magic-- n-not that I'd ever... I-I mean, I &lt;i&gt;could&lt;/i&gt; I'd just...</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">You... um... would like it if I lost too, huh? S-so, of course I liked it when you did-- </state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">I-I never imagined a boy would undress for me... but... you could be doing it for others, couldn't you? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-Happy.png">W-wow... you... you're really good looking-- </state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">I really appreciate that we're spending-- ~Name~? W-wait, don't deal yet--</state>
                <state img="#-Excited.png">I... a man took off his ~clothing~, and I was already naked! I-I'm so close to having a new friend... I can &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; feel it. </state>
                <state img="#-Crying.png">I... can you pose, like a Crimson Demon would? P-please? F-for me?! </state>
                <state img="#-Scared.png">I'm glad you're... um... you--you do like what you see, don't you? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-Happy.png">&lt;i&gt;(Should I try and distract the dealer so we can play for longer? Wait, they are already dealing cards!)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Can we just take a second just to appreciate the time we spend together before we deal the next hand?</state>
                <state img="#-Excited.png">Who would've known playing a game with so many other people would've been this fun? I mean, I fantasized it would be. But this is even better than my daydreams!</state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png">My heart! You'd make such a good friend! And I could share clothes with you! </state>
                <state img="#-Sad.png">I'm sorry! Don't hate me! You look great! I just want to be friends!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="kizuna" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-Crying.png">A-as your friend, d-don't rip your clothes, Kizuna! I-it's n-not as cool as someone else giving battle damage... but I guess if you said someone else did it, th‑that would be okay! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="streaming-chan" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-Excited.png">&lt;i&gt;Really!&lt;/i&gt; I can do that! Um... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="streaming-chan" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png">This is Y1Y1... a-and you should really pay close attention, chat! N-Nicole-- St-Streaming-chan is a good &lt;i&gt;friend&lt;/i&gt; and--</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="sakura" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-Scared.png">W-wow... I... I-I won't look-- b-but-- w-wait! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="33">
                <condition role="target" character="sakura" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-Crying.png">W-W-Wait! A-are you Undead?! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="34">
                <condition role="target" character="sakura" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-Scared.png">...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="amy" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Well... we could be friends! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="futaba" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Scared.png">Eh? Did I say something wrong? Is that really so? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="futaba" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">For some reason, I almost wish those were the last thing you were to remove... perhaps they are power limiters, and you're going to be showing us your full power!? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="natsuki" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-Scared.png">T-the rest of us could take something else off, if you wanted... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="natsuki" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-Facade.png">I... can see the wisdom in that, really, I can! But is cloth armor really that effective? Maybe being a mighty sorcerer suits you better than trying to be...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Excited.png">Are you really okay with &lt;i&gt;stripping&lt;/i&gt; in front of someone like me? Really?! T-Thanks so much!</state>
                <state img="#-Sad.png">If it's really embarrassing you can just pretend I'm not here... I'm used to it.</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">This game is heating up, huh? Can you please agree with me?</state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png">S-so, ~name~, I have heard that people often like to have girls who can flirt with each other as friends... </state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png">~Name~, if you take your ~clothing~ off, you'd be okay if I traded you something, so I would always be with you, wouldn't you?  </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-Shy.png">~Name~... I'm glad ~clothing.ifPlural(those aren't magical ~clothing~|that isn't a magical ~clothing~)~-- Wait, is that's what making me stare?</state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png">I... I w-wouldn't mind if you took more off! I'd be really happy-- I... I have nothing left to lose!</state>
                <state img="#-Excited.png">C-can we... um... do something after this? E-even if I have to do it naked, as long as we can do it as friends...</state>
                <state img="#-Excited.png">If you can beat me, you can beat... well, most people beat me at most things, but I still think you can win, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">~Name~! Removing your ~clothing~ was certainly a... positive. Think of it like letting go of concerns, like people don't like you, or you'll die alone, or that nobody respects you!  </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Well, ~name~, you're running out of small items. Right? Or do you have a bunch hidden?!</state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png">This isn't too embarrassing for you, right? I mean, it's barely anything... Wait, I'm not being condescending!</state>
                <state img="#-Excited.png">The more time we all get to spend together the better!</state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png">O-O-oh... your ~clothing~... quite admirable, considering my own state of undress... </state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png">Truly impressive, ~name~, to still have your ~clothing~ even though... </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_minor">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="futaba" stage="4" />
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Megumin, I still think she has a bit more of my body type than yours. Did Kazuma not describe me as... thick like a... milkshake? Futaba, why would you shake milk?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="kizuna" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">...Y-you're... very brave for showing off your body like this... a-and without even shame! And with such spirit... a-a true Crimson Demon! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="kizuna" stage="6" />
                <state img="#-Scared.png">Y-you'd really give me credit for-- w-wait! N-no! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="streaming-chan" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-Posing2.png" marker="Y1Y1" set-label="Y1Y1">I should come up with a streaming name, shouldn't I? How about Y1Y1! Now I am Y1Y1!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="streaming-chan" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-Scared.png">I-I am a fan, b-but I'm also a friend... r-right? I... I don't have my stream &lt;i&gt;yet&lt;/i&gt; but surely you'll... h-help, r-right, Streaming-chan? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="sakura" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-Sad.png">A-as your friend, your... um... a-are you okay, Ms. Number One? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="sakura" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-Sad.png">I-I-I've never &lt;i&gt;tried&lt;/i&gt; to be friends with an undead, b-b-but necromancers are always so weird! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="sakura" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-Crying.png">I-I can't use healing magic! It'll hurt you! N-Not that I could use it in the first place! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="amy" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-Excited.png">I can teach you all kinds of things-- a-and you could teach me about poetry! I-It'd be really fun! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="futaba" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Well... um... I'm sorry, but... do you think we could be friends? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="futaba" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png">You have rather long legs... my f-friend Megumin is much the same, though... I think you have the build of someone with more durability.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="natsuki" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-Crying.png">I just want to be your friend! H-How can I make that happen! I-I'll do anything! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="natsuki" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-Happy2.png">Oh! I didn't know that would make you so happy... that means I'm starting to understand you, isn't it? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Sad.png">You're enjoying this game, right? I hope I'm not ruining it...</state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png">Wow. This game is making me &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; hungry! Anyone else want to go for food afterwards? Just, you know, for practical reasons. &lt;i&gt;I'll pay!&lt;/i&gt; </state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">Well, at least we all see &lt;i&gt;something&lt;/i&gt;. Um, not that I'm lewd! I'm not!</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">She is really undressing for&lt;i&gt; me&lt;/i&gt;? I thought I'd never... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-Sad.png">I-I just wanted to give you a compliment... </state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">S-so! Since you're no longer wearing your ~clothing~, will we be enjoying any more time together?</state>
                <state img="#-Excited.png">This is even better than I had once imagined it being! And I have imagined it quite a lot! </state>
                <state img="#-Scared.png">I-If ~name~ has seen me... touch myself, will she think less of me? </state>
                <state img="#-Scared.png">Y-you wouldn't &lt;i&gt;not&lt;/i&gt; want to be my friend since you've taken off your ~clothing~ while I've... had my fingers inside of me... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-Sad.png">&lt;i&gt;(Should I try and distract the dealer so we can play for longer? Wait, they are already dealing cards!)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Can we just take a second just to appreciate the time we spend together before we deal the next hand?</state>
                <state img="#-Excited.png">Who would've known playing a game with so many other people would've been this fun? I mean, I fantasied it would be. But this is even better than my daydreams!</state>
                <state img="#-Happy2.png">This is fun, isn't it, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">I... rather enjoy watching you undress, ~name~! I'm sure we'd enjoy watching each other do other friendly things! </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_major">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Excited.png">You know, ~name~, if you are embarrassed and want to take a break where we all have snacks, that'd be fine by me! More than fine!</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Oh, um, wow... Are y-you really taking that off? N-Not that I mind! </state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">You're taking off &lt;i&gt;a lot&lt;/i&gt;! This game is &lt;i&gt;a lot!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-Happy.png">T-take off your ~clothing~, haha, ~name~? Isn't-- is not what friends do... j-jokingly command each other? </state>
                <state img="#-Posing.png">E-even if I'm down to zero layers, a Crimson Demon is-- is never defeated! U-unless you want to defeat me... a-and we can be friends!</state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png">W-wow! Your ~clothing~? That was almost... as much as what I lost... already... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-Happy.png">You don't have to take anything off, if you don't want! I'm against peer pressure... I know what it’s like to feel like you need to do something.</state>
                <state img="#-Posing.png">Y-You really don't have much left, ~name~? Well, um, that's what you g-get for playing against a Crimson Demon!  ...Sorry!</state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png">W-Wait, that already?! Um, time goes fast when you're having fun! You are all having fun, right?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_major">
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Ooh-- you're so... I &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; want you to be my friend!</state>
                <state img="#-Sad.png">I-I was first at losing, you know? S-so you could definitely acknowledge my skills! </state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I-I can be distracted-- d-did you want to distract me, ~name~? </state>
                <state img="#-Happy2.png">~Name~ y-you're so... w-wow! I want to be your friend! F-for a very long time. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">Oh wow... This game is surprisingly fun... and... &lt;i&gt;hot!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">This game is getting quite lewd... um, I'll try not to be distracted...</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">A Critical Hit! That’s something people in my village say a lot, but I never really understood why...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-Shy.png">I'm sorry if my eyes suddenly glow red! It's just a thing that happens when I'm excited... It's not dangerous, promise! </state>
                <state img="#-Sad.png">Oh... Well, at least I'm not the only loser now... I mean loser as in the game! Not generally!</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">This game is getting quite lewd... um, I'll try not to be distracted...</state>
                <state img="#-Happy2.png">I really wish I'd been invited to games like this in the past!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_major">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="futaba" stage="2" />
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" />
                <state img="#-Scared.png">Though... maybe she's too agile to wear my vestments, you hardly need to insult my size, Megumin... </state>
                <state img="#-Scared.png">Megumin, she might be closer to your frame... but she would doubtless prefer a more substantial garment...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="kizuna" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Scared.png">...R-really? I-I see... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="kizuna" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">...Y-you are!? &lt;i&gt;You are!&lt;/i&gt;? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="sakura" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">Wait, do you... have underwear and a bra under there...? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="amy" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-Crying.png">W-what kind of magic trick could you be doing? Is it... A-Amy have you been hiding something?! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="amy" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-Crying.png">S-stop distracting her! She's very smart but you're b-being bad friends! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="futaba" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-Excited.png">One step closer to friendship and a new outfit, Futaba! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="natsuki" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-Scared.png">Oh... oh no, I didn't mean that to be insulting-- p-please don't cry and please be my friend...!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="natsuki" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">Oh... I see. I had guessed because a fruit is a ripe... you know, how you're quite the mature woman and all... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Happy2.png">You know, ~name~, if you are embarrassed and want to take a break where we all have snacks, that'd be fine by me! More than fine!</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">Oh, um, wow... Are y-you really taking that off? N-Not that I mind!</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">You're taking off &lt;i&gt;a lot&lt;/i&gt;! This game is &lt;i&gt;a lot!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-Happy2.png">~Name~, are you going to show us your...</state>
                <state img="#-Posing.png">W-well, I think m-my... ~name~? </state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png">I'm having fun! A-aren't you, ~name~? W-wasn't that the right thing to say? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-Happy2.png">You don't have to take anything off, if you don't want! I'm against peer pressure... I know what it’s like to feel like to feel like you need to do something.</state>
                <state img="#-Posing.png">Y-You really don't have much left, ~name~? Well, um, that's what you g-get for playing against a Crimson Demon!  ...Sorry!</state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png">W-Wait, that already?! Um, time goes fast when you're having fun! You are all having fun, right?!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_major">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="futaba" stage="3" />
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" />
                <state img="#-Posing.png">She can answer this for us! Futaba, would you prefer to dress like Megumin or myself? P-Please pick me...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="kizuna" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-Facade.png">O-oh! Clearly this is... a deception! A-are you a person who says the opposite of what she means? T-then... perhaps I have a chance! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="kizuna" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-Crying.png">Y-y-you mean &lt;i&gt;everyone and&lt;/i&gt; Yunyun! P-please! N-not everyone &lt;i&gt;except&lt;/i&gt; Yunyun... r-right? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="streaming-chan" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png">A-are striped panties... r-really what chat wants to see...? I always though something plain that was easy t-to take off would...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="sakura" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-Happy2.png">Y-your body is... r-remarkably well preserved? I-If... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="amy" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-Posing2.png">Excellent, Amy! Such flair! Worthy of a friend! ...I was, truthfully, beginning to wonder if you were a spider monster or something... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="37">
                <condition role="target" character="amy" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">...I've worked so hard to be your friend... m-mostly... s-so... when... I'm sorry, Amy! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="futaba" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-Posing.png">I can see the appeal of showing alternating layers of skin... perhaps I should commit even more strongly to such a display! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="59">
                <condition role="target" character="natsuki" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-Facade.png">V-Very clever, Natsuki. &lt;i&gt;V-very.&lt;/i&gt; I-it's like we can't see anything!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="natsuki" stage="6" />
                <state img="#-Happy.png">I wish I had some like yours, Natsuki... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="78">
                <condition role="target" character="rin" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-Crying.png" marker="rin_arms">R-Rin, b-but-- y-you don't have-- a-are you okay? D-did something bad happen?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">Oh wow... This game is surprisingly fun... and... &lt;i&gt;hot!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">This game is getting quite lewd... um, I'll try not to be distracted...</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">A Critical Hit! That’s something people in my village say a lot, but I never really understood why...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I-I don't want to be distracted, but for some reason you... m-make me want to focus on you...</state>
                <state img="#-Sad.png">I lost the game, but... I-I didn't lose my dignity... t-tonight...</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">...C-can you teach me that spell, ~name~? The one where I cannot look away from you?</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">I'm so glad I finally got to play a game like this with people and not just alone in my room pretending there were--</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">This game is getting quite lewd... um, I'll try not to be distracted...</state>
                <state img="#-Sad.png">Oh... Well, at least I'm not the only loser now... I mean loser as in the game! Not generally!</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">I'm sorry if my eyes suddenly glow red! It's just a thing that happens when I'm excited... It's not dangerous, promise! </state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">I really wish I'd been invited to games like this in the past!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">T-This is hot. T-Thanks for inviting me. Or, um, at least not telling me to leave...</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">If you see me gawking in your direction, just ignore me! I'm very easily ignorable, promise!</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">A shirtless guy is normal... But in a game like this, it's completely different!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-Shy.png">I-I can't help but look! I-it would be rude to ignore such a strong chest! </state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png">Friends look at each other all the time. I'm looking at ~name~ lots, so we're friends! It's just basic f-friendship!</state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png">T-this distraction won't work! I've already touched myself at least once! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-Shy.png">I'm not blushing! It's, um, just the Crimson Demon complexion?</state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png">It's fine for me to look because we're friends now, right? Right?</state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png">Are you trying to distract me?! It's not working! I'm a Crimson Demon! Okay?!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Shy.png">You're quite cute, ~name~. I hope I'm not overstepping any boundaries by saying that!</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">I'm allowed to look, right? I'll close my eyes just in case!</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">If Funifura from the Crimson Demon clan knew I was playing this game they'd be so jealous! And, um... maybe a little ashamed of me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Y-you have a mighty chest! O-one worthy of... of being... &lt;i&gt;very&lt;/i&gt; friendly with!</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I-I-I-- y-you'd be more than a friend if I could rest my head on your chest, ~name~... y-you could also get a nice view...</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">Ha! My chest's power far exceeds yours! ...W-which i-is only fair! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-Shy.png">I'm not blushing! It's, um, just the Crimson Demon complexion?</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I've seen a shirtless man before! So... uh, why does this feel different?!</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">D-Don't distract me! A Crimson Demon's attention is supposed to be unwavering!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">The whole game has been building to this specific one moment! &lt;i&gt;(I hope it isn't as disappointing as me!)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">Wait, what? Now? This is happening?! But I haven't gotten the chance to mentally prepare myself!</state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png">I'm probably the first person ever to see a penis before making a single friend! Why is my life so weird?!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-Shy.png">~Name~'s... staff of power... </state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">T-the entire game has led to this climax-- o-of ~name~! N-not me! T-though I might--</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">~Name~--! As your newest friend, I demand y-you-- d-demand-- t-to see your--</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-Shy.png">... I, um... Are you really going to do this, ~name~? N-Not that I don't want you to!</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I know this is what the entire game is about... But I just really liked spending time with you all. I, um, can still look though... Right?</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">&lt;i&gt;(Don't panic, Yunyun! This is what all this daydreaming has been preparing you for!)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_small_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I-It's surprisingly... cute!</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">You've got a lot of confidence, ~name~! I-It's kind of... s-sexy actually...</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">Oh! I didn't expect it to be so... small. N-Not that I mind! I t-think it's adorable! W-Wait, is that the right word?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I-it's so... easy to manage... I could even put it in my mouth, or easily between my breasts, let alone inside of my-- U-um... s-sorry!</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I-I... it's...! ~Name~, you could put that &lt;i&gt;anywhere!&lt;/i&gt; I-it would be quite fun! </state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I-it's... it's so... amazing...! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">W-Wow. It's, erm... Is a-anyone else feeling hot right now?</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I-I'm not &lt;i&gt;blushing!&lt;/i&gt; It's just my Crimson Demon complexion! &lt;i&gt;I-It's not a blush!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">W-Why am I feeling like I do when I read one of my romance novels?!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_medium_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I... I won't be distracted! E-Even if it is very very distracting!</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">Y-You think you can fluster me with s-something like that? I'll still win! I'm a Crimson Demon! Okay?!</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">You &lt;i&gt;might&lt;/i&gt; expect me to become embarrassed. But I've already seen many, &lt;i&gt;many&lt;/i&gt; penises in pictures! Wait, that's supposed to be a secret!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I... I lost... but is it a loss as long as I can see ~name~'s... </state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I-it looks... amazing... t-to-to-to have on a friend! B-because... i-it means he has a big... &lt;i&gt;friendship&lt;/i&gt;!</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">I-I want you inside of me-- m-my heart! A-as friends! F-forever! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I... w-will not... b-be &lt;i&gt;flustered.&lt;/i&gt; I can... s-still win...</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">T-That... is  very nice, ~name~! Um, right... continue! Continue!</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I-I'm not turned on! I-I'm off! &lt;i&gt;I'm always off!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_large_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Scared.png">T-That's m-massive! A-And very very intimidating!</state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png">I-I, erm, t-that's way too large! I-It's almost scary!</state>
                <state img="#-Scared.png">T-That's the biggest one I've ever seen! A-And I've seen... relatively little actually...</state>
                <state img="#-Scared.png">I'm innocent! &lt;i&gt;Innocent!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-Happy2.png">I-it's... it's big! S-so bringing it down gives more XP! I'm ready!</state>
                <state img="#-Scared.png">It's... s-so... &lt;i&gt;big&lt;/i&gt;. </state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">Just because it's a big opponent doesn't mean I can't take it! In fact, I revel in the c-chance to... f-fight it... w-with... o-on... m-my terms...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-Scared.png">T-That's &lt;i&gt;dangerously&lt;/i&gt; large!</state>
                <state img="#-Scared.png">I-I'm more scared t-than aroused!</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">Y-You must have used a lot of Skill Potions, ~name~...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="streaming-chan" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I'm learning so much, S‑Streaming-chan... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="kizuna" />
                <state img="#-Scared.png">(&lt;i&gt;T-this is what you call a strip tease, isn't it? B-but who is she teasing? I just want someone to be my friend!&lt;/i&gt;) </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="35">
                <condition role="target" character="sakura" />
                <state img="#-Scared.png">T-they're so impressive... a-and she has great aim! W-what a powerful party member you'd be...!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="futaba" />
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">That's not surprising is it? I can't think of any Crimson Demon that wears anything under their dress or chest armor... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="natsuki" />
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">Huh? I thought Kazuma was always saying something about justice and women with small chests, which is why Darkness is such a bad crusader... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <condition filter="enf" role="target" />
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">I-I guess we can call the game quits then for your sake, ~name~... Wait, you're actually doing it?!</state>
                <state img="#-Scared.png">~Name~ doesn't really have to do this, does she? We can stop if-- ~Name~??</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Facade.png">I-I have those too! I-It's nothing s-special!</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Erm, this game is progressing fast! R-Really fast!</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I-I... am very very confused as to how I feel right now...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">W-well, since everyone's already seen mine... I-I guess they'd like to see something else, too... </state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">This is... lewd but quite... a-are you having fun, ~name~? I-I am! </state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">~Name~... I-I can look, right? Please?</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I-I'm really confused but I'm really enjoying it too!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">B-Breasts?! I... I mean, yes. Obviously. Boobs!</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">This game is very lewd... um, I don't mind if everyone is enjoying it though!</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">A-Am I allowed to look? I u-understand if not...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_small_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="streaming-chan" stage="6" />
                <state img="#-Posing2.png">For breasts big, and breasts small, Y1Y1 and Streaming-chan have you covered... e-even if you want us to cover something lewd... w-we-we can do it with our breasts! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="kizuna" />
                <state img="#-Crying.png">A-Ai chan! C-can we just be friends? Y-you don't need to spend so much time joking with us-- u-unless! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="57">
                <condition role="target" character="futaba" />
                <state img="#-Posing.png">Though you lack the proper eyes, bright orange hair certainly is Crimson! I count you among my Crimson Demon sisters regardless, Futaba! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="natsuki" />
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I think they're perky and perfect... they're less likely to get slapped by another Crimson Demon, that's for certain!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Posing2.png">Bigger doesn't always mean better. Sometimes the subtle spells are the most powerful!</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Y-You shouldn't worry about what other people think of you, ~name~! At least other people &lt;i&gt;are&lt;/i&gt; thinking of you!</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">T-They might be small... But they are perky and adorable!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">They're... very pretty, ~name~! I-I bet they... h-have a nice bounce to them!</state>
                <state img="#-Sad.png">I'm a little jealous, they're so perky and probably easier on your back... </state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I-I won't let anyone make fun of ~name~'s chest! T-they're-- they're small but t-that's even better, really! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">&lt;i&gt;Oh!&lt;/i&gt; They are so cute! And not in a condescending way!</state>
                <state img="#-Sad.png">A-At least you don't have big things like mine constantly getting in the way...</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">T-Those are l-lovely... Y-You shouldn't be ashamed, ~name~...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_medium_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">That seems to be a perfect size... What? I am not jealous!</state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png">They... erm, are nice? Is that a statement to make?</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">This game is rather lewd... But I will make the most of it...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">T-they're so full... y-you aren't using illusions, are you,  ~name~? </state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">Oh... ~name~! (&lt;i&gt;S-should I offer to use my mouth...? H-How lewd!&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I-In a game like this, shouldn't we... s-should I not offer to... take care of you, ~name~? ?</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I-I may not always be... um... y-you're very beautiful, ~name~! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">Whilst I am not ashamed of my own, I still wish mine looked like that... They are so pretty and perky! </state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">You're very beautiful, ~name~! </state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">&lt;i&gt;(My mind is filled with thoughts of boobies! This is so unprofessional of an Arch‑Mage!)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_large_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="sakura" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png">I-I think we could make a great party... I-I wouldn't mind joining yours, e-even if you are undead! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">A-Are those bigger than mine?!</state>
                <state img="#-Scared.png">B-but... K-Kazuma says my chest is all I have going for me... i-if yours are bigger...!</state>
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">They're... very impressive, ~name~! I-I hope nobody slaps those around... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">O-Oh... ~name~... they're... so full! </state>
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">T-they're... g-getting me quite... um... s-see how wet I am...?</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">They're... so beautiful, ~name~... I wish mine were that nice... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">A-Are those even bigger than mine?! How am I feeling insecure about &lt;i&gt;this&lt;/i&gt;?!</state>
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">~Name~'s boobs are even better than mine... b-but what will I have going for me if...? </state>
                <state img="#-Scared.png">B-b-b-b-but-- t-they're so big! E-even bigger than mine!? B-but... t-then! </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="futaba" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Regardless, I'm sure you have quite a beautiful pair of panties--</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" priority="302">
                <condition role="target" character="natsuki" saidMarker="shave1" notSaidMarker="hairy1" />
                <state img="#-Posing.png">What would be weird...? The nudity? Clearly not...! Don't be embarrassed! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" priority="302">
                <condition role="target" character="natsuki" saidMarker="hairy1" notSaidMarker="shave1" />
                <state img="#-Scared.png">Is this the part where you reveal you've been a shape‑shifter the entire game!? Eh?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="kizuna" />
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">Y-you're joking, right, Kizuna? Y-you're not... a Dark Lord, are you? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="sakura" />
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I-I guess this could be the start of something beautiful... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="amy" />
                <state img="#-Posing2.png">...You have the aesthetic sense of a Crimson Demon, Amy... I mean this in the best way! A Crimson Demon way! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="natsuki" />
                <state img="#-Excited.png">I have never seen a woman with pink hair before. It does match, does it not? I have heard it said that most women have dark hair, but I assume yours is a bright, sugary pink!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I feel like we've only started this game... And yet...</state>
                <state img="#-Posing2.png">Seeing this is not a usual occurrence for arch-mage... But we Crimson Demons are a versatile sort able to hand any situation... Even one l-like t-this!</state>
                <state img="#-Posing.png">The game demands you to reveal everything! Not me! I'm not some kind of pervert who would propose such demands!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-Excited.png">I-I can hardly contain myself! I wish to see how our womanhoods match!</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">~Name~... </state>
                <state img="#-Posing.png">I-I cannot help myself but gaze upon your most secret of selves! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-Excited.png">This is the most intimate part a woman owns! And yet, you are showing it to someone like me! I will always appreciate this!</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">You are brave, ~name~ for showing all to us! Maybe I will allow someone like you to join me in my travels... P-Please! </state>
                <state img="#-Posing.png">All will be revealed! I-I will endeavor not to stare, t-though no promises, as sometimes even a Crimson Demon cannot control their d-devilish u-urges...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-9" id="58">
                <condition role="target" character="futaba" stage="6" />
                <state img="#-Scared.png">N-No underwear? Is this why you didn't wear a skirt? ...And I've never seen hair in that color before... or that there's so much of it...!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" priority="302">
                <condition role="target" character="natsuki" saidMarker="hairy1" notSaidMarker="shave1" />
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">Oh, I see! I didn't know you had elf heritage... they don't have hair down there, either... unless... um... I-I'm sure it's fine. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" priority="302">
                <condition role="target" character="natsuki" saidMarker="shave1" notSaidMarker="hairy1" />
                <state img="#-Scared.png">W-Wait, we're expected to shave our... &lt;i&gt;nether region?&lt;/i&gt; W-why didn't anyone tell me? I-I must look... l-like someone who doesn't care about her appearance... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="kizuna" />
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">...I... I have to say I like this look... m-maybe I'd have more friends i-if I tried it out... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="streaming-chan" />
                <state img="#-Facade.png">Oh! Are those magic wands...? I think I have one of those... but what do you plan to do with them? I don't think you are a wizard... are you...?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="sakura" />
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">...A-as long as we're friends, I'd be happy... b-but... I... maybe if you wanted, I-I could be undead too, and we'd be happy and friends forever?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="amy" />
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">...Perhaps I should try that myself... do you think I'd make more friends if I did? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="natsuki" />
                <state img="#-Scared.png">You shaved... your... pubic hair...!? B-but... f-for what possible purpose? D-does it interrupt magic, somehow? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <condition filter="shaved" role="target" />
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">You don't have any pubic hair...? But... perhaps you are truly an ancient being, not even an adult for your magical species...? </state>
                <state img="#-Scared.png">W-where is your hair, ~name~? Were... we expected to de‑foliate before beginning the game?</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I... for some reason your lack of hair gives an excellent view that I am compelled to protect...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <condition filter="hairy" role="target" />
                <state img="#-Scared.png">I-I do not at all resemble ~name~... w-were we not to trim our pubic hair for a game like this? </state>
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">Is... I... a-are we supposed to have grown out our hair there for this game? </state>
                <state img="#-Crying.png">~Name~-- D-did you... forget to perform a ritual of grooming on yourself...? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">Y-You really are c-cute, ~name~... Much cuter than me...</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I-I see you. I s-shall take one glance and then s-stop looking out of politeness. M-Maybe a second.</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">You are a very attractive woman. You must have no troubles making friends...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I am mystified... but enchanted... you are quite a pinnacle of beauty... ~name~...</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">I-I... I have... quite a few lewd thoughts of my own regarding you, ~name~, p-perhaps you feel the same for me?</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">T-this is purely a matter of... c-curiosity! I... I have rarely occasioned to have attempted to climax before another nude woman! I-If ever... I... I am not that bold... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">As this game gets lewder... I feel myself feel become more titillated. Is this normal? Am I normal?!</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">A lustful sight! Even the most trained Crimson Demon would blush at such a sight... So, erm, that explains my f-face...</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">It's not often I get to glance upon another girl like this. Therefore my stares are purely curiosity! Not anything lewd!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-9" priority="0">
                <condition filter="hairy" role="target" />
                <state img="#-Scared.png">T-that is quite a lot of hair... in truth, mine rarely grows to such density, because I am diligent about its maintaining... </state>
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">I... I do not recall ever having so much hair on myself... i-is this what is preferred? </state>
                <state img="#-Crying.png">~Name~--! I-I wish to compliment you, but all I can think of is how your hair would g-get in the way of my tongue! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-9" priority="0">
                <condition filter="shaved" role="target" />
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">That look is... quite appealing... p-perhaps it &lt;i&gt;would&lt;/i&gt; be nice to protect someone who seems more vulnerable...</state>
                <state img="#-Scared.png">W-was I... I c-cannot believe you would remove your hair there... w-wouldn't such a maneuver hurt? </state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I-is this... I-I need to... a C-Crimson Demon can never be hairless unless they have p-performed a great and shameful act... did losing shame you, ~name~?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_lost">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="darkness" stage="0" />
                <condition count="0" role="opp" character="megumin" />
                <condition count="0" role="opp" character="kazuma" />
                <state img="#-Facade.png" marker="YunDarkness_0a">D-Darkness! You mustn't tell Megumin that I came here! I'll, er, not tell Kazuma or that strange blue haired girl!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="darkness" stage="0" />
                <condition role="opp" character="megumin" />
                <condition role="opp" character="kazuma" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png" marker="YunDarknessGroup_0a">W-Wow! It seems like the whole gang is here! You know, us! The gang! Doesn't look like we're missing anyone!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <condition role="target" character="darkness" stage="1" />
                <condition count="0" role="opp" character="megumin" />
                <condition count="0" role="opp" character="kazuma" />
                <state img="#-Crying.png" marker="YunDarkness_1a">O-Oh! Darkness, what kind of game have I got myself into?! You have to protect me! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <condition role="target" character="darkness" stage="1" />
                <condition count="0" role="opp" character="megumin" />
                <condition count="0" role="opp" character="kazuma" />
                <state img="#-Crying.png" marker="YunDarkness_1aa">O-Oh! Darkness, what kind of game have I got myself into?! You have to protect me! Protect me better!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="jim" stage="1" />
                <condition count="0" role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <state img="#-Happy.png">You are not the first man I've met from a different world. Though you are quite a bit more... rugged than the one I know.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="jim" stage="1" />
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Kazuma also comes from a different world. I do not wish to compare but... Erm, I'm sure you did a lot more in your world...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="bernadetta" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Posing2.png">You are here for a supposed Social Interaction seminar, correct? Why don't you practice with me?</state>
                <state img="#-Happy2.png">Um, Bernadetta, I am always willing to assist anyone, be it through my magic or conversation. We shall have your social skills increased swiftly!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="komi-san" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Y-You are very quiet Komi-san. D-Do not worry though, I am used to people not talking to me... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="20">
                <condition role="target" character="megumin" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Shocked.png" marker="Megumin_Winning1A">Oh! Did you just lose, Megumin? I'm still not quite sure how this game works...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2" id="25">
                <condition role="target" character="megumin" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-Stern.png" marker="Megumin_Winning3A">Yet another loss Megumin! You must be careful, lest you give us Crimson Demons a weak reputation!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-1" id="26">
                <condition role="target" character="megumin" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png" marker="Megumin_Winning2A">I apologize for my earlier outburst. Of course, I wish for you to get naked, Megumin! For I refuse to lose again!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-7">
                <condition role="target" character="meia" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="70" marker="meia_lost1b">Why, erm, Meia! Since you have taken an interest in me, it is only proper I do the same in response! Please tell me a little about Mejare!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="meia" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="71" marker="meia_lost1a">Please, tell me a little about your homeland, Meia! I am always interested in other people! Which may I mention, is a positive trait for a potential friend to have!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="chara_dreemurr" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Happy.png">&lt;i&gt;(I should compliment Chara to begin building the seeds of friendship...)&lt;/i&gt; Hm...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="tomoko" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Happy.png">&lt;i&gt;(This girl looks rather lonely! If anybody needs a friend... It must be her!)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" id="50">
                <condition role="target" character="megumin" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-Stern.png" marker="Megumin_Winning4A">You, um, aren't going to do some silly trick at the end of this game, right Megumin? If I win, it'll count, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" id="51">
                <condition role="target" character="megumin" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-Posing2.png" marker="Megumin_Winning5A">Another loss, Megumin...  Shall this be my victory? Fufufu.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4" id="52">
                <condition role="target" character="megumin" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png" marker="Megumin_Winning6A">You, um, aren't going to do some silly trick at the end of this game, right Megumin? If I win, it'll count, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4" id="53">
                <condition role="target" character="megumin" stage="6" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png" marker="Megumin_Winning7A">W-Well, I have seen your naked body before, Megumin... It suppose it is no big deal...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5" id="55">
                <condition role="target" character="megumin" stage="7" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png" marker="Megumin_Winning8A">W-While I am happy I am winning we can call the game off if we must, Megumin. I would never wish to force you to expose, well, everything...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="komi-san" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png">I think we have quite a lot in common, Komi-san. I can find it quite difficult to speak my mind and many would call me introverted compared to the rest of the Crimson Demons! While I do understand the flamboyant nature of my clan, I will admit to it being quite hard to adjust to as a quiet girl, like me. It may be due to this that I often find it impossible to speak up when meeting new people despite my wishes to be heard. Like you Komi-san, I do &lt;i&gt;wish&lt;/i&gt; to speak... I just find myself unable sometimes even though the situation may demand it. Despite my best attempts to be brave and talk freely I cannot help but fall back into my rather introverted shell; as I'm sure you've noticed. Though the thing about quiet girls like us, Komi-san is that we make fantastic listeners! As we do not trouble others with our woes we instead are able to listen deeply to others.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="tomoko" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Are you sure you do not wish to be friends Tomoko? You seem quite lonely.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="tomoko" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-Stern.png">Fine then, Kuroki. If you wish to rebuke my kindly offer of friendship, then it is you who loses out.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="tomoko" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-Sad.png">Why do you dislike me Tomoko? What ever did I do to you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="jim" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Do you... come from a different world, Mr Raynor? The things you speak of are unlike anything I've heard of before!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="yusuke" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Happy.png">You talk... quite oddly, Yusuke. Though I do not see that as a bad thing. Some have remarked the same way towards my pattern of speech.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="yuri" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Crying.png">You seem quite nervous, Yuri. You can go home if you wish! Um, I didn't mean that I don't want you here! I obviously want you here! To strip with us! Wait, no!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="bernadetta" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-Happy.png">It's time for the first practice conversation! Bernadetta, please tell me more about yourself!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="adrien" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-Sad.png" marker="noir_Summon">Plagg is very cute! I had a summon once too, ~name~. It ran away...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="jim" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png" marker="raynor_quest">Er... Well, while I'm quite the busy person with all the people who wish to meet me...  I could arrange to assist you on a quest sometime, Mr Raynor?</state>
                <state img="#-Posing.png" marker="raynor_quest2">I'm sure you must encounter many fiendish opponents on your travel. I'm sure a powerful magical companion would be a great boon! Er... But where could you find one of those, I wonder?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="asuna_yuuki" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png" marker="YunAsu_0a">Erm, Asuna... What does a chunni even mean? I do hear people use that word to describe me sometimes. Is it a good thing? Please tell me it's a good thing!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="leonie" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Excited.png" marker="yunLeo_0a">You should know I &lt;i&gt;am&lt;/i&gt; an arch‑wizard, Leonie! And yes, it's very very impressive. You should, um, be impressed!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="aaravi" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png" marker="yunAaravi_0a">Y-You like EXP, Aaravi? I've got an EXP Potion... We could split it if you want. I have one of those straws that splits into two...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" totalRounds="0" priority="20">
                <state img="#-Scared.png">Wait, we've got to do &lt;i&gt;what&lt;/i&gt; when we lose?! And that happens every round!?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" hidden="1">
                <condition filter="konosuba" role="target" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="konoFriend" notSaidMarker="konoFriend2" />
                <test expr="~self.slot.konoFriend~" cmp="!=" value="~name.slot~" />
                <test expr="~self.marker.konoFriend~" cmp="!=" value="~target.id~" />
                <state img="#-Scared.png" marker="konoFriend2=~name~">~Name~ and ~marker.konoFriend~? D-did you both come here to ignore me? I-I see. D-don't worry... I won't pay you extra a-attention since it's not like you'd want it... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" hidden="1" totalRounds="0-8">
                <condition filter="konosuba" role="target" />
                <condition role="self" notSaidMarker="konoFriend" />
                <state img="#-Sad.png" marker="konoFriend=~name~">Oh! Hi there, ~name~! I-I did not expect to play a game l-like this w-with you. My apologies f-for not acknowledging you until now... b-but I won't acknowledge you until you ask me.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_stripping">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="megumin" stage="2" saidMarker="megumin_komi_patheticYunyun1" />
                <condition role="other" character="komi-san" sayingMarker="megumin_friend_pathetic_yunyun" />
                <state img="#-Facade.png">Doubtful! It must be some other female friend with large boobs that Megumin is referring to, as I am not pathetic.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <condition role="target" character="megumin" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Well, erm, I &lt;i&gt;do&lt;/i&gt; have a cape. I just did not bring it to the game today. It can be quite inconvenient and get caught on things often when I am trying to flee from monsters...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <condition role="target" character="megumin" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png">W-Well, thank you, K-Kazuma. However, you do not need to compare me to Megumin in order to compliment my courage...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <condition role="target" character="megumin" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-Stern.png">I do agree with Kazuma here, Megumin. I understand you have a style thing going on but strangers will think you've just hurt yourself.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <condition role="target" character="megumin" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-Facade.png">Oh. Um, again, t-thank you for the compliment Kazuma... but there is really no need. &lt;i&gt;(That hat looks so obnoxious!)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <condition role="target" character="megumin" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-Facade.png">E-Excuse me? W-Who cares what feet look like?!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <condition role="target" character="megumin" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-Posing.png">While I agree her choker does look &lt;i&gt;fine&lt;/i&gt;, I think a tie is more fitting for an experienced adventurer.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <condition role="target" character="megumin" stage="6" />
                <state img="#-Stern.png">D-Do not speak about Megumin l-like that! H-Her tiny tits are a part of her! And there's nothing wrong with that!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <condition role="target" character="megumin" stage="7" />
                <state img="#-Facade.png">I-It is quite hard not to be embarrassed by such a lewd game! Especially with your wild comments, Kazuma...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="jim" stage="0" saidMarker="Yunyun0a" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Erm, yes. I think so... We have travelers from another world to ours occasionally. They usually are... not very heroic however.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="jim" stage="0" saidMarker="Yunyun0b" />
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Y-You flatter me, Mr. Raynor! Nobody has ever acknowledged my powers as such before...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="114">
                <condition role="target" character="aaravi" stage="0" saidMarker="YunyunSharingIsCaring" />
                <state img="#-Crying.png" marker="yunAaravi_0b">H-Huh?! N‑No, please don't beat me up! How about I give you the potion as a gift instead? {small}You know, like a gift from a friend...?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="22">
                <condition role="target" character="megumin" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Happy.png" marker="Megumin_Winning1B">You see Megumin, despite being new to this strange game, my innate abilities will cause me to become victorious! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-1" id="27">
                <condition role="target" character="megumin" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-Facade.png" marker="Megumin_Winning2B">If your nudity brings me victory, then I shall reveal your small, bare body to all playing! If you are okay with that, of course!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2" id="28">
                <condition role="target" character="megumin" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-Facade.png" marker="Megumin_Winning3B">Thank goodness for all these stylish accessories we Crimson Demons wear. Huh, Megumin?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="meia" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png">A planet of only women? Do you find... that there is a stronger bond between the people there? Is it easier to connect and befriend?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="bernadetta" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Happy.png">For this we should pretend to be friends, of course. For a conversation between friends is easier than one between strangers. I think.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="chara_dreemurr" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png" oneShotId="72">Erm, Chara? That... is a... nice knife you have there? Um, very sharp!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="tomoko" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Why Tomoko, do you wish to be friends? I think we could experience many fun times together!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4" id="54">
                <condition role="target" character="megumin" stage="6" />
                <state img="#-Scared.png" marker="Megumin_Winning7B">I am not saying "no big deal" as a mockery of your small frame! Y-You, erm, must understand... &lt;i&gt;(Oh, Eris!)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="tomoko" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-Sad.png">I, erm, did not mean it like that, Tomoko! I just think... that, erm... Sorry.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="tomoko" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png">...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="tomoko" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png">But making friends &lt;i&gt;is&lt;/i&gt; easy! You just... O-Okay, maybe you have a point...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="jim" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Oh, if only you were the one to come to my world instead of Kazuma... I can imagine you would've treated me with much more respect, respect deserving of an Arch‑Mage...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" totalRounds="0" priority="20">
                <state img="#-Shy.png">I guess I'll stay... just because a Crimson Demon never quits! Uh, right?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_stripped">
            <case stage="0-7" id="38">
                <condition role="target" character="megumin" stage="1" />
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <state img="#-Happy.png">W-Well, thank you, Kazuma. That is very kind of you to say.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="39">
                <condition role="target" character="megumin" stage="2" />
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <state img="#-Stern.png">Kazuma! P-Please do not say such lewd things to Megumin in front of me! I don't understand what kind of relationship you have while alone but I am her rival! I should not know these things!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="40">
                <condition role="target" character="megumin" stage="3" />
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <state img="#-Excited.png">Well, I'm glad you think they are cute! There's a reason I chose to wear them!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="41">
                <condition role="target" character="megumin" stage="5" />
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <state img="#-Stern.png">W-What kind of games are you playing, Kazuma? I am not a fool, you know!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="43">
                <condition role="target" character="megumin" stage="4" />
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <state img="#-Scared.png">I-It isn't &lt;i&gt;my&lt;/i&gt; fault Megumin is so tiny! Wait, s-sorry M-Megumin!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="44">
                <condition role="target" character="megumin" stage="6" />
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <state img="#-Happy.png">I suppose I could. I'm unsure if it would fit my aesthetic, however; I do put a great deal of thought into what I wear. Which, um, matters less in a game like this where you take it off...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="45">
                <condition role="target" character="megumin" stage="7" />
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <state img="#-Facade.png">Y-You coy cad K-Kazuma! T-Tell him off Megumin!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="46">
                <condition role="target" character="megumin" stage="8" />
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <state img="#-Facade.png">I-If you are not complaining, why bring it up Kazuma? T-This is highly embarrassing and your questions aren't making it any easier...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="jim" stage="2" />
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <state img="#-Stern.png">It is not just physical differences Mr Raynor. I think you've experienced enough of Kazuma so far to understand what I mean. Erm, no offense, Kazuma?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-1" id="21">
                <condition role="target" character="megumin" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-Stern.png" marker="Megumin_Winning2C">Hm, are you sure your hands won't get cold? You should be careful, Megumin- I mean, another victory for me! Good!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-1" id="23">
                <condition role="target" character="megumin" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-Scared.png" marker="Megumin_Winning1C">Say what you will! However your signature quick wit will soon leave when you are struck d-defenseless... Oh Eris, this game is going to end in at least one of us getting naked, isn't it?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2" id="29">
                <condition role="target" character="megumin" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png" marker="Megumin_Winning3C">Though you seem to be running out of small things...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="bernadetta" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-Happy2.png">Of course, this fake relationship may blossom into something real, but that would just be a bonus. Yes? Please?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="chara_dreemurr" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-Facade.png">Erm, should I have complimented something different?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="tomoko" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-Sad.png">Oh. Okay then.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="tomoko" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-Scared.png">Erm, do you accept my apology, Tomoko? Tomoko, are you listening? Tomoko, please!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="tomoko" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-Crying.png">But the offer is still there!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="tomoko" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png">O-Okay, maybe you have a point...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="tomoko" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-Excited.png">Very well! Then I understand your reluctance to declare friendship. Instead this shall be a small step on the road to friendship!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="jim" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-Stern.png">It is not just physical differences Mr Raynor, do not tell Kazuma I said this but he can be... quite the lecher at times.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="8" oneShotId="3" priority="20">
                <condition count="1" gender="male" status="exposed" />
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">Do... they &lt;i&gt;all&lt;/i&gt; look like that? Why do I feel so... fuzzy?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition filter="tentacle_forfeit" role="target" />
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">O-oh... I-I know some people have found themselves at the mercy of slimes... but yours seems very friendly, ~name~. &lt;i&gt;Very.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I... wouldn't be opposed to joining in... it seems like a rather... l-loving experience. </state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">That's... one very intimate form of... m-masturbating. </state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">O-oh... that's... is it wrong that ~name~'s... tentacle... friend looks very intimate? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition filter="tandem" role="target" />
                <state img="#-Scared.png">O-oh... they're not just m-masturbating, are they? </state>
                <state img="#-Crying.png">N-no fair! ~Name~ doesn't just get to masturbate, they get to experience a unique and deep form of friendship!? </state>
                <state img="#-Scared.png">I-if I did that with... ~player~--! Could we be friends if-- &lt;i&gt;w-wait&lt;/i&gt;-- &lt;i&gt;h-hold up&lt;/i&gt;--</state>
                <state img="#-Crying.png">D-do we all get to pair off? I-I didn't know this! </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Facade.png">I won! I beat ~name~! Eh!? ~Name~'s going to beat his-- </state>
                <state img="#-Scared.png">Victory is mine! I, Yunyun, have bested ~name~, and will now be showered with-- &lt;i&gt;oh no&lt;/i&gt;! I-I was going to say praise, not--! </state>
                <state img="#-Posing2.png">~Name~ has been defeated, and must perform the ritual of staff recharge! I-- as Arch‑wizard, it would be wrong for me not to oversee such a rite!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-6">
                <state img="#-Posing.png">I-I have completely beaten, ~name~! His clothing has fallen away, and soon he will spill his vital essence to... me? ~Name~! </state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Recognize the skill of  I, Yunyun! Now, ~name~, as is tradition for this game, p-please show me your skill in return...</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">You thought it would be Megumin, but it was me, Yunyun, who defeated you, ~name~! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7 9">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">~Name~, your stamina has been exhausted! But still you keep fighting? How noble and brave, but not enough! Show me your finishing move! ...Just not in the face, okay!? </state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Behold ~name~'s final moments! I-I will spare him the indignity of defeat as long as he... he looks at me while he... </state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Yes, ~name~, look upon the face of your... are you okay? D-don't be sad, you can look at me while you-- j-just... um... p-please don't make a mess of me... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-Stern.png">~Name~! You have already beaten me, the least you can do is show me that you find me beautiful!</state>
                <state img="#-Sad.png">P-p-please forgive me, ~name~! B-but I require you to look at me! </state>
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">I-I have never seen a man brandish his staff so brazenly-- t-though it would be v-very rude for you not to show proper appreciation!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Facade.png">I-I think you played really well, but... I-I really want to see this so please... </state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">U-um... ~name~... n-no... No! I won! You have to say my name when you finish! </state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png">I am an arch‑wizard! T-to be initiated into my... m-my mysteries you should-- ~name~? P-pay attention!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-6">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">...I-if my body is pleasing to you, you could at least compliment it... b-by looking... </state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I am a woman of no small skill! I will have you know that I-I... I-I studied the black speech of eroticism--</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">~Name~... a-are you going to... look at me while you...?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-9">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I-I see! You demand a fair trade! Very well, ~name~, I will speak your name and you will speak mine as we look at each other...</state>
                <state img="#-Posing2.png">W-whatever you do, ~name~, j-just please respect my abilities as an Arch‑wizard!</state>
                <state img="#-Posing.png">A-as an arch‑wizard, I can &lt;i&gt;e-enchant&lt;/i&gt; your &lt;i&gt;Divine Rod...&lt;/i&gt; w-with my &lt;i&gt;Sacred Oils...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">... I'm enjoying this game too much! Sorry!</state>
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">Oh, oh no! ~Name~, a-are you in need of healing? I don't know magic like that-- I'm so sorry?</state>
                <state img="#-Sad.png">A-Ah? ~Name~, am I... s-should I pose better?</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">W-would it help, ~name~, if you could stare up my skirt? ...O-or if I took it off-- &lt;i&gt;Wait!&lt;/i&gt; I can still win! Please be patient, ~name~! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-6">
                <state img="#-Posing2.png">I-I apologize for staring, ~name~, but a-as... a-as a woman and wizard, I must... a-acquire knowledge... however I can! </state>
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">~Name~, would... it help if I told you I am already imagining a future house full of our children-- b-because you... f-filled my w-wo-wo-wo-- I-I can't say that yet!</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">You... are having a rather good time, aren't you? Oh! I am too! V-very good! It would be even better if you-- said my name when you finished... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-9">
                <state img="#-Facade.png">Oh... ~name~...</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">~Name~... I-I wish I could help you out with my hands-- at the &lt;i&gt;very &lt;/i&gt; least! I-I'd much rather use my body-- um--  which part? Any! T-there's so many that are-- a-at least acceptable I hope?</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">~Name~! I... request that you use my name... at least a little? Please?</state>
                <state img="#-Posing2.png">W-where are you planning to finish, ~name~? A-are you brave enough t-to challenge an arch‑wizard? I-it is a Crimson Demon mating ritual to--</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Shy.png">~Name~! It was for me, wasn't it...? It wasn't... oh... g-good job?</state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png">What does a girl have to do around here to... oh! It was over so fast! Not... y-you did great! I just meant... n-normally when I'm... but I'm clearly not a boy so... oh... now he's not listening... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-6">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">~Name~! If... okay... &lt;i&gt;when&lt;/i&gt; I lose... I-I will remember this moment!</state>
                <state img="#-Posing2.png">This will become a memory I cherish when... um... I-I am having time to myself. B-but not tonight! Tonight it will be I, Yunyun, who obtains victory! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-9">
                <state img="#-Sad.png">I-It's exceptionally disrespectful to dishonor an esteemed arch‑wizard by not even once uttering her name aloud!</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">I... you have spilled your vitas vitae on the floor... i-is anyone else going to...? N-no? O-of course I wouldn't, that's... </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="megumin" />
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <state img="#-Stern.png">D-Do not suggest such l-lewd things, Kazuma! &lt;i&gt;(She absolutely has though...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">~Name~--! I... I am sorry you lost so soon. C-Can I support you by watching?</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">Oh! ~Name~, do you want help? O-oh... you... probably could have used that earlier... I-I know, I can help you by-- w-watching at very least!</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I'm... ~name~! I will be watching you and cheering you on-- s-so, since I'm saying your name, you should find mine easy to say and think about-- it-it is a bit embarrassing but I don't think anyone's ever thought of me while--</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-6">
                <state img="#-Facade.png">D-do not despair, ~name~! Though you have been defeated by me, Yunyun, I am gracious in victory and will a-allow o-or even encourage you to look at me-- </state>
                <state img="#-Posing2.png">I did it! I did it! I beat ~name~, and now she-- she should look at the woman who beat her! I-I am a powerful arch‑wizard deserving of respect!</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">H-hooray, ~name~! You... you let me win, didn't you? That was so generous and sweet. I'll... I'll m-make sure to speak the Dark Speech of Eroticism to you! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-9">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I-If we were looking in a mirror it would be rather boring... s-so we should look at each other, ~name~. P-please? Can I at least look at you? </state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">I would... I will help you by looking visually appealing! I am a quick learner, as well, so if you show me what you like, after the game I could--</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="megumin" />
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <state img="#-Facade.png">M-Megumin's desires are none of your business Kazuma! Though her tastes are certainly... wild.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="36" priority="302">
                <condition role="target" character="sakura" saidMarker="cum" sayingMarker="wet" />
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">...That... having a man's... inside of you... t-that sounds lovely... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">G-good luck, ~name~? I-I'd offer to help but... w-would you really ask me to? </state>
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">I-I really beat ~name~! S-sorry, ~name~, I just can't believe it!</state>
                <state img="#-Posing.png">This is the power of an arch‑wizard! N-now... ~name~... y-you should humbly show me your biggest spell! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-6">
                <state img="#-Happy.png">H-how can you be helped, here! You are so vulnerable and... i-it feels good to feel powerful! </state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">H-how can... w-would you like to stare at me? Should I undress more-- ~name~, are you even... no...</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Are you... do you want me to use the Dark Speech of Eroticism on you, ~name~! I am told... b-by my experiences that I am... s-skilled! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-9">
                <state img="#-Facade.png">~Name~, it is permissible that we gaze upon each others soft curves and enjoy the pleasures of-- o-of the flesh in each others... u-um is that okay?</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">G-go, ~name~! Show us your Eternal Spiral of Climaxing! ...O-or just... w-what makes you feel good...</state>
                <state img="#-Posing.png">W-what do you do that makes people look at you, ~name~? I-I demand you tell me! I-I have nothing left to lose but my pride! </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">~Name~, do you want me to...? O-oh, yes, ~name~, you're so much more graceful using your fingers on yourself than I would be-- </state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">~Name~! You'd... I-I wish I could touch you-- w-with my fingers, or my tongue, even! J-just because it would make you feel good.</state>
                <state img="#-Sad.png">I think you're a beautiful girl, with accomplished skills, who deserves the respect of her friends and comrades-- u-um... I-I know that's not sexual but I th‑thought it was what you'd want to hear... </state>
                <state img="#-Sad.png">~Name~... even if you've lost the game, you've gained a friend in me, and because we've shared this intimate moment, doubtless to be friends for far more than tonight!</state>
                <state img="#-Posing.png">It's truly impressive, ~name~, that you are making I, Yunyun, quiver with anticipation, ~name~! </state>
                <state img="#-Scared.png">~Name~ displays a greater degree of vigor than even I do when... I'm alone... untouched... save for myself...  </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-6">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">Oh... ~name~... I wish I looked like... d-do you want me to copy you? Would t-that be weird or flattering?</state>
                <state img="#-Posing2.png">T-this moment is a treasure, everyone! Y-you should enjoy ~name~-- a-and anyone that comes after! </state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">~Name~ is just... so hard to look away from. I'm really quite jealous! </state>
                <state img="#-Sad.png">You are far more graceful than when I am... r-relaxing. </state>
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">I wonder... if I could make you make those noises...</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">Oh! You must have really needed to enjoy the company of others-- I would be happy to volunteer in the future, ~name~...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-9">
                <state img="#-Sad.png">I-I truly can show you nothing else, ~name~, so please enjoy me as I am! </state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I... ~name~, your own spell is driving my i-incantations to new heights!</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I... I would love to repeat this with you in private, ~name~! I would take you out on a date first-- t-too! </state>
                <state img="#-Excited.png">You are giving me something to try when I am next alone-- o-o-or perhaps we could do this together and be less lonely!</state>
                <state img="#-Excited.png">You do not need to fear, ~name~! I am an eager learner, in both matters of friendship, and love, and... w-whatever it is you're doing! </state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png">I.. I am quite familiar with my own fingers, which doubtless is a skill t-that would be useful to your adventuring party...</state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png">I-I will admit I have always been interested and curious... but... you are truly engaging my mind, soul, and body--!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="megumin" />
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <state img="#-Scared.png">D-Do not suggest such lewd things K-Kazuma!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">Are you done...? O-oh! You're really done! You didn't fake it or anything?</state>
                <state img="#-Excited.png">Congratulations, ~name~! I... that looked very very fun!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-6">
                <state img="#-Facade.png">I... think we've gotten to know each other m-much better! S-so, it wouldn't be at all inappropriate for us to continue s-spending time together, would it ?</state>
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">I wish to see more of you in the future, ~name~ A-ah! I said that too late! I was hoping to... c-can I start over? Can we be friends?</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">~Name~, I want you inside of my deepest places-- m-my heart! E-eh? N-no! I didn't mean-- b-but you could if it meant we could be everlasting friends! A-after all, don't very good friends become intimate? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-9">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I-I watched you, ~name~, so if you wanted to watch me, that is-- v-very equitable!</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">I... I am... I wish I could have such a beautiful spell as yours, ~name~... </state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">...F-forgive me for being selfish, but I wish you had called my name, ~name~? </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate_first">
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I... I lost! I lost by every measurement-- b-but... I'm the first one! That means everyone has to watch me! Great!</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">Oh... I was the first out... that's... eh? I can... stay if I--if I touch myself?! R-really? B-but you'll all be watching, &lt;i&gt;you'll all be watching me? Yunyun!? Of course!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate">
            <case stage="7">
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" />
                <state img="#-Scared.png">O-Of course not... R-Right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" sayingMarker="megumin_yunyun_yunyunLost" />
                <state img="#-Crying.png">W-Well, y-you can just l-look away! T-That would be for the best!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" sayingMarker="megumin_yunyun_yunyunLostAlt" />
                <state img="#-Scared.png">I-I do n-not need your help to k-know how to masturbate! I-I've done it many times before! W-Wait, I shouldn't say that!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <state img="#-Scared.png">W-Why do you imagine me doing such lewd things?! Could you not just fantasize about me saving you from monsters like a normal person?!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-Posing.png">I... have never been so intimate with others... please... all I ask is that you acknowledge me... if not respect-- </state>
                <state img="#-Posing2.png">I... h-have been quite aroused for some time. P-please forgive me if I am in a hurry to start, t-though I hope to impress ! </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="start_masturbating">
            <case stage="7">
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" sayingMarker="megumin_yunyun_yunyunLostStart" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png">D-Do not imply such things, Megumin! The other players could get odd ideas about our rivalship!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" sayingMarker="megumin_yunyun_yunyunLostStartAlt" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png">T-This game is rather unbecoming in general...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png">I-I suppose you will find out, Kazuma...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-Facade.png">I have been waiting to show you my skills! I will have you know that... that I often work solo!</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">I... I am quite skilled at a variety of techniques, practiced in solitude, but finally ready to be shared with the world! </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="masturbating">
            <case stage="8">
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" sayingMarker="megumin_yunyun_practice" />
                <state img="#-Sad.png">A-And if I have?! I've heard lewd noises coming from your bedroom, Megumin! Do not pretend you haven't done your fair share of practice!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" sayingMarker="megumin_yunyun_situation" />
                <state img="#-soft1.png">L-Let us just get this over with and go back to our normal rivalship...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" sayingMarker="megumin_yunyun_practiceOften" />
                <state img="#-Stern.png">O-Oh, quiet, you! Do not make this embarrassing situation any worse for the both of us!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" sayingMarker="megumin_yunyun_neverImagined" />
                <state img="#-soft0.png">Y-Yes, this is certainly not what rivals should be doing...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" priority="6">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="pamper_forfeit&gt;4" />
                <state img="#-soft0.png" marker="+pamper_forfeit">&lt;i&gt;Oh! Would you really... but my head is so heavy... are you sure you can hold my head there for that long...?&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-soft1.png" marker="+pamper_forfeit">&lt;i&gt;My eyes are like... wow... that's so flattering...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-soft2.png" marker="+pamper_forfeit">&lt;i&gt;You think I've... do you truly find me so wonderful? If you'd like to kiss my neck, I would rather enjoy...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-soft3.png" marker="+pamper_forfeit">&lt;i&gt;If... you're sure. Can your face support that, there's so much of me...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-soft2.png" marker="+pamper_forfeit">&lt;i&gt;Oh... you... you think I'm beautiful? And talented? &lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-soft3.png" marker="+pamper_forfeit">&lt;i&gt;Ah but... you've had such a hard day too... would you really rub my back? Are you certain? Really?&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-soft0.png" marker="+pamper_forfeit">&lt;i&gt;Oh but... you don't think I'm too dirty there? You... like the way I taste...? I'd certainly enjoy if you...&lt;/i&gt; </state>
                <state img="#-soft0.png" marker="+pamper_forfeit">&lt;i&gt;I've never had someone tell me they wanted me to mother their children... and stick around... are you quite certain? Yes... I would...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <condition count="2-5" status="masturbating" />
                <state img="#-soft2.png">...I-is anyone even looking at me? </state>
                <state img="#-soft3.png">Oh... I guess... i-it's a bit like sex-- i-if I move c-closer... </state>
                <state img="#-soft0.png">W-wow, y-you're almost getting to watch me... um... make love... </state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">I... c-can we ignore the no-touching rule? No...? Okay...</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">I-I'd be happy to do what-- w-whatever you-- </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <condition count="1" status="masturbating" />
                <state img="#-soft0.png" marker="+pamper_forfeit">Oh... you want to... on my face...? Well... okay... </state>
                <state img="#-soft1.png" marker="+pamper_forfeit">Y-you want to put your... i-in my butt...? R-really? Will that feel good for you? O-okay then... </state>
                <state img="#-soft2.png" marker="+pamper_forfeit">I-I can swallow it, if you'd like...? A-anyone?</state>
                <state img="#-soft0.png" marker="+pamper_forfeit">D-do you want to kiss my neck... &lt;i&gt;choke&lt;/i&gt;-- w-well, i-if you need to...</state>
                <state img="#-soft1.png" marker="+pamper_forfeit">You want me to... I-I'm not sure I want that, but if you need it...</state>
                <state img="#-soft2.png" marker="+pamper_forfeit">O-oh... you want me to... be shared? B-but... o-okay... </state>
                <state img="#-soft0.png" marker="+pamper_forfeit">Y-you want to... s-stretch m-me out... w-well... I-I guess I-I m-might like that...</state>
                <state img="#-soft1.png" marker="+pamper_forfeit">B-but it would be hard to make my skin turn pink... y-you'd really... o-okay...</state>
                <state img="#-soft2.png" marker="+pamper_forfeit">B-but... o-of course I've never d-done something like... s-so!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-Scared.png">I'm s-sorry! T-This line s-shouldn't be p-playing! P-Please forgive me!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="heavy_masturbating">
            <case stage="8">
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" sayingMarker="megumin_yunyun_gettingIntoIt" />
                <state img="#-heavy0.png">Q-Quiet Megumin! J-Just let me... finish...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-heavy0.png">&lt;i&gt;Please make me happy...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-heavy1.png">&lt;i&gt;Respect me...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-heavy3.png">&lt;i&gt;Oh... please... kiss me, bring me flowers and chocolate... and captive monsters for XP...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-heavy0.png">&lt;i&gt;Oh... oh... you can finish wherever you like...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-heavy2.png">&lt;i&gt;You stayed the night!? I-I... A-ah!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-heavy1.png">&lt;i&gt;Y-you really mean it? Me? You want&lt;/i&gt; me?</state>
                <state img="#-heavy2.png">&lt;i&gt;Please... please... y-you don't have to give me so much attention... i-if it makes you happy, don't stop...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-heavy0.png">&lt;i&gt;Oh... that massage feels so good... and you're taking care of dinner...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-heavy3.png">&lt;i&gt;Please, please, keep respecting me--&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-heavy1.png">&lt;i&gt;O-oh... y-you want to flood my womb...? Y-Yes... p-please&lt;/i&gt;!</state>
                <state img="#-heavy2.png">I-I &lt;i&gt;would&lt;/i&gt; like another pillow...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy0.png">&lt;i&gt;Y-yes... that does feel quite good... thank you for being so considerate...!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-heavy2.png">&lt;i&gt;I-I l-love you too!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finishing_masturbating">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-finish.png">~Player~!</state>
                <state img="#-finish.png">N-notice me! </state>
                <state img="#-finish.png">A-ah...!</state>
                <state img="#-finish.png">&lt;i&gt;E-explosions!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-Happy.png">I'm embarrassed... but it's a nice kind of embarrassing. Like getting a r-random hug in public, or s-somebody telling you you've done really good! D-Does that make sense?!</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Nobody has ever seen me like this before! It's, um, not as bad as I thought it might be...</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Even if this is rather e-embarrassing... I-I'm glad it's you here, ~player~! And I-I'm really happy I met y-you all!</state>
                <state img="#-Sad.png">Well, I've lost duels to Megumin quite a bit. So I'm kind of used to the feeling of losing.</state>
                <state img="#-Happy2.png">We all became friends from this game, correct? We could play again sometime... if you all like...</state>
                <state img="#-Excited.png">Let it be known! That I, Yunyun, tried my hardest!</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">What an odd game. Enjoyable... but odd.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="after_masturbating">
            <case stage="9" oneShotId="34">
                <state img="#-finish.png">Oh... Erm, wow...</state>
                <state img="#-finish.png">Wait... What happened? I got a little... distracted.</state>
                <state img="#-finish.png">I really hope I didn't say all of that aloud...</state>
                <state img="#-finish.png">W-We're all friends now, y-yes?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_victory">
            <case stage="1-7">
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" />
                <state img="#-Scared.png">W-Wait, practice game?! N-No! W-When did we decide on that?!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" />
                <state img="#-Posing.png">Megumin, I am still fully clothed! Despite your claims of practice game, I shall count this as an absolute victory for me, Yunyun! Fufufu!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Excited.png">Wait, I won? I won! Wait, till I tell Megumin about this! Hehe!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-Sad.png">What, the game is over? Already?! But I want to keep playing with you guys!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_defeat">
            <case stage="9">
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" stage="0-6" />
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" />
                <state img="#-Stern.png">I-If you are not careful, Kazuma, you will have two Crimson Demons casting powerful magics at you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" sayingMarker="megumin_yunyun_callItADraw" />
                <state img="#-Happy2.png">I guess we could play again to decide a real winner? If ~player~ and the rest are up for it...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" />
                <state img="#-Scared.png">N-Next time? Y-You're not implying we will play such a game again, are you?!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Y-You guys want to hang out after this game? M-Maybe with clothes? U-Unless you want to visit a bathhouse together!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="global">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="adrien" sayingMarker="yunyun_post" />
                <state img="#-Stern.png" marker="noir_PostR">I'm not annoying, ~name~! And you should raise your summon, better! There's nothing worse than a rude summon.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

    </behaviour>
</opponent>
