<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>

<!--This file was machine generated using the Character Editor v5.9 at 2:01:26 AM on July 02, 2020. Do not edit this file directly unless you know what you're doing.-->
<opponent>
    <version>v5.9</version>
    <first>YunYun</first>
    <last>of the Crimson Demons</last>
    <label>YunYun</label>
    <gender>female</gender>
    <size>large</size>
    <timer>15</timer>
    <intelligence>average</intelligence>

    <tags>
        <tag>brunette</tag>
        <tag>medium_hair</tag>
        <tag>red_eyes</tag>
        <tag>fair-skinned</tag>
        <tag>trimmed</tag>
        <tag>pubic_hair</tag>
        <tag>large_breasts</tag>
        <tag>no_bra</tag>
        <tag>scantily-clad</tag>
        <tag from="0" to="2">thigh_highs</tag>
        <tag>cheerful</tag>
        <tag>ditzy</tag>
        <tag>lonely</tag>
        <tag>moe</tag>
        <tag>nerdy</tag>
        <tag>shy</tag>
        <tag>submissive</tag>
        <tag>bisexual</tag>
        <tag>single</tag>
        <tag>fantasy</tag>
        <tag>anime</tag>
        <tag>adventurer</tag>
        <tag>witch</tag>
        <tag>magic</tag>
        <tag>hero</tag>
        <tag>konosuba</tag>
    </tags>


    <wardrobe>
        <clothing name="panties" generic="underwear" position="lower" type="important" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="top" generic="shirt" position="upper" type="important" />
        <clothing name="skirt" position="lower" type="major" />
        <clothing name="socks" generic="socks" position="feet" type="extra" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="boots" generic="shoes" position="feet" type="extra" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="tie" position="neck" type="extra" />
        <clothing name="belt" position="waist" type="extra" />
    </wardrobe>


    <behaviour>
        <trigger id="selected">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-Posing.png">... My name is YunYun! An arch-wizard and... um, it's nice to meet you all! </state>
                <state img="#-Posing2.png">... My name is YunYun! An arch-wizard and future Chief to the entirety of the Crimson Demons! Be careful for... &lt;i&gt;(Eris, this introduction is so embarrassing!!)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_selected">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="megumin" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png" marker="megumin_greeting">Megumin! You finally arrived! Uh, not that I knew you were coming or anything...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_start">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" />
                <state img="#-Posing2.png" marker="meguminkazuma_intro">Ah, Kazuma, I'm sorry to interrupt your time with Megumin. But it is I, YunYun! Fate has brought Megumin and I together once again!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" priority="100">
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" />
                <state img="#-Posing2.png" marker="megumin_intro">My lifelong rival Megumin! How odd to see you here! I guess since we're both here we might as well duel! Uh, please!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <state img="#-Shocked.png" marker="kazuma_intro">Kazuma! W-Where is Megumin? S-She told me to come here...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Uh, wait! Has anyone seen a mage named Megumin? She's my rival! And she invited me here for a duel!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="swap_cards">
            <case stage="0" totalRounds="0" priority="200">
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" />
                <state img="#-Excited.png" marker="megumin_intro2">I challenge you to, um, whatever game we're playing!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" totalRounds="0" priority="200">
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" />
                <condition role="other" character="kazuma" />
                <state img="#-Excited.png" marker="meguminkazuma_intro2">I, um, c-challenge you to whatever game we're playing! And Kazuma, you will watch, to record my victory once and for all!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" totalRounds="0">
                <state img="#-Shy.png">... I guess since I'm here I'll play... &lt;i&gt;(And hopefully make friends!)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Shy.png">C-can we stop playing for just a second and all talk about our ambitions? No? O-okay!</state>
                <state img="#-Scared.png">I've got a bad feeling about these ~cards~ cards... I've also got a bad feeling in general... </state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">C-can I have ~cards~ new cards? Sorry for being a nuisance!</state>
                <state img="#-Happy2.png">I'll swap these ~cards~ cards... um, if I'm allowed to! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-Facade.png">I'm getting used to this! ~cards~ new cards dealer! W-wait, I didn't mean to sound pushy!</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Can I get ~cards~  new cards? You'll give me them? Really?</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Oh, um, can I get ~cards~ cards? Wait, I'll keep these ones if you want me to! </state>
                <state img="#-Happy2.png">&lt;i&gt;(If I ask to swap these ~cards~ cards, maybe people will think I'm smart!)&lt;/I&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-Excited.png">I'd like ~cards~ cards please. You can take your time dealer! No need to rush! I'm enjoying spending time with everyone and I want this game to last!</state>
                <state img="#-Sad.png">Hey, can I get ~cards~ cards? And, um, how are you doing today dealer? Um, do you want to hang out after this game? No? Maybe some other time?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="good_hand">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <condition count="0" character="megumin" />
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="1">If you see my rival Megumin, please tell her that I did good this hand!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Posing.png">Careful! I've played countless games of poker by myself. And won &lt;i&gt;every time!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-Happy2.png">I guess I can use these cards... T-this hand is good, r-right?</state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png">An experienced Crimson Demon like me was destined to get these cards! Uh, wait, that was embarrassing to say! Forget that!</state>
                <state img="#-Stern.png">Let us make a little wager! If I win this hand, you all have to hang out with me after the game!</state>
                <state img="#-Excited.png">Wait, this hand is good! I'm not going to lose! I'm going to win! Yay!</state>
                <state img="#-Posing2.png">I got a good hand? Wait, I'm not surprised! I was o-one of the first of my class to g-graduate, after all!</state>
                <state img="#-Sad.png">If I win can I earn a Skill-Up potion? No? T-That's fine... I probably didn't deserve one anyway...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-Excited.png">I got a good hand! I got a good hand! This game is so fun!</state>
                <state img="#-Excited.png">This is a really lucky hand! Thanks so much dealer!</state>
                <state img="#-Posing2.png">Hehe, what a hand! A Crimson Demon never loses! Uh, except for those times I lost before. Forget about those please!</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Wow, dealer! This hand is the nicest thing anyone has ever done for me!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="okay_hand">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <condition role="self" hasHand="One Pair" />
                <state img="#-Sad.png" oneShotId="3">Well, at least I have a pair! Of cards that is. I wish I knew somebody who was like me...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Facade.png">I'm, uh, the future chief to the Crimson Demon Clan! That means you should r-respect me! P-please!</state>
                <state img="#-Sad.png">Please let this hand win! &lt;i&gt;(I really need the self-esteem boost right now!)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-Sad.png">This is an average hand... average like me I guess...</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">This hand is good enough... I'll be okay as long as I don't lose!</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">I've always wanted to play a game of strip poker with others! Well, I didn't imagine the strip or the poker part...</state>
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">I hope you haven't heard any rumors about me... I promise, whatever they are, they are untrue! Unless they are nice ones!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Oh... um, well I don't know what to even make of this hand. That's kind of exciting, r-right?</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">It'd be nice if we could &lt;i&gt;all&lt;/i&gt; win...</state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png">I'll win even with these cards! J-Just watch! But not too i-intently!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="bad_hand">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Facade.png">This game isn't some kind of trick to get me &lt;i&gt;n-naked, &lt;/i&gt; right? Wait! I'm sorry for questioning you all! Don't hate me!</state>
                <state img="#-Scared.png">I don't deserve this awful hand! Why is everything so cruel?!</state>
                <state img="#-Scared.png">I hate this game! I mean not the game! It's just the c-cards! I mean, &lt;i&gt;sorry!</state>
                <state img="#-Stern.png">I'm a Crimson Demon! I should be doing better than this!</state>
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">What is wrong with me? Why do I keep losing? I'm an arch-wizard, I should be doing better than this!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Aw, I'll lose for sure with this terrible hand! But I'll get you all next time so watch out!</state>
                <state img="#-Happy2.png">T-thanks for playing with me! Even if I lose this hand, I'm still having fun!</state>
                <state img="#-Scared.png">Everytime I lose, I just get more determined to win! And everytime I l-lose, um, I also get a bit more n-naked!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="hand">
            <case stage="0" id="5" totalRounds="0">
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" />
                <state img="#-Facade.png">I'll win and finally defeat you, Megumin! Once... I, uh, figure out how to play!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="jessie" sayingMarker="MeguminYunyunPair" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png" oneShotId="17" marker="MeguminYunyunPair_response">Well, erm, yes. Megumin and I are intertwined by fate and were born to be rivals. Though, erm, this game may be a bit awkward...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" totalRounds="0" priority="100">
                <state img="#-Scared.png">Wait, she's not here?! I'm s-sure she'll arrive eventually! She wouldn't trick me like this, right?! I'll just, uh, keep playing for now!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" id="9">
                <condition role="other" character="tomoko" />
                <state img="#-Happy.png">&lt;i&gt;(This girl looks rather lonely! If anybody needs a friend... It must be her!)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" id="30">
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" />
                <state img="#-Facade.png" oneShotId="13" marker="megumin_adventuring">So, erm, how is the adventuring with Kazuma and those others going? My adventuring has been... um, great! Though I'd change a few things...</state>
                <state img="#-Stern.png" oneShotId="14" marker="megumin_crimsondemonword">You have been spreading the word of the Crimson Demon gang right? I hope you haven't just been messing around with your new friends!</state>
                <state img="#-Shocked.png" oneShotId="15" marker="megumin_embarrassingbirthmark">Megumin, you do understand that in a game like this everyone may see your... embarrassing birthmark, right?</state>
                <state img="#-Happy2.png" oneShotId="16" marker="megumin_explosionprogression">If you wish Megumin, we may have a proper duel after this game! I am quite interested to see how you have progressed with explosion magic.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" id="4" priority="0">
                <condition filter="enf" status="alive" role="opp" var="enfname" />
                <state img="#-Sad.png" oneShotId="2" set-intelligence="bad">&lt;i&gt;(~enfname~ seems really embarrassed... I feel so sorry for her! Do you think anyone would notice if I tried throw this hand for her?)</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" id="11" priority="0">
                <condition filter="taken" status="alive" role="opp" var="romname" />
                <state img="#-Facade.png" oneShotId="4" set-intelligence="bad">Is it true you are in a romantic relationship, ~romname~? That must be... wonderful... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" id="12" priority="0">
                <condition filter="pokemon" status="alive" role="opp" />
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="5" set-intelligence="bad">I'd quite like a Pokémon. It'd be nice to have someone to be unconditionally your friend...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" id="13" priority="0">
                <condition filter="lonely" status="alive" role="opp" var="lonname" />
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="6" set-intelligence="bad">You seem quite lonely, ~lonname~. I could become your friend if you wish? P-Please?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" id="14" priority="0">
                <condition filter="perverted" status="alive" role="opp" var="meanname" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png" oneShotId="7" set-intelligence="bad">Whilst you may be quite vulgar, ~meanname~... At least you are talking me to me...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" id="16" priority="0">
                <condition filter="scantily-clad" status="alive" role="opp" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png" oneShotId="9" set-intelligence="bad">I see you are also wearing a "friend-making" outfit. I'm a little unsure if mine needs to be skimpier as it's not worked so far...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" id="17" priority="0">
                <condition filter="nerdy" status="alive" role="opp" var="nerdname" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png" oneShotId="10" set-intelligence="bad">Are you one of those NEETs, ~nerdname~? Whilst I don't normally associate with that type I would be happy to introduce you to the world of adventures! And maybe you could show me a video game or two...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" id="18" priority="0">
                <condition filter="adventurer" status="alive" role="opp" var="adname" />
                <alternative>
                    <condition count="-0" filter="konosuba" role="opp" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-Excited.png" oneShotId="11" set-intelligence="bad">A fellow adventurer? If you ever need help, I am available! I will even work for free!</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="12">What types of adventures have you gone on, ~adname~? We could exchange stories of our travels and... bond over them.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state>This line can cover any of the Good/Okay/Bad hand cases if it has a higher priority</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state>This line can cover any of the Good/Okay/Bad hand cases if it has a higher priority</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip">
            <case stage="0" id="31">
                <condition role="other" character="emi" sayingMarker="emi_yunyun_name" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png" marker="emi_yunyun_name_response">Erm, I come from the Crimson Demon clan and this is a perfectly normal name there. You can, um, call me Yun for short if it's too weird for you!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="32">
                <condition role="other" character="emi" sayingMarker="emi_yunyun_school" />
                <state img="#-Facade.png" marker="emi_yunyun_school_response">I'm not a student! I'm an adventurer and quester! Um, this outfit was given to me by a friend. They told me it'd help me make friends... But it's a little revealing!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="jessie" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png">I am not some kind of magician who will preform cheap tricks on demand... I am a dignified arch-mage who will bring glory to the Crimson Demon clan! Though if you ask nicely, I could create some pretty sparkles. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="jura" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Erm, while I may seem a little nervous; the truth is that I am a confident and powerful mage from the Crimson Demon clan. Who has never played a strip game before...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="revy" />
                <state img="#-Stern.png">It's the Crimson Demon clan! And I don't see how the size of my chest would assist me with my confidence.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="revy" />
                <state img="#-Stern.png">It's the Crimson Demon clan! And I don't see how the size of my chest would assist me with my confidence.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="meia" />
                <state img="#-Excited.png">Oh! Of course Meia, thank you for asking! The Crimson Demon clan is an elite group of arch-mages who protect the land from destruction!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" totalRounds="0">
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">Wait, I've got to do &lt;i&gt;what&lt;/i&gt; for losing?! No, wait, I'll strip! Just don't hate me!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_winning">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">Well, I guess it is unfair if I never lose...</state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png">I feel really left out if you are all stripping and I'm not!</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Oh, I don't want to be the only one clothed! Or, I mean, I do but...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-6">
                <state img="#-Happy.png">I, um, you guys are &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; nice so I'm fine with stripping...</state>
                <state img="#-Excited.png">Oh, this game is getting really really close! It's so exciting!</state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png">This is e-embarrassing but I wouldn't play this game if I didn't want to! Not that I &lt;i&gt;want&lt;/i&gt; to strip!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_normal">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">I guess it's my turn... um, just don't stare! Or, um, you can if you want!</state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png">P-Please don't laugh! I promise you, there's nothing funny about me! Wait, I mean, I'm hilarious, okay?!</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Oh, um, it's only a small thing I have to remove, right? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-6">
                <state img="#-Scared.png">Oh, um... if you are all seeing me like, uh, &lt;i&gt;this&lt;/i&gt;. Then we are automatically friends, right?</state>
                <state img="#-Excited.png">You know... even if you don't think of me as a friend. I see all of you as my friends! And that's all that matters!</state>
                <state img="#-Crying.png">I-I'm still going to win! I-I'm just going to be a little more n-naked as I do so!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_losing">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Facade.png">I just want to remind you all that I could leave if I wanted to! And that means you should respect my resolve and like me for staying!</state>
                <state img="#-Stern.png">If anyone laughs, I'll make you regret it! I know magic! Believe me!</state>
                <state img="#-Crying.png">I keep losing! Are you guys bullying me?!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-6">
                <state img="#-Facade.png">Even if I'm losing badly... T-thank you for letting me p-play with you all!</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Well, um, that's a-another loss...</state>
                <state img="#-Scared.png">If I didn't know any better I'd say this game was just a ploy to see me naked! But you wouldn't do that, right? Right?!</state>
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">I might be constantly losing, but I still deserve respect! Even just a tiny tiny amount, please!</state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png">D-Don't worry about making me feel bad... I'm used to l-losing...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripping">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" />
                <condition role="self" notSaidMarker="Megumin_Winning1C" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png" marker="Megumin_StripLosing1B">I just realised this game is going to end with at least one of us getting completely, um, naked...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="meia" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png">We live in the Crimson Demon Village, where we are taught our magics from a young age, making us the most potent magical users! As long as we spend our points &lt;i&gt;wisely&lt;/i&gt;..</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-Strip.png">I wear this outfit because I was told it'd help me make friends... It's working, right?</state>
                <state img="#-Strip.png">These clothes are a little... embarrassing. But a trustworthy source told me they'd help make friends! It doesn't seem to have happened yet...</state>
                <state img="#-Strip.png">Don't judge me for my clothes! This is my friend-making outfit! My friend D-Dust told me it'd help!</state>
                <state img="#-Strip.png">I was told that this outfit would help me make friends? It's not, um, working. It's just really embarrassing me...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-Strip.png">Erm, well... I guess even a Crimson Demon can't win everytime... &lt;i&gt;(Even if Megumin wins every duel we have...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-Strip.png">I'm not lonely! I am just really really self-sufficient!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-Strip.png">I'll take off my boots and get comfortable, I guess. Or at least &lt;i&gt;try&lt;/i&gt; and get comfortable... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-Strip.png">For the first time I'm glad that as a Crimson Demon I have to wear all these strange accessories... otherwise I'd already have lost...</state>
                <state img="#-Strip.png">Eek! Uh, that's how an ordinary person would react to losing, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-Strip.png">I-I'm not insecure! About my body, that is...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-Strip.png">You can do this YunYun... you are a Crimson Demon!</state>
                <state img="#-Strip.png">Crimson Demons should care little about nudity! But, um, they do care about losing...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-Strip.png">O-oh, Eris! T-This is all I have l-left! Er, uh, don't laugh at me! I-I'll do it!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripped">
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="megumin" />
                <condition role="self" notSaidMarker="Megumin_Winning1C" />
                <state img="#-Crying.png" marker="Megumin_StripLosing1C">W-Well, it won't be me! N-Not that I want &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; to get naked Megumin! W-Why don't we play a game of chess instead?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-Facade.png">I'm s-sorry for being so w-weird... I'm sure you'd rather play with a different member of the  Crimson Demons...</state>
                <state img="#-Sad.png">There's my belt. It... uh, doesn't hold anything up. So it's mostly useless. &lt;i&gt;(Like me...)</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-Excited.png">T-this is so e-embarrassing! B-but even if my chances of winning may be virtually nothing... as long as they aren't &lt;i&gt;absolutely&lt;/i&gt; nothing, I'll never give up! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">The tie is just a fashion accessory! Losing it won't stop me from winning! It'll just make me one step closer to losing! Wait, that's bad!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-Sad.png">I hope I get better cards next round... I deserve that at least...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">This game kind of reminds me of my many duels with Megumin... And it's just as embarrassing!</state>
                <state img="#-Posing2.png">Hmph, okay! I'm done losing now! Promise! You better watch out because I'm going to use all the training I've had as a Crimson Demon!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-Shy.png">I-I thought these p-panties were c-cute okay! They a-are, right?</state>
                <state img="#-Excited.png">Y-You can stare... But only if you consider me a friend! And if you look, you're automatically a friend!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-Sad.png">A-are these okay? I know they are p-probably t-too big...</state>
                <state img="#-Crying.png">You might think this is embarrassing! But for someone like me who is experienced in the art of humiliation, it's just another day! Wait, that's a bad thing!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_human_must_strip">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">Oh... ~player~ lost? That's good. Really good. Not because I want to see him naked! Just because, uh, uh... Nevermind!</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">&lt;i&gt;(I want everyone to be my friend... but I really really want ~player~ to be my friend for some reason!)</state>
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">Why does ~player~ make me feel weird? Wait, did I say that aloud?! &lt;i&gt;So embarrassing... </state>
                <state img="#-Scared.png">You know... you don't talk much, ~player~. I've always thought my type of guy would be quiet and reserved... W-wait, w-why am I telling you this?!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-9">
                <state img="#-Happy.png">T-Thanks for spending time with me, ~player~... you're making this game really fun...</state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png">H-Hey, ~player~? Is it okay if I tell everyone you're my friend? Not in a weird way! Promise!</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">Oh... you've got to strip ~player~. I-Is it okay if I watch?!</state>
                <state img="#-Happy2.png">Even though you don't talk to me,  ~player~, that's still nicer than how most people treat me!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_strip">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Sad.png">Even if you lose, all that matters is that you tried! Why does nobody ever tell me that?</state>
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">... You've got to strip, right? That was a question, not a demand! Sorry!</state>
                <state img="#-Crying.png">I, um, this game is kind of lewd... isn't it? Not that I care! I'm very calm and comfortable, okay?!</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Wait, I didn't lose?! That's a nice feeling...</state>
                <state img="#-Sad.png">I know I should be happy I won... But I'm a little sad someone else lost...</state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png">I know I'm supposed to give a victory speech like most other Crimson Demons would... but that'd be so embarrassing...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">If you don't want to strip, I won't make you! I... I'd like it if you did though! Wait, not for perverted reasons! P-Promise!</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Y-You can strip too! If we're both embarrassed that means we can understand each other better, right?!</state>
                <state img="#-Happy2.png">Even if you lost, I really hope you're still enjoying yourself, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-Scared.png">YunYun just WonWon! Wait, that was the worst thing I ever said!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I-I would rather enjoy it if you continued to undress, but only because it would give us an experience to bond over, much like if we... became intimate. </state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">If you wish to undress faster, you would be able to more deeply understand my embarrassement... which would bring us closer!</state>
                <state img="#-Happy2.png">~Name~, are you... do you enjoy what I'm doing to myself? I hope you find it pleasing... </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_human_must_strip">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Happy2.png">&lt;i&gt;(I want everyone to be my friend... but I really really want ~player~ to be my friend for some reason!)</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">Oh... ~player~ lost? That's good. Really good. Not because I want to see her naked! Just because, uh, uh... Nevermind!</state>
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">Why does ~player~ make me feel weird? Wait, did I say that aloud?! &lt;i&gt;So embarrassing...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-9">
                <state img="#-Happy.png">T-Thanks for spending time with me, ~player~... you're making this game really fun...</state>
                <state img="#-Scared.png">H-Hey, ~player~? Is it okay if I tell everyone you're my friend? Not in a weird way! Promise!</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">Oh... you've got to strip, ~player~. I-Is it okay if I watch?!</state>
                <state img="#-Happy2.png">Even though you don't talk to me,  ~player~, that's still nicer than how most people treat me!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_strip">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">I, um, this game is kind of lewd... isn't it? Not that I care! I'm very calm and comfortable, okay?!</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">... You've got to strip, right? That was a question, not a demand! Sorry!</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Even if you lose, all that matters is that you tried! Why does nobody ever tell me that?</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Wait, I didn't lose?! That's a nice feeling...</state>
                <state img="#-Sad.png">I know I should be happy I won... But I'm a little sad someone else lost...</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">I know I'm supposed to give a victory speech like most other Crimson Demons would... but that'd be so embarrassing...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-Shy.png">I-if you want, you can certainly take off more... after all, you can already see me and my...</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">I hope you are still enjoying yourself! I know I am... e-enjoying myself-- b-because I'm... n-not because you lost... p-please forgive me!</state>
                <state img="#-Excited.png">We are closer than ever to bonding-- w-what other conclusion could you come to...? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-Scared.png">You know, winning this game feels really good! Wait, I'm sorry for boasting! I'm humble!</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Y-You can strip too! If we're both embarrassed that means we can understand each other better, right?!</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Even if you lost, I really hope you're still enjoying yourself, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-Scared.png">YunYun just WonWon! Wait, that was the worst thing I ever said!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Excited.png">I've always wanted to play a game like this with friends. It's okay if I pretend we're all friends, right?!</state>
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">This is my first time playing a game like this... does it always go so... slow?</state>
                <state img="#-Posing.png">You should all know that I'm the Greatest Genius of the Crimson Magic Clan! Or, um, the s-second Greatest G-Genius...</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">You know, I'm not dumb okay! I know when people are lying to me! I just... like to pretend they aren't...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-Happy2.png">Oh, I see! You're trying to... present yourself as a gentleman! I understand you're doing this because you're treating me like a lady... right?</state>
                <state img="#-Excited.png">I am enjoying the game more the longer it goes... so don't speed up, ~name~, it just means more time together!</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">You're very clever, ~name~, using your ~clothing~ to draw out the game... quite brilliant. Very smart. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-Happy2.png">It might not be much but it's the thought that counts! Thanks for stripping for us! Please like me!</state>
                <state img="#-Excited.png">Keep taking off small things like that! The longer this game lasts the better!</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">That's a really smart move, ~name~! I guess you've got to use all the advantages you have!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Sad.png">That's all? Wait, I'm not complaining! Sorry!</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Um, I'll keep playing if you all still want me here...</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">I had a fun idea for a game! Everytime you lose, you must give the winner a compliment. Why don't we start playing now?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-Facade.png">Can we keep playing now? Please! I'm having fun!</state>
                <state img="#-Scared.png">You know... I don't often get to play games like these with other people. I've always wanted to and I just really want to say- Wait, what? Next hand? Already?!</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Oh. You've still got a lot left, ~name~? Heh, you're... um... making me kind of nervous!</state>
                <state img="#-Sad.png">You're taking that off just now? Oh no! I'm totally going to lose!</state>
                <state img="#-Sad.png">Please strip more off! I could really use a win!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-Facade.png">We can keep going, right? I'm having an &lt;i&gt;excellent&lt;/i&gt; time. I-I can't imagine this going any better!</state>
                <state img="#-Scared.png">I-if I might, I want to say that I rather enjoyed this experience, and even though it's humiliating perhaps-- eh? N-nobody was listening, were they?</state>
                <state img="#-Sad.png">You're... not really giving me a lot to look at, ~name~... but I suppose th-that's what happens when you lose... </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Shy.png">I've always wanted to play a game like this with friends. It's okay if I pretend we're all friends, right?!</state>
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">This is my first time playing a game like this... does it always go so... slow?</state>
                <state img="#-Posing2.png">You should all know that I'm the Greatest Genius of the Crimson Magic Clan! Or, um, the s-second Greatest G-Genius...</state>
                <state img="#-Sad.png">You know, I'm not dumb okay! I know when people are lying to me! I just... like to pretend they aren't...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-Excited.png">Y-you must really like me if you want me to keep watching you... s-since it's just your ~clothing~. </state>
                <state img="#-Happy2.png">You're really trying to show off, aren't you, ~name~? T-that's what Kazuma c-calls a strip tease, r-right?</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">W-wow! I can't believe you're working so hard... you must be... r-really enjoying watching me like this, aren't you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-Excited.png">It might not be much but it's the thought that counts! Thanks for stripping for us! Please like me!</state>
                <state img="#-Happy2.png">Keep taking off small things like that! The longer this game lasts the better!</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">That's a really smart move, ~name~! I guess you've got to use all the advantages you have!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="0-9" id="3">
                <condition status="crotch_visible" role="target" />
                <state img="#-Crying.png">W-Wait, why didn't you take that off first? I'm so confused!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Facade.png">That's all? Wait, I'm not complaining! Sorry!</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Um, I'll keep playing if you all still want me here...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-Excited.png">Can we keep playing now? Please! I'm having fun!</state>
                <state img="#-Scared.png">You know... I don't often get to play games like these with other people. I've always wanted to and I just really want to say- Wait, what? Next hand? Already?!</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Oh. You've still got a lot left, ~name~? Heh, you're... um... making me kind of nervous!</state>
                <state img="#-Sad.png">You're taking that off just now? Oh no! I'm totally going to lose!</state>
                <state img="#-Sad.png">Please strip more off! I could really use a win!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-Excited.png">A-after this, I'd be happy to go shopping for ~clothing~ with you, ~name~! T-that's what friends do, right?</state>
                <state img="#-Scared.png">I... I lost very badly, didn't I? Y-you could always beat me if we played together! </state>
                <state img="#-Sad.png">I-it's really not &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; embarrassing! I'm hardly ashamed at all-- a-and I know a lot about-- </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Happy2.png">Are you really okay with &lt;i&gt;stripping&lt;/i&gt; in front of someone like me? Really?! T-Thanks so much!</state>
                <state img="#-Sad.png">If it's really embarrassing, you can just pretend I'm not here... I'm used to it.</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">This game is heating up, huh? Can you please agree with me?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-Shy.png">I think I've seen ~clothing~ like that... but I've never seen someone take it off... until now. </state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png">Is... this at all embarrassing for you, I think you're rather shameless-- s-so you shouldn't have shame and &lt;i&gt;should&lt;/i&gt; take it off!</state>
                <state img="#-Excited.png">Oh... ~name~, i-is your ~clothing~ magical? Or just you... i-is that flirting? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Well, ~name~, you're running out of small items. Right? Or do you have a bunch hidden?!</state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png">This isn't too embarrassing for you, right? I mean, it's barely anything... Wait, I'm not being condescending!</state>
                <state img="#-Excited.png">The more time we all get to spend together the better!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_minor">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Shy.png">You're enjoying this game, right? I hope I'm not ruining it...</state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png">Wow. This game is making me &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; hungry! Anyone else want to go for food afterwards? Just, you know, for practical reasons. &lt;i&gt;I'll pay! </state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">Well, at least we all see &lt;i&gt;something&lt;/i&gt;. Um, not that I'm lewd! I'm not!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-Happy.png">W-wow... you... you're really good looking-- </state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">I really appreciate that we're spending-- ~Name~? W-wait, don't deal yet--</state>
                <state img="#-Excited.png">I... a man took off his ~clothing~, and I was already naked! I-I'm so close to having a new friend... I can &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; feel it. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-Happy.png">&lt;i&gt;(Should I try and distract the dealer so we can play for longer? Wait, they are already dealing cards!)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Can we just take a second just to appreciate the time we spend together before we deal the next hand?</state>
                <state img="#-Excited.png">Who would've known playing a game with so many other people would've been this fun? I mean, I fantasized it would be. But this is even better than my daydreams!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Excited.png">Are you really okay with &lt;i&gt;stripping&lt;/i&gt; in front of someone like me? Really?! T-Thanks so much!</state>
                <state img="#-Sad.png">If it's really embarrassing you can just pretend I'm not here... I'm used to it.</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">This game is heating up, huh? Can you please agree with me?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-Shy.png">~Name~... I'm glad ~clothing.ifPlural(those aren't magical ~clothing|that isn't a magical ~clothing~)~-- Wait, is that's what making me stare?</state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png">I... I w-wouldn't mind if you took more off! I'd be really happy-- I... I have nothing left to lose!</state>
                <state img="#-Excited.png">C-can we... um... do something after this? E-even if I have to do it naked, as long as we can do it as friends...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Well, ~name~, you're running out of small items. Right? Or do you have a bunch hidden?!</state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png">This isn't too embarrassing for you, right? I mean, it's barely anything... Wait, I'm not being condescending!</state>
                <state img="#-Excited.png">The more time we all get to spend together the better!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_minor">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Sad.png">You're enjoying this game, right? I hope I'm not ruining it...</state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png">Wow. This game is making me &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; hungry! Anyone else want to go for food afterwards? Just, you know, for practical reasons. &lt;i&gt;I'll pay! </state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">Well, at least we all see &lt;i&gt;something&lt;/i&gt;. Um, not that I'm lewd! I'm not!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-Sad.png">I-I just wanted to give you a compliment... </state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">S-so! Since you're no longer wearing your ~clothing~, will we be enjoying any more time together?</state>
                <state img="#-Excited.png">This is even better than I had once imagined it being! And I have imagined it quite a lot! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-Sad.png">&lt;i&gt;(Should I try and distract the dealer so we can play for longer? Wait, they are already dealing cards!)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Can we just take a second just to appreciate the time we spend together before we deal the next hand?</state>
                <state img="#-Excited.png">Who would've known playing a game with so many other people would've been this fun? I mean, I fantasied it would be. But this is even better than my daydreams!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_major">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Excited.png">You know, ~name~, if you are embarrassed and want to take a break where we all have snacks, that'd be fine by me! More than fine!</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Oh, um, wow... Are y-you really taking that off? N-Not that I mind! </state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">You're taking off &lt;i&gt;a lot&lt;/i&gt;! This game is &lt;i&gt;a lot!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-Happy.png">T-take off your ~clothing~, haha, ~name~? Isn't-- is not what friends do... j-jokingly command each other? </state>
                <state img="#-Posing.png">E-even if I'm down to zero layers, a Crimson Demon is-- is never defeated! U-unless you want to defeat me... a-and we can be friends!</state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png">W-wow! Your ~clothing~? That was almost... as much as what I lost... already... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-Happy.png">You don't have to take anything off, if you don't want! I'm against peer pressure... I know what it’s like to feel like to feel like you need to do something.</state>
                <state img="#-Posing.png">Y-You really don't have much left, ~name~? Well, um, that's what you g-get for playing against a Crimson Demon!  ...Sorry!</state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png">W-Wait, that already?! Um, time goes fast when you're having fun! You are all having fun, right?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_major">
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Oo-- you're so... I &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; want you to be my friend!</state>
                <state img="#-Sad.png">I-I was first at losing, you know? S-so you could definitely acknowledge my skills! </state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I-I can be distracted-- d-did you want to distract me, ~name~? </state>
                <state img="#-Happy2.png">~Name~ y-you're so... w-wow! I want to be your friend! F-for a very long time. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">Oh wow... This game is surprisingly fun... and... &lt;i&gt;hot!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">This game is getting quite lewd... um, I'll try not to be distracted...</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">A Critical Hit! That’s something people in my village say a lot, but I never really understood why...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-Shy.png">I'm sorry if my eyes suddenly glow red! It's just a thing that happens when I'm excited... It's not dangerous, promise! </state>
                <state img="#-Sad.png">Oh... Well, at least I'm not the only loser now... I mean loser as in the game! Not generally!</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">This game is getting quite lewd... um, I'll try not to be distracted...</state>
                <state img="#-Happy2.png">I really wish I'd been invited to games like this in the past!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_major">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Happy2.png">You know, ~name~, if you are embarrassed and want to take a break where we all have snacks, that'd be fine by me! More than fine!</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">Oh, um, wow... Are y-you really taking that off? N-Not that I mind!</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">You're taking off &lt;i&gt;a lot&lt;/i&gt;! This game is &lt;i&gt;a lot!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-Happy2.png">~Name~, are you going to show us your...</state>
                <state img="#-Posing.png">W-well, I think m-my... ~name~? </state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png">I'm having fun! A-aren't you, ~name~? W-wasn't that the right thing to say? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-Happy2.png">You don't have to take anything off, if you don't want! I'm against peer pressure... I know what it’s like to feel like to feel like you need to do something.</state>
                <state img="#-Posing.png">Y-You really don't have much left, ~name~? Well, um, that's what you g-get for playing against a Crimson Demon!  ...Sorry!</state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png">W-Wait, that already?! Um, time goes fast when you're having fun! You are all having fun, right?!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_major">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">Oh wow... This game is surprisingly fun... and... &lt;i&gt;hot!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">This game is getting quite lewd... um, I'll try not to be distracted...</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">A Critical Hit! That’s something people in my village say a lot, but I never really understood why...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I-I don't want to be distracted, but for some reason you... m-make me want to focus on you...</state>
                <state img="#-Sad.png">I lost the game, but... I-I didn't lose my dignity... t-tonight...</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">...C-can you teach me that spell, ~name~? The one that I can't look away from you?</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">I'm so glad I finally got to play a game like this with people and not just alone in my room pretending there were--</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">This game is getting quite lewd... um, I'll try not to be distracted...</state>
                <state img="#-Sad.png">Oh... Well, at least I'm not the only loser now... I mean loser as in the game! Not generally!</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">I'm sorry if my eyes suddenly glow red! It's just a thing that happens when I'm excited... It's not dangerous, promise! </state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">I really wish I'd been invited to games like this in the past!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">T-This is hot. T-Thanks for inviting me. Or, um, at least not telling me to leave...</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">If you see me gawking in your direction, just ignore me! I'm very easily ignorable, promise!</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">A shirtless guy is normal... But in a game like this, it's completely different!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-Shy.png">I-I can't help but look! I-it woudl be rude to ignore such a strong chest! </state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png">Friends look at each other all the time. I'm looking at ~name~ lots, so we're friends! It's just basic f-friendship!</state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png">T-this distraction won't work! I've already touched myself at least once! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-Shy.png">I'm not blushing! It's, um, just the Crimson Demon complexion?</state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png">It's fine for me to look because we're friends now, right? Right?</state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png">Are you trying to distract me?! It's not working! I'm a Crimson Demon! Okay?!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Shy.png">You're quite cute, ~name~. I hope I'm not overstepping any boundaries by saying that!</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">I'm allowed to look, right? I'll close my eyes just in case!</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">If Funifura from the Crimson Demon clan knew I was playing this game they'd be so jealous! And, um... maybe a little ashamed of me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Y-you have a mighty chest! O-one worthy of... of being... &lt;i&gt;very&lt;/i&gt; friendly with!</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I-I-I-- y-you'd be more than a friend if I could rest my head on your chest, ~name~... y-you could also get a nice view...</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">Ha! My chest's power far exceeds yours! ...W-which i-is only fair! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-Shy.png">I'm not blushing! It's, um, just the Crimson Demon complexion?</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I've seen a shirtless man before! So... uh, why does this feel different?!</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">D-Don't distract me! A Crimson Demon's attention is supposed to be unwavering!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">The whole game has been building to this specific one moment! &lt;i&gt;(I hope it isn't as disappointing as me!)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">Wait, what? Now? This is happening?! But I haven't gotten the chance to mentally prepare myself!</state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png">I'm probably the first person ever to see a penis before making a single friend! Why is my life so weird?!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-Shy.png">~Name~'s... staff of power... </state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">T-the entire game has led to this climax-- o-of ~name~! N-not me! T-though I might--</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">~Name~--! As your newest friend, I demand y-you-- d-demand-- t-to see your--</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-Shy.png">... I, um... Are you really going to do this, ~name~? N-Not that I don't want you to!</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I know this is what the entire game is about... But I just really liked spending time with you all. I, um, can still look though... Right?</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">&lt;i&gt;(Don't panic YunYun! This is what all this daydreaming has been preparing you for!)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_small_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I-It's surprisingly... cute!</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">You've got a lot of confidence, ~name~! I-It's kind of... s-sexy actually...</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">Oh! I didn't expect it to be so... small. N-Not that I mind! I t-think it's adorable! W-Wait, is that the right word?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I-it's so... easy to manage... I could even put it in my mouth, or easily between my breasts, let alone inside of my-- U-um... s-sorry!</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I-I... it's...! ~Name~, you could put that &lt;i&gt;anywhere!&lt;/i&gt; I-it would be quite fun! </state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I-it's... it's so... amazing...! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">W-Wow. It's, erm... Is a-anyone else feeling hot right now?</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I-I'm not &lt;i&gt;blushing!&lt;/i&gt; It's just my Crimson Demon complexion! &lt;i&gt;I-It's not a blush!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">W-Why am I feeling like I do when I read one of my romance novels?!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_medium_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I... I won't be distracted! E-Even if it is very very distracting!</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">Y-You think you can fluster me with s-something like that? I'll still win! I'm a Crimson Demon! Okay?!</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">You &lt;i&gt;might&lt;/i&gt; expect me to become embarrassed. But I've already seen many, &lt;i&gt;many&lt;/i&gt; penises in pictures! Wait, that's supposed to be a secret!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I... I lost... but is it a loss as long as I can see ~name~'s... </state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I-it looks... amazing... t-to-to-to have on a friend! B-because... i-it means he has a big... &lt;i&gt;friendship&lt;/i&gt;!</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">I-I want you inside of me-- m-my heart! A-as friends! F-forever! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I... w-will not... b-be &lt;i&gt;flustered.&lt;/i&gt; I can... s-still win...</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">T-That... is  very nice, ~name~! Um, right... continue! Continue!</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I-I'm not turned on! I-I'm off! &lt;i&gt;I'm always off!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_large_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Scared.png">T-That's m-massive! A-And very very intimidating!</state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png">I-I, erm, t-that's way too large! I-It's almost scary!</state>
                <state img="#-Scared.png">T-That's the biggest one I've ever seen! A-And I've seen... relatively little actually...</state>
                <state img="#-Scared.png">I'm innocent! &lt;i&gt;Innocent!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-Happy2.png">I-it's... it's big! S-so bringing it down gives more XP! I'm ready!</state>
                <state img="#-Scared.png">It's... s-so... &lt;i&gt;big&lt;/i&gt;. </state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">Just because it's a big opponent doesn't mean I can't take it! In fact, I revel in the c-chance to... f-fight it... w-with... o-on... m-my terms...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-Scared.png">T-That's &lt;i&gt;dangerously&lt;/i&gt; large!</state>
                <state img="#-Scared.png">I-I'm more scared t-than aroused!</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">Y-You must have used a lot of Skill Potions, ~name~...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <condition filter="enf" role="target" />
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">I-I guess we can call the game quits then for your sake, ~name~... Wait, you're actually doing it?!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Facade.png">I-I have those too! I-It's nothing s-special!</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Erm, this game is progressing fast! R-Really fast!</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I-I... am very very confused as to how I feel right now...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7 9">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">B-Breasts?! I... I mean, yes. Obviously. Boobs!</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">This game is very lewd... um, I don't mind if everyone is enjoying it though!</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">A-Am I allowed to look? I u-understand if not...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">O-Oh, erm.. uh, yes?! I'm so c-confused!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_small_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Posing2.png">Bigger doesn't always mean better. Sometimes the subtle spells are the most powerful!</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Y-You shouldn't worry about what other people think of you, ~name~! At least other people &lt;i&gt;are&lt;/i&gt; thinking of you!</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">T-They might be small... But they are perky and adorable!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-9">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">&lt;i&gt;Oh!&lt;/i&gt; They are so cute! And not in a condescending way!</state>
                <state img="#-Sad.png">A-At least you don't have big things like mine constantly getting in the way...</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">T-Those are l-lovely... Y-You shouldn't be ashamed, ~name~...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_medium_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">That seems to be a perfect size... What? I am not jealous!</state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png">They... erm, are nice? Is that an statement to make?</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">This game is rather lewd... But I will make the most of it...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-9">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">Whilst I am not ashamed of my own, I still wish mine looked like that... They are so pretty and perky! </state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">You're very beautiful, ~name~! </state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">&lt;i&gt;(My mind is filled with thoughts of boobies! This is so unprofessional of an Arch-Mage!)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-Facade.png">C-Could you move them a little? No? Okay...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_large_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">A-Are those bigger than mine?!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-9">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">A-Are those even bigger than mine?! How am I feeling insecure about &lt;i&gt;this&lt;/i&gt;?!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I feel like we've only started this game... And yet...</state>
                <state img="#-Posing2.png">Seeing this is not a usual occurrence for arch-mage... But we Crimson Demons are a versatile sort able to hand any situation... Even one l-like t-this!</state>
                <state img="#-Posing.png">The game demands you to reveal everything! Not me! I'm not some kind of pervert who would propose such demands!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-9">
                <state img="#-Excited.png">This is the most intimate part a woman owns! And yet, you are showing it to someone like me! I will always appreciate this!</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">You are brave, ~name~ for showing all to us! Maybe I will allow someone like you to join me in my travels... P-Please! </state>
                <state img="#-Posing.png">All will be revealed! I-I will endevour not to stare, t-though no promises, as sometimes even a Crimson Demon cannot control their d-devilish u-urges...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">Y-You really are c-cute, ~name~... Much cuter than me...</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I-I see you. I s-shall take one glance and then s-stop looking out of politeness. M-Maybe a second.</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">You are a very attractive woman. You must have no troubles making friends...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-9">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">As this game gets lewder... I feel myself feel become more titillated. Is this normal? Am I normal?!</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">A lustful sight! Even the most trained Crimson Demon would blush at such a sight... So, erm, that explains my f-face...</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">It's not often I get to glance upon another girl like this. Therefore my stares are purely curiosity! Not anything lewd!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_lost">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="bernadetta" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Posing2.png">You are here for a supposed Social Interaction seminar, correct? Why don't you practice with me?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="komi-san" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Y-You are very quiet Komi-san. D-Do not worry though, I am used to people not talking to me... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="20">
                <condition role="target" character="megumin" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Shocked.png" marker="Megumin_Winning1A">Oh! Did you just lose Megumin? I'm still not quite sure how this game works...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2" id="25">
                <condition role="target" character="megumin" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-Stern.png" marker="Megumin_Winning3A">Yet another loss Megumin! You must be careful, lest give us Crimson Demons a weak reputation!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-1" id="26">
                <condition role="target" character="megumin" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png" marker="Megumin_Winning2A">I apologise for my earlier outburst. Of course, I wish for you to get naked Megumin! For I refuse to lose again!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-7">
                <condition role="target" character="meia" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="18" marker="meia_lost1b">Why, erm, Meia! Since you have taken an interest in me, it is only proper I do the same in response! Please tell me a little about Mejare!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="meia" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="19" marker="meia_lost1a">Please, tell me a little about your homeland Meia! I am always interested in other people! Which may I mention, is a positive trait for a potential friend to have!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" totalRounds="0" priority="20">
                <state img="#-Scared.png">Wait, we've got to do &lt;i&gt;what&lt;/i&gt; when we lose?! And that happens every round!?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_stripping">
            <case stage="0" id="22">
                <condition role="target" character="megumin" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Happy.png" marker="Megumin_Winning1B">You see Megumin, despite being new to this strange game; my inate abilities will cause me to become victorious! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-1" id="27">
                <condition role="target" character="megumin" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-Facade.png" marker="Megumin_Winning2B">If your nudity brings me victory, then I shall reveal your small bare body to all playing! If you are okay with that, of course!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2" id="28">
                <condition role="target" character="megumin" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-Facade.png" marker="Megumin_Winning3B">Thank goodness for all these stylish accessories we Crimson Demons wear. Huh, Megumin?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="meia" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png">A planet of only women? Do you find... that there is a stronger bond between the people there? Is it easier to connect and befriend?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" totalRounds="0" priority="20">
                <state img="#-Shy.png">I guess I'll stay... just because a Crimson Demon never quits! Uh, right?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_stripped">
            <case stage="0-1" id="21">
                <condition role="target" character="megumin" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-Stern.png" marker="Megumin_Winning2C">Hm, are you sure your hands won't get cold? You should be careful Megumin- I mean, another victory for me! Good!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-1" id="23">
                <condition role="target" character="megumin" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-Scared.png" marker="Megumin_Winning1C">Say what you will! However your signature quick wit will soon leave when you are struck d-defenceless... Oh Eris, this game is going to end in at least one of us getting naked, isn't it?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2" id="29">
                <condition role="target" character="megumin" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-Shy.png" marker="Megumin_Winning3C">Though you seem to be running out of small things...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="8" oneShotId="3" priority="20">
                <condition count="1" gender="male" status="exposed" />
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">Do... they &lt;i&gt;all&lt;/i&gt; look like that? Why do I feel so... fuzzy?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Facade.png">I won! I beat ~name~! Eh!? ~Name~'s going to beat his-- </state>
                <state img="#-Scared.png">Victory is mine! I, YunYun, have bested player, and will now be showered with-- &lt;i&gt;oh no&lt;/i&gt;! I-I was going to say praise, not--! </state>
                <state img="#-Posing2.png">~Name~ has been defeated, and must perform the ritual of staff recharge! I-- as Archwizard, it would be wrong for me not to oversee such a rite!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-6">
                <state img="#-Posing.png">I-I have completely beaten, ~name~! His clothing has fallen away, and soon he will spill his vital essence to... me? ~Name~! </state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Recognize the skill of  I, YunYun! Now, ~name~, as is tradition for this game, p-please show me your skill in return...</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">You thought it would be Megumin, but it was me, YunYun, who defeated you, ~name~! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7 9">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">~Name~, your stamina has been exhausted! But still you keep fighting? How noble and brave, but not enough! Show me your finishing move! ...Just not in the face, okay!? </state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Behold ~name~'s final moments! I-I will spare him the indignity of defeat as long as he... he looks at me while he... </state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Yes, ~name~, look upon the face of your... are you okay? D-don't be sad, you can look at me while you-- j-just... um... p-please don't make a mess of me... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-Stern.png">~Name~! You have already beaten me, the least you can do is show me that you find me beautiful!</state>
                <state img="#-Sad.png">P-p-please forgive me, ~name~! B-but I require you to look at me! </state>
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">I-I have never seen a man brandish his staff so brazenly-- t-though it would be v-very rude for you not to show proper appreciation!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Facade.png">I-I think you played really well, but... I-I really want to see this so please... </state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">U-um... ~name~... n-no... No! I won! You have to say my name when you finish! </state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png">I am an archwizard! T-to be initiated into my... m-my mysteries you should-- ~name~? P-pay attention!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-6">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">...I-if my body is pleasing to you, you could at least compliment it... b-by looking... </state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I am a woman of no small skill! I will have you know that I-I... I-I studied the black speech of eroticism--</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">~Name~... a-are you going to... look at me while you...?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-9">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I-I see! You demand a fair trade! Very well, ~name~, I will speak your name and you will speak mine as we look at each other...</state>
                <state img="#-Posing2.png">W-whatever you do, ~name~, j-just please respect my abilities as an Archwizard!</state>
                <state img="#-Posing.png">A-as an archwizard, I can &lt;i&gt;e-enchant&lt;/i&gt; your &lt;i&gt;Divine Rod...&lt;/i&gt; w-with my &lt;i&gt;Sacred Oils...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">... I'm enjoying this game too much! Sorry!</state>
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">Oh, oh no! ~Name~, a-are you in need of healing? I don't know magic like that-- I'm so sorry?</state>
                <state img="#-Sad.png">A-Ah? ~Name~, am I... s-should I pose better?</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">W-would it help, ~name~, if you could stare up my skirt? ...O-or if I took it off-- &lt;i&gt;Wait!&lt;/i&gt; I can still win! Please be patient, ~name~! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-6">
                <state img="#-Posing2.png">I-I apologize for staring, ~name~, but a-as... a-as a woman and wizard, I must... a-acquire knowledge... however I can! </state>
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">~Name~, would... it help if I told you I am already imagining a future house full of our children-- b-because you... f-filled my w-wo-wo-wo-- I-I can't say that yet!</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">You... are having a rather good time, aren't you? Oh! I am too! V-very good! It would be even better if you-- said my name when you finished... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-9">
                <state img="#-Facade.png">Oh... ~name~...</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">~Name~... I-I wish I could help you out with my hands-- at the &lt;i&gt;very &lt;/i&gt; least! I-I'd much rather use my body-- um--  which part? Any! T-there's so many that are-- a-at least acceptable I hope?</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">~Name~! I... request that you use my name... at least a little? Please?</state>
                <state img="#-Posing2.png">W-where are you planning to finish, ~name~? A-are you brave enough t-to challenge an archwizard? I-it is a Crimson Demon mating ritual to--</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Shy.png">~Name~! It was for me, wasn't it...? It wasn't... oh... g-good job?</state>
                <state img="#-Facade.png">What does a girl have to do around here to... oh! It was over so fast! Not... y-you did great! I just meant... n-normally when I'm... but I'm clearly not a boy so... oh... now he's not listening... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-6">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">~Name~! If... okay... &lt;i&gt;when&lt;/i&gt; I lose... I-I will remember this moment!</state>
                <state img="#-Posing2.png">This will become a memory I cherish when... um... I-I am having time to myself. B-but not tonight! Tonight it will be I, YunYun, who obtains victory! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-9">
                <state img="#-Sad.png">I-It's exceptionally disrespectful to dishonor an esteemed archwizard by not even once uttering her name aloud!</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">I... you have spilled your vitas vitae on the floor... i-is anyone else going to...? N-no? O-of course I wouldn't, that's... </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">~Name~--! I... I am sorry you lost so soon. C-Can I support you by watching?</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">Oh! ~Name~, do you want help? O-oh... you... probably could have used that earlier... I-I know, I can help you by-- w-watching at very least!</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I'm... ~name~! I will be watching you and cheering you on-- s-so, since I'm saying your name, you should find mine easy to say and think about-- it-it is a bit embarrassing but I don't think anyone's ever thought of me while--</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-6">
                <state img="#-Facade.png">D-do not despair, ~name~! Though you have been defeated by me, YunYun, I am gracious in victory and will a-allow o-or even encourage you to look at me-- </state>
                <state img="#-Posing2.png">I did it! I did it! I beat ~name~, and now she-- she should look at the woman who beat her! I-I am a powerful archwizard deserving of respect!</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">H-hooray, ~name~! You... you let me win, didn't you? That was so generous and sweet. I'll... I'll m-make sure to speak the Dark Speech of Eroticism to you! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-9">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I-If we were looking in a mirror it would be rather boring... s-so we should look at each other, ~name~. P-please? Can I at least look at you? </state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">I would... I will help you by looking visually appealing! I am a quick learner, as well, so if you show me what you like, after the game I could--</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">G-good luck, ~name~? I-I'd offer to help but... w-would you really ask me to? </state>
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">I-I really beat ~name~! S-sorry, ~name~, I just can't believe it!</state>
                <state img="#-Posing.png">This is the power of an archwizard! N-now... ~name~... y-you should humbly show me your biggest spell! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-6">
                <state img="#-Happy.png">H-how can you be helped, here! You are so vulnerable and... i-it feels good to feel powerful! </state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">H-how can... w-would you like to stare at me? Should I undress more-- ~name~, are you even... no...</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Are you... do you want me to use the Dark Speech of Eroticism on you, ~name~! I am told... b-by my experiences that I am... s-skilled! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-9">
                <state img="#-Facade.png">~Name~, it is permissible that we gaze upon each others soft curves and enjoy the pleasures of-- o-of the flesh in each other... u-um is that okay?</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">G-go, ~name~! Show us your Eternal Spiral of Climaxing! ...O-or just... w-what makes you feel good...</state>
                <state img="#-Posing.png">W-what do you do that makes people look at you, ~name~? I-I demand you tell me! I-I have nothing left to lose but my pride! </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">~Name~, do you want me to...? O-oh, yes, ~name~, you're so much more graceful using your fingers on yourself than I would be-- </state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">~Name~! You'd... I-I wish I could touch you-- w-with my fingers, or my tongue, even! J-just because it would make you feel good.</state>
                <state img="#-Sad.png">I think you're a beautiful girl, with accomplished skills, who deserves the respect of her friends and comrades-- u-um... I-I know that's not sexual but I th-thought it was what you'd want to hear... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-6">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">Oh... ~name~... I wish I looked like... d-do you want me to copy you? Would t-that be weird or flattering?</state>
                <state img="#-Posing2.png">T-this moment is a treasure, everyone! Y-you should enjoy ~name~-- a-and anyone that comes after! </state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">~Name~ is just... so hard to look away from. I'm really quite jealous! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-9">
                <state img="#-Sad.png">I-I truly can show you nothing else, ~name~, so please enjoy me as I am! </state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I... ~name~, your own spell is driving my i-incantations to new heights!</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I... I would love to repeat this with you in private, ~name~! I would take you out on a date first-- t-too! </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">Are you done...? O-oh! You're really done! You didn't fake it or anything?</state>
                <state img="#-Excited.png">Congratulations, ~name~! I... that looked very very fun!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-6">
                <state img="#-Facade.png">I... think we've gotten to know each other m-much better! S-so, it wouldn't be at all inappropriate for us to continue s-spending time together, would it ?</state>
                <state img="#-Shocked.png">I wish to see more of you in the future, ~name~ A-ah! I said that too late! I was hoping to... c-can I start over? Can we be friends?</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">~Name~, I want you inside of my deepest places-- m-my heart! E-eh? N-no! I didn't mean-- b-but you could if it meant we could be everlasting friends! A-after all, don't very good friends become intimate? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-9">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I-I watched you, ~name~, so if you wanted to watch me, that is-- v-very equitable!</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">I... I am... I wish I could have such a beautiful spell as yours, ~name~... </state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">...F-forgive me for being selfish, but I wish you had called my name, ~name~? </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate_first">
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">I... I lost! I lost by every measurement-- b-but... I'm the first one! That means everyone has to watch me! Great!</state>
                <state img="#-Aroused.png">Oh... I was the first out... that's... eh? I can... stay if I--if I touch myself?! R-really? B-but you'll all be watching, &lt;i&gt;you'll all be watching me? YunYun!? Of course!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate">
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-Posing.png">I... have never been so intimate with others... please... all I ask is that you acknowledge me... if not respect-- </state>
                <state img="#-Posing2.png">I... h-have been quite aroused for some time. P-please forgive me if I am in a hurry to start, t-though I hope to impress ! </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="start_masturbating">
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-Facade.png">I have been waiting to show you my skills! I will have you know that... that I often work solo!</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">I... I am quite skilled at a variety of techniques, practiced in solitude, but finally ready to be shared with the world! </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="masturbating">
            <case stage="8">
                <condition count="2-5" status="masturbating" />
                <state img="#-soft2.png">...I-is anyone even looking at me? </state>
                <state img="#-soft3.png">Oh... I guess... i-it's a bit like sex-- i-if I move c-closer... </state>
                <state img="#-soft0.png">W-wow, y-you're almost getting to watch me... um... make love... </state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">I... c-can we ignore the no-touching rule? No...? Okay...</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">I-I'd be happy to do what-- w-whatever you-- </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <condition count="1" status="masturbating" />
                <state img="#-soft0.png">Oh... you want to... on my face...? Well... okay... </state>
                <state img="#-soft1.png">Y-you want to put your... i-in my butt...? R-really? Will that feel good for you? O-okay then... </state>
                <state img="#-soft2.png">I-I can swallow it, if you'd like...? S-</state>
                <state img="#-soft0.png">D-do you want to kiss my neck... &lt;i&gt;choke&lt;/i&gt;-- w-well, i-if you need to...</state>
                <state img="#-soft1.png">You want me to... I-I'm not sure I want that, but if you need it...</state>
                <state img="#-soft2.png">O-oh... you want me to... be shared? B-but... o-okay... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-Scared.png">I'm s-sorry! T-This line s-shouldn't be p-playing! P-Please forgive me!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="heavy_masturbating">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-heavy0.png">&lt;i&gt;Please make me happy...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-heavy1.png">&lt;i&gt;Respect me...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-heavy3.png">&lt;i&gt;Oh... please... kiss me, bring me flowers and chocolate... and captive monsters for XP...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-heavy0.png">&lt;i&gt;Oh... oh... you can finish wherever you like...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-heavy2.png">&lt;i&gt;You stayed the night!? I-I... A-ah!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-heavy1.png">&lt;i&gt;Y-you really mean it? Me? You want&lt;/i&gt; me?</state>
                <state img="#-heavy2.png">&lt;i&gt;Please... please... y-you don't have to give me so much attention... i-if it makes you happy, don't stop...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-heavy0.png">&lt;i&gt;Oh... that massage feels so good... and you're taking care of dinner...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-heavy3.png">&lt;i&gt;Please, please, keep respecting me--&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finishing_masturbating">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-finishing.png">~Player~!</state>
                <state img="#-finishing.png">N-notice me! </state>
                <state img="#-finishing.png">A-ah...!</state>
                <state img="#-finishing.png">&lt;i&gt;E-explosions!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-Happy.png">I'm embarrassed... but it's a nice kind of embarrassing. Like getting a r-random hug in public, or s-somebody telling you you've done really good! D-Does that make sense?!</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Nobody has ever seen me like this before! It's, um, not as bad as I thought it might be...</state>
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Even if this is rather e-embarrassing... I-I'm glad it's you here, ~player~! And I-I'm really happy I met y-you all!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_victory">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-Excited.png">Wait, I won? I won! Wait, till I tell Megumin about this! Hehe!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-Sad.png">What, the game is over? Already?! But I want to keep playing with you guys!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_defeat">
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-Shy.png">Y-You guys want to hang out after this game? M-Maybe with clothes? U-Unless you want to visit a bathhouse together!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

    </behaviour>
</opponent>
