<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>

<!--This file was machine generated using the Character Editor v6.3.3 at 1:02:50 AM on January 23, 2021. Do not edit this file directly unless you know what you're doing.-->
<opponent>
    <version>v6.3.3</version>
    <first>Douglas Jay</first>
    <last>Falcon</last>
    <label>Captain Falcon</label>
    <gender>male</gender>
    <size>medium</size>
    <timer>10</timer>
    <intelligence>average</intelligence>

    <intelligence stage="1">good</intelligence>

    <intelligence stage="2">average</intelligence>

    <intelligence stage="3">good</intelligence>

    <intelligence stage="4">average</intelligence>

    <intelligence stage="5">good</intelligence>

    <intelligence stage="6">average</intelligence>

    <intelligence stage="7">good</intelligence>

    <intelligence stage="8">average</intelligence>

    <tags>
        <tag>hairy</tag>
        <tag>medium_penis</tag>
        <tag>hero</tag>
        <tag>sci-fi</tag>
        <tag>armor</tag>
        <tag>confident</tag>
        <tag>athletic</tag>
        <tag>bisexual</tag>
        <tag>smash_bros</tag>
        <tag>cheerful</tag>
        <tag>masked</tag>
        <tag>muscular</tag>
        <tag>f-zero</tag>
        <tag>video_game</tag>
        <tag>fair-skinned</tag>
        <tag>future</tag>
        <tag>anime</tag>
        <tag>perverted</tag>
        <tag>nintendo</tag>
        <tag>uncircumcised</tag>
        <tag>bounty_hunter</tag>
    </tags>


    <wardrobe>
        <clothing name="underwear" generic="Underwear" position="lower" type="important" />
        <clothing name="helmet" generic="Helmet" position="other" type="extra" />
        <clothing name="pants" generic="Pants" position="lower" type="major" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="top" generic="Top" position="upper" type="important" />
        <clothing name="boots" generic="Boots" position="other" type="extra" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="belt" generic="Belt" position="lower" type="minor" />
        <clothing name="pauldron" generic="Pauldron" position="other" type="extra" />
        <clothing name="gloves" generic="Gloves" position="other" type="extra" plural="true" />
    </wardrobe>


    <behaviour>
        <trigger id="selected">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-salute.png">Come off it! You think you can beat me? No way!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_start">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-salute.png">Come off it! You think you can beat me? No way!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="swap_cards">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-calm_a.png">Gimme ~cards~ cards!</state>
                <state img="#-calm_a.png">I gotta ask for ~cards~ cards, here.</state>
                <state img="#-calm_a.png">I'll change up my hand a little bit.</state>
                <state img="#-calm_a.png">Just a few different cards, maybe.</state>
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">Just a simple exchange. FOR HONOR!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">FALCON DRAW!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">FALCON SWAP!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="good_hand">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-up_sleeve.png">What does Captain Falcon have up his sleeve?</state>
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">Captain Falcon is ready for the chase!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">Wanna play? Take your best shot!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-show_off_a.png">My cards are easily S-Tier!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">My hand is manly! It's more like a fist! OF JUSTICE!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">This hand makes my body hard with excitement!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-show_off_a.png">The forecast calls for Falcon stylin' on his opponents this round!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_a.png">Cards worthy of a hero like me!</state>
                <state img="#-smug_a.png">I hope the rest of you are as confident in your cards as I am. I would hate to humiliate all of you!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-excited_a.png">Prepare to show your moves! Because there's no way I'm losing this round!</state>
                <state img="#-show_off_a.png">A hand worthy of my amazing manliness!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">HYEZS! I don't mind these cards in the slightest!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-show_off_a.png">I won't be losing this round! Just like every race I enter!</state>
                <state img="#-smug_a.png">Good luck beating my hand! It's as brash and fearless as I am!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_a.png">Stylin'!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">HYEZS!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-confident_c.png">This hand is as magnificent as my rockin' pecs!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_a.png">This hand is as great as my nipples are hard!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_a.png">Body: A, Boost: A, Cards: A!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">These cards are as great as my entire body is hard! Come at me!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">My cards are awesome! SHOW YA MOVES!</state>
                <state img="#-excited_a.png">If you think you can beat my hand, prepare to get bodied!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-smug_a.png">I hope you like looking at my underwear and scarf, because I won't lose either this match!</state>
                <state img="#-excited_a.png">You're gonna need to pull out all the stops if you want any chance of beating MY hand!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_c.png">If you want the slightest chance of coming out ahead in this race, you'll need a hand worthy of a true hero!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">I got a great hand! Give it your best shot!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">YESZ! No-one can stop me!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_a.png">Good luck! But unless you have a really bold hand, you'll be left in the dust!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="okay_hand">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">Not the greatest hand, but the mighty Falcon never backs down from a challenge!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">Time to prove my card playing abilities in the field of honor!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">It'll take more than a subpar hand to worry me!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">Winning this round could be a challenge. Luckily, that's how I like it!</state>
                <state img="#-sad_a.png">Hmmm. Not sure what to make of this hand.</state>
                <state img="#-show_off_a.png">Could I be enough of a badass to win with this hand? What am I saying? OF COURSE I AM!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">Could be a narrow victory. The most exciting kind of victory!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">This race could end in a photo-finish. Let's see what comes next!</state>
                <state img="#-show_off_a.png">I'm sure, with my skills, style, and charisma, I could make even this hand work!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-excited_a.png">Another suspenseful hand! But I always love excitement!</state>
                <state img="#-sad_a.png">This hand is like the anime. Exciting, but mediocre at best.</state>
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">I can still win this hand, but it'll be a close game! Think you can keep up with me?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">I will go with this hand! I like a good challenge!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_a.png">Not a terrible hand. No Falcon Punch, but good enough.</state>
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">Let's do this! I'm sure everything will work out!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-calm_a.png">Not an 'A' hand, not a 'C' hand, more of a 'B' hand.</state>
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">I can work with these cards. Falcon never backs down!</state>
                <state img="#-show_off_a.png">These cards might not be good, but I sure am!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-calm_a.png">My hand is a solid mid-tier. Like Link or Donkey Kong!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">My cards aren't as perfect as I am, but I won't back down!</state>
                <state img="#-show_off_b.png">My cards aren't as perfect as I am, but I'm not worried!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-friendly_b.png">I may have lost a lot to get where I am now, but you don't win by chickening out!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">My hand might have shaky acceleration and mediocre top speed, but I'll do my best to win this race!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_d.png">I might not have the greatest hand, but I will play it anyway! For JUSTICE! For GLORY!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-show_off_a.png">Might not be good enough to save my underwear, but I promise I'll go out in a blaze of glory!</state>
                <state img="#-excited_a.png">These cards could use a bit of a raptor boost, but I know I can win if I try!</state>
                <state img="#-show_off_a.png">I don't know or care whether I win or lose, as long as I look stylish while I do it!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="bad_hand">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">Bad cards, but the mighty Falcon never backs down from a challenge!</state>
                <state img="#-sad_a.png">Looks like a false start!</state>
                <state img="#-sad_b.png">Hooowah! Not looking good!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-sad_a.png">Less of a Melee hand, more of a Brawl hand.</state>
                <state img="#-sad_a.png">This matchup feels very disadvantageous for me.</state>
                <state img="#-show_off_a.png">Not even cards this terrible can make me look any less badass!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">I have a GREAT hand! FALCON BLUFF!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_c.png">I may lose a stock this round, but the game still continues!</state>
                <state img="#-show_off_a.png">Imagine how badass I would be if I won with this hand! Somehow even more than I am now!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">I could down-throw to forward-air these cards!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">I could Falcon PAWNCH these cards!</state>
                <state img="#-show_off_a.png">These cards are awful! But at least I look good while I hold them!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-confident_c.png">With a hand like this, it's fortunate that I don't mind showing off my body!</state>
                <state img="#-show_off_a.png">I will go with this hand! Who cares if I lost clothes?</state>
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">Who needs clothing?! Bring it on!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-show_off_a.png">The honorable hero Falcon will never back down! Not even against impossible odds!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">I can work with these cards! Even if they are outrageously bad!</state>
                <state img="#-sad_a.png">A bottom-tier hand. Worse than Kirby or Pichu.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">I may lose another hand, but I will stay resilient and strong!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">If I lose, I will strip. Strip Poker is a game of honor!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">You don't win by being lucky, you win by being BOLD!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-scarf.png">I'm pretty sure I'll lose. But it won't be my scarf I'll remove!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">I agreed to these terms when I signed up! And I will honor those terms. Strip Poker is an honorable game.</state>
                <state img="#-sad_b.png">OOOOUWAAAUGH!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">Looks like the race is ending for me. At least I fought with HONOR, PASSION and JUSTICE!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">If I lose, I'll do what I have to do. I promised I would, and I will honor that promise!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">I can't give up yet! Not even with these terrible cards! COME AT ME!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_winning">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-happy_a.png" marker="cf_must_strip_0b">Even champion racers like me can lose a lead sometimes.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" totalRounds="5-50" priority="0">
                <state img="#-smug_a.png" marker="cf_must_strip_0a">About time somebody managed to catch up to me!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_b.png" marker="cf_must_strip_0c">It looks like my winning streak has been broken! Well done everybody!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-friendly_a.png" marker="cf_must_strip_1a">Look who's aiming for a comeback!</state>
                <state img="#-friendly_b.png" marker="cf_must_strip_1b">Ha! You finally got me again! Well done!</state>
                <state img="#-friendly_a.png" marker="cf_must_strip_1c">Looks like somebody in second place is catching up to me!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-confident_a.png" marker="cf_must_strip_2a">Looks like you're all starting to gain on me! But I still have the lead!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_b.png" marker="cf_must_strip_2b">It'll take more than a few hands for me to relinquish the lead!</state>
                <state img="#-show_off_a.png" marker="cf_must_strip_2c">You've got me again! But I'm still in the A-Tier in terms of this tournament!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-friendly_a.png" marker="cf_must_strip_3a">I didn't think you'd hang in long enough to get my boots off. Kudos, my friends!</state>
                <state img="#-friendly_b.png" marker="cf_must_strip_3b">Here I thought my stripping days were over! Excellent comeback!</state>
                <state img="#-calm_a.png" marker="cf_must_strip_3c">Perhaps I got a bit cocky. That can happen sometimes when I get an early lead.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-confident_b.png" marker="cf_must_strip_4a">You took me down again! I think it's time I gave you all a valuable reward!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_b.png" marker="cf_must_strip_4b">You've worked hard and suffered great loss to see me strip again! It'll be worth it!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_c.png" marker="cf_must_strip_4c">Very well played! Nice comeback!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-confident_b.png" marker="cf_must_strip_5a">Looks like I'll soon be joining you all if you keep this up!</state>
                <state img="#-smug_a.png" marker="cf_must_strip_5b">I guess joining you all would be the most honorable thing to do!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_c.png" marker="cf_must_strip_5c">Here I was beginning to think my abs would be the only part of me you'd get to see!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-confident_b.png" marker="cf_must_strip_6a">As long as I'm still in the lead, I'll never be afraid!</state>
                <state img="#-excited_a.png" marker="cf_must_strip_6b">Captain Falcon will never lose without a fight! Bring it on!</state>
                <state img="#-show_off_a.png" marker="cf_must_strip_6c">You're getting close to seeing me completely naked, but don't forget that I am THE Captain Falcon! Don't underestimate me!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-happy_d.png" marker="cf_must_strip_7a">Looks like you've managed to hang in long enough to see me naked! Your card skills are amazing!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_b.png" marker="cf_must_strip_7b">Looks like you've finally won! But I know I put up one heck of a fight!</state>
                <state img="#-calm_a.png" marker="cf_must_strip_7c">You've done it! It wasn't easy, but you managed to strip my final article of clothing I care to remove!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_normal">
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="self" consecutiveLosses="1-5" />
                <state img="#-friendly_b.png" marker="cf_must_strip_5e">My turn again? You all aren't making this easy for me!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-serious_a.png" marker="cf_must_strip_0d">Looks like it's my turn! Bring it on!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_a.png" marker="cf_must_strip_0e">Not a problem! I'm still in the race!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_a.png" marker="cf_must_strip_0f">This isn't even a problem! I'll gladly strip!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-happy_c.png" marker="cf_must_strip_1d">Looks like it's me once again! Well played!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_c.png" marker="cf_must_strip_1e">Well played, everybody! I concede defeat this round!</state>
                <state img="#-show_off_a.png" marker="cf_must_strip_1f">Don't worry, an honorable hero like me will never be afraid to strip when he loses!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-friendly_a.png" marker="cf_must_strip_2d">You got me again! Now I'm down another stock! But I still have several more!</state>
                <state img="#-sad_b.png" marker="cf_must_strip_2e">Oooh, it feels like I just got hit with a hard read!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_b.png" marker="cf_must_strip_2f">Nice! With your boldness, you got me out of another piece of clothing!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-happy_b.png" marker="cf_must_strip_3d">Things are getting intense! The excitement is thrilling!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_b.png" marker="cf_must_strip_3e">What a rush! But don't get too excited! The race is just beginning!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_b.png" marker="cf_must_strip_3f">Looks like things are heating up! Well played, everybody!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-show_off_b.png" marker="cf_must_strip_4d">My turn again? I think you all deserve a nice reward for getting this far!</state>
                <state img="#-friendly_a.png" marker="cf_must_strip_4e">Perhaps playing poker is harder than I thought!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png" marker="cf_must_strip_4f">I lost again! Now it's high time I showed my moves!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-confident_b.png" marker="cf_must_strip_5d">Things are getting down to the wire! I'll have to focus if I want the glory of victory!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_c.png" marker="cf_must_strip_5f">Looks like it's time for me to get sexy! Well, SEXIER, anyway.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-happy_d.png" marker="cf_must_strip_6d">This party is getting really intense now! What should I remove now?</state>
                <state img="#-helmet.png" marker="cf_must_strip_6e">Take a good long look at my helmet, because this is the last you'll see of it this game!</state>
                <state img="#-helmet.png" marker="cf_must_strip_6f">Now you'll get to see what I look like under my helmet! Are you ready?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-salute.png" marker="cf_must_strip_7d">Well played, everybody! Now it's time for the mighty Falcon to show his moves!</state>
                <state img="#-scarf.png" marker="cf_must_strip_7e">I guess I could remove the scarf, buuuut...</state>
                <state img="#-scarf.png" marker="cf_must_strip_7f">You think I'm gonna take off my scarf? Ha! Captain Falcon is a little more stylish than that!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_losing">
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="self" consecutiveLosses="1" />
                <state img="#-show_off_b.png" marker="cf_must_strip_1i">I didn't expect to have to strip again so soon!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-show_off_a.png" marker="cf_must_strip_0g">With how fast I am, I never need a head start, but I'll take it!</state>
                <state img="#-show_off_a.png" marker="cf_must_strip_0h">I'm ready! Here we go!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_a.png" marker="cf_must_strip_0i">Don't worry! The mighty Falcon never backs down from a challenge!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-friendly_a.png" marker="cf_must_strip_1g">Looks like I still have a thing or two to learn about poker, huh?</state>
                <state img="#-friendly_b.png" marker="cf_must_strip_1h">Time for me to strip again! Well played!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-friendly_a.png" marker="cf_must_strip_2g">It's starting to look like I should stick to racing, bounty hunting, and smashing!</state>
                <state img="#-show_off_b.png" marker="cf_must_strip_2h">I suppose it would be silly to imagine the Mighty Falcon is perfect at EVERYTHING.</state>
                <state img="#-show_off_a.png" marker="cf_must_strip_2i">I have lost again, but don't get full of yourself! Falcon comebacks are always really hype!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-serious_a.png" marker="cf_must_strip_3g">Is this some kind of trick! Perhaps we should settle this honorably, like in a race!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_a.png" marker="cf_must_strip_3h">This game is going by pretty fast! Luckily, that's just how I like my games!</state>
                <state img="#-friendly_a.png" marker="cf_must_strip_3i">I never thought I would find brawling giant gorillas and giant turtle-monsters easier than playing a simple card game!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-sad_a.png" marker="cf_must_strip_4g">With how hard I'm losing, I'm starting to see how Samurai Goroh feels!</state>
                <state img="#-sad_a.png" marker="cf_must_strip_4h">I feel like my recovery was just gimped with a shine. No coming back!</state>
                <state img="#-sad_a.png" marker="cf_must_strip_4i">I could never guess I'd lose this badly! Playing Strip Poker takes a level of skill I have yet to master!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-show_off_a.png" marker="cf_must_strip_5g">I'm glad I am the one fate chose to get stripped this game. I can take the heat!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_b.png" marker="cf_must_strip_5h">I'm glad fate chose me to be the one to lose this game. I'm tough enough for it!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_a.png" marker="cf_must_strip_5i">I don't mind losing. I know some of you would be embarrassed in this situation, but not the Mighty Falcon!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-helmet.png" marker="cf_must_strip_6g">I don't have much left! My helmet will have to go!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_a.png" marker="cf_must_strip_6h">I don't have much left! Could I reclaim victory?</state>
                <state img="#-confident_a.png" marker="cf_must_strip_6i">I still have time for a last second comeback! Don't think you've won yet!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-scarf.png" marker="cf_must_strip_7g">I could just remove my scarf, but I'm a little sick of losing, so I think I'll just call it a day.</state>
                <state img="#-confident_d.png" marker="cf_must_strip_7h">Captain Falcon is afraid of nothing! Not even stripping in front of a clothed crowd!</state>
                <state img="#-scarf.png" marker="cf_must_strip_7i">Well played, everybody! Now who wants me to skip my scarf and get to the good part?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripping">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="cf_stripping_0a">FALCON STRIP!</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="cf_stripping_0b">STRIP OF JUSTICE!</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="cf_stripping_0c">Time to drop these gloves!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="cf_stripping_1a">FALCON STRIP!</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="cf_stripping_1b">STRIP OF JUSTICE!</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="cf_stripping_1c">FAL-CON... STRIP!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="cf_stripping_2a">FALCON STRIP!</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="cf_stripping_2b">STRIP OF JUSTICE!</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="cf_stripping_2c">GET A LOAD OF THIS!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="cf_stripping_3a">FALCON STRIP!</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="cf_stripping_3b">STRIP OF JUSTICE!</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="cf_stripping_3c">Removing the boots! FOR JUSTICE!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="cf_stripping_4a">FALCON STRIP!</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="cf_stripping_4b">STRIP OF JUSTICE!</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="cf_stripping_4c">TIME TO SEE MY NIPS OF JUSTICE!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="cf_stripping_5a">FAL-CON... STRIP!</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="cf_stripping_5b">STRIP OF JUSTICE!</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="cf_stripping_5c">Keep the room well-lit when watching me strip! And keep your distance from the computer screen!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="cf_stripping_6a">FALCON STRIP!</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="cf_stripping_6b">STRIP OF JUSTICE!</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="cf_stripping_6c">I now strip, a defeated champion!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="cf_stripping_7a">FALCON STRIP!</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="cf_stripping_7b">STRIP OF JUSTICE!</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="cf_stripping_7c">COME ON!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripped">
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-stripped_a.png" marker="cf_stripped_1a">I guess my gloves can go. I won't be punching anything tonight.</state>
                <state img="#-stripped_b.png" marker="cf_stripped_1b">My gloves can go. It's not like I'm behind the wheel right now.</state>
                <state img="#-stripped_b.png" marker="cf_stripped_1b">The gloves are off. Literally and figuratively.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-calm_a.png" marker="cf_stripped_2a">My pauldron is off. If you want more glorious skin, you'll have to earn it!</state>
                <state img="#-calm_a.png" marker="cf_stripped_2b">Pauldrons are all the rage in the 26th Century! Everybody has at least one!</state>
                <state img="#-confused_a.png" marker="cf_stripped_2c">My shoulder armour identifies me as a member of the Mobile Task Force! I think. These alternate timelines are a bit confusing.</state>
                <state img="#-calm_a.png" marker="cf_stripped_2d">I'm not expecting combat tonight, so I can part with my shoulder armour.</state>
                <state img="#-serious_b.png" marker="cf_stripped_2e">Want to see more of me? Tough! Captain Falcon doesn't give in without a fight!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-stripped.png" marker="cf_stripped_3a">I practically never use my gun anyway, so I won't need my holster.</state>
                <state img="#-stripped.png" marker="cf_stripped_3">I don't need a gun to get my dirty work done! Not that I'm on duty right now anyway.</state>
                <state img="#-stripped.png" marker="cf_stripped_3">A bounty hunter as tough as I has no need for firearms! I keep one purely as a precaution.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-stripped.png" marker="cf_stripped_4a">I know I probably won't need to stomp anybody into a bottomless pit tonight, but I still miss my boots!</state>
                <state img="#-stripped.png" marker="cf_stripped_4b">Hopefully I won't need to Falcon Kick anybody tonight!</state>
                <state img="#-stripped.png" marker="cf_stripped_4c">I am beginning to feel as though I came here overdressed. If you can strip me again, I promise I'll raise the stakes!</state>
                <state img="#-stripped.png" marker="cf_stripped_4d">Don't worry about my feet being cold! My FALCON KICK sets my feet on fire! The nerves are pretty much dead anyway!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-stripped.png" marker="cf_stripped_5a">I feel like I'm posing for a magazine! Please enjoy!</state>
                <state img="#-stripped.png" marker="cf_stripped_5b">These abs have made many men and woman cry! I hope you like them!</state>
                <state img="#-stripped.png" marker="cf_stripped_5c">To be as heroic as me, you need to be in shape!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-stripped.png" marker="cf_stripped_6a">Go ahead and stare! My body is ready!</state>
                <state img="#-stripped.png" marker="cf_stripped_6b">FALCON POSE!</state>
                <state img="#-stripped.png" marker="cf_stripped_6c">My body is as rock hard as my fists! Go ahead and feel if you wish!</state>
                <state img="#-stripped.png" marker="cf_stripped_6d">They say my body is a B, but I think most people would give it a solid A!</state>
                <state img="#-stripped.png" marker="cf_stripped_6e">Do you like my underwear? I like to think the flames make me go faster.</state>
                <state img="#-stripped.png" marker="cf_stripped_6f">Like my pair of underpants? I call it the cockpit!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-stripped_a.png" marker="cf_stripped_7a">Do you think my scar is attractive?</state>
                <state img="#-stripped_b.png" marker="cf_stripped_7b">Usually my face is a lot more... chiseled and manly than this.</state>
                <state img="#-stripped_c.png" marker="cf_stripped_7c">Without my helmet, it's hard to remember I'm the Mighty Falcon, isn't it? Maybe I'll keep the scarf on, then.</state>
                <state img="#-stripped_c.png" marker="cf_stripped_7d">People might forget who I am without the helmet. So I think I'll keep my scarf on.</state>
                <state img="#-stripped_a.png" marker="cf_stripped_7e">I tried to convince Sakurai to make this an alternate skin, but he said I'd be too similar to Shulk.</state>
                <state img="#-stripped_a.png" marker="cf_stripped_7f">I tried to convince Sakurai to make this an alternate skin, but he said I made him question his sexuality.</state>
                <state img="#-stripped_b.png" marker="cf_stripped_7g">Looks like you get to see the real Douglas Jay Falcon! Or am I Bart Lemming? Or Ryu Suzaku? These timelines are SO confusing!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-stripped_a.png" marker="cf_stripped_8a">Anybody have an issue with me keep my scarf? Anybody?</state>
                <state img="#-stripped_b.png" marker="cf_stripped_8b">FEAST YOUR EYES!</state>
                <state img="#-stripped_b.png" marker="cf_stripped_8c">What? What's so strange? Not everybody is circumcised, you know.</state>
                <state img="#-stripped_b.png" marker="cf_stripped_8d">Take a look at my magnificent FALCON COCK!</state>
                <state img="#-stripped_b.png" marker="cf_stripped_8e">There's a reason I've been nicknamed ''Captain Hotdog''!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_human_must_strip">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-happy_c.png">What will you take off, ~name~? We're all looking at you!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">Take it off, ~name~! I'm watching you!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">Make this hot, ~name~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">Strip it off, ~name~! For honor!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">No shame in defeat! Not against me!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-happy_c.png">Get to work, ~name~! You're in good company!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-confident_d.png">Let me see something nice, ~name~! You're seeing something nice!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">Come on, hot boy! Showya moves!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">Strip it, ~name~! Show me something that'll get me hard!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-masturbate_c.png">HYEZS... I w-wanted to see ~name~ while I'm doing this.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-salute.png">Take something off, ~name~. And make it stylish!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_strip">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-happy_c.png">What will you take off, ~name~? We're all looking at you!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">Showya moves!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">Whatever you remove, make sure it's nice and GLORIOUS!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">I can't wait to see what sexy thing you take off, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">Take it off, ~name~! I'm watching you!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">Take it off, ~name~! I'm watching you!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">Showya moves! Rock that hot body!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">Make this hot, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">SHOWYA MOVES!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_a.png">Take it off, ~name~! Don't worry about anything!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_c.png">Make this sexy, ~name~! You can do it!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">I can't wait to see more of your supple little body, ~name~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-salute.png">You cannot refuse! Strip poker is a game of honor!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">Showya moves, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">Strip it off, ~name~! For honor!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">No shame in defeat! Not against me!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">Strip, ~name~! We'd all love to see more of your body!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">Once again, time to showya moves!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">Time for ~name~ to strip! I was hoping it would be you this time!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-happy_c.png">Get to work, ~name~! You're in good company!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">Showya moves, you sexy beast!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">Strip it off, ~name~! Join me in glory!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-confident_d.png">Let me see something nice, ~name~! You're seeing something nice!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">With how much I've lost so far, I could use a pick-me-up! You'll do nicely, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-show_off_a.png">Wanna strut your stuff with me, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-confident_d.png">Wanna join me for an underwear party, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">Showya moves, ~name~! Let's see some hot ass!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">Come on, hot boy! Showya moves!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_d.png">Wouldn't you like to be naked like me, showing off your hot body?</state>
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">I've been waiting for your next strip, stud!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">Strip it, ~name~! Show me something that'll get me hard!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_d.png">Come on, ~name~! Come and join me in my glorious nudity!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">I have my eyes on you, ~name~! On ALL of you!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-masturbate_c.png">HYEZS... I w-wanted to see ~name~ while I'm doing this.</state>
                <state img="#-masturbate_c.png">Aw, ~name~! Aw yeah!</state>
                <state img="#-masturbate_c.png">Show me something exciting, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-masturbate_c.png">I've been looking at you since the game began! Showya moves, ~name~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-salute.png">Take something off, ~name~. And make it stylish!</state>
                <state img="#-friendly_a.png">Looks like ~name~ lost another stock!</state>
                <state img="#-friendly_a.png">I guess those were low tier cards, weren't they?</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">I might be done, but I can still admire a hot bod! SHOWYA MOVES!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_human_must_strip">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-salute.png">Come on, ~name~! Showya moves!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-salute.png">Showya moves, baby girl!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">You gotta make this hot, ~name~! We're all watching!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">Don't back down now! We all want to see more of you!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">Sorry, ~name~, but the rules are rules. And my job is to enforce those rules.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">Come on, baby! Shake what your mama gave ya!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">Come on, girl! Show me those hot curves!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-happy_d.png">Time to strip again! Show us some style!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">HYEZS! I could use a pretty sight to perk me up!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-masturbate_c.png">HYEZS! SHOWYA MOVES!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">Let's see something really nice! More of your body, for example!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_strip">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-happy_c.png">Show Falcon what he likes, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">Come on, ~name~! Showya moves!</state>
                <state img="#-smug_a.png">It's time for you to strip, ~name~! All eyes on you, babe!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-salute.png">Showya moves, baby girl!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">Take something off, ~name~! Make it stylish!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">Time to strip! Make it sexy, ~name~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">You gotta make this hot, ~name~! We're all watching!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">All eyes on you, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">We're watching you, ~name~! SHOWYA MOVES!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">I can't wait to see more of your sexy body undressed!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">Don't back down now! We all want to see more of you!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">Take something off! Your honor depends on it!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">HYEZS! Show us your sexiest stuff, ~name~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">Sorry, ~name~, but rules are rules. And my job is to enforce those rules.</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">Time to take your clothes of, ~name~! Put on a nice show!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">I'll be honest, ~name~, I will stare.</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">Showya moves, ~name~! Give me something to make me harder!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">Come on, baby! Shake what your mama gave ya!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_d.png">HYEZS! I was hoping it would be you this round!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">Showya moves! Show those sexy, luscious moves!</state>
                <state img="#-friendly_b.png">I'm topless, so you could go topless too! If you have any sense of JUSTICE!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">Come on, girl! Show me those hot curves!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_c.png">I'm really looking forward to seeing what you're gonna strip off, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_d.png">If you get nervous, I can hold you close to my chest!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-happy_d.png">Time to strip again! Show us some style!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">Showya moves, girl! It's your turn again!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">I've been waiting for your next strip! I'll try not to enjoy it too much!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">HYEZS! I could use a pretty sight to perk me up!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">Come on, ~name~! Take off something big!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_d.png">Come join me, ~name~! Together we can be two glorious naked beauties!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-masturbate_c.png">HYEZS! SHOWYA MOVES!</state>
                <state img="#-masturbate_c.png">C-come on! If there was ever a time to see s-something pretty... it's now!</state>
                <state img="#-masturbate_c.png">Yeah, girl! Give me a good look while I'm doing this!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">Let's see something really nice! More of your body, for example!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">Let's see some sexy curves!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">Don't take this the wrong way, but I'm glad you lost this time!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">I might be finished, but I still would love to see you show your moves!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">Don't fall behind too fast! I want a good race!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_c.png">Keep an eye on your accessories! I'm gunning for them!</state>
                <state img="#-show_off_a.png">As the future's greatest bounty hunter, I will hunt down the rest of your clothing!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-happy_a.png">Don't make this game too easy! Take something small off!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">It would be a shame if you stripped it all off at once. I'd like to savour this!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">Something small! Good! The night is still young!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">Just getting started? You're a worthy adversary, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-calm_a.png">Nice job, still having the ~clothing~!</state>
                <state img="#-confused_a.png">You still had the ~clothing~? I guess the game is still young.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">You may be a little more ahead, but do not underestimate my might!</state>
                <state img="#-smug_a.png">The game has just begun! Don't think you're that much more ahead!</state>
                <state img="#-show_off_a.png">I may not always be in first place, but I always catch up!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-smug_b.png">Only the ~clothing~? What a dishonorable loss!</state>
                <state img="#-smug_b.png">I can't believe you're only dropping the ~clothing~!</state>
                <state img="#-smug_b.png">Only that? What a pathetic, unstylish loss!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-happy_a.png">You still had that, huh? You are a powerful opponent!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">Your card playing skills are as strong as my fists if you still have that!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_a.png">What a glorious save! Kudos, ~name~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-shocked_a.png">How could I let this injustice continue for this long?</state>
                <state img="#-shocked_a.png">How have I managed to fall so behind in this race?</state>
                <state img="#-shocked_a.png">I did not realize I was so reckless with my cards, when you still have clothing like that!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">I was hoping for more, ~name~. I've had my eye on you since the beginning.</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">Are you should you wouldn't rather just strip it all off, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-confident_d.png">Just the ~clothing~, ~name~? It would be a darn shame to keep that awesome body covered.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-shocked_a.png">Wow. You're just beginning, and I've already been knocked out of the race!</state>
                <state img="#-sad_b.png">UooooWEEEAHHH!</state>
                <state img="#-sad_b.png">UGH!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-masturbate_b.png">Aw yeah, ~name~! Take off t-the ~clothing~ in that sexy way!</state>
                <state img="#-masturbate_d.png">It's... okay to take it slow, ~name~. I'll still be hard after my big finish.</state>
                <state img="#-masturbate_a.png">Only t-that, ~name~? I was h-h-hoping you could give me some inspiration!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">Wow, only the ~clothing~ this late into the game? Your poker skill is an inspiration to us all!</state>
                <state img="#-shocked_a.png">Only that, this late in the game? You might be the racer who doesn't finish this game!</state>
                <state img="#-friendly_a.png">Wow, I was hoping that I could at least see you naked AFTER I blew my load!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">You might think you're safe now, but nobody is safe from Captain Falcon!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_a.png">One accessory down! The race is on!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">Soon we'll move on to much more flashy clothes to strip!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-salute.png">HYEZS! You'll have all game to showya moves!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">I'm gonna enjoy seeing what's under everything else!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_a.png">We'll start slow, but soon, we'll accelerate!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">Your skill just makes me seeing you nude all the more exciting!</state>
                <state img="#-show_off_a.png">We'll see who has the last laugh when Falcon makes his move!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">You'll be showing your moves before too long, though. Mark my words!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">I will deliver you to justice! And expose your manhood to everyone!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">I will FALCON STRIP the rest of your clothes, ~name~! BELIEVE IT!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">Don't get too comfortable, ~name~! When I want to see somebody naked, Falcon can make it happen!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">It's not your fault, though. I will need to double my efforts!</state>
                <state img="#-smug_a.png">It's not your fault. I just need to step up my game!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">Don't worry, it's not your fault. Captain Falcon will show you REAL glory!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-happy_c.png">If this was a race, I'd worry about you stealing my thunder!</state>
                <state img="#-calm_a.png">Stay away from the race track! I don't need you stealing my thunder THERE too!</state>
                <state img="#-friendly_a.png">I know I could still beat you in a race or a brawl!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">I have been careless. Now I must make my comeback!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">The time for games is over! Now is the time for JUSTICE!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">I have brought shame to the Falcon name! Now I must bring redemption!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-confident_d.png">I suppose I can wait. Although I've never really been that patient.</state>
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">It's an injustice keeping that body to yourself. And solving injustice is my greatest skill!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_a.png">Soon, ~name~. Soon.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-applause.png">Impressive that you still had that. You're a much greater card player than I am!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_a.png">Impressive that you still had your ~clothing~. I need to train harder in the ways of strip poker!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">I will do anything it takes to get you stripped to my level, ~name~! Let's do this!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-masturbate_d.png">I'm s-still looking at you, kid. You're one beautiful man!</state>
                <state img="#-masturbate_d.png">Doesn't m-m-matter what you took off... A man as beautiful... as you is s-sexy already!</state>
                <state img="#-masturbate_d.png">I'll just p-pretend I can see your giant dick, ~name~. And that I could suck it if I wanted to.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">It's a bit sad. I hope I'm able to see your beautiful body before the game ends.</state>
                <state img="#-sad_a.png">It's not fair, you got to see me naked. Why did you have to be so good at this game?</state>
                <state img="#-friendly_a.png">As a bro to another bro, do you mind taking off something sexier next time? It would make me feel better.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-happy_a.png">Don't be shy, baby! The Mighty Falcon always has your back!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">Don't make it easy for me to strip you! I love a challenge!</state>
                <state img="#-show_off_a.png">You won't have accessories for long! When Captain Falcon starts a race, he never slows down!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-happy_a.png">Just remove the ~clothing~! We wouldn't want to make this too easy!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_a.png">Take it slow, ~name~! It would be anti-climactic if you gave up too easily!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_a.png">Just taking off the ~clothing~? Good! Let's not rush this.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-calm_a.png">Not a bad idea, removing your ~clothing~!</state>
                <state img="#-calm_a.png">Still on little things, eh? You're stronger than I expected!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">It's a shame you're not keeping that on. You'd look pretty sexy ONLY wearing the ~clothing~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">You're still ahead! Don't get too comfortable, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_a.png">You've played well to be this clothed still!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">It's a shame. A beauty like you should be seen by everyone!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">You can't hide behind your accessories forever!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">Your accessories won't save you forever!</state>
                <state img="#-calm_a.png">I didn't think you'd still have that at this point!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">You've been hiding this whole time! I didn't expect you to be this far in the lead!</state>
                <state img="#-shocked_a.png">How did you still manage to have that?!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">I'm jealous of your card skills. Who was your sensei?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-salute.png">I have underestimated you, ~name~! You're much more formidable than I expected!</state>
                <state img="#-show_off_b.png">It seems I was so charmed by your stunning beauty that I didn't even notice you not losing any clothing!</state>
                <state img="#-shocked_a.png">I was so blinded by your beauty I didn't realize I was letting you win!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-confident_a.png">Just taking that off? You're great at playing hard to get!</state>
                <state img="#-smug_a.png">Playing hard-to-get, huh? You're just like Jody Summer!</state>
                <state img="#-show_off_b.png">Are you should you don't feel like taking off more? To join me?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-friendly_a.png">Wow, and here I thought I would be the one getting the free show!</state>
                <state img="#-friendly_a.png">Next time we play, I'll have to be the one getting the free show!</state>
                <state img="#-friendly_b.png">Looks like you got to see my glorious body for free! Excellent playing!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-masturbate_d.png">Not what I was hoping you'd take off, b-but it's still fun to l-look at you!</state>
                <state img="#-masturbate_d.png">I was hoping you'd give me some inspiration. Or better yet, b-be inspired to help me!</state>
                <state img="#-masturbate_a.png">What an injustice... tits like those could r-really help me out.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-sad_a.png">I was hoping I would see a little more of you this late in the game.</state>
                <state img="#-shocked_a.png">Only your ~clothing~? While I'm completely finished?!</state>
                <state img="#-shocked_a.png">Just the ~clothing~? Not even my masculine display inspired you to strip more?</state>
                <state img="#-confident_c.png">I'm shocked you have the willpower to resist tearing off all your clothes after witnessing what I did!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">Enjoy your accessories for now! Your body won't be covered for long!</state>
                <state img="#-smug_a.png">The race just started, but the pace has been set!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_c.png">The night has just begun! I can't wait to see what's next!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-salute.png">There's plenty of time to showya moves, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">I wanna really enjoy you peeling off your cute outfit!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">Plenty of time left in the game! Let's keep this hype!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">Let's keep playing. I don't stop the chase so easily!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">Stay focused! When I want to see somebody naked, I stop at nothing!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">Your skill only makes me want to see your body even more!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">Captain Falcon doesn't lose that easily! Your clothing-days are numbered!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">The game is still young! I'll still take the lead! Or explode in a blaze of glory trying!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">Those curves won't be covered for much longer! Don't sleep on the Falcon!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">It seems I'll need to do some serious FALCON CARD PLAYING from now on!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">I'm setting my sights on you, ~name~! Not that they ever weren't!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">A bounty hunter let's nobody escape! I'm targeting you now!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-confident_a.png">Don't get cocky! I will do whatever I can to climb back up to the lead!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_a.png">Don't get distracted! Captain Falcon is never in last place for long!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">I will focus! It would be a shame if I never got to see YOU topless!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">It's time I fixed my mistakes. You're going down, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">Captain Falcon learns from his mistakes! I'm taking you down, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_a.png">I always had a tendency to rush into things blindly. Time to change my strategy!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-confident_d.png">Suit yourself, dollface. But sooner or later, my body is going to convince you otherwise!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_d.png">Fine, delay the inevitable. But no straight woman can resist my body's charms forever!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_c.png">Soon my body's manly charms will wear down your resistance. You'll see!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_c.png">Soon you will succumb to my body's manly awesomeness and lose all that meaningless modesty!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-friendly_a.png">Well, feel free to give me something in return later, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-friendly_a.png">Maybe later, I can take you back to my pad in Port Town so you can thank me!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_c.png">It's a good thing I don't care about you getting a free peep show. I love my body!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-masturbate_a.png">Y-you couldn't flash me right now, could you? If I asked... nicely?</state>
                <state img="#-masturbate_d.png">It's okay, ~name~. I can imagine your beautiful naked ass in my face. My i-i-imagination is incredible!</state>
                <state img="#-masturbate_a.png">If you can't strip for m-me, could you moan instead? T-that would help me out.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">I hope I can see you lose a little more before the game ends, though.</state>
                <state img="#-confident_d.png">I'd love to see your cute little tush before the game ends. Fingers crossed!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_d.png">If you don't get naked before the game ends, wanna come back home with me and play a rematch?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">HUH! One lap down! Let's finish this race!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">Just the ~clothing~? That's okay! There's loads of time left in the race!</state>
                <state img="#-smug_a.png">No rush! I mean, if you're OKAY with being a lame square.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-show_off_b.png">Who needs the ~clothing~ when you have bros?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-calm_a.png">You look a lot more swole without the ~clothing~ distracting everybody.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">Yeah! We're getting the engines warmed up, and the real race starts now!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">The ~clothing~ was only holding you back, ~name~! From achieving your true power!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-calm_a.png">I figured you would have lost that by now. No matter, ~name~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-happy_c.png">Pretty small loss for so late in the game! But your luck might run out!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">Your thirst for poker has paid off! You're barely stripped at all!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-happy_a.png">I expected nothing more! You've proven yourself a worthy opponent!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-masturbate_d.png">Expected n-nothing less! I d-don't mind... being teased.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">It's a shame I'm out of the game. Now that you're out of small things, I would love to peel your clothes off myself!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_minor">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">It won't take that much longer if us to strip you. Not if I have anything to say about it!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">Your frilly, meaningless garments aren't going to save you from showing your beautiful body forever!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">Whew! You're so sexy I'm getting flustered already, ~name~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">I'll always be your bro, ~name~! Don't be afraid of stripping in front of a bro!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-confident_a.png">Take it from the swolest guy in the universe, MORE accessories does not always equal ''better'' for your image.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">Now let's accelerate! I wanna see some REAL nudity!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-show_off_a.png">Only by showing off your totally hot bod can you achieve true JUSTICE!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-confident_a.png">I will catch up and be victorious! Captain Falcon always does!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">After all, luck doesn't hold a handle to SKILL, HONOR and JUSTICE!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">But I'm thirsty too! And Falcon always obeys his thirst!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">Worthier than Samurai Goroh, worthier than Blood Falcon, worthier than Black Shadow... But WAY sexier! Except for Blood Falcon. That guy's pretty hot.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-masturbate_b.png">Tease me some more, dirty boy!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-friendly_a.png">Maybe you can come back to my place, and let me do that for you without a card game!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-salute.png">HYEZS! Glad that ~clothing~ is out of the way!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_c.png">Not a major victory, but it does put you closer to showing something REALLY nice!</state>
                <state img="#-show_off_a.png">There's plenty of time for you to take off your sexier things. But I tend to finish much faster than just 'on time'!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-friendly_b.png">If you ask me, the ~clothing~ was unnecessarily covering up your radiance!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-calm_a.png">You didn't need that pesky clothing anyway! It didn't compliment your figure very well.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-friendly_a.png">Don't be nervous, ~name~! You were bound to start running out of tiny things sooner or later!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-happy_d.png">HYEZS! Might not be a big loss, but we're making progress!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">Is my hot body turning you on? Because yours certainly is for me!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-happy_a.png">You've done a great job holding onto your clothes. Great work, ~name~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-happy_c.png">Are you sure that's all you want to take off? I'm almost nude, after all!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-applause.png">Well played! Only the ~clothing~! Classic move!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-masturbate_d.png">J-just the ~clothing~? Well, I don't... mind getting teased.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">I wish I was still playing. I would love to help the others get the rest of your clothes off.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_minor">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-smug_a.png">The important thing is to have fun! While I win, as usual.</state>
                <state img="#-confident_a.png">Don't feel discouraged! I never lose at racing, so it makes sense my skill translates to Poker.</state>
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">Your body is hotter than the jets of the Blue Falcon! I can't wait to see more!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">Your sweet, sexy radiance!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">And trust me, babe, your figure deserves to be complimented!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-salute.png">Why delay the inevitable? Be bold! Showya moves!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">Captain Falcon never takes a short-cut. We're gonna earn this nudity! For JUSTICE!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">Not much longer before I'm staring at YOU shirtless! Falcon swears by it!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-confident_d.png">I was afraid that after you saw my godly figure that you'd just forfeit and tear away everything!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">That was a trick question! Don't make this easy! I love a strong woman who's tough to crack!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">You playing hard-to-get is just making me hard-to-take, if you know what I mean!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-masturbate_b.png">I am imagining your sexy body on me, though. And imagining you moaning like crazy!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-confident_a.png">I definitely won't mind you getting naked, but it's sweeter when you earn it!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_major">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">We're getting to the real fight, here! What truly counts!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">This is what I fight for! Aside from GLORY and JUSTICE, I mean!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">This is really what's best in life!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">HYEZS! Looks like we're about to see the true glory of ~name~'s body!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">HYEZS! Take off the ~clothing~! I was waiting for this from the start!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">My my! What do we have here?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">Come on, ~name~! Man up and remove the ~clothing~ already!</state>
                <state img="#-show_off_b.png">It's just the ~clothing~ you're taking off. Why do we have to make such a production out of it?</state>
                <state img="#-calm_a.png">Lost the ~clothing~, eh ~name~? It's not a huge loss!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-excited_a.png">Now we're making some real progress!</state>
                <state img="#-excited_a.png">The ~clothing~ is coming off? HYEZS!</state>
                <state img="#-excited_a.png">Oh yeah! This is AWESOME!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-happy_d.png">Take it off! And do it stylishly!</state>
                <state img="#-calm_a.png">TOO BAD! Lost your ~clothing~!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_c.png">Things are getting hotter than the jets of the Fire Stingray!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-confident_d.png">Come join me, ~name~, we're just hanging out like bros!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">Hey, ~name~, I bet you can't take off something sexier than what I took off!</state>
                <state img="#-show_off_b.png">Hey ~name~, I bet you can't be as sexy as me!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-confident_d.png">Come on, ~name~, remove the ~clothing~! Enjoy yourself!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">Looking forward to seeing you without the ~clothing~ blocking my view!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_c.png">With me in my underpants, I think I deserve to see at least the ~clothing~ stripped!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">HYEZS, take off the ~clothing~! I've wanted to see you without that for a while now!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_d.png">HYEZS! You're stripping for JUSTICE!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">What a glorious decision! I was hoping you'd remove the ~clothing~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-friendly_b.png">It's about time you took off the ~clothing~! I was getting worried I'd come in last place!</state>
                <state img="#-friendly_a.png">I figured you'd remove the ~clothing~ a LONG time ago!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">Come on! Make my dick hard, ~name~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-masturbate_a.png">Oh HYEZS! T-take it off, ~name~! I need it!</state>
                <state img="#-masturbate_b.png">Show me more of that sweet, sweet body, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-masturbate_b.png">Give it all you got, ~name~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-happy_c.png">Quite a bit further than me, eh ~name~? Well, don't lose focus!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">Don't think the race is over simply because I'm eliminated!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">Don't get cocky, ~name~!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_major">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-confident_a.png">And after we strip the rest, it'll only get better!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">Seeing such a hot dude start to realize he's going to be stripped for the Falcon's pleasure!</state>
                <state img="#-show_off_a.png">No slowing down! We gotta take off EVERYTHING. FOR JUSTICE!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-friendly_a.png">Why not give us a sexy little twirl, ~name~? Haven't we earned it?</state>
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">Your body is looking hard! I'm impressed! And I don't impress easily!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_c.png">If I complimented your body, would you hold it against me? FOR JUSTICE?!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-show_off_a.png">Trust me, you haven't even STARTED losing yet!</state>
                <state img="#-show_off_b.png">I mean, we're just a couple of bros chilling! Who needs clothing?</state>
                <state img="#-happy_c.png">Nobody is judging you! Especially not me! Just be comfortable with your hotness, ~name~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-friendly_a.png">I ain't gonna celebrate too quickly though. Plenty of sexiness left to see!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">I ain't gonna be content with just that, beautiful as that sight is!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">Glorious! Now let's get back to it!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">~Name~, you are one sexy beast! One I'd like to tame!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">Give us a sexy smile, ~name~! While you're showing us your body!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">I've been waiting for you to drop the ~clothing~! But we're not finished the race yet!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-confident_c.png">You're not QUITE as sexy as I am, but that was impossible to achieve anyway!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">Still looking forward to seeing your awesome chest, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-calm_a.png">I can get you in touch with my tailor. Get some fantastic golden nipples on your outfit too!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">You really are a remarkable specimen, ~name~! One I'd like to bend over!</state>
                <state img="#-excited_a.png">GLORIOUS BODY! I need to see it stripped more!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">We're both close to being nude! Exciting, huh?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">Now, what shall we do about taking off the rest?</state>
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">I'm coming for you hard, ~name~! I'm stripping the rest no matter what it takes!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">We're both so close to getting nude! Now it's just a race! My forte!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">NICE! Very nice! But neither of us is finished yet!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">NICE! I gotta stay in the race so I can get the rest of you!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">Very nice body, ~name~. Now I need to get you on my level!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-masturbate_d.png">Y-yeah... Close enough!</state>
                <state img="#-masturbate_d.png">Good enough... for my imagination to take over the r-rest!</state>
                <state img="#-masturbate_d.png">Thanks, ~name~! My imagination can do... the rest!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">You may be ahead of me, but the race isn't over until it's over!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">The others will do their best to strip you. Because that bod needs to be uncovered!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_d.png">Your time may be closer than you think!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_major">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-confident_a.png">Don't be shy, girl! You aren't the first girl to strip for the Captain!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">Drop the ~clothing~, girl! Show me those sweet, sweet moves!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">Let's see those curves a little more clearly!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">My my! What do we have here? Out of smaller things already?</state>
                <state img="#-show_off_b.png">Removing the ~clothing~? How did it come to this so soon?</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">I didn't expect to see ~name~ in this compromising position so soon!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">Oh HYEZS! I wanted to see you without the ~clothing~ since the game started!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">Take off the ~clothing~! Haven't we earned a good show?</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">Come on, babe! You know the rules!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-excited_a.png">Oh HYEZS! We're seeing some development here!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">Strip off the ~clothing~! I can help take it off for you if you want!</state>
                <state img="#-calm_a.png">HYEZS! Show us something real nice, ~name~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">Taking off the ~clothing~? Would you like me to help you with that?</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">I've been looking forward to seeing your sexy body!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">Lost your ~clothing~? Tough break! But good for us!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">Taking off the ~clothing~, I see! That's so HOT!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">Throw your ~clothing~ to the floor! I wanna see you rock it!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">I wanna see that body without the ~clothing~ blocking my view!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-happy_c.png">Looks like you're about to strip off enough to join me!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_d.png">Come on! We can be sexy together!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_d.png">Come join me! We can both be in our underwear together!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-friendly_a.png">Let's see you without the ~clothing~! You're seeing me with less!</state>
                <state img="#-excited_a.png">Take off your clothes! Neither of us needs them!</state>
                <state img="#-friendly_a.png">You'd look even sexier without the ~clothing~! Though you look pretty sexy already!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-excited_a.png">Let's go, ~name~! I've been itching to see you without the ~clothing~!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_d.png">Take off the ~clothing~! FOR JUSTICE!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">I'm glad you're removing the ~clothing~. I could use something to get my dick harder!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-masturbate_d.png">Show me your moves, ~name~! Take off the ~clothing~!</state>
                <state img="#-masturbate_a.png">I'm... gonna enjoy this!</state>
                <state img="#-masturbate_a.png">Oh ~name~, am I gonna get to see you without the ~clothing~?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-happy_a.png">Looks like you're losing the ~clothing~, finally!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_d.png">After all this time, I didn't think you'd ever lose the ~clothing~!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_d.png">I had started to give up hope seeing you without the ~clothing~!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_major">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">You got better curves than a race-track!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">My spandex is tight, but you're making it much tighter!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">That is an A-ranked Body!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-show_off_a.png">I guess I shouldn't be surprised. Falcon is always fast!</state>
                <state img="#-smug_a.png">That's what you get when you play against Falcon. Swift defeat!</state>
                <state img="#-smug_a.png">Maybe you can delay your nudity a little longer with a few more good hands! I doubt it, though.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">Doesn't it feel better? Knowing that everybody here loves looking at your glorious body?</state>
                <state img="#-happy_a.png">That is a body for the ages! I give it an A!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">Your body reminds me of Jody Summer! She's also a sexy young fox!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-thirsty_d.png">Now that's a body worthy of the Mighty Falcon's love!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_c.png">Suddenly, my pants bulge feels even bulgier!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_e.png">Now that's a body I'd Falcon Tap!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">Come on, babe! Lighten up! Falcon loves ya!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">Oh, that body is hotter than Jody Summer's! I don't say that lightly!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">What a beautiful body! I'd love to get that silhouette on my vehicle's mud flaps!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">It was worth playing just to see you like this!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">This is my favorite part of the stripping. The period where there's both titillation and possibility remaining!</state>
                <state img="#-show_off_c.png">Nice booty! Almost as sexy as my booty!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">Enjoy this moment while it lasts. I won't give up stripping you!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">Which one of us will be stripped first? I hope it's you!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">I hope you're enjoying me as much as I'm enjoying you!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-salute.png">HYEZS! Babe, you are one mighty fine woman!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">I like your underwear. Do you like mine?</state>
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">Things are pretty hot, huh? Well, they're about to get hotter!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">I have to make my next remaining hands count if I want to see the rest of that glorious body!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">I was hoping I could've removed that much earlier, but it was worth the wait!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_a.png">I was hoping I could've stripped that earlier, but don't count me out of the race yet!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-masturbate_c.png">Beautiful! That... body is s-smokin' harder than my engine jets!</state>
                <state img="#-masturbate_d.png">That h-helps a lot. My imagination can d-do the rest!</state>
                <state img="#-masturbate_b.png">I'm i-imagining pulling those panties to the side and getting a b-better look!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">You may have outraced the Falcon, but beware your other competitors!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">If you can outlast me, you can outlast anybody! Stay focused!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">Never surrender that molten fiery body, ~name~! Make the others work for it!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-salute.png">Oh yeah! Showya moves, boy!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">Now here's where things get REAL!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_a.png">Show us those glorious hard nips, ~name~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">That didn't take long at all! Time to see a nice show!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">Showya moves, ~name~! I'll be watching closely!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">Let's see how manly you look under the shirt, ~name~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-happy_a.png">HYEZ! I was wondering how MANLY your chest is!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">COME ON! Let's see some shirtless hunk!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">I love me some beefcake! Let's see some, ~name~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">That chest better have some hair on it, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">Let's see that manly chest, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">Showya moves! And your chest!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-confident_a.png">Let's see that shirtless wonder, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">This is gonna be awesome, ~name~! Showya moves!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">Give us a peek! We've been waiting in anticipation the whole game!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-confident_d.png">Join me, bro! We don't need shirts at this party!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_d.png">We're just two bros, hanging out, topless, staring at each other's abs Perfectly normal!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_c.png">Come join me for the shirtless party! Let's show these other players how it's DONE!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-show_off_b.png">Hey, if I can stand here in my underpants, couldn't you indulge me in some chest?</state>
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">If I can show everybody my chest, you can do! Believe in yourself!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">You got this, ~name~! Show everybody how sexy you can be!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-friendly_a.png">Yeah, let's see that manly chest! Join the party!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_d.png">You don't need that top here, ~name~! Join the party! OF JUSTICE!</state>
                <state img="#-show_off_b.png">Showya chest! And it better have some manly hair on it!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-friendly_a.png">Hey, I'm totally naked, aren't I? You got nothing to be afraid of!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_d.png">Join me, boy! Join me in sexy glory!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">Let's see those rippling chest muscles! And that wild, untamed chest hair!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-masturbate_a.png">HYEZS! I-I could use a little inspiration... right now!</state>
                <state img="#-masturbate_d.png">~Name~'s manly body...just what I needed!</state>
                <state img="#-masturbate_a.png">Showya moves, ~name~! I n-need something to look at!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">Don't worry, ~name~! Even without a shirt, you have a strong chance to win this!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_d.png">Victory is in your grasp! You can afford to show some beefcake!</state>
                <state img="#-show_off_b.png">You got this, bro! Who cares if you gotta be shirtless before your win?</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">Don't worry about losing! Just SHOWYA MOVES!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-show_off_b.png">Nips that good deserve to be seen while wearing clothing. Look at mine!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">Nips that good deserve to be seen while wearing clothing. I'll put you in touch with my tailor who does that for me.</state>
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">Those abs aren't as good as mine, but still praiseworthy!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-salute.png">HYEZS! Not bad at all, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-show_off_b.png">Not as manly as my chest is, but I guess that was impossible from the start!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">Glad I got a glimpse of that! But I won't stop until I see everything!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-happy_c.png">Nice! How often do you work out?</state>
                <state img="#-happy_a.png">What's your work-out routine? Punching people in the face and running really fast keep me in shape!</state>
                <state img="#-smug_a.png">Nice! Not as manly as my chest, but that's a bar nobody reaches!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-happy_a.png">No complaints! That's a fine chest!</state>
                <state img="#-show_off_a.png">Abs worthy of a hero! Though they aren't as hard as mine!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_c.png">Your abs and pecs aren't as hard as mine, but worry not! My standards aren't THAT high!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">Very nice! Very stylish!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_d.png">HYEZS! Falcon approves!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_a.png">I dig it! You have a CAPTAIN'S BODY!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-show_off_b.png">Who's pecs are better? Maybe we should press them side by side and compare!</state>
                <state img="#-show_off_b.png">See? Let them marvel at our perfectly sculpted breast muscles!</state>
                <state img="#-show_off_a.png">Men like us need to show off! For the good of the people!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">Glorious! I love a good rocking set of abs!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">Those pecs are a sight of beauty! Not quite as much as mine, but still!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_d.png">Enjoying yourself? We're just two bros, appreciating each other's sexy bodies!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">Incredible! Don't mind me staring!</state>
                <state img="#-show_off_a.png">Your muscles aren't as awesome as mine, but you're still a sight to behold!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">Fabulous, ~name~! Simply fabulous!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">HYEZS! Great show, ~name~! I know I'm getting harder!</state>
                <state img="#-show_off_a.png">Those muscles don't compare to mine, but nobody's does! Great show!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">Oh HYEZS! Glad I have some inspiration if I lose next round!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-salute.png">Perfect body! I wanna hold it!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">Amazing pecs... I can picture them held against me...</state>
                <state img="#-masturbate_d.png">Your body is i-incredible, ~name~... I'm picturing using it...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">Looking good, bro! Show off those pecs nice and proudly! Then focus up!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">Aw sweet! Doing a great job showing off those moves! I'm cheering for ya!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_a.png">I'm rooting for you to win this, ~name~! You're the coolest dude here besides me!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0 3">
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">
                    <alt-img stage="3">#-excited_a.png</alt-img>
                    <text>Let's see some nice dick!</text>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">I've been excited to see your cock the whole game, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">As a huge fan of dick, let's see how yours compares to others I've seen!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-salute.png">Showya moves! And your moves better be rock hard!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">Do you have the balls to showya balls?</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">Let's look at that rocket you pilot!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">Time for the main event! The dick I've wanted to see since the first hand!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">Let's see how well that bulge of yours represents the real deal!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">I've had my eye on that package! Let's take a look!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">Let's take a peak under that hood!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-smug_a.png">Tough luck, ~name~!  Now showya moves!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">Let's take a good look at that vehicle!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">Here it is! The glory we've worked for!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">I've beaten you fair and square! And show me my prize!</state>
                <state img="#-calm_a.png">You know the rules! Obey your honor and show us your dick!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">Let's see that dick, ~name~! Let's see if my abs made it any harder!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">Time to give the people what they want! A good look at a nice cock!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">You entered the game, and agreed to the terms! Strip those bottoms off!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-happy_d.png">HYEZS! Time to showya moves, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_d.png">I've been waiting to see your sexy dick the entire game! Go for it!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_d.png">Drop those bottoms, ~name~! FOR JUSTICE!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">Let's take a good look at that hotdog, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-calm_a.png">Looks like you beat me to losing the bottoms! Let's see!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_d.png">HYEZS! That was close! But you have to show yours first!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-confident_d.png">Join me in nudity, ~name~! Let us show off our glorious packages!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_d.png">Don't be shy, ~name~! We're all guys here! This is nothing I haven't seen before!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">It's time, ~name~! Where you gotta SHOWYA MOVES!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-masturbate_a.png">Showya moves, ~name~! I could u-use some inspiration!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">G-give me a show, ~name~! For... JUSTICE!</state>
                <state img="#-masturbate_a.png">HYEZS! I w-was hoping you'd show me yours... before I came...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">Looks like you hit a major setback, ~name~! A SEXY major setback!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">Don't worry, ~name~! You still have a chance to pull this off! Speaking of ''pulling'', though...</state>
                <state img="#-excited_a.png">Time to SHOWYA MOVES, ~name~! Give us all a show!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_small_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">I guess a man who is as... feminine as you... would have a dick that size.</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">Somehow, I expected your dick to be small and adorable.</state>
                <state img="#-show_off_a.png">Don't worry, ~name~, I'm man enough for both of us!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-smug_b.png">Ha! You can be the bottom!</state>
                <state img="#-smug_b.png">Not everybody can be as manly as the Mighty Falcon!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_a.png">It's not the size of the vehicle, it's the skill of the pilot!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-thirsty_d.png">Maybe your dick is a bit low-tier. But I still wouldn't mind getting my hands on it!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_c.png">Don't feel bad, ~name~! I'm sure your stylish moves make up for it!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_a.png">Underwhelming, but don't worry! My manhood is enough for both of us!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-friendly_a.png">Tough break! But I bet you make up for your lack of penis in other ways!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">It's not the size of the vehicle that matters, it's the heart of the pilot!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">It's not the size of the vehicle that matters, it's the speed you race at!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-salute.png">Chin up, cadet! You still have your HONOR and nobody can take that away from you!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">SHOW YOUR TINY GIRLY DICK OFF PROUDLY! BE CONFIDENT!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">Despite having a cock that tiny, you entered Strip Poker anyway. You've earned my respect for your boldness!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-smug_b.png">I didn't expect it to be so... compact!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_a.png">Perhaps a bit small, but I'm sure your power and style make up for it!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">It's not the size of the cock that matters, it's if you go off-stage for the clutch down-air! Get what I'm saying?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-happy_a.png">You knew you were small, and you joined the game anyway. You're a brave dude! I respect that!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">Show off your tiny penis proudly! There's nothing for you to be ashamed of!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">Showing us your tiny dick shows you have HONOR! That's all a hero needs to be truly sexy!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-smug_b.png">Don't be discouraged, ~name~! If I lose again, people will forget about your tiny penis!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">Small, soft things can be a lot more effective than they look! Anybody who's been gimped by a Jigglypuff backair knows what I mean!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">If we get together, ~name~, I promise you I'm man enough for the both of us!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-show_off_a.png">I bet it's not actually that small, it just looks that way compared to mine!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">Well, we can't all be as super manly as I am! But you're still really sexy!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_d.png">I'm guessing you prefer to be more of a bottom in a relationship, eh? Just the way I like it!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-masturbate_a.png">Not... what I was hoping for... b-but it's still sexy!</state>
                <state img="#-masturbate_d.png">Ha... I guess I could use a laugh...</state>
                <state img="#-masturbate_d.png">Is... that as big as it gets? And you showed it anyway. I r-respect that!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">Oh! Well, no matter! It's not the size of the cock, it's the intensity of the moves!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_a.png">Not what I expected, but in a strange way, it makes you even MORE manly!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">Never forget that you're a sexy, manly, awesome, virile beast! Don't let anybody tell you that ''cock size'' means anything!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_medium_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">And that's the finish line we were aiming for! Now let's do a victory lap!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">HYEZS! That's a dick worthy of a hero!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">Let's see that dick get nice and hard! For JUSTICE!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-friendly_b.png">Excellent vehicle. I give it an A for body!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">Looks like your vehicle handles well! Should we take it for a test drive?</state>
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">I think mine is larger, but size isn't the only factor in a race!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-thirsty_e.png">Fabulous dick! Let's smash later!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">Amazing dick! Let's see how hard it gets!</state>
                <state img="#-shocked_a.png">FALCON STARE!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">Not bad! Now let's see it get nice and hard!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">Nice! I'd love to get my hands on that!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">What a dong! That's a dong of JUSTICE!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-thirsty_c.png">Amazing dick! Let's see how fast we man make it explode!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">Amazing girth! I bet that would feel really nice!</state>
                <state img="#-friendly_a.png">Popular with the ladies, ~name~? How about the guys?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">A perfect member! You have brought honor to your name!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">Don't mind me gazing upon it! Falcon treasures the human body of both male and female!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_a.png">Your cock is amazing! Thanks for sharing it with us!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-happy_a.png">That cock gets the Captain Falcon seal of approval! Alright!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">I wanna see that cock get hard! Let's see if we can make you lose one more time!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">That is a penis of JUSTICE! Which is also the best name for a Smash Brothers move!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-happy_a.png">Excellent! I expected nothing less of a worthy opponent like you!</state>
                <state img="#-friendly_b.png">Great penis! Better hope I don't lose next, or else yours will looks small by comparison!</state>
                <state img="#-friendly_a.png">Looks top tier! May even give mine a run for my money! Probably not, though!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-excited_a.png">A cock of JUSTICE! Glad I have something to look at if I lose next!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_c.png">I bet my display is making you nice and hard, huh? ADMIT IT!</state>
                <state img="#-calm_a.png">Now that's a vehicle! I can't wait to see how it handles when I beat your next hand!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-masturbate_b.png">HYEZS! I'd love to... get me hands on that...</state>
                <state img="#-masturbate_a.png">Looks... tasty...</state>
                <state img="#-masturbate_d.png">Oh HYEZS.... I'd love to be r-rubbing against that...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-happy_d.png">That's a wiener for the ages! Seriously! Could go in the Hall of Fame!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_a.png">That's a cock at deserves its own Smash Trophy!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_d.png">It's just right! Not too big, not too small, just right across the board! Just like the Blue Falcon!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_large_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-salute.png">Now THAT is a worthy of a TRUE HERO!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_a.png">What a cock! And as a Poker master, I haven't lost once to see it!</state>
                <state img="#-shocked_a.png">And I thought my bulge was large!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">That dick might even be larger than mine!  Impressive!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-happy_a.png">That vehicle gets an A in every category!</state>
                <state img="#-friendly_a.png">Now that's a Black Bull if I ever saw one!</state>
                <state img="#-friendly_a.png">Now that's a Fat Shark if I ever saw one!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-shocked_a.png">FALCON CRAVE!</state>
                <state img="#-shocked_a.png">You were manlier than I expected! Maybe you're a worthy adversary after all!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">Now that's a vehicle that looks like it handles well!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-5 7">
                <state img="#-shocked_a.png">FALCON STARE!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">HYEZS! I knew we'd see a good show!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_a.png">Sexy! Almost as sexy as I am!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">That dick looks like it packs a punch! A Falcon Punch!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">You need a real man to get that dick off! I volunteer!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">A member worthy of a true hero! I bet you get a lot of praise from the ladies with that!</state>
                <state img="#-friendly_a.png">That bulge in your pants didn't exaggerate! Great show!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-shocked_a.png">Whoa! That gift deserves to be shared with the whole world!</state>
                <state img="#-excited_a.png">I wonder if my sexy body did that to you! It wouldn't be the first time!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_d.png">Now that's a real vehicle! Let's see that baby in action!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-shocked_a.png">S-TIER COCK! Impressive!</state>
                <state img="#-shocked_a.png">SS-TIER COCK! They'd probably ban it in tournaments!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-shocked_a.png">FALCON STARE! That's a cock that could provide some REAL inspiration if I lose next round!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_d.png">Now that's a cock I'd love to get my hands on! Give it a FALCON RUB!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_c.png">I bet seeing my outrageously sexy body is what made you as large as you are! It wouldn't be the first time!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-shocked_a.png">WHOA... That's one sexy dick...</state>
                <state img="#-shocked_a.png">And I thought I w-was sexy!</state>
                <state img="#-shocked_a.png">Bigger than... the ROB building... in Port Town...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-show_off_a.png">Oh, that size would make me jealous if I wasn't the Mighty Falcon and was jealous of NOBODY!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_c.png">That dick could destroy anybody in Smash! You just need to find a sweet catchphrase to shout for that move!</state>
                <state img="#-shocked_a.png">WHOA! I might be Captain Falcon, but you might as well be Captain Dick!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0 2 4 6-8">
                <state img="#-salute.png">
                    <alt-img stage="4">#-happy_d.png</alt-img>
                    <text>SHOWYA BOOBS!</text>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-salute.png">It's time, ~name~! Showya boobs!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">Showya moves! Or rather, showya boobs!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">Obligatory ''showya boobs'' pun!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">SHOWYA BOOBS! I bet you never heard that joke before!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-thirsty_d.png">Let's take a good look at those tits! Now that the gloves are off, I can feel 'em!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">SHOWYA BOOBS! Bet you never heard THAT joke before!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">SHOWYA BOOBS! That's the first time THAT joke has ever been made!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">Showya boobs, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">That didn't take long at all! You wanted to showya boobs from the start!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">Showya moves! Your round, perky moves!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">Oh HYEZ! Here's the cup for winning the race! Make that cups!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">There's the rack I've been waiting for since the first hand!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">Don't mind me staring at your sweet rack, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">SHOWYA BOOBS! You were waiting for that meme, weren't you!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">Let's see what your cup size is, ~name~! We wanna know!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">Oh HYEZS! Showya boobs!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">Time to show us your boobs, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">I've been waiting for your turn to come around! Let's see some nice nips!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">Awesome! Let's see some nips of JUSTICE!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">Let's see some real rockin' knockers!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_d.png">We've worked hard! We've earned our prize! Honor the deal!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">Show us your rockin' tits! FOR JUSTICE!</state>
                <state img="#-friendly_b.png">SHOWYA BOOBS! Ha! What a funny meme!</state>
                <state img="#-friendly_a.png">SHOWYA... BOOBS! I bet you expected me to say ''moves''!</state>
                <state img="#-friendly_a.png">SHOWYA... BOOBS! I replaced ''moves'' with ''boobs''. Aren't I witty?</state>
                <state img="#-friendly_b.png">SHOWYA BOOBS! Bet you never heard that joke before!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">Let's see some amazing tits! I have been looking forward to this the entire game!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_d.png">Join me in shirtlessness! Who cares what gender or sex you are?</state>
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">You have seen me shirtless, so honor dictates you show us without covering up!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-thirsty_e.png">We've been waiting, and we've been patient! Give us a real show!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_e.png">Your time has come, ~name~! Drop that top!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_d.png">You knew this was coming! Give us a titty drop of JUSTICE!</state>
                <state img="#-friendly_b.png">You knew I was going to say this eventually...SHOWYA BOOBS!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-excited_a.png">Give us a good look at that rack! I can see it clearer without my visor!</state>
                <state img="#-excited_a.png">I've been waiting to see that rack! Glad I can see it without my helmet blocking anything!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">Don't hold back, ~name~! Show those titties of JUSTICE!</state>
                <state img="#-friendly_b.png">SHOWYA BOOBS! I've been waiting all game to say that!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">You've seen all of me! It's only fair you strip down yourself! FOR JUSTICE!</state>
                <state img="#-friendly_b.png">My hot, naked body warmed up the crowd for you! Let loose, ~name~! Enjoy yourself!</state>
                <state img="#-friendly_a.png">Let that cleavage free! For the good of the people! And me! Who might lose next round!</state>
                <state img="#-friendly_a.png">SHOWYA BOOBS! Heh! I've been waiting all game to say that to you!</state>
                <state img="#-friendly_a.png">SHOWYA BOOBS! Get it? Because ''Showya moves'' is my catchphrase and I replace ''moves'' with... oh forget it.</state>
                <state img="#-friendly_a.png">You've been waiting all game for me to say this, I know it! SHOWYA BOOBS!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-salute.png">J-just what I needed! SHOWYA BOOBS!</state>
                <state img="#-masturbate_a.png">Quickly, ~name~! I need to s-see something REALLY sexy!</state>
                <state img="#-masturbate_c.png">Finally! Too bad... it took me losing first to see them...</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">SHOWYA BOOBS! I n-need the inspiration!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-friendly_a.png">SHOWYA BOOBS! I've waited the whole game to say that to you!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">SHOWYA BOOBS! You've been waiting the whole game for me to say that to you, admit it!</state>
                <state img="#-excited_a.png">Showya boobs, ~name~! Showya boobs!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_small_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">I prefer 'em buxom, but I would still gladly hold those tits!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">I bet with tits like those, you could run really fast!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_c.png">At least your tits don't extend your hurtbox. That would put you down a couple tier-list spots.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-nervous_a.png">You are, uh, above age, right? Many lie to get with the Captain!</state>
                <state img="#-friendly_a.png">Adorable little flash, bunny!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">Those are boobs I would handle with great care! Can't be too rough!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-show_off_b.png">I prefer there being more to grab, and combo into a downward fuck, but I still like those!</state>
                <state img="#-calm_a.png">I prefer larger boobs, but I'm not complaining about those!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">Maybe those are A cups, but I feel like I won the X cup!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">Not my ideal size, but I can make an exception for you!</state>
                <state img="#-show_off_b.png">A shame they aren't bigger. I love giving boob massages!</state>
                <state img="#-show_off_b.png">A shame they aren't bigger. I love racks I can play with!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">Not a whole lot to grab onto, or look at, but your fighting spirit is sexy enough!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">Not my personal taste, as a boob guy, but you're still one sexy mama anyway!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-happy_c.png">Not my ideal rack, but I'm glad I got a peek!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_d.png">I prefer BIGGER and more EXCITING! But your tits are marvelous regardless!</state>
                <state img="#-show_off_b.png">A shame there is barely anything to grab. My grab game is exceptional!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">Reminds me of Marth's rack. That chick is hard to fight in Melee!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-salute.png">Personally, I prefer large tits! But that doesn't mean you can't party with the Captain!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">Not much to play with. But they are still gorgeous!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_d.png">Your nipples look almost as hard as mine! Could I feel for comparison?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-happy_c.png">I've seen better, but do not be discouraged! You're sexy in other ways!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_c.png">I have never been a fan of small tits, but I know other racers who are! Should I put you in touch with James McCloud?</state>
                <state img="#-happy_a.png">At least your tits won't slow you down in a brawl!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-sad_a.png">Barely tits at all. A shame. A lady like yourself deserves more!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_c.png">I prefer some boobs I can actually grab and play with. But your hotness makes up for it!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_d.png">What you lack in tits, you more than make up for in HONOR!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">Not the pair of tits I was hoping for, but you're still one sexy fox nonetheless!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-masturbate_b.png">I shall... imagine them bigger... it won't be easy, b-but I'm amazing!</state>
                <state img="#-masturbate_b.png">The l-loser cannot be choosey! I will make do... though b-bigger would have been n-nice...</state>
                <state img="#-masturbate_a.png">A sh-shame... but for the best... I w-wouldn't want to get too lustful... and lose control...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-friendly_a.png">Shame about the lack of boobs to show, but hey! You can at least win the game if you stay focused!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">You have to be extra careful, ~name~! Without boobs to distract them, you'll have to rely on pure skill to crush the competition!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">I believe in you, ~name~! And your lack of tits! You can win this game!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_medium_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">I would love to lightly pull those nipples. Would that turn you on?</state>
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">What beautiful titties! I wanna grab 'em and never let go!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">HYEZ! I'd love to up-special those tits!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-salute.png">HYEZ! I wanna up-special those great titties!</state>
                <state img="#-calm_a.png">Reminds me of the groupies that flash at the racetrack!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">I never get tired of those!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-thirsty_d.png">Now those are tits I can up-special!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_d.png">I gotta get my hands on that rack sometime!</state>
                <state img="#-show_off_a.png">Magnificent tits! Worthy of the Mighty Falcon!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-thirsty_d.png">HYEZS! Now that's a rack that gets the Captain Seal of Approval!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_d.png">I'd love to play with those tits! FOR JUSTICE!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_d.png">Give us a FALCON BOUNCE, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_d.png">Nice! Falcon likes!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_d.png">Girl, you know you got a rack worthy of a Captain!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-thirsty_d.png">Now that's the kind of prize I would like to see more of! That should be the prize in the annual Grand Prix!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_d.png">HYEZS! Those are some impressive jugs!</state>
                <state img="#-shocked_a.png">FALCON STARE!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-thirsty_d.png">Your rack does not disappoint!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_d.png">Would you like a breast massage by a professional racing bounty hunting hero? I know a volunteer!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">I feels right, us both being topless. I say we both get bottomless to see if that feels good too!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">HYEZS! That is a sight for sore eyes!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_d.png">HYEZS! I'd love to get my hands on those!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_d.png">HYEZS! I'd love to up-special those!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_d.png">I bet those are as soft as I am hard!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-thirsty_d.png">Oh, how I would like to up-special those!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_d.png">Now that's a rack fit for a Captain! Wiggle them for JUSTICE!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_c.png">I would race around the world in record time to get a feel of those knockers!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-confident_a.png">Let's say you and I catch a Groovy Taxi out of here and back to my place?</state>
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">HYEZS! You have the boobs of an angel! And angel of JUSTICE!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_d.png">I would fight anybody, large or small, to grab onto those tremendous tits!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-masturbate_b.png">HYEZ! I sh-should finish this race much... faster!</state>
                <state img="#-masturbate_a.png">That almost boosted... me to the f-finish line!</state>
                <state img="#-masturbate_a.png">J-just in time! They look... AMAZING!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-happy_d.png">With perfect boobs like that, you can distract your foes and win the game! Stay strong!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">Amazing boobs! Don't lose focus because I'm staring at them! Concentrate and win the game!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_c.png">If you bounce around a lot, you can use them to distract your foes! As long as it isn't cheating, a true warrior uses ALL their skills!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_large_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">I bet I would explode in a fiery blaze of excitement if I grabbed those beauties!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">If you're having trouble holding those, I work out regularly to lift heavy objects.</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">I'd love to see those beauties pressed against my bedsheets. Or the Blue Falcon.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9-10">
                <state img="#-shocked_a.png">FALCON STARE!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-salute.png">HYEZ! I gotta grab those boobs sometime!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_d.png">Sometime you have to let me give that glorious chest a FALCON MASSAGE!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">GLORIOUS TITS! TITS OF JUSTICE!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_d.png">Give us a FALCON BOUNCE, ~name~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-friendly_a.png">Good thing you lost when you did! Your clothes probably couldn't handle those much longer!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_d.png">Those look heavy. Want me to hold them? I have the strength of a hero!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-thirsty_d.png">Now that's a rack I wanna up-special! Let me at 'em!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_d.png">Give us a nice bounce, ~name~! I wanna see this rack in action!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">You're curvier than the Big Blue Race Track!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-thirsty_d.png">Those are fun-bags I could play with for ages and never get bored!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_d.png">Those curves are so dangerous I'm worried about crashing!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">I can't remember a time I saw a rack as great as that! Maybe Kate Alen...</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_d.png">Now those are some giant boobs! Every bit worth the wait!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-thirsty_d.png">I could play with those for days and never get bored!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_d.png">I would Falcon Punch my enemy so hard the entire solar system explodes and kills me, just to get a feel of those amazing boobs!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-shocked_a.png">WHOA! FALCON STARE!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_c.png">Never in all my life have I seen tits as large or wonderful as those! Mmmmmaybe Jody Summer's...</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_d.png">That's a rack I'd love to up-special!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-shocked_a.png">Those giant tits... are gonna g-give me a massive speed boost... in THIS race!</state>
                <state img="#-masturbate_a.png">Staring at those voluptuous bosoms... it's almost too much! EVEN FOR ME!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">Those giant tracts of land are big enough to race on! I hope I get to, sometime!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">I'm impressed, ~name~! But I'll be even more impressed with you winning this game! FOCUS! I believe in you!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-show_off_a.png">Let's see what's under the hood!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">Let's take a look at the cockpit!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">Everything else about you is beautiful, so let's see the main bounty!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-salute.png">Showya moves, ~name~! Don't be shy!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">Here's why I play this game!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">Showya wet, dripping, quivering moves!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">Finally! Let's see those lips</state>
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">Show us that clit! That clit of JUSTICE!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">Showya moves! And your pussy!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">HYEZS! We're gonna see some real JUSTICE!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">Don't be shy, ~name~! We'll all appreciate your beauty!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">You know the rules, ~name~. And you must keep your honor by following them!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">Time to see something really stylish!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">I don't make the rules, ~name~, but as a bounty hunter I am paid to enforce them!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">Showya moves! And a few other things this time!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">Drop those panties! For JUSTICE!</state>
                <state img="#-smug_a.png">Let's see how wet my rock-hard abs made your sweet little puss!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_a.png">I'm used to girls dropping their panties for me. Don't be shy!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">Show us how brave you can be, ~name~! Don't hold back!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_d.png">Show us your pretty wet pussy! FOR JUSTICE!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_e.png">Do not be shy! Captain Falcon has seen many vaginas! You have nothing to fear!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-smug_a.png">Looks like you beat me in the race to show our crotch!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">Let's see this pretty pussy! You've been beaten by the Falcon, fair and square!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">SHOWYA MOVES! I've been waiting to see your pink precious the whole game!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-calm_a.png">Let's take a look at how wet my sexy, manly body made your pussy!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">You've been enjoying my crotch, ~name~, so now it's my turn!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">You've been ahead for a while, but your luck just caught up with you! Time to showya moves!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-masturbate_a.png">I c-could use the show, ~name~! Don't h-hold back!</state>
                <state img="#-masturbate_b.png">COME ON! The race is on! And the cl-clock is ticking!</state>
                <state img="#-masturbate_c.png">HYEZ... I was h-hoping you'd help me... in my t-time of need!</state>
                <state img="#-masturbate_c.png">N-now it's time I could use your help! SHOWYA MOVES!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-salute.png">SHOWYA MOVES!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">Time to drop those panties and SHOWYA MOVES!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_c.png">A shame you lost again, but you can bounce back after you SHOWYA MOVES!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-shocked_a.png">FALCON STARE!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">I would love to give that a FALCON LICK!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">Ever been fingered by a bounty hunter from the future? Can I schedule you for next week?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-happy_c.png">There's the finish line! I hope I can cross it!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_d.png">I have no gloves! Wanna a FALCON RUB!</state>
                <state img="#-friendly_a.png">Wanna FALCON LICK? It's my true Final Smash!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-thirsty_e.png">Excellent cockpit, ~name~! I wanna take her for a test drive!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">HYEZ! What a tasty sight!</state>
                <state img="#-smug_a.png">Does my manliness make your drip, ~name~?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">Breath-taking!</state>
                <state img="#-show_off_a.png">Wanna come back to my place after this? I can give that a FALCON LICK or two!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">It's a nice pussy, but the race isn't over until we see it in action!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">What amazing folds! They fill me with HEROIC RESOLVE!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">A pussy fit for a hero! But can a hero even fit?</state>
                <state img="#-calm_a.png">The prize has been revealed! But we still have to properly cross the finish line!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">That sight never gets old!</state>
                <state img="#-smug_c.png">Now that is sexy! I'd love to give it a FALCON LICK!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">You just made my skin-tight pants even tighter!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-thirsty_e.png">Glorious! A sight worth waiting for!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_d.png">Now that's a wonderful finish line! I can't wait to cross it!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">It's amazing! But we still need to see it in action! Then I'm sure it's amazing!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-friendly_a.png">HYEZS! A sight to behold! I knew it would be!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">Now that's a pussy! But we aren't done yet! Let's see it in action!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_c.png">I love that smell. Did my sexy body make you wet, ~name~?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-confident_c.png">I knew your pussy would be wet! No woman can resist the Mighty Falcon!</state>
                <state img="#-smug_c.png">That's one sexy pussy! I'd love to give that a Falcon pounding!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">Those folds are incredible! And that clit just screams JUSTICE!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-shocked_a.png">M-more beautiful than an off-stage Falcon Punch...</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">I can picture...penetrating that... making you scream in pl-pleasure!</state>
                <state img="#-masturbate_b.png">J-just what I needed! It's b-beautiful!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-happy_a.png">Lovely! Now it's time to concentrate on your comeback!</state>
                <state img="#-excited_a.png">Everybody is staring at it! Now's your time to make your epic comeback!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_d.png">You can still win this! Especially with everybody distracted by your clitoris of JUSTICE!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-salute.png">RACE TO THE FINISH!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">Now it's REALLY time to showya moves!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">Let's see how fast you can go!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-salute.png">This is it, ~name~! The end of the line! Time to SHOWYA MOVES!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">How long can you last? Show us how much of a hero you are!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">Time for you to kick those skills into high gear! RACE TO THE FINISH!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">Your time to shine, bro! Take that wiener to the next level!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">Rock that cock, ~name~! We're watching!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">SHOWYA MOVES! One last time!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">Your turn, ~name~! SHOWYA MOVES! SHOWYA SKILLS!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">Looks like somebody has some moves to show!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">Oh HYEZS! I was hoping I could see you jerking that sweet rod!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">Let's see the fire in your eyes! Give it your all, ~name~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">Looks like it's ~name~'s turn to turn up the heat! Get to it!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">I had high hopes for your victory, ~name~, but now you can go for a different kind of glory!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_c.png">Don't feel bad you lost! I challenge you to give this jerk-off your all!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">Your turn, bro! SHOWYA MOVES!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">It's finally time for you to SHOWYA MOVES! I've been waiting for this!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">Come on! Let's get this race STARTED!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-excited_a.png">Come on, ~name~! Here's your chance to show everybody else how it's done!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">Your time to shine, bro! GIVE IT ALL YOU GOT!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">Take it to the next level! TAKE IT TO THE DANGER ZONE!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">It's been a long and tough battle, but now it's time for you to SHOWYA MOVES!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">You fought well! But now it's time to SHOWYA MOVES!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_a.png">You almost beat me, ~name~! That is no small feat! Be proud in your defeat!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-salute.png">THAT WAS CLOSE! But now it's time for you to SHOWYA MOVES!</state>
                <state img="#-applause.png">You fought well, ~name~. But you have been beaten!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">You almost beat me, ~name~! But almost nobody defeats the MIGHTY FALCON!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-salute.png">Join me, ~name~! Join me in glorious defeat!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">We may... h-have lost the race, but we'll give them one hell of a show, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">L-let's give these winners a show to remember! For sportsmanship and honor!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-friendly_a.png">Oooh, wipe out! Time to join the rest of us in last place!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_a.png">I believed you could do it, but worry not! You'll get 'em next time!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_c.png">Tough break! You were closer to winning than I was!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">Hold nothing back, ~name~! Show everybody your fighting spirit!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">Grip it hard and firm! Look your opponents in the eyes! SHOW NO MERCY!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">You can do it, ~name~! Release your inner animal! Let loose!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">You got this, ~name~! Don't slow down till the race is over!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">Keep jerking it, ~name~! FOR JUSTICE!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">Get pumping! Show us how fast you can go! THIS IS YOUR MOMENT!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">Don't stop till your reach the finish line and give your best battle cry!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">You got this! Everybody is watching! SHOW NO FEAR!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">Even though you couldn't win the game, YOU CAN STILL BE THE MOST STYLISH MOFO TO JACK IT!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">You're a manly man! You're a true hero! GIVE IT YOUR ALL!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">GRIP IT HARD! STROKE LIKE IT'S YOUR LAST TIME!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">You might not win the game, but you can be the SEXIEST FAPPER!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">Hold nothing back! Show us here how sexy you can really be, stroking that cock!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_a.png">Make this count! Make sure when you come, you scream your best battle cry!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">Look us in the eye! Show your dominance! This is YOUR moment, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">Kick it into high gear, ~name~! You can do it! SHOWYA MOVES!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-confident_d.png">It could be worse! At least you can enjoy my super sexy abs!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_d.png">Aim that dick at my chest! I DARE YOU!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_d.png">Don't you stop until you're finished! Like me! I didn't get these abs by giving up!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-confident_d.png">Don't mind me staring! And I don't mind you staring at me, if you want!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">You got this, man! JACK IT! DON'T HOLD BACK!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_d.png">You can look at my glorious body! DO NOT BE AFRAID! Take inspiration if you need it!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">Jerk that dick off, ~name~! Hold nothing back! Give it your all!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">Jerk off, ~name~! Jerk off for JUSTICE!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_c.png">If it helps you, feel free to gaze on my almost naked body! I FEEL NO SHAME!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">Now stroke that dick like you mean it!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">Now pump that penis! FOR JUSTICE!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">Now jerk it like FURY! SHOW US WHAT YOU'RE MADE OF!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-salute.png">How about we have a race? I'm the fastest bounty hunter around, though!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">I'm g-glad you could...join me! S-seeing you in action is hot!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">We're just two bros, jackin' it. Perfect normal Sunday afternoon for me!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">Let's do this, ~name~! SHOWYA MOVES!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">Let's have a race to the finish, shall we?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-salute.png">Let's see that dick getting pulled! It's been a long time coming!</state>
                <state img="#-show_off_a.png">Time to SHOWYA MOVES, ~name~! Think you can give them a show as good as mine?</state>
                <state img="#-happy_d.png">Might as well enjoy yourself! Jack that dick!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_masturbating">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-happy_a.png">Keep going, ~name~! You're almost there!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">Just a few more laps, ~name~! You got this!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">Looks like your percentage is building up!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">UGH! That's the stuff, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">You got this, ~name~! Tug it for daddy!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">Oh HYEZS! I could watch you all night long!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">Work it, ~name~! Work it till it hurts!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">Show these losers how a REAL MAN jacks his meat!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">Grip it tight, ~name~! Grab it! Go for the down-throw!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">That technique is incredible! Keep it up!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">HYEZS! I love watching you beat it!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">BEAT YOUR MANLY MEAT OF JUSTICE!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">Oh HYEZS, that's it! Stroke that junk!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">Kick it up a notch! Increase your speed! You can never have enough speed, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">Come on, jerk it faster! Let's see that fire in your eyes!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">Yeahhhh. Keep jerkin' it! Just like that!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">You got this! You got the power! You have the strength!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">Give it all you got, ~name~! TAKE IT TO THE NEXT LEVEL!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">Oh HYEZS! You're doing great! Keep racing!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">Speed into the finish line! Blow that load of JUSTICE!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">Pick up the speed! Jack that sausage with FURY and PASSION!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-happy_a.png">You're doing incredibly! Keep it up!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_c.png">Very sexy, ~name~! Rub that penis!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">Keep going! You're almost at the finish line!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">Keep going, ~name~! Faster!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">I like this! You're performing like a champion!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">Oh, that face, ~name~! You're a gorgeous stallion! OF JUSTICE!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-masturbate_d.png">Work that dick, ~name~! Work it goooood!</state>
                <state img="#-masturbate_b.png">FALCON JERK! Try it with me, ~name~! Scream your battle cry!</state>
                <state img="#-masturbate_c.png">You're doing great, ~name~! You're jerkin' it with the best in the galaxy!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-salute.png">Doing great! You're amazing, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">Yeah, look me in the eyes when you jerk it!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_d.png">Give me that sweet cum, ~name~! Blast it all over me!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">Good shot! That was an incredible Final Smash!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">What a load! A sign of virility and manliness! Nice!</state>
                <state img="#-show_off_a.png">I may have defeated you without losing a single article of clothing, but do not despair! That's usually how games with me are played.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">A load worthy of a TRUE HERO! Too bad it wasn't inside of one! This time, anyway...</state>
                <state img="#-friendly_a.png">Take a break, ~name~! You earned it! You showed true grit!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">Awesome! Your fapping skills are a sight to behold!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-salute.png">Great finish! Now that's Final Smash material!</state>
                <state img="#-smug_a.png">Great work, ~name~! Hit the showers! I'll join you in a bit!</state>
                <state img="#-applause.png">Finished like a true hero! A round of applause for a worthy opponent!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">Watching that hot load got me hot and bothered! I feel like I gotta either fuck or punch something!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_c.png">HYES! That as incredible! You're one sexy beast, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_a.png">That was a Final Smash for the ages!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-salute.png">That was incredible! Nice Final Smash!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">Excellent finishing move! You are a force to be reckoned with!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">You might not have won the Poker game, but you've come in first place for jizzin' stylishly!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-happy_d.png">HYEZS! That is a load of JUSTICE! And jizz. Mostly jizz.</state>
                <state img="#-applause.png">Excellent moves! You really did show them!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_d.png">Great load! Be honest, you came harder looking at my manly chest hair!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-happy_d.png">THAT WAS AN EPIC FINISH!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_d.png">That was a load for the ages! Admit it, it was seeing me in my speedo!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">That load shot out fast enough to win the Ruby Cup! Amazing!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-happy_d.png">That's one heck of a finish! You've done me proud, my boy!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_d.png">HYEZS! That's one giant load! Very cool!</state>
                <state img="#-applause.png">That was an epic jizz, ~name~! Take a well-deserved break!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">HYEZS! A load to be proud of! A hero's load!</state>
                <state img="#-applause.png">An amazing Final Smash!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_c.png">Admit it, ~name~, you were looking at my amazing body the entire time!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-salute.png">Even with your head start, great job beating me and yourself to the end!</state>
                <state img="#-shocked_a.png">AMAZING LOAD! I'll have to top that! It won't be easy!</state>
                <state img="#-masturbate_d.png">I knew you couldn't last longer than me! Nobody can resist my sexy body!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-applause.png">HYEZS! Excellent load! Catch your breath! The race is over!</state>
                <state img="#-applause.png">You've done well, better than I did! I commend your efforts!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">That was an amazing load! A load of JUSTICE! Great work!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-salute.png">RACE TO THE FINISH!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">Now it's REALLY time to showya moves!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">Are you up to the challenge, ~name~? You better be, because you signed up for this race!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-salute.png">Ha HA! Your time has come, ~name~! SHOWYA MOVES!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">Give it your all, ~name~! FOR JUSTICE!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">That was your last chance to win, BUT NOT TO STYLE! Go out with a BANG!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">That was your last hand! Looks like ~name~ is out of the race! And into a new one!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">Time for you to SHOWYA MOVES! For the final time!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">Don't be afraid, ~name~! Nobody is judging! Everybody is on your side!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">GIVE IT YOUR ALL! POKE THAT PUSSY!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">HYEZS! It's time for you to take this to the next level!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">SHOWYA MOVES! Come on, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-friendly_a.png">You got this, ~name~!  Reach for the stars!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-happy_c.png">It's time, ~name~! You've started a NEW race!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">No escaping it, ~name~! Use this moment and show your opponents you have NO FEAR!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">This is your moment, ~name~! Time to show all these other pansies how a REAL HERO pets her pussy!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">You knew I would say this! SHOWYA MOVES!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-confident_c.png">It's your turn, ~name~! Give it your best shot!</state>
                <state img="#-show_off_a.png">Time for your last lap, ~name~! Make it stylish!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">Make this the masturbation of the century, ~name~! GIVE IT YOUR ALL!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-happy_d.png">Oh HYEZS! I was looking forward to this the whole game!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">Time to SHOWYA MOVES! For the last time!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">You've entered into the final round! SHOW NO MERCY!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-happy_d.png">Oh HYEZS! I've been waiting to see your amazing show, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">You've fought well and almost defeated me! But now your time has come!</state>
                <state img="#-show_off_a.png">You almost defeated me! Don't worry, almost nobody beats The Falcon!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-show_off_a.png">Oh HYES! Just in time! Photo finish!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">It was a race hard won! You put up one heck of a fight!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">Once again, Falcon reigns supreme! You know what that means, ~name~?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-masturbate_d.png">Come on, girl! Join me in entertaining the winners!</state>
                <state img="#-masturbate_b.png">Join me in masturbating! For Sportsmanship and HONOR!</state>
                <state img="#-masturbate_c.png">Come dollface! We have work to do!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-smug_a.png">You came close to victory, ~name~, but it wasn't close enough!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">Tough break, ~name~. Hopefully next time the cards will be more in your favor.</state>
                <state img="#-happy_a.png">You came closer to victory than I did. I'm proud of you, ~name~!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">Have no fear! SHOW NO MERCY! Spank it like nobody is watching!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">You can go it, ~name~! Pedal to the metal!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">Take it to the next level, ~name~! Let loose! NO FEAR!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">Give into your pleasure! Go the distance! Show everybody here how a HERO masturbates!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">Make everybody here watch in awe at your amazing masturbation skills! YOU ARE A CHAMPION!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">That's right! You got this! This is YOUR MOMENT! RUB IT FOR JUSTICE!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">You're a champion! You're beautiful! Show them all who the REAL boss is!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">Let me see your eyes! I wanna see the fire in your eyes while you do it!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">Don't stop until you unleash that Final Smash!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">Show us all how you masturbate for JUSTICE!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">Touch yourself for JUSTICE! Hold nothing back!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">You might not win the game, but you can still prove you're the sexiest girl here!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">You got this! SHOW NO MERCY! Give us a show of JUSTICE!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">Let's see that fire in your eyes! Masturbate like NEVER BEFORE!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">This is your challenge! Conquer your passion and CLAIM THE GLORY!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-show_off_b.png">Look at my manly chest for inspiration. I'm not a professional stripper, but I could have been!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_d.png">You can stare at my glorious chest muscles! Most women immediately cream when they see them!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">I'm surprised you haven't creamed already when you saw me take my shirt off. It shows you have inner STRENGTH!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-confident_c.png">Look upon my body! Imagine all the lewd things we could do! LET THOSE THOUGHTS FILL YOU WITH STRENGTH!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_c.png">You can gaze at my magnificently sculpted figure! Most women would have already came by now!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_c.png">I'm surprised you haven't already came after seeing my body! That means you are STRONG! SHOW ME THAT STRENGTH!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-salute.png">For the moment I've been waiting for, SHOWYA MOVES!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">Time for you to show us how sexy you can be! SHOWYA MOVES!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">Take it to the next level! Look your foes in the eyes and SHOWYA MOVES!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-salute.png">It's time for you, once and for all, to SHOWYA MOVES!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">You came close to defeating me! But now it's time to SHOWYA MOVES!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_b.png">It took the loss of every article of clothing, but now I'm making you SHOWYA MOVES!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-salute.png">I'm glad you could join me! We will give JUSTICE together!</state>
                <state img="#-masturbate_c.png">We've been looking at each other for a while! Let's just give in to our animal instincts!</state>
                <state img="#-masturbate_c.png">I know my body has been driving you crazy! Let it all out!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">Time to SHOWOUR MOVES!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">Glad you're gonna SHOWYA MOVES. I love the inspiration!</state>
                <state img="#-masturbate_d.png">This is amazing foreplay, ~name~. I LOVE foreplay!</state>
                <state img="#-masturbate_b.png">I know it's hard for you to resist coming over here and sucking me off, ~name~, but you must! This crowd demands solo shows from us!</state>
                <state img="#-masturbate_d.png">I know it's hard for you to resist my body's charms, but let's try to keep our shows separate. For now!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">I know this is a dream come true for you, ~name~. You're welcome!</state>
                <state img="#-masturbate_d.png">How about a fun race! Who can cum first? Don't go easy on me!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-salute.png">For now, let's forget about winning! SHOWYA MOVES!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">But now it's time to SHOWYA MOVES, ONCE AND FOR ALL!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">Time to see your sexiest moves! Give it all you got for the big finale!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_masturbating">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">Keep going, ~name~! FOR JUSTICE!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">FALCON STARE!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">My tight pants never felt tighter than when I'm watching you!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">SHOW NO MERCY! Not even to yourself! RELEASE YOUR INNER FALCON!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-salute.png">Aw yeah! I mean ''HYEZS!'' That's the thing I say!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">You're awesome, ~name~! Just keep going!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_c.png">You're almost at the finish line! You just gotta cross it!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">Feel good? I bet having me help would feel better.</state>
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">Oh, that wet pussy! You're loving this!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">Don't hold back! You're almost finished! Just a few more laps!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">Mmmmm, that's a tempting sight.</state>
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">Hit the gas! Pedal to the metal! SPEED INTO THE FINISH LINE!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">That's it, ~name~! Show these people your REAL SKILLS!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">That's PERFECT! You're doing great, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">That face you're making shows a real CONFIDENCE! YOU GOT THIS!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_a.png">Lose control! This is YOUR moment of glory! Feel the power of your hands!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-happy_a.png">That's right! Keep up the good work!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_c.png">You look like you're enjoying yourself! GREAT! USE THAT ENERGY!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">You're so sexy, ~name~! NEVER FORGET IT!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-confident_d.png">Oh HYEZS, keep showing those moves! You're doing great!</state>
                <state img="#-excited_a.png">Keep pounding that pussy! Make it spray!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">I see you sweating, I see you moaning... you're thinking of me, aren't you!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">Great job! Keep playing with that clit!</state>
                <state img="#-excited_a.png">You're racing to the finish! Set a record time!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_c.png">Are you picturing me in that pussy? You can flatter me! The Mighty Falcon HAS NO EGO!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-confident_d.png">Looking at my penis of JUSTICE?! Of course you are!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_d.png">Don't worry, stare at my rod! You've earned it for holding on for so long!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_c.png">Mmmmmm. You're one sight for sore eyes, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-smug_c.png">Give that clit a nice rub for FALCON!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-masturbate_b.png">Oh, that's hot! You're gonna make me come early!</state>
                <state img="#-masturbate_c.png">You got the moves, ~name~! You're burning hot!</state>
                <state img="#-masturbate_c.png">Rub that clit for me!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">I wanna see your eyes! Look into my eyes, ~name~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-happy_d.png">Aw yeah! You got the right stuff, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-excited_a.png">That pussy is getting pummeled! Combo into orgasm!</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">Give that clit a good spit-covered rubbing for me, ~name~!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-confident_a.png">I wish I could have helped more! But you're welcome to ride home with me any time!</state>
                <state img="#-show_off_a.png">Don't worry, usually my opponents never touch me! Strip Poker is no exception!</state>
                <state img="#-show_off_b.png">I'm sorry I didn't lose any clothes. I can't help being THIS awesome!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-thirsty_a.png">Nice cum! Shame I couldn't help you. Maybe after the game?</state>
                <state img="#-happy_c.png">You have a warrior's spirit! I'm proud of you, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_a.png">That's a real nice squirt! That could have been your final Smash!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">Oh that's so hot! You're hotter than a fiery Falcon Punch, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-applause.png">That was an amazing show! Let's give ~name~ a round of applause!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">HYEZS! You did well! You spanked it like a true hero!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-happy_a.png">Amazing finish! You got the skills!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_a.png">Stylish finish! It was a blast watching you!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">HYEZS! You've shown everybody your skills! Great job!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-applause.png">HYEZS! That was beautiful! You've exceeded my expectations wonderfully!</state>
                <state img="#-applause.png">Majestic finish! Like a bird of prey, you were beautiful and DEADLY!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">Fantastic show! I'll have to see it again! Hope you're down for a rematch soon!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">HYEZS! Amazing finish! You were a glorious bird in action!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">What a scream! That was a scream of GLORY! Excellent work!</state>
                <state img="#-applause.png">You might not have won the game, but you've secured your place in history as the masturbating champion!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-salute.png">That was a squirt for the ages! Only could be achieved through MY encouragement!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_d.png">You came so hard! That was a display of JUSTICE!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_d.png">That red, quivering, dripping, squirting pussy! Sweeter than a REVERSE FALCON PUNCH!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-happy_a.png">AMAZING SQUIRT! You're a champion, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_c.png">I know you were watching me. I can see it in your eyes!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_c.png">I know my epic body was what caused that squirt! NO WOMAN CAN RESIST THE FALCON!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-confident_d.png">I know you were fantasizing about me the whole time. Wanna do it for real?</state>
                <state img="#-confident_a.png">Nice moan! But I bet I could make you moan harder and louder!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">You got the moves, ~name~! Want me to show you mine, now?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-masturbate_d.png">Excellent work! Even if you had a head start, you still beat me to the end!</state>
                <state img="#-masturbate_d.png">Amazing squirt! I knew the sight of my body would inspire it!</state>
                <state img="#-masturbate_d.png">I know I could get you wet, ~name~. But this is just the appetizer for what we could do later tonight!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">I'm surprised you didn't cum sooner, seeing me naked and jacking it off. You have the constitution of Jody Summer!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_a.png">Amazing squirt! You've fought like a champion! We should celebrate after the match at my place with champagne!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_a.png">That scream was incredible! You're one incredible woman, ~name~!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate_first">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-calm_a.png">Captain Falcon wins EVERY RACE! Just not in the way I was expecting.</state>
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">Ha! I guess I do everything fast! Including losing at Strip Poker!</state>
                <state img="#-nervous_a.png">Shame I wound up in last place. I'll have to learn this game better for next time!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-calm_a.png">It was an honor playing with you all! You have bested me fair and square!</state>
                <state img="#-serious_b.png">It's time I showed MY moves! Get ready!</state>
                <state img="#-applause.png">Kudos on snatching the lead from me! Now it's time to show my sportsmanship and honor!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="start_masturbating">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-salute.png">This is g-gonna be over fast! I even... m-masturbate with FULL INTENSITY! So enjoy it while you can!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">A n-new race begins! Enjoy the view, my friends!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">I'm giving it all I got! Time... to cross this finish line... l-like a true HERO!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="masturbating">
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-masturbate_a.png">Ooooh. OOooooh YEAAAAH....</state>
                <state img="#-masturbate_b.png">FALCON JERK!</state>
                <state img="#-masturbate_a.png">Uhhh, uhhh, huhh....</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="heavy_masturbating">
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-heavy_masturbate_a.png">I'm... close to the f-finish line...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy_masturbate_a.png">F-final lap! F-for JUSTICE!</state>
                <state img="#-heavy_masturbate_b.png">S-Samus...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy_masturbate_a.png">Gonna c-cum... FOR JUSTICE!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finishing_masturbating">
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-finish.png">FALCON CUM!</state>
                <state img="#-finish.png">UUUUGH! CUM ON!</state>
                <state img="#-finish.png">SAMUS! OH YEAH BABY!</state>
                <state img="#-finish.png">OOOOOGHHHUH!</state>
                <state img="#-finish.png">HERE COMES MY FINAL SMASH! CUM ON!</state>
                <state img="#-finish.png">HYEZ! Here it is! FALCON CUM!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-salute.png">You have witnessed the glory of Falcon masturbating! Bask in the glow!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">I don't cum that fast with a partner. But I finish jerking it as fast as possible! Falcon has no time for masturbating!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">I'm not usually that fast to cum, especially not when with somebody else. I just wanted to go ALL OUT for you guys!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_victory">
            <case stage="0-1">
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">
                    <alt-img stage="1">#-salute.png</alt-img>
                    <text>GAME! This game's winner is: Captain Falcon!</text>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-show_off_a.png">Flawless victory! But that's just a Tuesday for The Mighty Falcon!</state>
                <state img="#-show_off_a.png">JV5 stock! Perfect victory! Still, great game!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_a.png">Amazing game! While nobody could compete with me, I respect you all as worthy opponents!</state>
                <state img="#-smug_a.png">Victory! And not a single piece of clothing astray! Let's put up a challenge next time, huh?</state>
                <state img="#-happy_c.png">Victory! Thanks for showing me your moves, everybody!</state>
                <state img="#-smug_a.png">Victory! Next time you'll have to show me your WINNING moves!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-smug_a.png">Victory! Please, hold your applause, everyone!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">I can't say I'm surprised about this victory, but great game nonetheless!</state>
                <state img="#-friendly_b.png">This was an incredible game! Thanks for inviting me!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">I have defended my honor again! Always a blast!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_b.png">I win! As usual! But great game, everybody!</state>
                <state img="#-show_off_a.png">Don't feel bad about losing to me! The Mighty Falcon is very skilled in many things. Bounty Hunting, Racing, Brawling, Cooking, Love-making, Fashion, Taunting, Heroism, and apparently Strip Poker too!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">It was an absolute honor playing with you all! I will be sure to return for another serving of JUSTICE and naked hotties!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-show_off_b.png">I'm glad I was inviting to see a bunch of hotties get naked for me. I hope I didn't kill the mood by winning TOO much!</state>
                <state img="#-show_off_a.png">Don't feel bad for losing to me! You had to know this was coming when you invited the Mighty Falcon!</state>
                <state img="#-show_off_a.png">I am honored I was invited to join! I will race as fast as I can in record time to join another game!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">Please, hold your applause! Captain Falcon is humbled by your praise!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-happy_d.png">The game's winner is: Captain Falcon!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">Mighty Fine! The Falcon wins another race!</state>
                <state img="#-smug_a.png">You had to know I would win before you even invited me! This was clearly a ruse to get me to see you all naked!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_c.png">You're all wonderful! It was an honor playing with you! I hope you now know that the Mighty Falcon doesn't go down easy!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-confident_c.png">Another victory for Captain Falcon! Clearly I belong in the S-Tier after all!</state>
                <state img="#-show_off_b.png">I'm sorry you didn't get to see more of me. My super-manly chest will have to suffice, my friends!</state>
                <state img="#-show_off_b.png">Looks like my abs and pecs will have to get you through your fantasies tonight. Maybe next time!</state>
                <state img="#-show_off_b.png">You got to see my manly chest before I won! But the rest of me won't get shown THAT easily!</state>
                <state img="#-friendly_c.png">Captain Falcon doesn't show his underwear THAT easily! Unless my pants rip, that is...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6">
                <state img="#-salute.png">
                    <alt-img stage="6">#-happy_d.png</alt-img>
                    <text>This game's winner is: Captain Falcon!</text>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-salute.png">Please, please, hold your applause! Just doing my job!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_d.png">Captain Falcon reigns supreme! Still, that was a close game! You got me in my underpants!</state>
                <state img="#-show_off_a.png">Great game! You got me in my underwear! That is no small feat! But I still win!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">I hope the sight of my underwear is enough for you! I would love to play again though. Any time!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-excited_a.png">Any time you want a rematch, call me and I'm there! I have a lot of free time between Smash games since Nintendo doesn't make F-Zero games anymore.</state>
                <state img="#-show_off_a.png">You got me out of my helmet. Very few have seen me without it! Great game, but I am still the champion!</state>
                <state img="#-smug_a.png">There are two kinds of Strip Poker players... me, and the losers!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">I now retire undefeated champion! Until next game, that is!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">You all came very close! But in the end, Captain Falcon is too hard to beat!</state>
                <state img="#-confident_b.png">Good game! I almost didn't win! Close game!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-happy_d.png">I was born to be a Strip Poker player!</state>
                <state img="#-friendly_b.png">Ha ha! Everybody is naked and dripping! I LOVE THIS GAME!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_d.png">This game was fun! Really fun!</state>
                <state img="#-show_off_b.png">I don't remember the last time I was around this many naked hotties! Maybe that one time in the Smash Bros change room...</state>
                <state img="#-applause.png">Close game! Really close game! You've all earned my respect as worthy opponents!</state>
                <state img="#-salute.png">This is, by far, the sexiest game I have ever played! Thanks for inviting me!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_defeat">
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-applause.png">GAME! This game's winner is: ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-applause.png">You won the race, ~name~! Great work!</state>
                <state img="#-applause.png">Round of applause for ~name~! You've fought like a TRUE HERO!</state>
                <state img="#-happy_d.png">FINISH! ALRIGHT! FIRST PLACE!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

    </behaviour>
    <epilogue gender="any" img="epilogue-snr-3.jpg">
        <title>Sweet New Ride</title>
        <scene background="epilogue-snr-1.jpg" width="1361" height="657">
            <directive type="text" width="20%" arrow="right" x="50%" y="20%">Greetings, ~name~! Glad you could come out to Port Town to check out my latest car mods!</directive>
            <directive type="pause" />
            <directive type="text" width="20%" arrow="right" x="centered" y="45%">I spent almost all my last race winnings on this car! And I've been waiting all day to show you! Step inside my garage!</directive>
            <directive type="pause" />
            <directive type="text" width="20%" arrow="right" x="50%" y="70%">By the way, you look particularly hot this evening! You been working out? And that outfit is simply fabulous!</directive>
            <directive type="pause" />
        </scene>
        <scene background="epilogue-snr-2.jpg" width="1361" height="657">
            <directive type="text" width="20%" arrow="left" x="centered" y="35%">Feast your eyes on the latest in bounty-hunting technology! The Nero Falcon Flyer! This baby has everything and more!</directive>
            <directive type="pause" />
            <directive type="text" width="30%" arrow="left" x="50%" y="55%">The top speed is 615 kilometers per hour! It's on-board computer can perform a thousand different functions, from autopilot to remote control, it's engine is a CL05-S16x4, and it's capable of 15 seconds of boost!</directive>
            <directive type="pause" />
            <directive type="text" width="20%" arrow="left" x="70%" y="75%">Oh, and how could I forget! It's big enough to sleep in! It even has it's own bed!</directive>
            <directive type="pause" />
        </scene>
        <scene background="epilogue-snr-3.jpg" width="1361" height="657">
            <directive type="text" width="20%" arrow="right" x="15%" y="30%">Enough talk! All this car talk is making me horny! Come on, ~name~! Come inside the Falcon Flyer with me and help me christen the new bed! I'll put on the autopilot and we'll drive around the city and make all of Port Town hear our moans!</directive>
            <directive type="pause" />
            <directive type="text" width="20%" arrow="left" x="70%" y="35%">Don't pass up this opportunity, ~name~! You know I have the skills to fuck you better than anybody else!</directive>
            <directive type="pause" />
        </scene>
        <scene background="epilogue-snr-4.jpg" width="1361" height="657">
            <directive type="text" width="20%" arrow="right" x="20%" y="20%">Get ready, ~name~! You have never experienced foreplay as amazing as mine! Prepare for an oral stimulation of JUSTICE!</directive>
            <directive type="pause" />
        </scene>
        <scene background="epilogue-snr-5.jpg" width="1361" height="657">
            <directive type="text" arrow="down" x="25%" y="15%">Mmmmmm. *slurp* Mmmmmm...</directive>
            <directive type="pause" />
            <directive type="text" width="20%" arrow="down" x="50%" y="20%">Are you enjoying my mighty tongue, ~name~? My head-giving skills are second only to my driving!</directive>
            <directive type="pause" />
        </scene>
        <scene background="epilogue-snr-6.jpg" width="1361" height="657">
            <directive type="text" width="20%" arrow="right" x="15%" y="20%">I hope you're ready, ~name~! I certainly am! I'm going to fuck you so hard your screams will be heard in Mute City!</directive>
            <directive type="pause" />
        </scene>
        <scene background="epilogue-snr-7.jpg" width="1361" height="657">
            <directive type="text" width="20%" arrow="right" x="15%" y="20%">Oh my god... Holy Fuuuuck... you're so fucking tight. Mmmm! This might even be too much for me!</directive>
            <directive type="pause" />
            <directive type="text" width="20%" arrow="left" x="65%" y="22%">No! I'm Captain Falcon! I can finish this race! I can do ANYTHING! I can last another twenty minutes EASY!</directive>
            <directive type="pause" />
        </scene>
        <scene background="epilogue-snr-8.jpg" width="1361" height="657">
            <directive type="text" width="20%" arrow="right" x="15%" y="20%">Okay, that's it! I can't hold on any longer! Here it comes!</directive>
            <directive type="pause" />
            <directive type="text" width="10%" arrow="left" x="65%" y="20%">FALCON FACIAL!</directive>
            <directive type="pause" />
        </scene>
        <scene background="epilogue-snr-9.jpg" width="1361" height="657">
            <directive type="text" width="15%" arrow="right" x="20%" y="20%">*pant* *pant* WOOO! You were incredible!</directive>
            <directive type="pause" />
            <directive type="text" width="20%" arrow="right" x="15%" y="50%">Oh! Uh, sorry! I swear I didn't mean to facial you. My dick slipped out of my hand at the last second, honest!</directive>
            <directive type="pause" />
            <directive type="text" arrow="left" x="70%" y="25%">In any case, you look really fuckin' cute wearing my cum. What do you say we lower the sunroof and parade you around the city? It'll be fun!</directive>
            <directive type="pause" />
        </scene>

    </epilogue>

</opponent>
