<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>

<!--This file was machine generated using the Character Editor v5.5 at 6:03:44 PM on March 31, 2020. Please do not edit it directly without preserving your improvements elsewhere or your changes may be lost the next time this file is generated.-->
<opponent>
    <version>v5.5</version>
    <first>Gray</first>
    <last>Fullbuster</last>
    <label>Gray</label>
    <gender>male</gender>
    <size>medium</size>
    <timer>15</timer>
    <intelligence>average</intelligence>

    <tags>
        <tag>april_fools</tag>
        <tag>black_hair</tag>
        <tag>short_hair</tag>
        <tag>dark_eyes</tag>
        <tag>fair-skinned</tag>
        <tag>athletic</tag>
        <tag>shaved</tag>
        <tag>medium_penis</tag>
        <tag>uncircumcised</tag>
        <tag>tattoo</tag>
        <tag>straight</tag>
        <tag>fantasy</tag>
        <tag>anime</tag>
        <tag>manga</tag>
        <tag>adventurer</tag>
        <tag>magic</tag>
    </tags>
    <nicknames />

    <start />

    <wardrobe>
        <clothing name="clothes" position="both" type="important" plural="true" />
    </wardrobe>

    <poses />

    <behaviour>
        <trigger id="selected">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-selected.png">I'm Gray Fullbuster from the Fairy Tail guild. Time to show you what we're capable of!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_start">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-start.png">Alright, let's do this!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="swap_cards">
            <case stage="0-1">
                <state img="#-serious.png">Gimme ~cards~ cards.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I need ~cards~. Hit me.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="good_hand">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Nice, looks like I'm going to make the guild proud today!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Don't feel too bad when you lose. Fairy Tail is the best magic guild in the world for a reason.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I bet Natsu would have lost already. Pinky actually lost a strip poker game to his cat once.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-happy.png">I'm not done yet!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">With this hand, I won't need any clothes to win this.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I've been stripping since I first learned ice magic. Not the best habit, but I can still win despite it.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="okay_hand">
            <case stage="1">
                <condition count="0" status="masturbating" />
                <condition count="0" status="finished" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">Wait, so what happens if we lose while we're naked?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Well, this hand's hard to read. Ah well, I've been in worse scrapes than this before.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Can't really tell how this hand will turn out, so guess I just have to keep my cool.</state>
                <state img="#-serious.png">Looks like this round is anyone's to win.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">This could go either way, so I better be careful.</state>
                <state img="#-serious.png">Come on Gray, you've gotta protect the guild's reputation.</state>
                <state img="#-unimpressed.png">Well, it's not the best hand ever, but I guess things could be worse.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="bad_hand">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-angry.png">I haven't been this annoyed about something since the last time that flame for brains Natsu challenged me to a fight in the guild hall.</state>
                <state img="#-serious.png">I don't care how bad my hand is. I refuse to lose because Fairy Tail's honor is at stake!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Oh well, stripping in public isn't new to me. It's a bit of an unfortunate habit of mine, actually.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-shocked.png">I haven't been this afraid since the time Natsu and I knocked over Erza's strawberry cake.</state>
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">Well, Master Ur did tell me my stripping habit would land me in a jam someday.</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">I can't believe I'm about to lose. If Natsu ever finds out about this he'll never let me live it down.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="hand">
            <case stage="0-1" id="3" alsoPlaying="jura" alsoPlayingStage="6" alsoPlayingSayingMarker="tharja3">
                <condition role="other" character="tharja" stage="5" saidMarker="TharjaJuraBoob3" />
                <condition role="other" character="jura" sayingMarker="tharja3" />
                <condition count="1" role="opp" character="meia" />
                <state img="#-impressed.png">I know a wizard named Brandish who did that to a friend of mine once.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-1" id="5" alsoPlaying="jura" totalFemales="3-4" alsoPlayingSayingMarker="seduction">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I'd tell you what I like, but a certain female guildmate of mine would probably hunt you down if I did.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-1" id="1" priority="102">
                <condition role="other" character="arash" saidMarker="waver-iskandar" sayingMarker="question-waver-iskandar" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">Yeah, my friends Alzack and Bisca are married with a cute little girl named Asuka. They're pretty happy together.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_winning">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-loss.png">Ice wizards have a tendency to strip in public so taking off one item isn't a big deal to me.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_normal">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-loss.png">Well, it looks like we're all about even, so I can't complain about losing a round.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_losing">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-loss.png">Guess I shouldn't have taken my shirt off before we started. Well, at least I have a few small items left.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripping">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-strip.png">Well, I guess I could start with my belt.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripped">
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="lucy" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Ah, I did it again! Hey Lucy, can I borrow your panties?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-stripped.png">What? Why are you all staring? Oh crap, my clothes! I did it again!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_strip">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Tough luck, man.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">This is kind of weird. Usually I'm the one stripping.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">Aw man, just when I finally got Juvia to stop saying Boys' Love after the incident with me and Lyon at the waterpark.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I've been stripping way longer than you have! Wait, that sounded cooler in my head.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">Well, this isn't helping me get this over with.</state>
                <state img="#-unimpressed.png">This is starting to remind me of my fight with Sugarboy. At least there's no mucus this time.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Look, can you just hurry it up. I'm ready to get this nightmare over with.</state>
                <state img="#-serious.png">I am keeping this game a secret forever.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_strip">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">This kind of reminds me of the woman who taught me ice magic...I really miss her.</state>
                <state img="#-serious.png">Hey, if anyone gives you a problem, just let me know. I've got a fistful of ice magic ready and waiting.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-impressed.png">I think my stripping habit has finally become contagious!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Usually my female guildmates just yell at me to put my clothes back on instead of stripping down with me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-horny.png">S-sorry! It's just kind of hard not to stare given my, um, situation!</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">This is definitely better than how my stripping incidents usually end.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">This would have been more helpful earlier.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Hey, do you think you could hurry it up? I want to get back to Magnolia as soon as possible.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" oneShotId="2">
                <state img="#-shocked.png">I just got a weird feeling...like a certain girl I know just detected a "love rival".</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">If you keep taking stuff like that off, we're gonna be here all day, man.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Feeling scared? I took off more than that before the game even got started.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">Really wishing I had done something like that  instead of accidentally getting naked.</state>
                <state img="#-serious.png">I don't care if I am naked already. I'm still not going to lose to you!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Erza is going to kill me for losing this badly.</state>
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">Damn, I haven't been this humiliated since my first fight with Rufus.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-angry.png">Well, this is a first. You might annoy me more than Natsu.</state>
                <state img="#-unimpressed.png">Seriously, do I have to stay for the rest of this? It's gonna take forever at this rate.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-unimpressed.png">You're just delaying the inevitable. I will win this!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Nothing to see here. Let's move on to the next round.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">Looks like I've got my work cut out for me if I want to win.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I love being an ice wizard but the random stripping side effect has its drawbacks.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Well at least you took something small off.</state>
                <state img="#-unimpressed.png">I'm a little busy at the moment so sorry if I don't pay attention.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-unimpressed.png">It's a good thing I'm an ice wizard because it's freezing in here and I'm gonna be naked forever at this rate.</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">You're starting to remind me why my guild has a reputation for property damage.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-unimpressed.png">I figured taking my shirt off would earn me something bigger than that.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Take your time. I don't plan to lose today.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Well, this is better than being yelled at to put my clothes back on, at least.</state>
                <state img="#-impressed.png">Looks like you came prepared, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Come on, can't you take a little pity on a guy?</state>
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">Okay, that's just adding insult to injury.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Even if it is only an accessory, Juvia would be very upset if she found out you stripped in front of me.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Don't get too cocky. I made this pretty easy for you.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="0-3" id="4" target="lucy" targetStage="4">
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Didn't you learn from the last time that happened to you, Lucy? Our friend Erza grabbed her belt and her skirt fell down just like that a while back.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-calm.png">So what brings a girl like you to a place like this?</state>
                <state img="#-serious.png">Sorry, but you lost the moment you challenged a Fairy Tail wizard.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png"></state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Well, it's a small victory but it means I'm still in the fight!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">You seem a bit distracted, ~name~. Any reason for that?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">Okay, taking that off while I'm paying this forfeit is just wrong.</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">Ugh, this is humiliating in so many ways.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">You're enjoying this, aren't you?</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">I am so freezing the next person who takes something like that off in a block of ice.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-smug.png">I don't need small stuff like that to beat you.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">If I win this without losing a single round, I bet I'll get an invite to the S class trials this year!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-unimpressed.png">You seemed like the kind of guy who's afraid to take risks. Guess I was right.</state>
                <state img="#-serious.png">A Fairy Tail wizard never gives up as long as they draw breath! I am still going to win this game!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Uh, thanks for not taking something big off while I do this. That would have made this even harder...wait I didn't mean it like that!</state>
                <state img="#-unimpressed.png">Yeah, let's just avoid eye contact, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-angry.png">Fairy Tail really sent the wrong guy on this job. I end up naked in public almost every day!</state>
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">You're not secretly a fire dragon slayer are you? Just wondering because of how annoying you are.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_minor">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-serious.png">I'm not into stripping dudes normally but I'll do whatever it takes to prove Fairy Tail is the best!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">So what brings you here? I came to give backup to a guildmate of mine. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-smug.png">A little nervous about being compared to me? I was on Sorcerer Weekly's Wizards You'd Like to Be Your Boyfriend list.</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">How's it feel to know I'm going to beat you after taking all my clothes off at once?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Thanks for not taking anything big off while I'm doing this, man.</state>
                <state img="#-serious.png">Is it illegal for me to use my ice magic to make a wall around me for privacy?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">I bet the wizards from Blue Pegasus and Lamia Scale never have to deal with this.</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">How many items did you bring?!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Normally, I wouldn't strip a lady like this, but my guild's reputation is on the line here.</state>
                <state img="#-serious.png">Oh, would you like to know how I got these scars?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-impressed.png">I do admire that you're a woman of her word. Fairy Tail takes our oaths very seriously.</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Oh, uh, you're sort of staring. The girls at my guild have gotten so used to me stripping they mostly just yell at me now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-horny.png">I really need to focus. The last thing I need is to accidentally use my ice magic while I'm doing this.</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">This is about as bad as the time Erza made me get naked and yell out the name of someone I love at the Christmas party.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">You wouldn't mind taking off a couple things to make this go a little faster, would you/</state>
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">This would be a lot more enjoyable to watch if I hadn't lost.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_minor">
            <case stage="0-3" id="8" target="kyoko" targetStage="6">
                <state img="#-impressed.png">Hey, don't worry about it, Kyoko. It took a lot of guts to do that. Besides, emotional scars matter more than the physical ones.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-calm.png">So what brings you here? I came to give backup to a guildmate of mine. </state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Well, all three of my scars were actually caused by good friends of mine. I've picked up more than my share of bad memories.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-impressed.png">If you ever want to learn ice magic, stripping off your clothes is the first step. Seriously, that's not a cheesy pickup line.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Sorry, but there's another girl I kind of...well, have feelings for .</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-horny.png">I'm sorry about getting..um, excited. I'm only human after all.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">W-would you mind not looking at me while you strip? This is awkward enough already.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Well, at least Natsu and Erza didn't come with me. The guild doesn't need to know how badly this went.</state>
                <state img="#-unimpressed.png">If it wasn't for my stripping habit I totally would have beaten you.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_major">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-smug.png">If you don't want to end up naked, you might want to start taking this seriously, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-unimpressed.png">I'd be happy to let you walk away with your clothes if you give up now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Hey, I might still have a chance after all!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I thought I was done for after I accidentally got naked, but I may still have a shot at winning this!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">And this just got worse somehow.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I'm starting to understand why everyone in the guild gets so annoyed when I strip.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Well, at least this job will be over soon if people are losing stuff like ~clothing~.</state>
                <state img="#-serious.png">When I get home, I'm going to train to overcome my stripping habit and return for a rematch!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_major">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-smug.png">If I hadn't taken my shirt off at the start of the game, I probably wouldn't have lost anything the whole game.</state>
                <state img="#-unimpressed.png">So, uh, are you trying to lose or something?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Did you get a little overconfident when I took everything off, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I'd be careful about playing this too much. My master had me strip for training and now I can't control when I strip.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-angry.png">Why don't you stop staring at me and pay attention to ~name~?!</state>
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">I better not hear any complaints. I'm keeping my word here.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-serious.png">Just remember a Fairy Tail wizard never loses to the same opponent twice.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">You might want to play better if you don't want to end up like me, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_major">
            <case stage="0-3" id="6" target="lucy" targetStage="4">
                <state img="#-angry.png">Hey, no fair Lucy! At least have Virgo bring me extra clothes too!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Sorry, but I won't go easy on you because you're a woman. I treat everyone who challenges Fairy Tail the same.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Wow, you're already taking that off? This may be the first time I've ever finished a job without getting naked.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-impressed.png">Given the amount of wardrobe malfunctions the ladies in my guild have, you'd fit right in.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Maybe this whole strip poker thing wasn't such a bad idea after all.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-horny.png">S-sorry, I actually don't have much experience with this. Honest!</state>
                <state img="#-impressed.png">Gotta say, I respect a woman who keeps her word. That's the kind of spirit Fairy Tail honors.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">This would have been more helpful when I was paying the forfeit.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">You were happy to watch me lose. This is only fair.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_major">
            <case stage="0-3" id="7" target="lucy" targetStage="5">
                <state img="#-unimpressed.png">Heh, we can always count on you to lose your clothes, Lucy.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Getting embarrassed yet, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I won't even need my magic to win this.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-serious.png">I won't lose again!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I've looked at plenty of Sorcerer Weekly pinup shoots but seeing a girl strip live is different. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-shocked.png">I did live with a female guildmate of mine for half a year, but it was platonic, I swear!</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Sorry! I'm trying not to stare at you, but it's hard not to!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">Are you sure you don't want to get naked? Uh, I mean I just want this to be over with quickly of course.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Not so fun now is it, ~name~?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-smug.png">What's the big deal? I went shirtless before the game even started!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Actually, now that I think about it, there's a lot of guys in Fairy Tail who run around shirtless most of the time.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I train pretty regularly so don't feel too bad if your abs don't compare to mine.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-angry.png">I was shirtless before the game started, and you're just now getting there?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-calm.png">One of my guildmates Wendy has asked if I want her to heal the scars on my chest, but I said no because they're important reminders for me.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I usually go shirtless during a fight. When I first trained to use ice magic, my teacher had me strip down in freezing weather to master the cold.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I bet these games would be a lot quicker to play if everyone started out shirtless like me.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-calm.png">I guess I'm the last person who has a right to complain about someone getting naked in public.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">This kind of reminds me of when I was a kid and Cana used to yell at me about stripping in the guild hall...okay, well she still does it.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Huh, so this is what it's like for my guildmates when I start stripping.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_small_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="1-3">
                <state img="#-unimpressed.png">I know this is ironic coming from me, but you should probably try not to strip in the future.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I'm an ice wizard, so I can say for a fact, it isn't cold in here.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I may have gotten naked first, but looks like I win where it counts.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-shocked.png">So, uh, do you have a thing for humiliation or something? I haven't even lost once!</state>
                <state img="#-unimpressed.png">For the record, you can't blame my ice magic for making you shrink!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_medium_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Huh, I don't think anyone's ever stripped before I did before.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I strip without meaning to constantly and you couldn't get me to lose once. Not your finest moment.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-3">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Well, I guess we can just treat this like we're at the guild's public bath.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Looks like we're pretty evenly matched.</state>
                <state img="#-serious.png">The only other guy I've seen strip at random in public is my fellow ice wizard Lyon Vastia.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_large_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-impressed.png">Wow, you actually managed to get naked before me. That's not easy to do.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Honestly, you might have the worst luck of anyone I've ever met.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-3">
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Uh, I think I accidentally used my ice magic on myself, so I just look a little smaller right now. That's all!</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">Any jokes about being bigger than me and I will use my ice magic to make you shrink.</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">Oh come on, you're bigger too! This is just pouring salt on the wound.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="lucy" />
                <state img="#-smug.png">Don't be so embarrassed, Lucy. At this point I've seen them plenty of times thanks to your wardrobe malfunctions.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Wait, you're really going to go topless?!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Maybe my stripping habit has finally become contagious!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I'm starting to have flashbacks to that time I dared my friend Erza to go streaking as a joke and she actually insisted on doing it.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_small_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-3" id="9" target="megumin" targetStage="7">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Guess with someone as small as you are, you probably don't need a bra.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-unimpressed.png">You kind of remind me of a guildmate of mine named Levy McGarden. She's always been a bit...size challenged.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I did take my shirt off before the game. Nice of you to return the favor.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Don't worry, I won't use my ice magic while you're topless. I'm not a ladies' man like my guildmate Loke.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Well, I guess that'll be a little bit of help with paying this forfeit.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_medium_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-3" id="2" target="panty" targetStage="1" targetSayingMarker="panty_angel_titties">
                <state img="#-impressed.png">Hey, you get naked almost as quickly as I do!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Now that I think about it, most of the girls in my guild are either flat or stacked. You're just in between.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">There's nothing wrong with being average!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I'm guessing you didn't plan to go topless in front of a bunch of strangers this morning, eh?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Uh, I'm not staring at you! Nope!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_large_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Um, I honestly forgot what I was going to say right now.</state>
                <state img="#-impressed.png">Well, looks like you'd fit in with the girls back at the Fairy Tail guild. It's a well endowed organization.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">This may be the best job the guild has ever sent me on.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-heavy.png">I may need to use my ice magic to calm myself down here.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">You don't happen to be an ice wizard, do you? Stripping is kind of our thing.</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Does anyone else hear rain? Uh, sorry. It's kind of a long story.</state>
                <state img="#-impressed.png">You're really gonna take off your ~clothing~? Gotta say, I'm impressed you didn't back out. Not everyone can strip in public.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <condition role="target" character="lucy" />
                <state img="#-impressed.png">You know, you may be the only Fairy Tail wizard who gets naked as much as me, Lucy.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-unimpressed.png">Wow, you couldn't even get me to strip once. That's a first.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-serious.png">Not to put more pressure on you, but you do realize if you keep losing like this we'll be doing this together, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-3">
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Uh, wow. I thought for sure you'd try and back out at the last second.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Thank you stripping habit. You're finally paying off for me!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Hey, I saw you look at me when I got naked. So this is only fair.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-smug.png">You couldn't even beat me once! You might want to practice more before playing again.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Either you were trying to lose on purpose, or you're just as dumb as Natsu.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-shocked.png">I do get naked a lot, but no one's ever...you know, touched themselves, while I'm naked before.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Doesn't matter if I'm not into guys. Juvia is still going to be jealous of you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-angry.png">Don't look at me and I won't look at you.</state>
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">Worst. Job. Ever.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Just try and get this over with quickly. I doubt that's a problem for you.</state>
                <state img="#-unimpressed.png">I may have lost first, but we're both still losers.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-shocked.png">I've seen a lot of crazy stuff during my time with Fairy Tail, but this takes the cake.</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">When I get back to the guild, I need to have a chat with Mira about the jobs she's posting on the guild board.</state>
                <state img="#-serious.png">This is even worse than the time Master Makarov punished me for taking an S-class quest without permission.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Welcome to the club.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-angry.png">Beating someone at poker usually doesn't mean they get to touch themselves to you.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_masturbating">
            <case stage="2-3">
                <state img="#-angry.png">Hey ~name~, did you know this was a possibility when you signed up for this game?</state>
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">I am so filing a complaint to have the Magic Council ban this place from posting job requests.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-1">
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">Okay, I might strip in public, but ~name~ is taking it to a whole other level.</state>
                <state img="#-unimpressed.png">I'm just going to ignore ~name~ and focus on the game.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Well, that just happened.</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Oh man, that's what I'm gonna look like when I finish?!</state>
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">I can't believe I have to do this too.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-1">
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Well, that just happened.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Another victory for Fairy Tail.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I ran around naked half the time, and you still couldn't beat me at strip poker.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Well, that just happened.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">So, was that as humiliating for you as it was for me?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Sorry, but looks like you're not in the same class as Fairy Tail.</state>
                <state img="#-unimpressed.png">Um, did you want me to see you do this? It's just...I didn't lose even once.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-smug.png">I guess getting naked was all I had to do to distract you from the game.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Sorry, but I stay cool under pressure even when I'm naked.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-shocked.png">W-we really are gonna do it together?</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">I, uh, guess I don't mind if we do this together.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-angry.png">Letting you watch me touch myself was bad enough. Letting you use me as inspiration is just adding insult to injury.</state>
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">Can you try and get it over with quickly at least? I'm sure we'd both like to go home as soon as possible.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Wait, have girls been doing this with the pictures of me in that story Weekly Sorcerer did a while back?</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Before today, I had never seen a girl do this. Sorry if I get embarrassed.</state>
                <state img="#-impressed.png">I respect you being a woman of your word, but I would let you out of this if you don't want to do it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-calm.png">I kind of feel like I should buy you dinner before we do something like this together.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">I won't tell anyone we did this if you won't, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Not as much fan when you're the one everyone is watching,  is it ~name~</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Just so you know it's even more humiliating when you finish in front of everyone, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Usually, the girls at the guild just yell at me to put my clothes back on when I strip. Nice to finally be appreciated.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I bet you thought you'd beat me for sure when I took all my clothes off right away.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Uh, are you staring at me while you're doing that, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">The other guys at the guild are going to be jealous when I tell them about what ~name~ is doing.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Guessing you didn't think you'd end up doing this today, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Well, at least this isn't quite as bad with some company.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">After doing this together, we should at least be friends, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Oh man, if Juvia finds out about this, she's gonna flood the guild hall...again.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-smug.png">How's it feel to know you couldn't even win one round against me?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Remember this humiliation the next time you challenge a Fairy Tail wizard to a contest.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Um, well, I...uh, I don't really know what to say. No one's ever reacted to me getting naked like that before.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Hey, what can I say? I'm a gentleman, so ladies first and all that.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate_first">
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Wait, what do you mean the game isn't over?!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate">
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-loss.png">I mean sure I strip naked all the time, but I don't touch myself in public!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="start_masturbating">
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-starting.png">Dammit, alright! Fairy Tail wizards always honor our word...even if it is humiliating.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="masturbating">
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-serious.png">I really hope this doesn't become a habit like stripping in public did.</state>
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">Oh sure, let's send the guy with a stripping problem on the strip poker job. Might as well send Natsu to drive a racecar.</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">Can't believe I have to do this in front of all of you.</state>
                <state img="#-serious.png">N-no, I'm not thinking of anyone specific! W-why do you ask?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Could you maybe not stare at me, ~player~? This is difficult enough as it is.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="heavy_masturbating">
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-heavy.png">N-no, not here!</state>
                <state img="#-heavy.png">I c-can't hold it much longer!</state>
                <state img="#-heavy.png">D-don't think about her, not now!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finishing_masturbating">
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-finishing.png">JUVIA!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="lucy" />
                <state img="#-serious.png">Lucy, I will do whatever you want if you don't tell Juvia I yelled out her name!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-finished.png">Look, uh, could you all please not tell anyone I said my guildmate's name just now.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_victory">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Wow, can't believe I didn't lose once. I guess that's why I belong to the greatest guild in Fiore!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Usually I'm the only one who gets naked in public. Guess everyone's joining in today!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_defeat">
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-loss.png">Aw man, I can't believe I shamed the guild like that! I may have a stripping problem, but this is a new low.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

    </behaviour>
</opponent>
