<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>

<!--This file was machine generated using the Character Editor v6.7.8 at 12:54:34 AM on November 13, 2022. Do not edit this file directly unless you know what you're doing.-->
<opponent>
    <version>v6.7.8</version>
    <first>Aloy of the Nora</first>
    <last />
    <label>Aloy</label>
    <gender>female</gender>
    <size>medium</size>
    <timer>22</timer>
    <intelligence>average</intelligence>



    <wardrobe>
        <clothing name="underwear" generic="underwear" position="lower" type="important" />
        <clothing name="pants" generic="pants" position="lower" type="major" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="shirt" generic="shirt" position="upper" type="major" />
        <clothing name="overshirt" position="upper" type="minor" />
        <clothing name="skirt" generic="skirt" position="waist" type="minor" />
        <clothing name="boots" generic="shoes" position="feet" type="minor" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="gauntlets" generic="armbands" position="arms" type="extra" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="necklaces" generic="scarf" position="neck" type="extra" plural="true" />
    </wardrobe>


    <behaviour>
        <trigger id="selected">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-Bored.png">Aloy here. Erend told me I should take some time off, so... here I am.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_selected">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="sucrose" />
                <state img="#-Confident.png">Good to see you, Sucrose. You taught me a lot about mixing herbs together. Maybe this time, I'll have something to teach you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="hu_tao" />
                <state img="#-Confident.png">Hu Tao, right? Sorry to disappoint, but I'm not dead yet. Haven't met a machine that can keep me down.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="barbara" />
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Hey, Barbara. I enjoyed your shows while I was in Teyvat. Guess you'll be putting on another one for us today.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="ganyu" />
                <state img="#-Quizzical.png">Still working hard, Ganyu? Me too. Maybe we're both here to try to relax a little, whether we want to or not.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="fischl" />
                <state img="#-Awkward.png">Oh... Fischl. That bird friend of yours still creeps me a little. I hope he couldn't hear me say that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="noelle" />
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Still working to become a knight, Noelle? Positions like that aren't as great as they seem... but good luck, all the same.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_start">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-Happy.png">We getting started? Alright, let's not waste any more time.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" hidden="1" addCharacterTags="genshin_impact">
                <condition filter="genshin_impact" />
                <state>This is what the character says when the game starts</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="swap_cards">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <test expr="~cards~" value="0" />
                <state img="#-Confident.png">I don't need any help. Not this time.</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png">This should be fine. My luck's working out this time.</state>
                <state img="#-Confident.png">I've always been kind of lucky, so... I think I'll keep what I have.</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">No thanks. This should be fine.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <test expr="~cards~" value="5" />
                <state img="#-Bored.png">...Better just start over.</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png">Yeah, this isn't working. I'll throw these all out.</state>
                <state img="#-Bored.png">You don't get these in the field, so... for once, I'll take a do-over.</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png">The first draw didn't work out. I'll hedge my bets on the second.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-Thinking.png">I'll take ~cards.text~ ~cards.ifPlural(cards|card)~. I think that's a good strategy.</state>
                <state img="#-Bored.png">...~Cards.text~? That should be fine.</state>
                <state img="#-Confident.png">I'll put my confidence in ~cards.text~ ~cards.ifPlural(cards|card)~. That usually works.</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png">Give me ~cards.text~. I could use it.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="good_hand">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-Thinking.png" oneShotId="472">I don't know a lot about games, but I'm pretty good at Machine Strike. Hope some of that knowledge transfers over.</state>
                <state img="#-Confident.png">A lot of people have doubted me. A lot of people have also been proven wrong.</state>
                <state img="#-Confident.png">Easier than hunting rabbits.</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png" font-size="small">Why do so many worlds meet here, anyway...?</state>
                <state img="#-Sarcastic.png">If you guys didn't want to see me naked this badly, you could've just said so.</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png">Maybe I should've gotten a good view of the landscape before we started.</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">I'm not so reckless as to do it for fun, but... there &lt;i&gt;is&lt;/i&gt; a certain thrill to hunting.</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png">Cards make more sense to me than people. They're just numbers. At least they're objective.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="2">You guys treat me with a lot less suspicion than I'm used to. It's... nice.</state>
                <state img="#-Sarcastic.png">Is this the part where I'm supposed to cover my chest and act like I didn't know what I was getting into?</state>
                <state img="#-Confident.png">I know I have nothing to prove to him, but sometimes I just want to rub my victories in Sylens's face.</state>
                <state img="#-Confident.png" oneShotId="14">Only wish I had some war paint. It's silly, but it makes me feel like I can take on the world.</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">You can get knocked on your ass all you want, but the important part is not staying down.</state>
                <state img="#-Confident.png">I'm not giving up until the hunt is over.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">It's hard to make sense of what I'm feeling right now. I'll just let instinct guide me.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">Stare if you want. I'll pay you back for it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-5">
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Feels like I just found some fresh salvebrush in the wild. Always nice to stumble upon just what I need.</state>
                <state img="#-Confident.png" oneShotId="6">It doesn't matter how many layers of defense you have. If you're my prey, I'll just tear right through them.</state>
                <state img="#-Stretch.png">&lt;i&gt;Mmh...&lt;/i&gt; Gotta make sure to stretch every once in a while.</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png">Ever gone gliding over an open plain? It's a lot more fun than I expected... not that I do it for fun.</state>
                <state img="#-Confident.png">The right tools for the right job. Always a good mantra.</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png">Find the weak spot and strike. Too bad none of you have obvious weak points.</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Nothing feels better than silencing the people who doubted you.</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png">Some people are happy just to make it through the day. Me, I'm always trying to do better.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="okay_hand">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-Bored.png">I'd say I can work with this, but... that'd imply there's anything I can do but wait for the result.</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png" oneShotId="1" font-size="small">Chances of victory are... &lt;br&gt; And the focus says...</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png">Lot of downtime in this game. Almost makes me want to pull out my supplies and start crafting.</state>
                <state img="#-Bored.png">Rost always said: "patience."</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png">I'm not usually one for small talk, but... I think I can learn.</state>
                <state img="#-Sarcastic.png">I'd ask the All-Mother to lend me a hand, but I know better than to put my faith in that stuff.</state>
                <state img="#-Bored.png">Guess I'll have to work for this. Nothing's ever easy, is it...</state>
                <state img="#-Bored.png">I'm about to start pacing. I don't know how you all can just stand around like this.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-Horny.png">A victory can be hollow... But here, I think that's less of a concern.</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png" oneShotId="7">Any of you know anything about machines? Might have to pick your brains later...</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png" oneShotId="8">I've always wanted to meet a person from another time. This place is perfect for me.</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">It took me a while to realize this, but strong allies are a must if you're fighting a strong foe.</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png">Honestly, I've never understood the taboo around nudity. I only respect it because Rost taught me to.</state>
                <state img="#-Awkward.png">There's a statue of me in Meridian. I don't like being revered, but... At least I look good.</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png" font-size="smaller">Why obsess over size, anyway...? &lt;br&gt; They all serve the same function...</state>
                <state img="#-Annoyed.png">I had a lot of defense... Wish my strategy was half as sound...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-5">
                <state img="#-Stretch.png">Any of you want to go for a run after this? It'd be nice to get some exercise after all this standing around.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png" oneShotId="5">I'm not much for faith, but... Hopefully these cards will show me something good.</state>
                <state img="#-Awkward.png">Never liked attention... but it's not so bad when it's for the right reasons.</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png" oneShotId="495" font-size="small">Beta could use some socializing... But at a place like this...?</state>
                <state img="#-Confident.png">I've gotten a lot better at climbing recently. Practice makes perfect.</state>
                <state img="#-Bored.png" oneShotId="12">Nobody's going to start raving about "Land-Gods" all of a sudden, right?</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png">I'm starting to get the hang of this. Never tried exposing myself for fun before...</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">As far as I'm concerned, you're all my prey here -- and I &lt;i&gt;never&lt;/i&gt; lose a hunt.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="bad_hand">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-Thinking.png">Even an AI couldn't win every time at this game, huh? Too much luck involved.</state>
                <state img="#-Nervous.png">...Sorry. Thought I heard something.</state>
                <state img="#-Awkward.png">I'm used to making my own equipment, so being stuck with something someone else gave me...</state>
                <state img="#-Nervous.png">Hunt's off to a bad start. Not too late to pull it back, though...</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png">I've got this instinct telling me to win at all costs... Need to remind it that this game isn't so serious.</state>
                <state img="#-Bored.png">Let's just try to keep this quick.</state>
                <state img="#-Annoyed.png">I don't want to be a sore loser, but... nobody &lt;i&gt;likes&lt;/i&gt; losing, do they?</state>
                <state img="#-Confident.png">I'm not so desperate as to &lt;i&gt;want&lt;/i&gt; to lose. I'll at least try my hardest first.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-5">
                <state img="#-Upset.png" oneShotId="9">I'm lucky I had Rost teaching me when I was growing up. He taught me everything I know about foraging, hunting, socializing... I miss him.</state>
                <state img="#-Awkward.png">The hunter usually doesn't become the hunted this fast...</state>
                <state img="#-Annoyed.png">Machines, AI, gods, dragons... Trouble just follows me everywhere.</state>
                <state img="#-Bored.png">And this is why a hunter doesn't divide her attention.</state>
                <state img="#-Annoyed.png">I think I have a reputation for being more blunt than I actually am. I just often deal with insufferable people.</state>
                <state img="#-Sarcastic.png" oneShotId="471">I heard that when Rost named me, he held me over a cliff and yelled it to the skies. A little over-dramatic, if you ask me.</state>
                <state img="#-Surprised.png">Huh, this is... Oh. This is pretty terrible, isn't it? Just my luck.</state>
                <state img="#-Nervous.png">{small}Let's see... No pairs, no matches, no... Hmm...{!reset} &lt;br&gt; Oh, sorry. Talking to myself is a force of habit.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-Horny.png">I thought this was a winning strategy... Well, it's not all bad.</state>
                <state img="#-Annoyed.png" oneShotId="11">Turns out "out with the old, in with the new" doesn't always result in something better.</state>
                <state img="#-Annoyed.png">Like getting discovered by a Thunderjaw... which is to say, this sucks.</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png">Nothing makes me want to strip more than the heat in the middle of the year... But that's usually a recipe for burning my skin.</state>
                <state img="#-Sarcastic.png">The Tenakth say I have hair like blood. I'm pretty sure it's supposed to be a compliment.</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png" oneShotId="505">The outcome doesn't matter to me either way... Though &lt;i&gt;winning&lt;/i&gt; feels like more of a punishment now.</state>
                <state img="#-Stretch.png">I'm not sure how much longer I'm going to last, so... It helps to stretch first.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">Should've known better than to underestimate my prey. So, ready to "eat" me?</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png">This is... probably a bad time to talk about "mounting," right?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="hand">
            <case stage="2" id="1" priority="999">
                <condition role="self" timeInStage="0" />
                <state img="#-Calm.png" oneShotId="17" marker="Focus">Oh, and this thing on my ear is called a Focus. It can interface with technology. It lets me see things about machines other people can't. I won't take it off. It's too important to me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <test expr="~background.location~" value="indoors" />
                <state img="#-Bored.png" oneShotId="4">If you grew up in the wilds, staying indoors for too long feels stifling. I'll play the game, but I'm not sticking around afterwards.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-8" id="2" oneShotId="1" totalRounds="7-">
                <state img="#-Calm.png" marker="HistoryPrompt">No Nora cares about dead people as much as I do. What about all of you? Anything interesting in your history?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-8" priority="0">
                <condition count="0" filter="genshin_impact" role="other" />
                <state img="#-Thinking.png" oneShotId="13">I've actually been to another world once before. It was a mystical land called Teyvat. Interesting place. Maybe some of the people there have found their way here.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="petra" stage="0" sayingMarker="petra_aloy_jewelsHair01" />
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="default" />
                <state img="#-Calm.png" marker="PetraNecklaces1Reply">I doubt I'll be changing up my look anytime soon, but... Well, a culture exchange doesn't sound too bad. I can teach you what Rost taught me, too.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="3">
                <condition role="other" character="meia" stage="0-5" sayingMarker="aloy0" />
                <state img="#-Nervous.png" marker="MeiaNecklaces1Reply">That's the gist of it, yeah. Us humans struggle to survive while the Cauldrons spit out more machines than we can count.</state>
                <state img="#-Nervous.png" marker="MeiaNecklaces1Reply">That's the long and short of it. I'm doing what I can to correct that balance, but it's hard enough for us humans to survive in the wild.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="7">
                <condition role="other" character="jura" stage="0-6" sayingMarker="aloy0" />
                <state img="#-Nervous.png" marker="JuraNecklaces1Reply">It's not &lt;i&gt;just&lt;/i&gt; machines. People can turn their backs on you at the drop of a hat. You've always got to be wary.</state>
                <state img="#-Nervous.png" marker="JuraNecklaces1Reply">I'm not &lt;i&gt;just&lt;/i&gt; cautious of machines. Humans have honestly caused me more trouble -- and they don't have the excuse of AI guiding them.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="9">
                <condition role="other" character="revy" stage="0-7" sayingMarker="aloy0" />
                <state img="#-Annoyed.png" marker="RevyNecklaces1Reply">...At least you get to the point. Yeah, I hunt machines. It's kind of a way of life where I'm from.</state>
                <state img="#-Sarcastic.png" marker="RevyNecklaces1Reply">...Points for honesty, at least. Yeah, I fight robots. High-tech machines with full arsenals of weaponry, but robots nonetheless.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="mercy" stage="0-6" sayingMarker="AloyRobotFoes" />
                <state img="#-Thinking.png" marker="MercyNecklace1Reply">Well, to summarize, self-replicating machines nearly wiped out life on Earth. A number of AI were supposed to restore it, but they were sabotaged and their own machines went rogue.</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png" marker="MercyNecklace1Reply">To get you up to speed, self-replicating machines pretty much ate everything on the old world. Some AI nearly restored it, but they were sabotaged and the machines they made went berserk.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="hu_tao" stage="0-6" sayingMarker="tao01" />
                <state img="#-Calm.png">I'm &lt;i&gt;a&lt;/i&gt; traveler, but yeah. I come from a world other than Teyvat, but I did visit for a time.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="hu_tao" stage="0-6" sayingMarker="tao11" />
                <state img="#-Thinking.png">Well, there's a lot. It really depends on what tribe you come from...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="sucrose" stage="0-7" sayingMarker="sucrose01" />
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Good to see you too, Sucrose. I should come back sometime. Starting to miss all the people in Mondstadt.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="sucrose" stage="0-7" sayingMarker="sucrose11" />
                <state img="#-Bored.png">No, it disappeared when I returned. My world doesn't have magic like that, so I didn't expect it to come with me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="sucrose" stage="0-7" sayingMarker="sucrose21" />
                <state img="#-Calm.png">Honestly? Mondstadt. I admire how you guys can live free. It's even a part of your faith. The tribes could use a belief system like that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="sucrose" stage="0-7" sayingMarker="sucrose31" />
                <state img="#-Stretch.png">...You think? I'm glad to hear it. I stretch and do some exercise to start off the day, but I think most of it comes from my regular activities.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="sucrose" stage="0-7" sayingMarker="sucrose41" />
                <state img="#-Quizzical.png">Huh? Speak up a little.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="17">
                <condition role="other" character="yuno_uno" stage="0-6" sayingMarker="yuno_aloy_name1" />
                <state img="#-Bored.png" marker="YunoNecklaces1Reply">It's Aloy. &lt;i&gt;A-loy&lt;/i&gt;. Pretty standard name among the Nora, I think.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="18">
                <condition role="other" character="yuno_uno" stage="0-6" sayingMarker="yuno_aloy_funTimes1" />
                <state img="#-Thinking.png" marker="YunoGauntlets1Reply">I don't do a lot of things for fun. Usually I'm hunting, climbing, talking, eating, or sleeping... Well, that game, Machine Strike, is pretty fun.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="21">
                <condition role="other" character="magma_grunt" stage="0-8" sayingMarker="mg_aloy_worldOffer1" />
                <state img="#-Quizzical.png">...Alright, I'm listening.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="other" character="sucrose" stage="0-7" sayingMarker="sucrose51" />
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png">I haven't thought about it that much, but... people who can handle themselves, I think. The ones that aren't afraid to rush into combat with me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="mercy" stage="0-6" sayingMarker="AloyHunting" />
                <state img="#-Happy.png" marker="MercyGauntlets1Reply">The same way any hunter does. Planning, intuition... and the tools of the trade.</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png" marker="MercyGauntlets1Reply">With a good plan, some intuition, and the right tools, any machine can be overcome.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="hu_tao" stage="0-6" sayingMarker="tao21" />
                <state img="#-Thinking.png">It doesn't happen &lt;i&gt;everywhere&lt;/i&gt;. Some tribes plant seeds. Others are just happy to leave their dead where they fell.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="hu_tao" stage="0-6" sayingMarker="tao31" />
                <state img="#-Sarcastic.png">What, a bunch of scattered tribes one bad day away from killing each other isn't the height of civility?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="blake_belladonna" sayingMarker="blake_aloy_wilds" />
                <state img="#-Nervous.png" marker="BlakeGauntlets1Reply">Well, that sentiment goes both ways. Difference is, I'd like to see some "fleshy" beasts. You probably don't want to meet any machines.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="blake_belladonna" sayingMarker="blake_aloy_outcasts" />
                <state img="#-Calm.png" marker="BlakeNecklaces1Reply">Nice to meet you too. It's rare to see other outcasts. I have to know, though... I've been an outcast since birth. How about you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="28">
                <condition role="other" character="cheryl" sayingMarker="aloy_neckA" />
                <state img="#-Calm.png" marker="CherylNecklaces1Reply">A little bit of this, a little bit of that. Anything the craftsmen in my world can scavenge off of machines, they put to use.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="31">
                <condition role="other" character="nami" sayingMarker="aloy0" />
                <state img="#-Calm.png" marker="NamiNecklaces1Reply">It's a little bit of both, Nami. My society is primitive, but a highly advanced one lived long ago. We use what they left behind.</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png" marker="NamiNecklaces1Reply">We're definitely not that advanced, but the society before ours was. We're just putting what they left us to good use.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-Calm.png" marker="Expo1">I guess this is the part where I introduce myself, right? I'm Aloy, a Nora Seeker.</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png">Right, maybe it's time for a proper introduction. I'm Aloy, of the Nora.</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png">I didn't get a lot of time to introduce myself. Name's Aloy, of the Nora.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-Confident.png">I'm up again? It's a good thing this armor has plenty of protection. I can last for a little while.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-Confident.png">You must all be taking this pretty seriously. That's good. I like a little competition.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-Nervous.png" marker="Expo2">Damn, another one down. I'm not very good at games. Not a lot of time for them when you're saving the world.</state>
                <state img="#-Nervous.png">A hunter getting torn apart like this... Well, if this were the wilds, I'd already be dead.</state>
                <state img="#-Nervous.png">Taking this much of a beating on a hunt... Guess I'll count myself lucky you're not machines.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-Annoyed.png">Hmm. Not a big deal. I don't mind the nudity. Just my terrible luck...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-Bored.png">All eyes on me again. I'm used to it at this point. Growing up an outcast, then becoming a Seeker, then the Savior... Most people can't help but stare.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-Calm.png">I've still got a couple layers of defense left. That said, I'm not too worried about winning or losing. I'm trying my best to relax.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png">Last one. I might look a little... excited. I don't help myself down there very often, so I get pretty pent up.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripping">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="MercyNecklace1Reply" />
                <condition role="other" character="mercy" stage="0-6" saidMarker="AloyRobotFoes" sayingMarker="AloyRobotFoes2" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png" marker="MercyNecklace2Reply">Our world still had our heroes, but I wish we had something like your "Overwatch." Maybe things wouldn't have turned out so badly.</state>
                <state img="#-Strip.png" marker="MercyNecklace2Reply">Elisabet, Project Zero Dawn... They were heroes, but nothing like your "Overwatch." Just a bunch of scientists and researchers doing their best.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="4">
                <condition role="other" character="meia" stage="0-5" sayingMarker="aloy01" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png" marker="MeiaNecklaces2Reply">...I guess that's not impossible. I've already met a few people from space. Ted Faro, the Faro Plague, Zero Dawn -- that ring any bells?</state>
                <state img="#-Strip.png" marker="MeiaNecklaces2Reply">...Well, I won't rule it out. You're not the first person from space I've met. Depends on whether the Faro Plague is what wiped out humanity for you, though.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="hu_tao" stage="0-6" sayingMarker="tao02" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png">...No, that's the other one. I'm Aloy. You know, the machine hunter? Thought you'd have heard of me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="hu_tao" stage="0-6" sayingMarker="tao12" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png">Yeah, it really just depends on where you come from. We all send off the dead in different ways.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="sucrose" stage="0-7" sayingMarker="sucrose02" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png">In my eyes, it was just another piece of equipment. I stuck to my bow, and I only tried to use it to augment my techniques.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="sucrose" stage="0-7" sayingMarker="sucrose42" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png">Huh. Didn't think you would care. Well, yeah, I have. It was... &lt;i&gt;alright&lt;/i&gt;, but it's not exactly a priority.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="22">
                <condition role="other" character="magma_grunt" stage="0-8" sayingMarker="mg_aloy_worldOffer2" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png">...Well, I can kind of see the logic in that, honestly. For the tribes, the sea isn't good for much more than fishing and getting attacked by the water-bound machines.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="sucrose" stage="0-7" sayingMarker="sucrose12" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png">In my world, we call them Freeze Bombs. Made out of metal scraps and Chillwater -- a liquid coolant used by machines.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="sucrose" stage="0-7" sayingMarker="sucrose22" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png">If only, Sucrose. Too many people let their faiths control them, even when they lead to nothing but carnage.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="sucrose" stage="0-7" sayingMarker="sucrose32" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png">A curiosity, huh? You're starting to sound like Sylens. Guess that's just how scientists think of people.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="hu_tao" stage="0-6" sayingMarker="tao22" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png">I liked the flowers in Teyvat, but it's not something I've stopped to think about. Traditions like that don't mean much to me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="hu_tao" stage="0-6" sayingMarker="tao32" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png">Trust me, I'd take Mondstadt any day over a tribe. They live free, but at least they have people keeping the peace.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="other" character="sucrose" stage="0-7" sayingMarker="sucrose52" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png">That's my &lt;i&gt;preference&lt;/i&gt;, but... Well, what's important to me is that it's with somebody I like.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="29">
                <condition role="other" character="cheryl" sayingMarker="aloy_neckB" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png" marker="CherylNecklaces2Reply">That's... part of it, yeah. If you can show everybody you took down a great machine, it shows you're not somebody to be messed with.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="5">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="aloy_carja_blazon" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png">You need to be armored up when you're in the wild. Otherwise, you might get your chest caved in by a Behemoth.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="25">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="aloy_carja_blazon" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png">This all might seem like overkill, but you need to be ready for anything when you're hunting machines. Would've gotten my legs torn off a dozen times without these.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Expo1" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png">And if that doesn't mean anything to you, then the Nora are my tribe, and Seeker is my rank. Not that I put much stock in it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Expo2" />
                <state img="#-Strip.png">I know how that sounds, but it's the truth. If any of you are from the old world, you might remember Elisabet Sobeck. Inventor of GAIA, and... my mother. Sort of.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-Strip.png">Good boots are necessary when you're out in the wild. Otherwise you might slip while climbing, or get your legs bitten off by a Snapmaw.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-Strip.png">This all might seem like overkill, but you need to be ready for anything when you're hunting machines. Would've gotten my arms torn off a dozen times without these.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-Strip.png">I don't mind my body being seen. It's not like I show off, but... I figure I've got bigger things to worry about.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-Strip.png">This place is... different, though. You all don't treat me much differently than anybody else. It's strange, but it's also... kind of nice.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-Strip.png">I don't usually &lt;i&gt;want&lt;/i&gt; to relax. I've got more important things to do. Every second spent laying down is one I could've spent on helping the world.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-Strip.png">It's been a little while since last time, so... Yeah, I should stop talking. You don't need to know all of this.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-Strip.png">And... I guess none of you know who I am. That's fine by me.</state>
                <state img="#-Strip.png">...Huh, that's weird. Most people have some sort of reaction when I tell them my name. Well, I don't mind.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-Strip.png">I've hunted plenty of quarry. Machines, animals... even humans.</state>
                <state img="#-Strip.png">As a hunter, I've faced down all sorts of foes. Machines, animals... humans...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripped">
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="MercyNecklace2Reply" />
                <condition role="other" character="mercy" stage="0-6" saidMarker="AloyRobotFoes2" sayingMarker="AloyRobotFoes3" />
                <state img="#-Happy.png" marker="MercyNecklace3Reply">I know. And... thanks. It hasn't been easy, but I won't stop until I've brought back the world Elisabet wanted to protect.</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png" marker="MercyNecklace3Reply">You're right, I know that. And... thank you. Elisabet fought to save my world for a reason. I won't stop until I've made it right again.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="hu_tao" stage="0-6" sayingMarker="tao03" />
                <state img="#-Confident.png">Hmph. Weird way to size someone up, but you're right. I don't plan on keeling over any time soon.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="hu_tao" stage="0-6" sayingMarker="tao13" />
                <state img="#-Happy.png" marker="HuTaoGauntlets3Reply">I'm an outcast, so I don't put much stock in stuff like that. But... the Utaru plant seeds, so new life can sprout from death. I think that one is nice.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="other" character="sucrose" stage="0-7" sayingMarker="sucrose43" />
                <state img="#-Horny.png">No, I had my sights set on bigger things. ...But, well, I'm not opposed to it, if the right person came along.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="23">
                <condition role="other" character="magma_grunt" stage="0-8" sayingMarker="mg_aloy_worldOffer3" />
                <state img="#-Annoyed.png">Well, as good as that sounds for &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt;, I'd still have to say no. I'm fighting to bring the world back how it should be. I won't let anybody screw that up now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="sucrose" stage="0-7" sayingMarker="sucrose13" />
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Yeah? I'll bring you a Blaze canister next time, then. I'd like to see what you could do with a mechanical source of Pyro.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <condition role="other" character="sucrose" stage="0-7" sayingMarker="sucrose53" />
                <state img="#-Horny.png">That so? You're a different breed from the people I know, Sucrose. ...Literally. If you're trying to bait my curiosity, you've succeeded.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="sucrose" stage="0-7" sayingMarker="sucrose23" />
                <state img="#-Nervous.png">Right, but it's not exactly something you can naturally synthesize. It's probably for the best that you don't rely on it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="sucrose" stage="0-7" sayingMarker="sucrose23" />
                <state img="#-Happy.png">It's in my genes. No matter who tries to stop me, I'm never going to stop fighting for what I need to do.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="sucrose" stage="0-7" sayingMarker="sucrose33" />
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Don't worry, I know what you meant. You're just... fun to tease.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Expo1" />
                <state img="#-Thinking.png">It's hard to consider myself a Nora, anyway. I was made an outcast at birth, and... I won't bore you with the details. We can just move on.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Expo2" />
                <state img="#-Upset.png">Since I'm the only one who can control her tech, it's my duty to finish what Elisabet started. Fix GAIA, save the world. If only it were that simple...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-Calm.png">I know "hunting machines" might sound weird. Machines are everywhere on my world. They're more like animals than the ones you're probably used to, and most of them aren't friendly.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-Nervous.png">...That might've been too morbid. Still, that's just one of the things I have to worry about. Machines are ruthless, so I'm trying my best to pacify them.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-Horny.png">Maybe you all can change my tune, though. The people I usually get attention from are rarely worth a second glance.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-Stretch.png">...That being said, I imagine you're all inclined to stare at me right now. Well, go ahead. Getting &lt;i&gt;this&lt;/i&gt; kind of attention isn't so bad.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-Happy.png">But this has been fun. I'm not very good with people, but I've enjoyed the time I got to spend here. So... thanks.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-Awkward.png">I've just never had a crowd before. Or, well, &lt;i&gt;anybody&lt;/i&gt; watching me. It definitely feels weird, but... I'm not complaining.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-Confident.png">If I'm a nobody here, it just means I have to prove myself. I'm used to that by now.</state>
                <state img="#-Confident.png">All this means is that I have to show you why my name is worth remembering. No problem.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-Confident.png">Don't worry, I'm not coming for any of you. But you're all still my prey, and I'm not giving up until I've won.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">I'm still on the hunt here, don't get me wrong. But... my goal here is something a little more intimate.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_strip">
            <case stage="0-10" id="24">
                <condition role="target" character="dunban" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Quizzical.png" marker="DunbanSabre1">A swordsman, huh? I prefer a spear, but I couldn't imagine going into battle without my bow.</state>
                <state img="#-Quizzical.png" marker="DunbanSabre1">Do you really rush into combat without a ranged weapon? Must be hard fighting with nothing but a sword.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" id="26">
                <condition role="target" character="dwight" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Nervous.png" marker="DwightBracelets1">...You seem nervous, Dwight. It's not because of me, is it?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" id="27">
                <condition role="target" character="dunban" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-Sarcastic.png" marker="DunbanCape1">So your world is ravished by machines too... Let me guess. The mistakes of an egotistical madman?</state>
                <state img="#-Sarcastic.png" marker="DunbanCape1">Let me take a guess, Dunban. A madman with delusions of grandeur messed everything up, and that's why you fight machines?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-Confident.png">Rare sight to get to see a man strip. Most of them are too scared of a machine attacking.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">I don't care about what you take off. Just how you are in a fight... and how you look underneath.</state>
                <state img="#-Quizzical.png">Let's see your scars, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-Confident.png">No shame in losing to a Nora, ~name~. We always get our mark.</state>
                <state img="#-Sarcastic.png">Men take defeat gracefully... as least, they're &lt;i&gt;supposed&lt;/i&gt; to.</state>
                <state img="#-Confident.png">I've still got plenty of stamina. The hunt's just getting started.</state>
                <state img="#-Sarcastic.png">I just hope you're not a man who thinks good looks is enough.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">A decent man is better than a good-looking one... but, well, both are nice.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <state img="#-Sarcastic.png">Some tribes might forbid me watching you right now. Good thing I really don't care.</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png">I may not have a lot of experience, but I can still see the appeal here.</state>
                <state img="#-Quizzical.png">Lots of questions I could ask you, ~name~. Tell me a thing about yourself first.</state>
                <state img="#-Quizzical.png">You're not dressed for hunting, so... more for appeal?</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">You've caught my interest, ~name~. Even the hunter gets ensnared sometimes.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">&lt;i&gt;This&lt;/i&gt; is the part of the hunt that always gives me a thrill.</state>
                <state img="#-Sarcastic.png">Going to show me your tribe's mating ritual?</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">It's rare I get to appreciate something like this. I'll have to give you my full attention.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-Masturbate Generic 1.png">Hmm... Hard to focus... I'll have to try for ~name~, at least...</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png">~Name~'s up? Good...</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">My Focus isn't picking up much... I'll need to see all of ~name~ directly...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-Confident.png">No need for shame, ~name~. See? I don't have much.</state>
                <state img="#-Sarcastic.png">My experience with men tells me they won't pass up an opportunity to show off.</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png" oneShotId="15">...It's odd that we come from totally different worlds, but we can understand each other without a problem. Hmm...</state>
                <state img="#-Awkward.png">There &lt;i&gt;is&lt;/i&gt; a thrill in being exposed... Well, let's see how ~name~ feels about it.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">The breeze here feels nice. I'm sure you'll like it, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_strip">
            <case stage="0-10" id="12">
                <condition role="target" character="chie" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Thinking.png" marker="ChieShoes1">Chie, right? I'm glad that people from other times like meat too, though you probably have more variety than I do.</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png" marker="ChieShoes1">I knew they still liked meat in the old world, but... even in my time, I've never met somebody as dedicated as you, Chie. Wish I had the same amount of variety as you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" id="13">
                <condition role="target" character="leonie" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Quizzical.png">Always glad to run into another warrior. I just hope you're fighting for a good cause, not the money.</state>
                <state img="#-Quizzical.png">Leonie, is it? I'm happy to see another warrior... though I do hope you're not only in it for the money. The cause is more important.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" id="6">
                <condition role="target" character="meia" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Annoyed.png" marker="MeiaEyepiece1">...Another human from deep space, huh? &lt;i&gt;Please&lt;/i&gt; tell me you're not with Far Zenith. They've caused me enough trouble...</state>
                <state img="#-Annoyed.png" marker="MeiaEyepiece1">Far Zenith aren't stupid enough to follow me here, right? ...Sorry, I'm just wary of people from space now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" id="8">
                <condition role="target" character="jura" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Annoyed.png" marker="JuraRapier1">You're... gaudy, aren't you? Dealing with people so self-important is pretty exhausting...</state>
                <state img="#-Annoyed.png" marker="JuraRapier1">I've met a lot of vain people in my journeys. ...They're always a real pain in the ass.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" id="10">
                <condition role="target" character="revy" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Thinking.png" marker="RevyGloves1">...That's an old world weapon, isn't it? I've never seen one like that in pristine condition. Wish I had something like that...</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png" marker="RevyGloves1">You're just trudging around old world weapons all the time, huh? Well, I'm at least glad I got to see one in good condition. Only wish I had one on me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" id="11">
                <condition role="target" character="mercy" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Thinking.png" marker="MercyGloves1">So where you come from, humans and machines live side-by-side? I wish I could live in a world like that...</state>
                <state img="#-Upset.png" marker="MercyGloves1">It must be nice having machines and humans living together, Angela. Wish my world was as united.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" id="14">
                <condition role="target" character="hu_tao" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Awkward.png" marker="HuTaoShoes1">...Honestly, I always thought it was weird that funerals are a &lt;i&gt;business&lt;/i&gt; in Liyue.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" id="15">
                <condition role="target" character="hu_tao" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-Bored.png" marker="HuTaoSocks1">I'm grateful for that "Vision" thing and all, but Liyue's obsession with their Archon felt wrong.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" id="16">
                <condition role="target" character="sucrose" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Sarcastic.png" marker="SucroseGloves1">So, how's Mondstadt holding up, Sucrose? Can those Knights keep it together without me?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" id="19">
                <condition role="target" character="sucrose" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-Calm.png" marker="SucroseBoots1">I've been finding a lot of really interesting flora in the west. Sometimes, it makes me think of you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" id="30">
                <condition role="target" character="cheryl" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Awkward.png" marker="CherylBoots1">I've never heard of a "Silent Hill" in my travels. ...Based on what I'm getting from you, it sounds like that's a good thing.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10" id="32">
                <condition role="target" character="nami" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Awkward.png" marker="NamiBelt1">Rare to meet a woman of the sea. Especially one who's so obsessed with money...</state>
                <state img="#-Sarcastic.png" marker="NamiBelt1">Are you just here to try and make money? Sorry to say, but I doubt you'll find Metal Shards as valuable as I do.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-Calm.png">I promise I'm not that judgmental, ~name~. Just meet a lot of people who need judging.</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">The card part is a competition, but you have nothing to prove now, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-Sarcastic.png">Some people see it as a badge of honor to get defeated by me. No idea why.</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png" font-size="small">I've always been pretty curious... Not to say ~name~ is nothing special, but...</state>
                <state img="#-Quizzical.png">Looks can be deceiving. Let's see what ~name~'s really made of.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">Why restrict yourself to men &lt;i&gt;or&lt;/i&gt; women? They both have their appeals.</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">You fought a good fight, and that's really what matters.</state>
                <state img="#-Bored.png">A good start, but I know better than to get complacent during the hunt.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <state img="#-Quizzical.png">Is it not a big deal when it's between women? I don't really understand that, but alright.</state>
                <state img="#-Sarcastic.png">Are you from a tribe too, ~name~? ...No, you're &lt;i&gt;way&lt;/i&gt; too open-minded.</state>
                <state img="#-Bored.png">I've taken a liking to you, ~name~. Really hope you're not secretly crazy.</state>
                <state img="#-Sarcastic.png">I've had some female admirers too... Not that they're easier to deal with than the male ones.</state>
                <state img="#-Confident.png">I'm open to anyone, ~name~, so long as they can keep up with me.</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Are you going to pay off my patience, or what?</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">You know I've been showing a lot of restraint by not coming over there, right?</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">I'm starting to feel all hot... and it looks like ~name~'s about to turn up the heat.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-Calm.png">This is the good part, right...?</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png">Hmm... I'll have to try to stay focused for ~name~...</state>
                <state img="#-Quizzical.png">I'm a patient woman, but... Everything has its limits...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png">This is normally no big deal for me, but... in this context...</state>
                <state img="#-Quizzical.png">Are you more fit for hunting or gathering, ~name~? Let's find out.</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png">Sometimes, I prefer hanging around other women more than men. Feels like they have less to prove.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">I'm already spent, but... you can still impress me, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">A lot of people see me as an inspiration. Have I inspired you at all, ~name~?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="tie">
            <case stage="0-10">
                <state img="#-Annoyed.png">...Well, &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; was a waste of time.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0-10">
                <condition role="target" character="dwight" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Awkward.png" marker="DwightBracelets2">I may be a hunter, but I don't go after other people. ...Not unless they give me a good reason to.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10">
                <condition role="target" character="dunban" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Calm.png" marker="DunbanSabre2">Hmph. Considering you're still standing, I trust you know what you're doing. What's your primary quarry, anyway?</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png" marker="DunbanSabre2">Well, you're here, so... I trust it's worked out well enough for you. What is it you use that sword to fight, anyway?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="18">I know "small" things can hold a lot of value. Rost's necklace is still special to me.</state>
                <state img="#-Sarcastic.png">Give it a thousand years, and a whole tribe could sprout up around ~name~'s ~clothing~.</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png">I won't disparage you, ~name~... but how important is it if you're willing to take it off...?</state>
                <state img="#-Sarcastic.png">I never knew this game was so... &lt;i&gt;thrilling&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-Bored.png">Never read about ~clothing.ifPlural(those|that)~ in any old world documents...</state>
                <state img="#-Stretch.png">Like going out to hunt boars and coming back with frogs.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <state img="#-Bored.png">My Focus isn't picking up anything. Must not even be worth scanning.</state>
                <state img="#-Sarcastic.png">That's all? No, great. I've got &lt;i&gt;plenty&lt;/i&gt; of time to kill.</state>
                <state img="#-Annoyed.png">...My patience is wearing thin. I said I came here for a good time.</state>
                <state img="#-Annoyed.png">You're not trying to get me to come over there and strip you myself, right? I don't fall for tricks like that.</state>
                <state img="#-Sarcastic.png">&lt;i&gt;This&lt;/i&gt; is what men had to offer in the old world? Really?</state>
                <state img="#-Sarcastic.png">Oh, no, don't worry. I'm used to men who can't back up their talk.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-Thinking.png">...Huh. Not really what I expected...</state>
                <state img="#-Upset.png">No, that's... that's fine... really...</state>
                <state img="#-Annoyed.png">Good thing I'm used to relying on my thoughts...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-Sarcastic.png">I don't like people who play games... And yeah, I know that's ironic.</state>
                <state img="#-Annoyed.png">You're taunting me, right? I'll get you back for that next time.</state>
                <state img="#-Awkward.png">A little teasing makes the ending better, right? I'm still figuring this out.</state>
                <state img="#-Bored.png">Stalling for time? That's a... valid strategy. Just not a &lt;i&gt;fun&lt;/i&gt; one.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-Calm.png">You've got nothing to prove to me, ~name~. Seems like you already know that.</state>
                <state img="#-Bored.png">That didn't take very long, at least. Let's keep the game moving.</state>
                <state img="#-Upset.png">I... appreciate the effort.</state>
                <state img="#-Sarcastic.png">Who knows. Maybe in ~name~'s culture, taking ~clothing.ifPlural(those|that)~ off is taboo.</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png">Worth recording in the Focus, at least. Maybe somebody can recreate ~clothing.ifPlural(them|it)~.</state>
                <state img="#-Stretch.png">Well, at least we can all stop to stretch.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <state img="#-Thinking.png">Trying to increase your mobility? I doubt we'll have to make a quick getaway, but you never know.</state>
                <state img="#-Awkward.png">...Still, I understand not wanting to be exposed, ~name~. It's... odd for me too.</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png">Oh well. Not exactly on my list of things worth getting angry over.</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png">At least we can keep this game moving along, right?</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Better than trying to impress me. I prefer men who can do that without trying.</state>
                <state img="#-Confident.png" oneShotId="509">Are you just going to be another cowardly man I've met, ~name~, or do you want to prove yourself better than them?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-Thinking.png">Skin against skin... always feels nice...</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png">The warmth of a fire, the sound of rushing water... I like that sense of peace...</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png">A nice, warm bed... Maybe somebody to join me in it...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-Stretch.png">&lt;i&gt;Mmh...&lt;/i&gt; Enough time to stretch, at least.</state>
                <state img="#-Upset.png">That all? Feels like we didn't have to stop and wait around just for that.</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png">You have nothing to prove to me, ~name~. Not sure if everybody else feels the same way.</state>
                <state img="#-Bored.png">Are we all stopping to stare? I don't see the point.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0-10">
                <condition role="target" character="hu_tao" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Annoyed.png" marker="HuTaoShoes2">I mean, everybody deserves to be sent off. Charging people money for it just seems wrong.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10">
                <condition role="target" character="sucrose" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-Thinking.png" marker="SucroseBoots2">It just makes me think, "I wonder what Sucrose would say about this." I know a lot about foraging, but you study this stuff for a living.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10">
                <condition role="target" character="mercy" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Nervous.png" marker="MercyGloves2">I understand how you must feel. Machines once served a peaceful purpose where I'm from. Hard to imagine that now.</state>
                <state img="#-Nervous.png" marker="MercyGloves2">I get that, really. People keep telling me that machines weren't as bad before I was born. I find it hard to imagine.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10">
                <condition role="target" character="sucrose" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Thinking.png" marker="SucroseGloves2">...Do you really have to do it like that...?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-Thinking.png">Wonder if ~clothing.ifPlural(those were|that was)~ made by hand, or by a machine.</state>
                <state img="#-Quizzical.png">I think I saw something like ~clothing.ifPlural(those|that)~ in a Zero Dawn recording...</state>
                <state img="#-Sarcastic.png">Wow, ~name~ is &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; busting out all the stops. I'm swooning.</state>
                <state img="#-Quizzical.png">We're still in the setup phase, right? I learned about that in Machine Strike.</state>
                <state img="#-Awkward.png">Are you more or less nervous because we're both women? Still figuring that out.</state>
                <state img="#-Awkward.png">Not a lot of time to worry about fashion in the wilds.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <state img="#-Awkward.png">Are you just psyching yourself up? Well, it &lt;i&gt;can&lt;/i&gt; be nerve-wracking...</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png">If you're hesitating, it helps to just move your body before your brain can stop to think about it.</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Really interesting stuff, ~name~. No, seriously. I've never seen anything like ~clothing.ifPlural(them|it)~ before.</state>
                <state img="#-Annoyed.png">At this rate, I should've just stayed back at base...</state>
                <state img="#-Sarcastic.png">Glad to see you saved the good stuff until I was nearly out, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-Quizzical.png">You're only psyching me up for the hunt. You know that, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-Annoyed.png">Ugh...</state>
                <state img="#-Awkward.png">Whatever... I'll make do...</state>
                <state img="#-Awkward.png">Hmph...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-Annoyed.png">...Is this an insult? It feels like you're taunting me.</state>
                <state img="#-Bored.png">I'm not too thrilled right now, but it's not like I'm going to walk over there and start ripping your clothes off.</state>
                <state img="#-Sarcastic.png">You're just being careful in case a Slaughterspine shows up, right? Smart. &lt;br&gt; ...That was a joke, by the way.</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png">I'm out of the running, right? All I can hope is that everybody else knocks ~name~ down another peg.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="0-10">
                <condition role="target" character="hu_tao" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-Nervous.png" marker="HuTaoShoes3">...R-Right. Nobody's come back to haunt me yet, so I'm pretty sure ghosts only exist in Teyvat. Over here, we just do it because it's the right thing to do.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10">
                <condition role="target" character="sucrose" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-Quizzical.png" marker="SucroseGloves3">You guys sure put a lot of faith in your knights. Wish I could have half as much confidence in the tribes.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10">
                <condition role="target" character="sucrose" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-Awkward.png" marker="SucroseBoots3">Not on me, but I'll keep it in mind for next time. ...Assuming you're coming back here.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10">
                <condition role="target" character="mercy" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-Nervous.png" marker="MercyGloves3">I'm glad you have that peace, but... Well, you don't need me to tell you how fragile it is.</state>
                <state img="#-Nervous.png" marker="MercyGloves3">Must be nice, living in harmony like that. Still, I'm sure you know that it can break apart at a moment's notice.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-Bored.png">Let's keep moving, alright? I don't want this to drag on for too long.</state>
                <state img="#-Sarcastic.png">Might make useful fodder for a Foundry, at least. Grind it into scrap, make more machines...</state>
                <state img="#-Sarcastic.png">No better time to practice sleeping while standing up.</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png" font-size="small">She seems a little nervous... &lt;br&gt;Because of the build-up...?</state>
                <state img="#-Quizzical.png" oneShotId="511">I'm curious about why you wear ~clothing.ifPlural(those|that)~. Doesn't seem too useful for hunting or gathering. Just for sentimentality?</state>
                <state img="#-Quizzical.png">I'm more curious about your hair, honestly. It's unlike any style I've ever seen...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <state img="#-Horny.png">It &lt;i&gt;does&lt;/i&gt; make sense to stall with the smaller things, doesn't it? Tease the competition a little?</state>
                <state img="#-Sarcastic.png">I'm not impressed... but, well, I've been told I'm hard to impress.</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png">Are you trying to attract a mate or something? You could try a little harder.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png" oneShotId="513">Peeling off your defenses is thrilling on machines &lt;i&gt;and&lt;/i&gt; humans.</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png">Just don't keep me waiting &lt;i&gt;too&lt;/i&gt; long. I... have things I want to see too.</state>
                <state img="#-Sarcastic.png">Don't steal all the attention away from the rest of us now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-Thinking.png">The rhythm of rain hitting the ground, feeding the land...</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png">The silence of night, hearing the beat of your own heart... Maybe somebody else's, too...</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png">The safety of shelter... No machines, no danger, just peace...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-Awkward.png">If the rest of you are getting impatient, you could... soak ~name~ in water? Make her want to strip as fast as possible? Actually, &lt;i&gt;don't&lt;/i&gt; do that.</state>
                <state img="#-Sarcastic.png">And here I thought people were inspired to do what I do. Not inspiring enough for ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-Confident.png">If I didn't know any better, I'd say ~name~ is trying to get me to go for a second round.</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png">I'll record it in the Focus, at least. Who knows, maybe I can learn something about the old ones from it.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-Thinking.png">That's... interesting. Not the kind of things I'm used to men wearing...</state>
                <state img="#-Confident.png">Letting down your guard, ~name~? Let's hope that doesn't come back to bite you.</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png">Nothing to complain about, but we're only just getting started.</state>
                <state img="#-Quizzical.png">So does &lt;i&gt;everybody&lt;/i&gt; walk around wearing something like ~clothing.ifPlural(those|that)~ in your time?</state>
                <state img="#-Quizzical.png">Can't be doing that badly if you've got ~clothing.ifPlural(those|that)~ to spare.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <state img="#-Quizzical.png">I see you're not too concerned with your defenses. Maybe you care more about your image?</state>
                <state img="#-Quizzical.png">Different clothes serve different purposes. ...~clothing.ifPlural(Do those|Does that)~ only serve to look good?</state>
                <state img="#-Sarcastic.png">Rost taught me not to judge other people for how they look. ...Don't worry, I'm not saying you look unappealing.</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">I'm glad that's not some sacred item you can't take off no matter what.</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png">The material your ~clothing~ ~clothing.ifPlural(are|is) made out of... The Focus recognizes it, but I don't...</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">This hunt's picking up steam. A little further now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-Masturbate Generic 1.png">&lt;i&gt;Now&lt;/i&gt; we're getting somewhere...</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png">Alright... I can work with this...</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Don't be a coward, ~name~... Be strong...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-Calm.png">...I see. I think I'm starting to understand your culture, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png">Does seeing me like this do anything for you, ~name~? ...I'm honestly asking.</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Nothing ventured, nothing gained.</state>
                <state img="#-Bored.png">Not worth going crazy, but... not worth complaining about, either.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_minor">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-Quizzical.png">I think I'm learning something from all of this. Not just about ~name~, but his culture, too.</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png">That's all? I'm not complaining. Just wondering.</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png">Keep track of your ~clothing~, ~name~. Who knows if you'll need ~clothing.ifPlural(them|it)~.</state>
                <state img="#-Quizzical.png">You can tell a lot about a man based on how he acts around women... and how he strips around them, apparently.</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png">I'd like to study the material of your ~clothing~, ~name~. I might learn something from it.</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">The hunt's just getting started. Don't run out of stamina now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Honestly, I'm impressed. It takes a lot of courage to make yourself more vulnerable on purpose.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">Be careful about making yourself more vulnerable, ~name~. A hunter's always ready to pounce.</state>
                <state img="#-Sarcastic.png">Let's keep up this momentum. Should be done before the sun goes down.</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png">Hmm... I don't know how fit you are for hunting, but a person like you would be a great help in my world.</state>
                <state img="#-Awkward.png">Do you make clothes yourself, ~name~? I've got a lot of skills, but tailoring is still a bit beyond me.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">Letting your guard down? Is that because you &lt;i&gt;want&lt;/i&gt; me to strike?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-Happy.png">&lt;i&gt;Phew...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-Stretch.png">I'm getting a little tired... Let's keep going...</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png">No problems on my end...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-Happy.png">We don't have to rush through this now. It's nice to stop and appreciate the moment.</state>
                <state img="#-Awkward.png">Let's just... keep moving along, alright? I don't like being exposed to the elements.</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png" font-size="small">...Really speaks for itself, doesn't it...</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Not bad, ~name~. But we can do better.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0-10">
                <condition role="target" character="hu_tao" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-Awkward.png" marker="HuTaoSocks2">Having some invisible deity watching over me all the time sounds more creepy than anything.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-10">
                <condition role="target" character="chie" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-Annoyed.png" marker="ChieShoes2">It's not about seasoning, but the choice of animal. We don't have a lot. If I eat raccoon meat one more time, I think I'll throw up...</state>
                <state img="#-Annoyed.png" marker="ChieShoes2">We have plenty of seasoning, but ARTEMIS could only bring back so many animals. I think I've eaten nothing but raccoon for days...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-Calm.png">I want to learn more about you, ~name~. I'm sure you have plenty to tell me.</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">So it's not forbidden for you to take ~clothing.ifPlural(those|that)~ off, huh? That's good.</state>
                <state img="#-Quizzical.png">You're in good shape, ~name~. I want to see just &lt;i&gt;how&lt;/i&gt; good.</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png">Is this strategy, or are you just nervous? It's fine by me either way.</state>
                <state img="#-Quizzical.png">Even in recordings, I've never seen anything like ~clothing.ifPlural(those|that)~ before...</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">It's always good to strip your prey's defenses before going in for the kill.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <state img="#-Calm.png">...I'd be lying if I said I wasn't curious. Still a lot to learn about ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">I'm studying ~name~... Always good to do research before you strike.</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">I think... maybe ~name~ and I could be allies. Just for a start.</state>
                <state img="#-Quizzical.png">Tell me all about it, ~name~. Not just your ~clothing~, but yourself, too.</state>
                <state img="#-Quizzical.png">I have to wonder what ~clothing.ifPlural(that's|it's)~ made out of. An alloy? An animal I've never even heard of?</state>
                <state img="#-Confident.png">A bit of a tease, aren't you? Well, that only makes taking you down all the more fun.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-Bored.png">Hmm...</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Okay... We're getting somewhere...</state>
                <state img="#-Sarcastic.png">Not bad... Not &lt;i&gt;good&lt;/i&gt;, but not bad...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-Awkward.png">...Mind lending ~clothing.ifPlural(them|it)~ to me? It's getting drafty... and it has a nice scent...</state>
                <state img="#-Bored.png">...I should check in on Meridian. Haven't been back since I went out west.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">You don't have to impress me. But if you &lt;i&gt;wanted&lt;/i&gt; to...</state>
                <state img="#-Sarcastic.png">I was going to complain about how slow this is, but at least it's faster than Machine Strike.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_minor">
            <case stage="0-10">
                <condition role="target" character="hu_tao" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-Sarcastic.png" marker="HuTaoSocks3">Well, I think this God of Commerce does a pretty poor job, anyway. I've saved the world twice over, and I'm &lt;i&gt;still&lt;/i&gt; getting ripped off.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-Thinking.png">Dressing lighter &lt;i&gt;can&lt;/i&gt; improve your mobility...</state>
                <state img="#-Confident.png">I wonder which of us will fall first. I don't mind competing.</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png">This is... more fun than I expected. I could use something low stakes from time to time.</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Nice to not be the center of attention for once.</state>
                <state img="#-Surprised.png">Tactical choice. Oh, are you not worried about tactics?</state>
                <state img="#-Confident.png">You've taken a blow, ~name~, but I know better than to underestimate my prey.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <state img="#-Happy.png">The Nora are big on revenge, ~name~. If you're gonna stall, I'll just have to beat you again.</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png">I think we've got good momentum. We should try to maintain it.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">Erend has more experience with things like this. I'll just have to catch up with him.</state>
                <state img="#-Awkward.png">No pressure here, ~name~. Unless me being under-dressed counts as pressure.</state>
                <state img="#-Sarcastic.png">I'd love to see what the Nora make out of ~clothing.ifPlural(those|that)~. They'd probably call it metal devil spawn or something.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">You've gotten me all curious, ~name~... about &lt;i&gt;every&lt;/i&gt; part of you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-Masturbate Generic 2.png">I'm... getting closer...</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png">...Huh...</state>
                <state img="#-Masturbate Generic 1.png">This is... getting easier...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-Surprised.png">...Oh, that's it? I hoped I had inspired something in ~name~, at least.</state>
                <state img="#-Nervous.png">I promised not to get too competitive, but it &lt;i&gt;is&lt;/i&gt; kind of annoying to be stuck like this.</state>
                <state img="#-Sarcastic.png">Show me something better, alright? I think I've already shown you &lt;i&gt;plenty&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png">I mostly buy clothes off of craftsmen and salesman... Don't know much about making them.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_major">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-Horny.png">You've caught my attention, ~name~. I hope you can keep it.</state>
                <state img="#-Sarcastic.png">I hope you're not trying to impress me. You &lt;i&gt;have&lt;/i&gt;, but it'd be better if you weren't trying.</state>
                <state img="#-Sarcastic.png">That's weird. When I'm not on a life-or-death adventure, turns out I can &lt;i&gt;enjoy&lt;/i&gt; flirting with men.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">Keep an eye on your ~clothing~. I'll... keep an eye on the rest of you.</state>
                <state img="#-Nervous.png">Isn't it a bit early for this? ...No, I'm just thinking about it too much.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">Now &lt;i&gt;this&lt;/i&gt; is the part of the hunt I look forward to.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <state img="#-Horny.png">Who am I to complain about a nice view?</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Wasn't sure how I would feel once we got here, but... this is pretty nice.</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png">I've seen plenty of men like this on my own world, but there's something different about ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Are you trying to make a show out of it? ...Huh. I like it.</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Afraid to show weakness? Don't be. Nobody can be strong all the time.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">I like men who can keep up with me. You'll have to show me if you can after this.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-Happy.png">...This is nice...</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">Mm... I'm starting to see the appeal...</state>
                <state img="#-Masturbate Generic 1.png">D-Don't... Don't keep me waiting, alright?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-Awkward.png">I'm pretty curious now. All this waiting is making me anxious.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">Worth the wait? ...I'd say so.</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png">You put up a good fight, ~name~. Even if you're taking blows, I'm still impressed.</state>
                <state img="#-Awkward.png">This is nice. Only wish I could appreciate it a little more.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_major">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-Happy.png">I respect a man willing to take risks. So, congratulations.</state>
                <state img="#-Confident.png">I almost feel bad that I've got so much left to go. Think you can take me down a peg?</state>
                <state img="#-Awkward.png" font-size="small">...It's too early to start getting excited, though...</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png">Let's keep up this momentum. We're starting to get into a good rhythm.</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png">You're not getting nervous because of me, are you? I'm not anybody special here.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">I think you're getting ahead of yourself. You're lucky I've taken a liking to you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <state img="#-Horny.png">Alright, that's recorded in the Focus. Just for preservation.</state>
                <state img="#-Confident.png">No stopping now. I don't ever leave a job half-done.</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Your body is definitely different from what I'm used to... Some variety is definitely nice.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">You're not out of the woods yet, ~name~. There's still a predator on your tail.</state>
                <state img="#-Confident.png">Wonder which of us will lose again first. I'm down for some friendly competition.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">My prey doesn't usually look this... delicious.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-Confident.png">Hah... &lt;i&gt;This&lt;/i&gt; is more like it...</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">I'm starting to see the appeal...</state>
                <state img="#-Masturbate Generic 1.png">...Just hurry up and join me already.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-Horny.png">...I'll just come out and say it. You've caught my eye, ~name~. Maybe we can get to know each other.</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png">I wasn't expecting a lot out of you, ~name~, but maybe I've grown to expect disappointment too much.</state>
                <state img="#-Confident.png">I can't influence the game anymore, but... does telling you I'm interested make you want to join me, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-Awkward.png">I haven't spent a lot of time with men, so maybe you have more experience than me, but... you get the idea.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_major">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-Happy.png">What's there to be afraid of? No machines here. Just go for it.</state>
                <state img="#-Confident.png">I know it's scary to make yourself more vulnerable, but... if push comes to shove, I'll protect you.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">Not sure how much my interest is worth here, but... ~name~'s definitely caught my eye.</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png" font-size="small">Hmm... I've not met many women from more developed societies, so...</state>
                <state img="#-Annoyed.png">Glad you're not keeping me waiting. It always annoys me when people are delaying the inevitable.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">Nothing to fear here, ~name~. Unless the predator on your tail has you nervous?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <state img="#-Horny.png">...Fine, I'm excited, I can admit it. ~Name~'s caught my interest, that's all.</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png">~Name~'s stealing all the attention? You know, that's fine by me.</state>
                <state img="#-Confident.png">Plenty of men have shown interest in me, but... I'm more curious what it's like coming from a woman.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">You want to know one great thing about the tribes? None of them really care if two women are intimate with one another.</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png" font-size="small">...This isn't good. ~Name~'s making me lose focus... &lt;br&gt; Is she doing it on purpose...?</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">I don't usually think of people like this, but... you're really cute, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-Horny.png">Ahh... Keep that up, ~name~...</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png">That's good... Your ~clothing~ ~clothing.ifPlural(was|is)~ just getting in the way...</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Easier to move around, right? &lt;i&gt;And&lt;/i&gt; easier to admire...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-Awkward.png">Only wish I could've taken part in taking ~name~ down.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">I'm surprised this game is still going, but at least I get to see ~name~ do this while my mind is clear.</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">To be blunt, I didn't think ~name~ had much to offer. For once, I'm happy to be proven wrong.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">Turns out, being honest is easy when you're dealing with someone as attractive as ~name~.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_major">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-Confident.png">Almost feels unfair that I'm still doing so well. Almost.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">Are you motivated to beat me yet, ~name~? I'm going to try even harder to stay on top, so get ready.</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Don't give up now, ~name~. Unless you &lt;i&gt;want&lt;/i&gt; me to take you down...</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Let's both try our hardest. A hunt's not fun if it's easy.</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png">At least your mobility is increased. Probably not worth the loss of defense, though...</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">You're not making this easy on me now, right? Starting to think you &lt;i&gt;want&lt;/i&gt; me to pin you down.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <state img="#-Awkward.png">...My friend, Alva, is in a relationship with another woman. I wonder what that's like, sometimes.</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png">I'm still treating this as a competition, but... It's difficult to &lt;i&gt;not&lt;/i&gt; want to lose at this point, right?</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">I liked the look of you before, but now...</state>
                <state img="#-Nervous.png">I'm gonna need to bathe after this... I'm starting to sweat...</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">I was wondering what ~name~ looked like under ~clothing.ifPlural(those|that)~, but... my imagination couldn't match up here.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">I mean what I say, you know. You're my prey, and I'm going to &lt;i&gt;eat&lt;/i&gt; you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-Horny.png">That's good... &lt;i&gt;Really&lt;/i&gt; good...</state>
                <state img="#-Masturbate Generic 1.png">Mmh... You're pretty good at this, ~name~...</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png">I... I can't focus...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-Confident.png">Next time, I want to be the reason why you had to take ~clothing.ifPlural(those|that)~ off.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">I'm actually having fun just watching. I... guess it helps that ~name~ is pretty good looking...</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">You've got a different look from the women where I'm from, but that's fine. I can appreciate styles from any era.</state>
                <state img="#-Nervous.png">I only wish I wasn't down and out before this happened. Maybe next time.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-Calm.png" oneShotId="20">This isn't a rare sight for me, but... I'm paying attention all the same.</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="21">I think I have more reason to care about this than most. A healthy hunter usually has some muscle.</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png" oneShotId="22">Isn't it better to walk around shirtless anyway? So all the sweat doesn't get trapped in there.</state>
                <state img="#-Awkward.png" oneShotId="23">I've never paid much attention to what men look like up there. Guess this place is making me more aware of it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8 10">
                <state img="#-Calm.png" oneShotId="28">I've already shown you so much, ~name~. Always fair to return the favor, right?</state>
                <state img="#-Confident.png" oneShotId="29">Remember, ~name~. Confidence is quiet.</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="30">The men here are a different breed from my own, but I'm pretty sure I can still enjoy this.</state>
                <state img="#-Confident.png" oneShotId="31">Hope nobody's thanking the Sun or any deity for this, because this was all me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-Masturbate Generic 1.png" oneShotId="24">Always nice to get a helping hand... Just don't keep me waiting.</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="25">That's nice. I was getting close to coming over there and ripping off your ~clothing~, myself...</state>
                <state img="#-Bored.png" oneShotId="26">Just show me something nice, alright? Make all this build-up worth it...</state>
                <state img="#-Bored.png" oneShotId="27">I was getting kind of bored, so this should be good...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-Thinking.png" oneShotId="36">Well, your anatomy's still the same. ...Never understood why men need nipples.</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png" oneShotId="37">No need for modesty. I've seen this a thousand times over by now.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png" oneShotId="38">Lots of tribes &lt;i&gt;love&lt;/i&gt; to have men running around with their chests bared. ...Wonder if the women had anything to do with that.</state>
                <state img="#-Bored.png" oneShotId="39">Nothing new to me. Maybe it's too early for me to appreciate it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8 10">
                <state img="#-Sarcastic.png" oneShotId="40">I'll flirt with ~name~ in the same way men flirt with me. You're... competent. &lt;br&gt; Only kidding. You look nice.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png" oneShotId="41">...I want to touch it. See how muscular you really are.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png" oneShotId="42">I think I can appreciate this more than most. I'm starting to get a little excited.</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="43">I'm glad you didn't run away, ~name~. Always like a man with some courage.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-Masturbate Generic 2.png" oneShotId="32">&lt;i&gt;Nn...&lt;/i&gt; Yeah, this is what I needed...</state>
                <state img="#-Masturbate Generic 1.png" oneShotId="33">Well, this just got a lot easier...</state>
                <state img="#-Awkward.png" oneShotId="34">Ugh, it's dripping... I almost feel bad for making a mess here...</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="35">&lt;i&gt;Mm...&lt;/i&gt; Gotta pick up the pace...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-Awkward.png" oneShotId="52">Now &lt;i&gt;this&lt;/i&gt;, I'm not very used to. I only see them when we're bathing, so...</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="53">This is what the game has been building up to, huh? Let's hope ~name~ doesn't disappoint everyone.</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png" oneShotId="54">I've never cared much about size. The person it's attached to is more important.</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png" oneShotId="55">I'm... not blushing, am I? Most things don't embarrass me, but this is a little much...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8 10">
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png" oneShotId="44">I've been looking forward to this... but that's probably pretty obvious.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png" oneShotId="45">Show me what you have, ~name~. I think I've shown you plenty already.</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png" oneShotId="46">You're supposed to make a show out of it, right? Well, I don't care much about that.</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="47">Don't keep us waiting, ~name~, or else you might get pounced on.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-Masturbate Generic 1.png" oneShotId="48">Finally...</state>
                <state img="#-Quizzical.png" oneShotId="49">I expect good things out of ~name~... Don't let me down.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png" oneShotId="50">I don't care that much about size, but... I'd be lying if I said I didn't like them bigger.</state>
                <state img="#-Masturbate Generic 1.png" oneShotId="51">It'd be nice if it was hard... Just to prove that this is good for you...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_small_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-Bored.png" oneShotId="56">Well, that's fine. I care more about confidence, really.</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png" oneShotId="57">It's more about how you flaunt it, I think...</state>
                <state img="#-Quizzical.png" oneShotId="58">Maybe you're more of a... "grower," I think? Not much to be excited about yet.</state>
                <state img="#-Sarcastic.png" oneShotId="59">Like the build-up to opening an old world container, and finding it has nothing but lint.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8 10">
                <state img="#-Calm.png" oneShotId="60">Something small can still make for a great tool. Just a matter of how you use it.</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png" oneShotId="61">Not my preference, but I'm not going to complain about it. It's not like you could make it bigger on the fly... Well, besides the obvious way.</state>
                <state img="#-Annoyed.png" oneShotId="62">I'm not so rude as to make fun of you for your size... Well, unless you make fun of mine.</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="63">You probably already know that you're not the biggest guy around. Only means you must know how to use it, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-Awkward.png" oneShotId="64">Not exciting, but... Mm...</state>
                <state img="#-Bored.png" oneShotId="65">...Hmph. Sorry, but this doesn't do much for me...</state>
                <state img="#-Awkward.png" oneShotId="66">Oh well... Not your fault, but...</state>
                <state img="#-Bored.png" oneShotId="67">This is a bit of a letdown, I'll admit...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_medium_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-Calm.png" oneShotId="68">That seems about average to me. That's fine. Never had a problem with average.</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png" oneShotId="69">This is... interesting. It's rare you see this when you're not gonna touch it.</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png" oneShotId="70">Honestly, this is just making me want to get out of these clothes faster...</state>
                <state img="#-Bored.png" oneShotId="71">I feel overdressed. That's pretty rare.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8 10">
                <state img="#-Horny.png" oneShotId="72">I've used... toys, I guess you'd call them, but honestly, nothing feels as good as the real thing.</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png" oneShotId="73">It's not like me to be getting this worked up. This place is really getting me in the mood...</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png" oneShotId="74">...What do we do after this is all over, anyway? Just say our goodbyes? Am I supposed to forget that I saw you naked... or how it made me feel?</state>
                <state img="#-Quizzical.png" oneShotId="75">Not bad. I just hope you have some experience.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-Masturbate Generic 1.png" oneShotId="76">Mm... Oh yeah, I can work with this...</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png" oneShotId="77">It's getting harder to sit still...</state>
                <state img="#-Masturbate Generic 2.png" oneShotId="78">&lt;i&gt;Ahh&lt;/i&gt;... Much better than doing it in the wild...</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png" oneShotId="79">Pretty forward of you... For once, I don't mind...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_large_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-Surprised.png" oneShotId="80">...Wow, uh... Give me a moment to collect myself.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png" oneShotId="81">Huh... I guess the men here really &lt;i&gt;are&lt;/i&gt; made differently.</state>
                <state img="#-Awkward.png" oneShotId="82">If you have it, flaunt it, right? I bet that makes all the other guys jealous.</state>
                <state img="#-Quizzical.png" oneShotId="83">It must be hard to hide it like that. Do you even &lt;i&gt;want&lt;/i&gt; to hide it?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8 10">
                <state img="#-Horny.png" oneShotId="84">Confidence, experience, skill... I think that all matters more, but I can't deny that size is nice, too.</state>
                <state img="#-Awkward.png" oneShotId="85">I've experienced a lot of different cultures, but I think preferring them bigger is a constant across them all.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png" oneShotId="86">I'm gonna be mad if we never meet again, ~name~. Especially if not in a context where we can be more intimate.</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png" oneShotId="87">I'm not the type to go after somebody after just meeting them, but... this place is messing with my inhibitions.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-Surprised.png" oneShotId="88">Wow, I'm... I'm stunned...</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png" oneShotId="89">...So you're just gonna show that to me and &lt;i&gt;not&lt;/i&gt; do anything with it?</state>
                <state img="#-Masturbate Generic 1.png" oneShotId="90">Well, you know how to make this easier, I'll give you that...</state>
                <state img="#-Awkward.png" oneShotId="91">Would it even fit? Ugh, I shouldn't be thinking about that...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-Calm.png" oneShotId="100">It's pretty normal to bare your chest in most tribes. Don't worry about it.</state>
                <state img="#-Bored.png" oneShotId="101">Size isn't very important to me up there. Your character matters more.</state>
                <state img="#-Sarcastic.png" oneShotId="102">Some men worry too much about size, to the point that they ignore... everything else.</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="103">I have an idea, but... better to see it with my own eyes, I think.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8 10">
                <state img="#-Quizzical.png" oneShotId="92">I've never cared too much about chests, but maybe ~name~ can change my tune.</state>
                <state img="#-Sarcastic.png" oneShotId="93">You'd be surprised how much of a status symbol these things can be. Something about bigger breasts being better for childbearing.</state>
                <state img="#-Confident.png" oneShotId="94">I don't care if you're bigger or smaller than me, really. I'm happy with my size.</state>
                <state img="#-Nervous.png" oneShotId="95">There &lt;i&gt;is&lt;/i&gt; something attractive about them, I'll admit, but it's not a huge deal to me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-Calm.png" oneShotId="96">This... should be a help...</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png" oneShotId="97">Not a big deal to me... Still, I appreciate it...</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png" oneShotId="98">I've had an idea, but... Let's see if this confirms it...</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="99">Don't hesitate... Just do it fast...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_small_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-Sarcastic.png" oneShotId="104">Smaller ones make it easier to climb... Probably.</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png" oneShotId="105">I think they're fine like that. Nothing to be ashamed of.</state>
                <state img="#-Nervous.png" oneShotId="106">I never understood why everybody cares so much about them being small. It's not like you can control it.</state>
                <state img="#-Bored.png" oneShotId="107">Maybe I could appreciate it more if I was more in the mood... For now, though, it's fine.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8 10">
                <state img="#-Calm.png" oneShotId="112">Some people prefer them small. Just gotta find them.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png" oneShotId="113">I can't really say why, but... smaller ones make you seem more like prey. Guess that makes me the predator.</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="114">You're pretty cute, ~name~. I think I can properly appreciate that now.</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png" oneShotId="115">I rarely think of other women as cute, but ~name~'s just giving me that feeling now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-Calm.png" oneShotId="108">I'm glad you didn't back out...</state>
                <state img="#-Confident.png" oneShotId="109">Nothing to be ashamed of, alright...?</state>
                <state img="#-Bored.png" oneShotId="110">Not exactly falling over myself, but... it's fine.</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="111">Could be better, but... it could be worse.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_medium_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-Thinking.png" oneShotId="120">It's an... interesting sight. Even where I'm from, it's allowed, but most women don't &lt;i&gt;choose&lt;/i&gt; to walk around with their breasts out.</state>
                <state img="#-Quizzical.png" oneShotId="121">I've always been curious about why so many animals have breasts... I'd imagine they knew in the old world.</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png" oneShotId="122">I don't like walking around with mine out, personally. That's why I've been avoiding it...</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png" oneShotId="123">It's less of a penalty if you think about how everybody is appreciating it, I think.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8 10">
                <state img="#-Awkward.png" oneShotId="116">...I'm a little lucky that Elisabet was on the larger side, I think.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png" oneShotId="117">You know, I think I'm starting to see the appeal.</state>
                <state img="#-Awkward.png" oneShotId="118">Are they... hard? That usually only happens to me when it's cold...</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="119">It's a nice view, I'll give you that. Still, you've got something better to show, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-Masturbate Generic 2.png" oneShotId="124">...I wonder how it would feel if we pressed ours together...</state>
                <state img="#-Masturbate Generic 1.png" oneShotId="125">I think we're about the same size... That means I know how to treat you.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png" oneShotId="126">Not bad. It helps that I'm in the right state of mind to appreciate them...</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="127">Not my favorite part, but this &lt;i&gt;is&lt;/i&gt; fun...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_large_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-Awkward.png" oneShotId="128">Huh... I don't place any faith in deities, but one must've been watching over you.</state>
                <state img="#-Quizzical.png" oneShotId="129">That would just make it harder to get around, wouldn't it?</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png" oneShotId="130">I bet you get a lot of stares because of that. Hope that doesn't get you down.</state>
                <state img="#-Awkward.png" oneShotId="131">I say it's about how you flaunt it, but it must be easier when they're that big. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8 10">
                <state img="#-Awkward.png" oneShotId="132">It's not my preference, but... Ugh, fine, it &lt;i&gt;is&lt;/i&gt; attractive. You happy?</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="133">You must be pretty proud of those. Pride always comes before a fall, though.</state>
                <state img="#-Confident.png" oneShotId="134">I can't match up in that department, but that's fine by me.</state>
                <state img="#-Awkward.png" oneShotId="135">It &lt;i&gt;would&lt;/i&gt; be nice to get my hands on them, and... No, I shouldn't say that...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-Masturbate Generic 1.png" oneShotId="136">Well, that makes this easier...</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png" oneShotId="137">Seems like they'd be nice to play with...</state>
                <state img="#-Quizzical.png" oneShotId="138">I have to wonder how sensitive they are...</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png" oneShotId="139">I think I can work with this...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-Surprised.png" oneShotId="140">...Wow, didn't expect this so soon. Maybe I'm better at games than I thought.</state>
                <state img="#-Confident.png" oneShotId="141">Sorry about this, ~name~, but one of us had to come out on top. Guess it had to be me.</state>
                <state img="#-Awkward.png" oneShotId="142">It's not a big deal to me. Unless you're already dripping wet or something, but...</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png" oneShotId="143">It had to come to this eventually. Better than just standing around fully clothed while everybody else goes at it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8 10">
                <state img="#-Calm.png" oneShotId="144">We're not too far off from one another, so... It's not a surprise.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png" oneShotId="145">I'm curious, ~name~... Not just what you look like, but maybe if I've excited you.</state>
                <state img="#-Awkward.png" oneShotId="146">You can't complain about this, right? You knew what would happen. We all did.</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png" oneShotId="147">If you fail, you have to pay the consequences. At least they're not so bad here.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-Calm.png" oneShotId="148">Ready to join me, ~name~? I hope so...</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png" oneShotId="149">I wonder if you're as wet as I am...</state>
                <state img="#-Quizzical.png" oneShotId="150">...Always wondered what women from other times looked like...</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="151">I won't record this in the Focus... It'll just live in my memory...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-Bored.png" oneShotId="152">...Well, it's just a little slit at the end of the day. Still, worth the wait.</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png" oneShotId="153">The tease is more fun than the reveal, I think...</state>
                <state img="#-Awkward.png" oneShotId="154">Not much left to go. Sorry if I'm not much to look at right now.</state>
                <state img="#-Nervous.png" oneShotId="155">A lot can change in an instant, but... Yeah, I think ~name~ should get ready for what comes next.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8 10">
                <state img="#-Horny.png" oneShotId="156">&lt;i&gt;Somebody's&lt;/i&gt; excited.</state>
                <state img="#-Confident.png" oneShotId="157">Don't hide it, ~name~. Walking around without caring about what anybody thinks about your body is pretty freeing.</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="158">It's not much to look at, but, well, there's a lot you can do with it.</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png" oneShotId="159">...I've never actually been with another woman, so... it's hard for me to judge.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-Masturbate Generic 1.png" oneShotId="160">Feel free to join me whenever...</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="161">...You're excited. I'm happy to see that...</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="162">I don't know how ours match up, but... you're pretty down there.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png" oneShotId="163">The sight is one thing, but... the feel is another...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8 10" priority="0">
                <condition filter="hairy" role="target" />
                <state img="#-Thinking.png" oneShotId="196">Helps to keep stuff out of there, right? At least, I think that's the point of the hair.</state>
                <state img="#-Sarcastic.png" oneShotId="197">Nobody really shaves where I'm from. Who has time for that?</state>
                <state img="#-Quizzical.png" oneShotId="198">Seems we're similar in one way. I don't know if it's just because of laziness or lack of time for you, though.</state>
                <state img="#-Sarcastic.png" oneShotId="199">...Do people here &lt;i&gt;actually&lt;/i&gt; care that much about hair? Actually, scratch that. I'm more than used to people caring way too much about the stupidest things.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8 10" priority="0">
                <condition filter="shaved" role="target" />
                <state img="#-Awkward.png" oneShotId="192">...Weird. I've never met a woman who shaves before.</state>
                <state img="#-Surprised.png" oneShotId="193">Wow, uh, that honestly surprised me. I'm so used to seeing a ton of hair down there...</state>
                <state img="#-Quizzical.png" oneShotId="194">I... guess this was a thing people did in the old world.</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png" oneShotId="195">...Okay, I'm starting to realize I actually a preference for hair.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_lost">
            <case stage="0-8" oneShotId="2">
                <condition count="0" filter="post-apocalyptic" role="target" />
                <state img="#-Thinking.png">I &lt;i&gt;am&lt;/i&gt; curious about your world, considering it's not totally in ruins like my own, but... you're not from &lt;i&gt;my&lt;/i&gt; Earth, are you? That's what I care about most.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_stripped">
            <case stage="0-10">
                <condition filter="royalty" role="target" />
                <state img="#-Calm.png" oneShotId="16">I don't place too much stock in royalty, but I've met a few good ones. Sun-King Avad is a good man, even if he can come on a little strong.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0-8 10">
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="164">I can only imagine how a man does it. Care to demonstrate for me, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png" oneShotId="165">Sometimes, I've wondered if men do this while thinking about me...</state>
                <state img="#-Confident.png" oneShotId="166">I've been looking forward to this part. Happy you caught my eye, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-Quizzical.png" oneShotId="167">Nothing else to do. I don't think you're the type to back out now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-Masturbate Generic 2.png" oneShotId="168">Come on, ~name~... Join me...</state>
                <state img="#-Masturbate Generic 1.png" oneShotId="169">Contact is better, but... I can live with looking...</state>
                <state img="#-Bored.png" oneShotId="170">It's about time...</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png" oneShotId="171">Oh, I've definitely been looking forward to this...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8 10">
                <state img="#-Awkward.png" oneShotId="172">Well... Good luck. ...I don't know what else to say.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png" oneShotId="173">You can look at me, if you'd like. That'd be pretty flattering, honestly.</state>
                <state img="#-Confident.png" oneShotId="174">I receive plenty of attention from men, but this is the first time I actually &lt;i&gt;want&lt;/i&gt; it.</state>
                <state img="#-Quizzical.png" oneShotId="175">Is there skill or technique involved with it, or do you just go with the flow? Guess I'll find out.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-Calm.png" oneShotId="176">Doing things together is definitely easier than going at it alone...</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png" oneShotId="177">I hope... I can encourage you, ~name~. You're definitely encouraging me.</state>
                <state img="#-Masturbate Generic 1.png" oneShotId="178">I think it'll be easier like this... for both of us.</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="179">Hard to concentrate, but... I'll try for you, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8 10">
                <state img="#-Quizzical.png">I'm... learning something about technique, at least...</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png">That must take a lot of energy, huh? Save some for the journey back home.</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png">Am I on your mind right now? ...I wouldn't mind if I was.</state>
                <state img="#-Awkward.png">This is awkward, isn't it? I mean, I'm just standing around...</state>
                <state img="#-Annoyed.png">Just say what you're feeling. I hate it when people dance around their feelings.</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png">Do you like getting watched? I guess you must, seeing how hard you are...</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">I don't know what I'm supposed to say right now. All I can tell you is that watching ~name~ is more fun than I expected.</state>
                <state img="#-Stretch.png">It's better when you can feel the wind in your hair on a breezy day, isn't it?</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">I've imagined how men must do it, sometimes. The reality is definitely better.</state>
                <state img="#-Sarcastic.png">With the way you're going at it, I'm almost starting to think you like me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-Awkward.png">Not much for getting intimate with strangers, but... we're hardly strangers at this point.</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">You're making nice noises. Never heard them out of a man before...</state>
                <state img="#-Masturbate Generic 1.png">I'm just glad I'm not going at it alone. Always better to have allies...</state>
                <state img="#-Awkward.png">Just, um... try not to get any of it on me, alright...?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8 10">
                <state img="#-Sarcastic.png" oneShotId="180">If any of that gets on me, am I gonna get pregnant? &lt;br&gt; ...I'm kidding. Still got a &lt;i&gt;lot&lt;/i&gt; left to do before I think about kids.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png" oneShotId="181">That was fun to watch. I'll have to preserve a recording for future generations.</state>
                <state img="#-Awkward.png" oneShotId="182">I've never seen a man finish... outside. There was more than I expected...</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png" oneShotId="183">You know, whenever I imagined a man doing it, I always... thought of them yelling my name when they finished. ...I guess that's what you call a fantasy.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-Masturbate Generic 1.png" oneShotId="185">I'm getting there myself...</state>
                <state img="#-Confident.png" oneShotId="186">Beating me to it, ~name~? You're lucky this isn't a competition...</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png" oneShotId="187">I need to pick up my pace, apparently...</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png" oneShotId="184">I wonder how it would feel inside of me... Ugh, I'm feeling weird...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0-8 10">
                <state img="#-Happy.png" oneShotId="188">You knew the rules, ~name~. Ready to put on a show?</state>
                <state img="#-Annoyed.png" oneShotId="189">Just don't back out halfway through. There's nothing I hate more than a job half-done.</state>
                <state img="#-Confident.png" oneShotId="190">Well? Show us what you can do.</state>
                <state img="#-Sarcastic.png" oneShotId="191">There's no danger, no monsters, no machines. Just you, and a group of people watching your every move. No pressure.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-Bored.png" oneShotId="200">...Oh, ~name~'s out? I wasn't paying attention...</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png" oneShotId="201">Well, don't keep me waiting...</state>
                <state img="#-Confident.png" oneShotId="202">If I can do it... Well, I won't say you can do it too, but you can try.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png" oneShotId="203">Give it your best, ~name~... I already am...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8 10">
                <state img="#-Calm.png" oneShotId="204">Me watching shouldn't be &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; big of a deal, right? I'm a nobody here.</state>
                <state img="#-Awkward.png" oneShotId="205">I won't stare at you if you don't want me to. I hate it when people do that to me. At the same time... you came here because you want people to look, right?</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png" oneShotId="206">It's awkward to just watch, but I'm glad I can give you all of my attention without distractions.</state>
                <state img="#-Quizzical.png" oneShotId="207">I've done it myself, but there are definitely still things for me to learn... I'm curious what ~name~ can teach me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-Calm.png" oneShotId="208">Let's see if it's better with friends...</state>
                <state img="#-Masturbate Generic 1.png" oneShotId="209">Now &lt;i&gt;this&lt;/i&gt; is an experience I could never have back home...</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png" oneShotId="210">If you want to touch me... that's fine, honestly. So long as I can do the same in turn.</state>
                <state img="#-Sarcastic.png" oneShotId="211">Two attractive women going at it next to each other? Who would ever want to see &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt;?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8 10">
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png">Your method is different, but not too far off from mine... Guess that's one thing that doesn't change.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">You rely on sound a lot as a hunter. ...That's probably why ~name~'s noises are making me so hot.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">Seeing somebody's body in a different light like this is pretty captivating...</state>
                <state img="#-Awkward.png">The sight of a naked woman alone doesn't do a lot for me. Seeing her do &lt;i&gt;this&lt;/i&gt;, though...</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png">I wonder how culture effects our attraction to others. If I weren't a Nora, would I still be looking at ~name~ like this...?</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">There's some biological reason why I'm feeling like this, I'm sure. I don't care about that. I only care about how ~name~ makes me feel.</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Your whole body is trembling. Normally I'd be concerned. Right now, I'm just amused.</state>
                <state img="#-Awkward.png">...I hope it's not just the women in Meridian that think I'm attractive.</state>
                <state img="#-Quizzical.png">I'm surprised you're able to do that without much trouble. Even when I'm alone, it usually takes me longer...</state>
                <state img="#-Awkward.png">...Ugh. I don't mind the excitement, but I'm not much of a fan of the mess...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-Happy.png">Mmph... Maybe I should try copying you...</state>
                <state img="#-Confident.png">It's not a competition, but... we could make it one.</state>
                <state img="#-Nervous.png">Ugh, I'm getting covered in sweat... It's all because of ~name~...</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">Getting deep inside myself is one thing... Getting deep inside ~name~, though...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8 10">
                <state img="#-Horny.png" oneShotId="216">That was... pretty great. I hate being this excited when I can't act on it... Maybe you can help me out, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-Awkward.png" oneShotId="217">I hope this place doesn't make me develop any weird fetishes. People already think I'm strange.</state>
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png" oneShotId="218">Did I help with that at all? I'm not sure if you were even looking at me.</state>
                <state img="#-Stretch.png" oneShotId="219">Pretty exhausting, right? We can stretch together if you'd like. Always helps me feel less tired.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-Horny.png" oneShotId="212">I-I'm getting there too...</state>
                <state img="#-Awkward.png" oneShotId="213">Damn... I wanted to finish first... Be the one to egg ~name~ on...</state>
                <state img="#-Masturbate Generic 2.png" oneShotId="214">Huh? Oh, ~name~'s done... I-I can't concentrate...</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png" oneShotId="215">Just a little more... I'll be there with ~name~ soon...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate_first">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-Confident.png">...Me first. I'm so used to having to prove myself, work harder than anybody to be the best. But... for once, I don't mind being in last.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-Awkward.png">...Honestly, I don't care at this point. It'd be &lt;i&gt;more&lt;/i&gt; of a punishment if I just had to walk out of here while I'm still craving something.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="start_masturbating">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-Horny.png">I don't mind if you all stare. I'd actually find it comforting if I knew you liked this. ...Alright, here goes nothing.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="masturbating">
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-Horny.png">&lt;i&gt;Ah&lt;/i&gt;... Never been watched before... It's not so bad...</state>
                <state img="#-Awkward.png">I'm not... &lt;i&gt;totally&lt;/i&gt; inexperienced... but I've still got things to learn...</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">I already know how good this feels... Wish I could do it more often...</state>
                <state img="#-Masturbate Generic 1.png">Being near the same people for so long at our base... Sometimes, I get temptations...</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png">I don't have all the fancy material they had in the old world, but... my imagination suits me fine...</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png">It helps to think of sensations... Like the warmth of a Blaze canister on a chilly night...</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png">Better than doing it in the wilds... I can tell you that much...</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">I know how to make myself feel best, but... you have to work up to it...</state>
                <state img="#-Awkward.png">I haven't spent a lot of time with men &lt;i&gt;or&lt;/i&gt; women, but... this place is making me curious...</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">&lt;i&gt;Mmph...&lt;/i&gt; Can't rush it... Just be patient and build up to it...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="heavy_masturbating">
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-Embarrassed.png" oneShotId="458">&lt;i&gt;Nngh...&lt;/i&gt; I can't... stop these noises...</state>
                <state img="#-Masturbate Generic 2.png" oneShotId="459">I-I'm losing control...</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png" oneShotId="460">I-I'm going to... Mm...</state>
                <state img="#-Masturbate Generic 2.png" oneShotId="461">&lt;i&gt;Hah&lt;/i&gt;... Deep breaths... Just ride it out...!</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png" oneShotId="462">This is going... a lot better than I thought it would, hah...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finishing_masturbating">
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-Finish.png">&lt;i&gt;Ah... I'm... Mm!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-Finish.png">&lt;i&gt;Oh... That's... Ahh!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-Awkward.png">Wow, that was, um... &lt;i&gt;a lot&lt;/i&gt; better than I expected. I didn't realize how much I needed that.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="after_masturbating">
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-Awkward.png" oneShotId="19">It might be weird to get back on my feet so soon, but I hate sitting around for too long.</state>
                <state img="#-Sarcastic.png">HADES caused me a lot of trouble. I thought things might get easier when he was destroyed. Hah, as if my life's ever been easy.</state>
                <state img="#-Calm.png">Some people think of AI like they're just tools. The ones I know... they're more human than some &lt;i&gt;people&lt;/i&gt; I've met.</state>
                <state img="#-Bored.png">...Sorry if I was too self-conscious back there. I'm just too used to people looking at me like I'm some kind of freak, or their savior. I'm really just a person.</state>
                <state img="#-Happy.png">After the Battle of the Alight, I didn't want any of my friends to get caught up in my battles. ...I won't make that mistake again.</state>
                <state img="#-Thinking.png">Before I was born, most machines were actually docile. I hope I can make a world like that again, someday.</state>
                <state img="#-Annoyed.png">This guy in the old world, Ted Faro, caused a &lt;i&gt;lot&lt;/i&gt; of problems. If you see him in your time period, punch him in the face for me.</state>
                <state img="#-Stretch.png">Nothing like riding around on a machine with the wind on your back after a ~background.time~ like this.</state>
                <state img="#-Horny.png">I need some time to rest, but... maybe another round wouldn't hurt...</state>
                <state img="#-Awkward.png">...I didn't tell any of my friends about this, by the way. This is &lt;i&gt;strictly&lt;/i&gt; between us.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_victory">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-Annoyed.png">Oh, that's it? Really? Could you put up more of a fight next time?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <state img="#-Annoyed.png">...Hmm. That's annoying. Just when I was getting started. Could you all put up more of a fight next time?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_defeat">
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-Happy.png">That was a good time. I don't have much more time to spare, but maybe you'll see me around. Until next time, ~player~.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

    </behaviour>
</opponent>
