<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<metadata>
    <owner>meia</owner>
    <noteworthy>
        <case name="Mahiru Selfie" min="5" max="5">
            <description>Meia takes a selfie with Mahiru--somewhat reluctantly.</description>
            <trigger alsoPlaying="mahiru" alsoPlayingStage="7" tag="stripped" priority="990" alsoPlayingSaidMarker="meiaselfie">
                <state img="selfieblank.png"></state>
            </trigger>
        </case>
        <case name="Mahiru Selfie" min="5" max="5">
            <description>Meia takes a selfie with Mahiru--somewhat reluctantly.</description>
            <trigger alsoPlaying="mahiru" alsoPlayingStage="9" tag="stripped" priority="990" alsoPlayingSaidMarker="meiaselfie">
                <state img="selfieblank.png"></state>
            </trigger>
        </case>
        <case name="Butt Pose" min="5" max="5">
            <description>Meia turns around and shows her butt off in a nonchalant fashion.</description>
            <trigger alsoPlayingStage="" tag="stripped">
                <state img="butt.png">Well, here I am.  Satisfied?</state>
                <state img="butt.png">Always expect the worst in your battle plan...</state>
                <state img="butt.png">Yes, the carpet matches the drapes...or it would, if I had one.</state>
                <state img="butt.png">I was cocky coming into this game...not anymore.</state>
                <state img="butt.png">Seeing me like <i>this</i> would get you forty lashes on Tarak.</state>
                <state img="butt.png" marker="pubic_hair_comments">Shaved is the way to be.  One less thing to worry about.</state>
                <state img="butt.png">Knowing Jura, she's planned this and has Paiway on the scene...</state>
                <state img="butt.png">I hope Paiway isn't lurking around here with her camera...</state>
                <state img="butt.png">This'd be one hell of a <i>Pai-check</i>...</state>
                <state img="butt.png">Now to get rid of these things.  I'm sure you'll appreciate the view...</state>
                <state img="butt.png">Enjoy the rear view while you can.  I need to find a place to put these...</state>
                <state img="butt.png">As you can now clearly see, these shorts were all I had left.</state>
                <state img="butt.png">And now my clothes pile is complete...as is your view.</state>
                <state img="butt.png">Don't think you've embarrassed me.  That suit leaves nothing to the imagination...here, look.</state>
                <state img="butt.png">My backside is nothing stimulating, right?  Not after you saw it in the suit already.</state>
                <state img="butt.png">Well...here I am.  All of me.</state>
                <state img="butt.png">Best to sate your curiosity now than let it simmer.  Here I am from the back...</state>
                <state img="butt.png">Considering my wardrobe, my situation has hardly changed at all.</state>
                <state img="butt.png">If you think I'm ashamed of my body, you're mistaken...but I <i>am</i> ashamed of losing.</state>
                <state img="butt.png">Seems my bare breasts weren't enough to satisfy you.  Perhaps my backside is.</state>
                <state img="butt.png">Breasts are fetishized on Mejare...butts are usually an afterthought.  What about Earth?</state>
                <state img="butt.png">I'm fond of the butt...exercise can improve it, unlike breasts.</state>
                <state img="butt.png">I'm told the exercising I do has improved my backside.  You be the judge...</state>
                <state img="butt.png">When my more earnest subordinates finally pipe up about their crushes on me, my butt is usually the subject of her compliments.</state>
            </trigger>
        </case>
        <case name="Revy Fight" min="5" max="5">
            <description>Meia gets into a nude fistfight with Revy.</description>
            <trigger alsoPlayingStage="" tag="female_crotch_is_visible" target="revy" targetStage="">
                <state img="revy.png" marker="revyfight" location="60">You removed that black eye thing--<i>lemme give it back to ya</i>!</state>
                <state img="revy.png" marker="revyfight" location="60"><i>Bitch</i>!</state>
                <state img="revy.png" marker="revyfight" location="60">They throw <i>haymakers</i> on your fuckin' rock?</state>
                <state img="revy.png" marker="revyfight" location="60"><i>Fuck you</i>!</state>
                <state img="revy.png" marker="revyfight" location="60"><i>Welcome to Earth, cunt</i>!</state>
                <state img="revy.png" marker="revyfight" location="60">Let's see how many space dykes wanna eat you out <i>after this</i>!</state>
                <state img="revy.png" marker="revyfight" location="60"><i>Kiss my ass</i>!</state>
                <state img="revy.png" marker="revyfight" location="60"><i>Arrraaaagh</i>!</state>
                <state img="revy.png" marker="revyfight" location="60">Hope you don't need a <i>man to save you</i>!</state>
            </trigger>
        </case>
        <case name="Jura Dual Masturbation" min="5" max="5">
            <description>Jura takes it upon herself to help Meia's masturbation.</description>
            <trigger alsoPlaying="jura" alsoPlayingStage="8" tag="start_masturbating" priority="990" saidMarker="jurafinish" alsoPlayingSaidMarker="meiamast">
                <state img="shock.png">Wha--J-Jura, what are you doing?  I--agh!  (<i>The crew can't have a pent-up, lonely squadron leader, Meia</i>.)</state>
                <state img="shock.png">J-Jura?  (<i>It's time you remembered how beautiful you are, Leader</i>.)</state>
                <state img="shock.png">Agh!  J-Jura!  Don't--I--  (<i>It's OK, honey.  You deserve to be treated right</i>...)</state>
                <state img="shock.png">Jura?  I-I--what's the meaning of this?  (<i>This is the only way you'll remember what it's like to be loved</i>.)</state>
                <state img="shock.png">Ah!  Jura, what are you--mm!  (<i>If you keep on masturbating alone, you'll forget what having a girlfriend is like</i>.)</state>
                <state img="shock.png">Mm!  J-Jura--!  (<i>Any girl would be lucky to have you, Leader.  It's time you remembered how sexy you really are</i>).</state>
                <state img="shock.png">J-Jura--!  We--you can't!  (<i>Sssshh...let's show these Earth people how Mejarians make love.  You need it, after all</i>.)</state>
                <state img="shock.png">Jura!  Don't--what about Barnette?  (<i>That's right, I have Barnette.  You don't have anyone...that's why you need this</i>.)</state>
            </trigger>
        </case>
    </noteworthy>
</metadata>
