<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<markers>
    <marker scope="Public" name="armor_lasers">"...My armor deflects lasers.  That's about the extent of it."</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="bc_confusion">Meia expresses confusion when other players fail to explain birth control to her.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="bc_response">Meia doesn't know what birth control is.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="bee_react">Meia reacts to a bee bothering Florina.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="blue_hair">Meia comments that another player has blue hair.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="bodysuit">Meia comments that another player wears a bodysuit like hers.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="cap_uncomfortable">Meia questions why Captain America, a man, is uncomfortable with nudity.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="challenging_sei">"Finish me off and I'll tell you."</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="chi_mush">Meia is forced to listen to Chiaki tell her about Super Mario.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="chi_mush2">Meia continues to listen to Chiaki tell her about Super Mario.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="chi_mush3">Meia continues, irritated, to listen to Chiaki tell her about Super Mario.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="chi_po">Meia is forced to listen to Chiaki tell her about Pokemon.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="chi_sam">Meia is forced to listen to Chiaki tell her about Samus.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="chi_sf">Meia is forced to listen to Chiaki tell her about Street Fighter.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="chi_sf2">Meia continues to listen to Chiaki tell her about Street Fighter.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="claustrophobia">Meia has claustrophobia and expresses a hatred of restrained movement.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="corrinrinkequals">Meia is surprised that Corrin, a member of royalty, would treat her comrades as friends even when she hasn't.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="country_as_planet">Meia misinterprets an Earth country as a whole planet.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="dark_skin">Meia rather bluntly observes that another player's skin is dark, and that such is rare on Mejare.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="dread_response">Meia responds to Sei's comments about her Dread.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="dropout">Meia claims she dropped out of school at a young age, living on the streets.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="earth_sightseeing">Meia asks the table what sights and activities Earth has to offer.  (Prompt Marker)</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="earth_wasteland">Meia comments that the Earth in her universe is a ravaged mechanical wasteland.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="elaine_drink">Meia responds to Elaine's late-game offer for a drink.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="femplayer">Meia greets the female player the first time she strips.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="gwen_comfort">"These bodysuits can get uncomfortable...although you seem quite comfortable in yours."</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="gwen_spiders">"Mejare doesn't have many animals...and I &lt;i&gt;wish&lt;/i&gt; it didn't have spiders."</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="gwen_style">Good to see someone who shares my fashion sense...sort of."</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="hates_soldiers">Meia expresses a hatred for anyone affiliated with government or a military.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="hitechdread">"My &lt;i&gt;Dread&lt;/i&gt; is advanced...nothing about &lt;i&gt;me&lt;/i&gt; needs to be."</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="honorifics">Meia questions a character's use of honorifics.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="ignoring_moon">After Moon removes her bracelet, Meia will ignore Moon entirely until the latter is about to show her chest.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="ini_hakazura">Meia appreciates Ini's suggestion to visit Hakazura Temple, noting Mejare has little snow.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="jura_comparison">Meia claims that a character's breasts are probably smaller than Jura's.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="jura_sei">Meia claims Jura and Sei would get along.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="jurafinish">Meia sees that Jura has finished masturbating...which could lead to interesting developments.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="jurafinished">Meia and Jura relax for a moment.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="kizuna_japan">Meia asks Kizuna to tell her moreabout Japan.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="laser_ring">Meia offhandedly mentions her laser ring early on, or that she is armed with it.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="lizbluehair">Meia tells Elizabeth that she should not be confined to anyone else's restrictions over her hair.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="lizmen">Meia tells Elizabeth about the first man she ever saw in person.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="maleplayer">Meia greets the male player the first time he strips.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="mari_insult">Meia rebukes Marinette's French insult.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="mari_insult2">Meia thinks it's cute how Marinette is timid about saying "bitch."</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="marinette_phc">Meia responds to Marinette's complaints about her distaste for pubic hair.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="meia_quirk_marriage_response">Meia is offended when Ochako suggests she was engineered.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="Mejare_few_animals">Meia claims that very few animals exist on Mejare.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="men_in_school">Meia questions men's ability to function in coeducational settings.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="mikobabies">Meia is surprised to hear that Miko enlists a pharmacist's aid for women to have children.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="mulan_hair">Meia questions why Mulan chooses shaving pubic hair as unacceptably unnatural.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="mulan_tungshao">Meia is confused about Mulan's planetary origins and notes she's only rarely seen snow in person.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="nagisa_thanks">Meia thanks Nagisa for complimenting her breasts...or at least admits she might be insecure about them.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="navi_men">Meia notes that Navi, a fairy woman, isn't likely to understand how men's penises work anyway.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="nayru_doubt">Meia tells Nayru it's better to have to let go of the past.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="nayru_intro">Meia returns Nayru's greeting and notes their similar blue hair, yet opposite personalities.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="nayru_mj">Meia claims to Nayru that she is only playing out of curiosity about men, not to relax.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="ochako_qm">Meia resents Ochako's implication that women can't fall in love.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="oma_and_fama">Meia mentions her Oma and/or Fama, the women who spliced their eggs together to give birth to her, or expresses confusion with the terms "mother" and "father."</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="one_on_one">Meia acknowledges that the game has come down to her and one other player.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="pilot">Meia realizes another character is a pilot and perks up with interest.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="pit_mast">Meia comments on Pit's apparent feelings towards her masturbating.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="pubic_hair_comments">Meia questions a woman's choice to have pubic hair.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="ravenfriendly">Meia says she was equally unfriendly to Raven at first.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="react_mast">Meia first reacts to someone masturbating after learning about the rule.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="revyfight">Meia gets into a brief (naked) scuffle with Revy.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="riches_to_rags">Meia mentions that she was wealthy as a child, but lived on the streets as a teenager.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="rinkcorrinconflict">Meia asks with whom Rinkah and Corrin have been in conflict.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="sei_bc_response">Meia expresses disbelief that Earth women might get pregnant unintentionally.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="sei_jiggles">Meia shoots down Sei's offer to jiggle her breasts.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="sei_lasers">Meia responds to Sei's comments about lasers.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="sei_response">Meia responds to Sei's greeting.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="sei1">Meia reacts to Sei telling her to relax.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="sei2">Meia explains planet Mejare to Sei.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="sei3">Meia is not impressed with Sei's high-tech armor.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="seibaby">Meia thinks she's better-suited to carrying a child than Sei is.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="seiof_response">Meia explains Omas and Famas to Sei.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="shyness">Meia comments on or questions another character's shyness.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="state_schools">Meia claims that Mejarian schools are all government propaganda machines.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="tablet">Meia busies herself early on with work on her electronic tablet.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="unaware_mast">Meia is first made aware that players have to masturbate upon losing.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="veranhand">Meia rebuffs Veran's requests for submission.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="wearing_tech">"No, it isn't.  Technology is for using, not wearing."</marker>
</markers>
