<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<markers>
    <marker scope="Public" name="armor_lasers">"My armor deflects lasers...that's about the extent of it."</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="blue_hair">Meia comments that another player has blue hair.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="bodysuit">Meia comments that another player wears a bodysuit like hers.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="cap_uncomfortable">Meia questions why Captain America, a man, is uncomfortable with nudity.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="challenging_sei">"Finish me off and I'll tell you."</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="claustrophobia">Meia has claustrophobia and expresses a hatred of restrained movement.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="country_as_planet">Meia misinterprets an Earth country as a whole planet.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="dark_skin">Meia rather bluntly observes that another player's skin is dark, and that such is rare on Mejare.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="dropout">Meia claims she dropped out of school at a young age, living on the streets.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="hates_soldiers">Meia expresses a hatred for anyone affiliated with government or a military.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="hi-tech_dread">"My <i>Dread</i> is high-tech...nothing about <i>me</i> needs to be."</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="honorifics">Meia questions a character's use of honorifics.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="ignoring_moon">After Moon removes her bracelet, Meia will ignore Moon entirely until the latter is about to show her chest.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="jura_comparison">Meia claims that a character's breasts are probably smaller than Jura's.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="Mejare_few_animals">Meia claims that very few animals exist on Mejare.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="men_in_school">Meia questions men's ability to function in coeducational settings.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="nagisa_thanks">Meia thanks Nagisa for complimenting her breasts...or at least admits she might be insecure about them.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="oma_and_fama">Meia mentions her Oma and/or Fama, the women who spliced their eggs together to give birth to her, or expresses confusion with the terms "mother" and "father."</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="pilot">Meia realizes another character is a pilot and perks up with interest.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="pubic_hair_comments">Meia questions a woman's choice to have pubic hair.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="riches_to_rags">Meia mentions that she was wealthy as a child, but lived on the streets as a teenager.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="sei_response">Meia responds to Sei's greeting.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="shyness">Meia comments on or questions another character's shyness.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="state_schools">Meia claims that Mejarian schools are all government propaganda machines.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="unaware_mast">Meia is first made aware that players have to masturbate upon losing.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="wearing_tech">"Technology is for using, not wearing."</marker>
</markers>
