<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<metadata>
    <owner>aimee</owner>
    <noteworthy>
        <case name="Bullet strip 1" min="0" max="2">
            <description>Aimee strips by firing a bullet which ricochets around the room and rips apart either her cowboy outfit, her armbands, or her footwear.</description>
            <trigger alsoPlayingStage="" tag="stripping">
                <state img="z2.png">Kinda tickles...</state>
                <state img="z2.png">Oh drat, I forgot ta adjust for sudden changes in local humidity. From the look you'se guys, it's on the rise.</state>
                <state img="z2.png">Chillax, people. If I wanted ta change somethin's diaper, I'd place an order with my darlin'.</state>
                <state img="z2.png">Hmmhmmhmmm...</state>
                <state img="z2.png">Oh, the look on yer faces...</state>
                <state img="z2.png">Deep breaths--ya wouldn't want any unintentional discharges.</state>
                <state img="z2.png">Ya better hope I ain't a klutz today...</state>
                <state img="z2.png">For yer own safety, please keep yer arms and legs inside yer character boxes at all times.</state>
                <state img="z2.png">I really put the "casual" in "casualty," don't I?</state>
                <state img="z2.png">Careful--ya saw how shaky my poker hand was--better hope that don't translate.</state>
                <state img="z2.png">The first time darlin' saw this, I'll tell ya, he regretted feedin' me that cake!</state>
                <state img="z2.png">I spray--you pray!</state>
            </trigger>
        </case>
        <case name="Bullet strip breasts" min="4" max="4">
            <description>Aimee strips by firing a bullet which ricochets and rips apart her skirt and tube top, revealing her breasts</description>
            <trigger alsoPlayingStage="" tag="stripped">
                <state img="z0.png">Ngh! The shockwave! I'm so jiggly all of the sudden! Hehe!</state>
                <state img="z0.png">320 degrees celsius. 590 kelvin! 610 farenheit! So hot!</state>
                <state img="z0.png">Right 'tween my ta-tas! Right by my...ngh!</state>
                <state img="z0.png">Wah! Right where I wanted it! Right by my...Oh darlin'!</state>
                <state img="z0.png">Ah! Now that's what I call a vest buster!</state>
            </trigger>
        </case>
        <case name="Bullet strip cum" min="5" max="5">
            <description>Aimee cums a little due to firing a bullet which grazed her legs as it shredded her panties</description>
            <trigger alsoPlayingStage="" tag="stripped">
                <state img="z0.png">C-c-cummin!</state>
                <state img="z0.png">Gr-grazed me!</state>
                <state img="z0.png">A-ahhh!</state>
                <state img="z0.png">It touched! Aah!</state>
            </trigger>
        </case>
    </noteworthy>
</metadata>
