<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<metadata>
    <owner>aimee</owner>
    <noteworthy>
        <case name="Bullet strip B: bouncing bullet" id="1" priority="MustTarget" min="0" max="2">
            <description>Aimee strips by firing a bullet which ricochets around the room and rips apart either her cowboy outfit, her armbands, or her footwear.</description>
        </case>
        <case name="Bullet strip G: breasts" id="2" priority="MustTarget" min="4" max="4">
            <description>Aimee strips by firing a bullet which ricochets and rips apart her skirt and tube top, revealing her breasts</description>
        </case>
        <case name="Bullet strip I: cum" id="3" priority="MustTarget" min="5" max="5">
            <description>Aimee cums a little due to firing a bullet which grazed her legs as it shredded her panties</description>
        </case>
        <case name="Bullet strip A: first shot" id="4" priority="MustTarget" min="0" max="0">
            <description>Aimee aims her gun and fires. The other characters have not yet seen that she intends to shoot off her clothing.</description>
        </case>
        <case name="Bullet strip C: clothing in shreds" id="5" priority="Noteworthy" min="1" max="2">
            <description>Aimee's outfit falls to the ground in shreds</description>
        </case>
        <case name="Bullet strip D: shooting again" id="6" priority="MustTarget" min="1" max="4">
            <description>Aimee fires her gun each time she wants to strip. You can target each stage individually if you want to sequence your responses</description>
        </case>
        <case name="Bullet strip E: close call" id="7" priority="Noteworthy" min="3" max="3">
            <description>Aimee accidentally shot off her neck accessory when shooting off her armbands, which was more than she intended!</description>
        </case>
        <case name="Bullet strip F: waiting for the bullet" id="8" priority="Noteworthy" min="3" max="3">
            <description>Aimee shot a bullet high up and is waiting for it to return to shoot her top off</description>
        </case>
        <case name="Bullet strip H: final bouncing bullet" id="9" priority="MustTarget" min="4" max="4">
            <description>A bullet ricochets around as Aimee waits for it to shoot off her panties</description>
        </case>
        <case name="Aimee finished" id="10" priority="Noteworthy" min="7" max="7">
            <description>Aimee let off a stray shot as she was climaxing, and it hit her in the arm</description>
        </case>
    </noteworthy>
    <notes>
        <note id="11">This case was hidden due to no longer making sense after changes were made to the targeted character. If you're rewriting this character, feel free to delete it.</note>
    </notes>
    <nextId>11</nextId>
    <markers>
        <marker scope="Public" name="48spec">Aimee has 48 Specialties. What are they? Who knows. </marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="aimee_teases_silent">Aimee bullies silent characters, pretending they said slutty things. </marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="funny_joke">Aimee offers to tell the player a joke if they throw their hand in round 6. </marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="funny_joked">Aimee laughs at the player if they lose in round 6. </marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="twi_resp">Aimee </marker>
    </markers>
</metadata>
