Aimee Targetted Lines Documentation

Aimee uses the markers:
aimee_teases_silent
	Aimee bullies silent characters by pretending they said slutty things. 
48spec
	Aimee has 48 specialties! What are they? Well one's friendly fire...



For those targetting Aimee: 
Every round that she loses:
she fires her gun wildly during her must_strip line. 
bullets ricochet during her stripping line. 
her clothes fall as tatters during her stripped line. 

VARIATIIONS:
on stage 3 (the stage that ends with her removing her tube top and skirt)
rather than ricocheting bullets, the bullets fall from the sky

when she begins to masturbate, no shots are fired. 

When she climaxes, she will fire shots again, ultimately hitting herself. 



Some info about Aimee: 

SPOILER WARNING for Bravely Second: End Layer

Aimee Matchlock, the Silver Sniper:

* She's a wild, brash woman. She is a sucker for romance and even hands out relationship advice while in a battle to the death. 

* She speaks with a Brooklyn accent and frequently uses Yiddish. I have written her as ambiguously Jewish. 

* She is modelled to look like a sexy Native American. Her Native American costume was her original design, but fearing that it would be offensive, the localizers gave her a cowgirl outfit in the international release. She wears both in SPNatI. Her original design was made by the character designer of Sword Art Online. 

* She is from a fantasy world. She once lived with her tribe in Florem Gardens, a dungeon in the game. 

* She's a Hawkeye--that's a magical sniper that has a connections with the spirits of nature. She can fire magical elemental bullets. An outside source says she can speak with the spirits of the dead, though she has never done this in canon. 

* She never misses a shot. She once pinned down an entire army with just her sniper fire. While holding them off, she sniped someone who was on the far side of the planet. When Aimee died, she shot a bullet in the air. Attached to this bullet was a note to her lover. Three days later, this bullet fell from the heavens and knocked a suicide cake from her darling's hand, saving his life without harming him. The letter convinced him to not commit suicide. 

* She is devoted in her love to her "darlin" Angelo. Angelo is a polite, womanizing, aristocratic pretty-boy. He is an amazingly good chef--His cakes make women fall desperately in love with him, chanting that the food (and him) are "to die for" and "we're in heaven!" He also has the ability to literally send someone straight to heaven with a bite of cake. Angelo calls Aimee "sugarcake." He's very much a tsundere towards her. 

* She and Angelo were once members of the Glanz Empire, a villainous organization headed by a masked man and his evil fairy companion. After Aimee and Angelo both dreamed Aimee died in battle (same death mentioned above--it's complicated), the pair left the empire and eloped in Florem Gardens, opening a Pancake shop. Said pancake shop attracts female customers from around the world, despite being located in a deadly dungeon. 

* In SPNatI, Aimee has a dominant role in her relationship with Angelo. I heavily imply that though Angelo is a womanizer, he's a total sub in bed. She actively promotes him and invites women to join his harem. She is devoted to Angelo, but is fine with fooling around with other women. 

* I have written her as a BIG fan of guns and other weapons. She's also written as a math savant, using that math to understand sharpshooting to a ridiculous degree. 

* Her favorite food is pancakes. 

* Her gun is called "Guncleaver." It's a silver rifle with an axehead and wings on it's barrel. It was not modelled for this game--she's just using an AK-47. She mentions that this gun is not her normal gun. 

* In SPNatI, she frequently breaks the fourth wall. She often references "epilogues" and "text boxes."

* For more information and a list of only character-targeted lines, please see the file "targetted lines documentation.txt" [here](https://gitlab.com/nomoreatheismspamplz/spnati.gitlab.io/tree/master/opponents/aimee). She also has a wiki page [here](http://finalfantasy.wikia.com/wiki/Aimee_Matchlock). 





Beatrix: 
shy character must masturbate, Aimee is finished, Beatrix is stage 0-3 or 5:
Y-yeah! Absolutely no way to accidentally injure yersellf while jillin'. Only purposeful. 

Blake: multiple times:
as Blake is removing her armbands: 
What kinda gun needs ribbons? 
Yer weapon uses yer ribbons...?
Yer gun uses ribbons...some sorta Spider-Man thing?
after Blake has removed her armbands:
Seriously, what's with the guns of these RWBY dames? What kinda heavenly world are ya from, Blake!?
C-can I swing by yer place later and meet yer gun? I wanna hold it...I wanna tell it that it's loved...
Gambol Shroud...ya named it! Ya went and named yer gun...*Sniff* Sorry, I'm...I'm just so happy!
as Blake is removing her bow:
Huh? What're ya goin on about? Some sorta bonus content?
What, ya have some sorta secret weapon?
after Black removes the bow: 
So that's what's been twitchin under there!
I worked with a cat-girl. Two of ya are like night and day. Ya hide it--she won't shut up bout it.
That was s'posed to be secret? Yer gonna hafta invest in a higher thread-count ribbon to fool these eyes.
when Blake must_strip her bra: 
What nyow, Blake? Mew gonna show us yer kitties?
Blake's strippin again? Pawsome! Purrfect! I cat wait! 
Aww, whata cat-astrophic loss! At least we nyow ya ain't a cheetah!
Aww, it'll be feline, just keep a pawsitive catitude. 
Hey Blake, yer next fur strippin. I'm not kitten. Not even lion. 
Immediately after, when Blake's chest will_be_visible:
Strikin yer weak point, ain't I? Don't worry, I'll stop. 
Sorry. I shared barracks with a half-pint spewin cat puns every two words. Had to adapt to survive.
Heh, sorry to give ya an EARful. Okay, okay, I'll stop ribbon ya. 
Blake removing vest, whle Marinette is present:
Ooo, Blake and Marinette, sittin in a tree, k-i-s-s-i-n-g.
Blake must masturbate, while Marinette is present:
Whoa! Blake and Marinette, sittin in a tree, f-u-c-k-i-n-g!

Buffy: when buffy has removed her bra
Feh...Well played. 
I have to admit, it's a clever tactic. 

Chiaki: 
when lyn must strip stage 0 and chiaki is stage 0-3:
Whoahoho! Shots fired!
kyoko must strip stage 0 and chiaki is stage 0-6:
Out of the two, I'd put my bet on the ULTIMATE SNIPER!
kyoko must masturbate and chiaki has not yet lost:
Wins second place, ya mean! 'Cause the Ultimate Sniper's go ya in her sights!
Chiaki has removed ribbon (note, in BD, ribbon prevents many status effects, including Dread.):
Darlin' would make ya regret removin' that if he were here. Man's big on his status effects.
Removin' yer ribbon so soon...Don't blame me if ya start feelin some Dread.
Surely the "Ultimate Gamer" knows how dangerous it is to lose a ribbon...
Chiaki must masturbate, Rinkah is present: 
Don't think there's an exact rule 'bout 8 items max, but more don't really seem fair.

Chica: 
Chica is removing arms:
Okay, Ducky--Whataya got left to lose? Cause...Yer kinda...
Okay, Ducky--What're we in for this time? Ya bust already?
Chica has removed arms:
O--oh! Okay! That's definantly a thing! 
Uah! The arms!? Well, I guess ya ain't technically disarmed...
Oh...! I, uh, I take it yer not a natural blonde, huh?
Chica's chest is visible (Medium chest):
And here I thought robots were just for killin. Now they're for jigglin.
I wonder what darlin would think of ya...
I wouldn't mind me some soft serve from them user interfaces.
Chica's crotch wll be visible AND Mettaton is playing: 
But...Mettaton has pink panties AND tits. Don't tell me ya got a wing-wang tucked in there...
Chica's crotch is visible: 
That's...suprisinly life-like. What is that, silicon?
I can tell yer a well oiled machine...
Oh man! Once this is done, I'mma need to take a look under the hood.
Chica starts masturbating:
Alright Ducky, time for a test drive. Ya do good here and I might get darlin to place an order.
Alright Ducky, its sink or swim. Do good here and I'll getcha a job servin pancakes. Among other things.
Chica finishes masturbating:
Ya pass! Ya definitely pass! I'm definantly takin ya to my darlin's pancake shop! He'll be so happy to meetcha!
Oh wow--is this what restauranteerin is like in the big leagues? Fazbears must be a classy dig!

D.Va: 
must strip, first time D.Va strips:
Hey Cottontail, I'm still tryin to wrap my head round somthin. How'd ya learn to shoot a gun by playin Starcraft? 
D.Va has removed headphones, Futaba is also playing: 
Huh? I get that they're cute, but why're ya so mad Shorty?
D.Va must masturbate:
Not gonna self-destruct, are ya Cottontail?
Aww, Cottontail's not gonna call down her Meka?

Elizabeth: Finished (self), in addition to normal lines: 
Thanks for passin me that health kit, Elizabeth. If ya ever need somebody dead, I'm yer gal.
Thanks for the patch-up, Elizabeth. Yer an angel.
Yer a lifesaver, Elizabeth. Never though we'd actually need first aid. Thanks.

F_Corrin:
at Aimee's first must_strip:
Ya see Princess Footsie, this is a gun. And the gun goes bang bang bang bang bang!
Oh, ya never seen a gun before, Princess Footsie? Well yer in for a treat!
Well well well, Princess Footsie's never seen a gun before! Let me show ya what they do.
at Aimee's second must_strip:
I'm doin <i>that</i> again! 
Male large cock is visible and marker:cursed is said: 
A curse for him, a blessin for us!
Don't knock it till ya try it, Princess Footsie!
Corrin's stage 0 must_strip: 
Ya'd drive my darlin nuts, ya know that Princess Footsie? The man likes him some toes.
I guess ya can't start with yer shoes!
My dalin would love yer getup, Princess. I'll need to show ya to him after this.
As Corrin is removing armor:
Don't worry, Princess, ya don't need that armor. 
Yer armor? Heh, no beatin round the bush with you! At least not yet. 
Dropping yer armor? Good! I hate the stuff. Clothes have no business bein bullet-proof. 
As Corrin is removing pants:
One one-thousand. 
I'll give ya till ~player~ hits "continue." 
Ya can drop yer pants in only one second? Ya must have a lotta practice!
Corrin starts masturbating: 
I already know my darlin will like ya--lets find out if he'll love ya!
Corrin is masturbating: 
How practiced are ya with yer feet, Princess? Ya think ya could jack a guy off?
Do ya like foot rubs, Princess? Cause my darlin can gve a mean foot rub. 
Ya should get my darlin to give ya a foot rub. Just melts the stress away... 
Ya wakin the dragon, Princess Footsie?
Corrin has finished:
Lookit that stamina! If I got ya and darlin together, would there be any of him left for me!?
Princess, I need ya to swing by my darlin's pancake shop later--no shoes, extra service!
Wow! That climax deserves cake. And a foot rub. I'm takin ya to meet my darlin. 
Male must masturbate, F_Corrin masturbating or finished, said marker:fuckme:
Sorry Princess Footsie. That just ain't gonna happen...
Male start masturbate, F_Corrin masturbating or finished, said marker:fuckme:
If the devs made image sets for each boychik ya wanna bone, there'd be no space for the rest of us!

Florina:
After Aimee strips, stage 2: 
Don'tcha worry yer little head Flo--I never miss! Never ever!
Aww Flo, ya want a hair cut? A little off the back?
Florina stage 7 or 8, male crotch will be visible, said: dumb_say: 
Pst--Flo, tell'm ya like his penis!
Male crotch visible (all sizes), said: dumb_say, not said dumb_over: 
Bahahaha! Flo, yer killin' me!
What!? Ya fell for that?
Florina stage 7 or 8, male cortch will be visible, said: dumb2_say: 
Pst--Flo, ask'm if ya can touch it!
Male crotch visible (all sizes), said: dumb2_say, not said dumb2_over: 
Mwahahaha! Flo, yer the best! I love ya!
Fool ya once, shame on me. Fool ya twice? Yer just usin' me as an excuse, ain'tcha?
Florina stripping stage 0, said:fled:
Flo! I said I'd shoot ya if ya ran! Don't call my bluff!
Just say the word and I'll blow her boots off. She won't be runnin' then!
I got 48 specialties, and patience for cowards ain't one. 
Florina stripping tunic, said:bee, notsaid:beestop: 
Huh? What's goin' on?
A bee? What's so scary 'bout a bee?
...Do ya want me to shoot it?
As above, stripped:
Ha! Destroyin' yer clothin' over a little bee? Somethin' tells me yer popular. 
What kinda idiot destroies their clothin'!? Over a bee!?
Oh man, If a bee could do that...? Do ya think I could weaponize 'em? Make a bee-bee gun?
Aimee must masturbate, Florina mast and said:tickle:
H-Huey as in yer horse? ...Damn Flo, yer kinky. 
H-Huey the horse!? ...Never pegged Flo for a pegasus pegger. 
As above, Aimee starts masturbation:
Go on, go on! Give me somethin' to schlick to!
Flo...I didn't think ya had it in ya. Mostly cause horse dicks are huge. 

Futaba:
Aimee must strip stage 2: 
Shorty calls for moar and moar there shall be!
Back by popular demand! This shot's for you, Shorty!
Aww Shorty, I ain't gonna start lettin' ya down!
D.Va has removed headphones:
Huh? I get that they're cute, but why're ya so mad Shorty?
Moon must strip stage 1:
She oughta commit to an insane asylum. 
Yang has removed scarf (stage 1):
Whoa! Shots fired! I hope yer as good at duckin' as ya look, Shorty!

Hermione: multiple areas: 
Hermione must strip while fully clothed (stage 0):
Home-irony....uh, Hum-ione....ugh...Oh! Herm like hermaphrodite! Hermione! Hermione! Got it!
How did it go...rhymes with...crap, rhymes with nothin. Hermione! No, still wrong...
Hermione. Hermione. I'm getting it wrong, ain't I? Hermione. Yeah, definantly mispronouncin. 
Hrm. Hrrrrm. HRRRRMMMM. HERMIONE! Hah! I got it! ...I think.
when Hermione has removed her shirt:
I don't know, Witchy, we might need more evidence.
Are ya? News to me. Might need to see some proof.
I thought Yew was a girlie too when I saw him in his panties. Might need to show us yer cooter.
when Hermione starts masturbating: 
Whoa! Ya can use magic for that? I'm know a witch, but her magic just blows yutz's up in new and interestin ways.
Wow, it's like ya got yer own harem! Ya can do that with magic!?
While Hermione is masturbating--no added lines, but targetting was used to remove deafult lines that wouldn't make sense. 
After Hermione climaxes: 
I know what I gotta give darlin for his birthday! You!
If that's what magic's all about, I should head off to school, too!

Jasmine: 
Remove Minor, removing the cloak:
Wait, yer a princess?
A princess!? Wow, I didn't see that comin.
Whoa, Jasmine is a princess? 
Aimee is stripping the first time:
Don'tcha dare close yer eyes. 
Hold your breath, it gets better.

Kim: Must Strip, when Kim first loses.
Uh Kim, bout that skuff in Al Kampis? Total misunderstandin--cakes come with consent forms now.
Say Kim...yer not still mad bout that misunderstandin in Al Kampis? Right? Cause we're totes legit now!
Kim? No need to blow up our shop again, kay? We've gone straight--honest!
Kim has removed bra: 
Hey Kim, let's make a bet--If I win, I get yer cheer squad epilogue. And if ya win, I have to feed ya cake.
Kim, darlin and me really miss ya and yer cheer dames. Maybe after this we can try a do-over?
Hey Kim, darlin does caterin if ya wanna give us another chance. Yer cheer dames seemed to like him.
When Kim has removed panties: 
Well, yer entire school could be watchin like last time...oh, retorical question, gotcha.
Well, yer parents could be chaperonin like last time...oh, retorical question, gotcha.
Well, ya could be runnin around with a pin roller shoved up yer...oh retorical question, gotcha.
Must Masturbate: 
Ack! Last time I saw Kim like this, she nearly squeezed off darlin's nuts!
Kim, no need to...blow up darlin's pancake shop just cause yer horny, kay? Not our fault this time!
Oh jeez! Last time I saw Kim like this, she tied me up to a windmill and called the police! Naked! Both of us!
Start Masturbating:
Yer...not gonna violently lash out? Oh. Good. Yeah, that's good. 
Yer actually...? Oh whata relief--I can't go to prison again. Worst fourty-five minutes of my life. 
Yer...Oh, yer cool with it? Okay. That's a relief. 
Finished (Kim): 
See, that ain't so bad! That's all we wanted with the cakes--to make ya happy and horny!
Ya know Kim, our customers say darlin's cakes are even better than sex...if ya wanted to give them another try.
Way to go, Kim! Now, while yer in the mood for broadining yer horizons, maybe ya'd like some cake?

Kyoko: 
kyoko must strip stage 0 and chiaki is stage 0-6:
Out of the two, I'd put my bet on the ULTIMATE SNIPER!
after she loses her gloves:
Ehh, tradin leather for leather. Big whoop. 
Yer hands are fine. My darlin likes it rough. 
Looks like we caught ya red-handed, detective.
kyoko must masturbate and chiaki has not yet lost:
Wins second place, ya mean! 'Cause the Ultimate Sniper's go ya in her sights!

Link: 
when he first speaks (must_strip, stage 4), before Aimee has begin masturbating:
Mess with the best, strip like the--Ah! He speaks!
I took ya down without even firin a--Oh, did ya just say somethin?
Ya never stood a--Ohoho! Not so silent all the sudden.
As above, but Aimee can be in any stage: 
That's a shaky hand ya--Ohoho, ya DO talk!
Better strip if ya value yer--Ahah! I knew it! Yer a faker!

Lyn:
when lyn must strip stage 0 and chiaki is stage 0-3:
Whoahoho! Shots fired!

Marinette: multiple times: 
Aimee must strip at stage 1, while Marinette is still costumed:
Chillax Ladybug, these bullets only go where I tell them to. 
Ladybug: I don't miss. 
Oh no, Ladybug! My hand slipped! Duck! -- Ha, I'm just kiddin. I never miss. 
when losing her yo-yo:
Scuse me if I sound like a yo-yo, but what's with the yo-yo? Some sorta weapon system?
A yo-yo? What do ya...wait do ya fight with that thing?
That's like a toy-weapon thing, right? 
after losing her yo-yo: 
What's it do? Does it drop grenades? Shurikens? Uh, does it shoot poison spines? 
The string's the weapon part, right? A garrote? Razor wire? Oh, I know, it's coated with neurotoxin, ain't it?
Soooo....Is it a flail? Does it grow spikes? Axe-heads? Buzzsaws?
when losing costume: 
Huh? What's happinin? Ya changin Jobs?
What's...oh ya must be swappin Jobs. 
Ya moon people sure do dress weird--oh, yer changin Jobs?
after losing costume: 
Dang, I was hopin there wasn't anythin under that latex. 
B-but ya didn't have any panty lines or nothin! 
Ya went from body-tight camel-toe to this? I though ya were supposed to get sexier!
after removing shirt:
Heh, yer so cute when ya reveal uncomfortable sexual truths!
No, no, keep goin.
Ya must like what ya see--yer polka dot pattern can't hide yer cute little pokies!
Aimee is at start_masturbation, in reaction to a marinette targetted line:
Use it as a toy...oh Marinette, ya got such a lewd imagination don'tcha?
Use my gun as a sex toy!? And you call me crazy. Ladybug, I like how ya think!
Use my gun? I mean, it's a sexy piece of metal but...Uh I'll try it, Ladybug. Just for you. 

Mei:
On round 5, rather than talking about hand quality, Aimee will ask: 
Hey Snow-Angel, I got some ice-rounds too--really good for keepin the barrel cool. Could I check out yers sometime?
Hey Snow-Angel, I'm bettin yer gun ain't ballistic, but could I compare it to my icehead rounds some time?
When Link strips first time and Mei is not yet masturbating:
Don't bother, Snow-Angel. He's one of them "silent" characters. Speaks entirely in mid-coitus grunts.
When Mei is removing bra and has used marker mei_overdressed:
Ya look like yer meltin, Snow-Angel. Must be yer still overdressed. 
Aimee stage 1 has stripped: 
Aww, thank ya Snow-Angel! 
Huh, ya like that? Well...I guess I gotta give an encore!
Glad to see somebody here's got taste, Snow-Angel!
Aimee stage 2 stripping: 
I'm aimin to impress!
I'm aimin for yer heart, Snow-Angel!

Mercy: 
when mercy is removing her armor: 
Ugh, I hate armor. I mean, it's fun poppin bank shots off it, but actually penetratin?
Good news Mercy--no medical bills from me! Though caskets are pretty pricy...
Mercy's breasts are visible: 
8. I'll bump it up to 9 if ya jump around some. 
8. I'd give ya higher, but as they ain't wrapped round my darlin's cock, yer losin style points.
8 outta 10. Wait--no, definantly a 8. 
when Aimee has finished masturbating. 
Thanks for the healin, Mercy. If ya ever need somebody dead, I'm yer gal.
Thanks for the patch-up, Mercy. Yer an angel.
Yer a lifesaver, Mercy. Never though we'd actually need a healer on board. Thanks.

Mettaton: 
Mettaton must strip, stage 0: 
Coulda sworn ya were box shaped...
Yer sposed to be the Mettaton in the posters, right? So why ain't ya a big gray box?
Honest, I was kinda lookin' forward to seein how a big gray box strips. But I guess ya will do. 
when he has removed his undershirt:
And here I thought robots were just for killin. Now they're for jigglin.
I wonder what darlin would think of ya...
When Chica is removing panties and mettaton has already lost pants:
But...Mettaton has pink panties AND tits. Don't tell me ya got a wing-wang tucked in there...
When Mettaton starts to masturbate and Aimee is in stage 1 or later: 
Ya gotta guy up top? I was wonderin why the ceiling pissed it self while I was shootin earlier.
That's his name? With how close my bullets came by him, I'm sure there's more than just burger in those pants. 
When Aimee must strip after stage 0, Mettaton is masturbating or finished: 
Hey Burgerpants! Duck!
Look alive Burgerpants! Wouldn't want ya to wet yerself again!
Hahaha! Dance Burgerpants, dance!
Hey Burgerpants! Catch!
Special delivery here for ya, Burgerpants!

Mia: 
must strip, removing magatama:
Yer a ghost, right Mia? I knew a ghost kid once--real sweetie. Cept the apocalypse thing, but uh, he's reformed now.
Yer a ghost, ain'tcha Mia? I can sense these things. Not sure how canon that is, but it's what my creators told the press.

Moon: 
Moon must strip stage 1, Futaba is also playing:
She oughta commit to an insane asylum. 
visible crotch (while Moon climaxes) but only before Aimee is naked
(Aimee also climaxes upon stripping nude, though for a different kink.):
Ya came just from people lookin at ya? Yer messed up ain'tcha?
Climaxin? Really? Yer totally fakin it.
There's no way ya just came, ya attention hog.
Look: the only way to cum without touchin it is from my darlin's cakes. There's no cakes here. Ya faked it.
Moon starts masturbating:
Would darlin like like this Moon character? I really don't know...
This Moon dame's nuts. I'm not sure if darlin would be more aroused or annoyed...
Moon finishes masturbating: 
Ah, that was fun. No way in hell am I invitin her to darlin's pancake shop though. Too crazy. 
Never seen any that eager without darlin involved. If they met, she'd be a weapon of mass destruction!
That was hot...though I'm glad I got my gun. This Moon wacko is dangerous. 
Moon has lost 2 times in a row: 
Ugh! Yer pissin me off here, Moon. 
Jeez, is it too much to ask ya to give a single solitary flip about winnin?
For the love of--Moon! Play to win! Yer killin me here!
Oh come on! Again!? Ya ever hear that variety is the spice of life?
Feh. No fun when they wanna lose...
Oh come one! It's "strip poker," not just "strip."
Do we gotta call management in on ya, Moon?

Nagisa: multiple times:
Nagisa must strip stage 0, marker:nagisa_first_time_playing:
Yer a first timer, huh? It's fine to start of small. 
Yer a first timer, huh? Just do whatever yer comfortable with. 
Aww, I remember my first time...but uh, no need to live up to giants. Start small.
as Nagisa removes her shoes (stage 0)
That's a pretty catchy song yer always hummin. ♫ Do-ongo dongo dongo dongo do-ongo dongo daikazoku ♫
♫ Do-ongo dongo dongo dongo do-ongo dongo daikazoku ♫ Every time I lookatcha, I hear that song.
♫ Do-ongo dongo dongo dongo do-ongo dongo daikazoku ♫ Heh, cute song. 
after Nagisa removes her shoes, marker:nagisa_first_time_playing:
See, that wasn't so hard! 
See? Easy-peasy! 
as Nagisa removes her socks (stage 1)
♫ Do-ongo dongo dongo dongo do-ongo dongo daikazoku ♫
as Nagisa removes her Jacket (stage 2) marker:nagisa_first_time_playing:
Think of it like practice. The more ya flaunt it, the easier it gets. 
Just keep practicin'. The more ya strip, the better ya get. 
after Nagisa removes her jacket:
♫ Do-ongo dongo dongo dongo do-ongo dongo daikazoku ♫
nagisa is removing shirt, marker:nagisa_first_time_playing:
Aww come on first-timer, we ain't strangers no more!
Nagisa must strip stage 4 (removing skirt):
♫ Do-ongo dongo d ♫ -- Dang it! It's stuck in my head!
♫ Do-ongo dongo d ♫ -- Dagnabit! I can't stop singin it! 
Nagisa stripping, stage 4 (removing skirt):
Maybe I can get somethin else stuck in my head. ♫ Set in my sights, get you tonight. Love in the crossfire. Ready, aim, fire! ♫ 
♫ Do-ongo dongo d ♫ -- N-no! Uh... ♫ Set in my sights, get you tonight. Love in the crossfire. Ready, aim, fire! ♫
Nagisa has removed skirt, stage 4:
♫ Set in my sights, get you ton-- ♫ -- Agh! Now that's stuck in my head!
♫ Set in my sights, get you ton-- ♫ -- Ugh! What've I done? This song's worse! I shoulda just stayed with that Dongo tune in my thinker.
nagisa has removed bra:
Eh. Knew a kid who kept sayin "coup de gravy." Compared to him, yer alright.
Eh. Knew a catgirl who spoke exclawsively in cat puns. Compared to her, yer alright.
When Nagisa starts masturbating:
Uh, sorry, I'm a bit lost here...what're we talkin bout? 
...Uh...Okay?
What're ya...?
When Nagisa finishes: 
I've watched a lotta dames schlick, but I've never seen somethin like that before. 
Well...whatever gets ya off I guess. 
Darlin says I'm "uncultured." Was that a culture thing? Was that art? Is that why I'm confused right now?

Nugi-chan
small male crotch is visible, marker:nugi-chan_sph
Holy crap, Nugs! Ya know, yer a real bi--wait, did he just get harder?
Whoahoho! Nugs! Yer a monster! ...uh, did he just get a bit bigger?

Palutena: 
when Aimee has removed footwear:
Aww, Angel...! It feels good to be appreciated. 
Aww, Angel...! Next shot's gonna be even wilder, just for you. 
Aww, Angel...! Ya know, I was thinkin of callin it quits, but if ya like it...
when Aimee is removing tube top and skirt:
Don'tcha worry Angel, no heavenly host were harmed in the makin of this shot. 
Bullet's ricochetin round yer heavens rght now, Angel. Don't worry--nobody's gettin hurt. 
Palutena has removed her stocking:
Well dang. Was hopin yer sock would turn into a glock, like in that angel anime. 
Aww, yer stockin doesn't turn into a gun? Yer not that type of angel?
Palutena has removed her panties:
Can't figure which I want more--yer undies shiftin into a handgun, or ya schlicking yer next loss.
Aw, yer knickers didn't transmorgify into a gun neither! Least I get to see yer godly tush.

Raven:
When Raven is removing her cloak:
Ooo--bout time! I've got the best eye this side of my head and even I can't see under that hood.
Ooo--we get to see yer face? I bet yer a cutie!
When Raven has removed her cloak:
I knew it! Yer a super-cutie! 
D'awww, yer blushin! 
Raven has removed leotard:
Next time yer up gainst my eyes, ya might want a higher thread-count leotard. Been oglin yer clam since ya first arrived.
Yeah yeah, old news. Think I didn't notice ya had no pantylines with that skin-tight leotard?

Revy: Multiple Times:
Must_strip, revy's first loss:
That's a Beretta 92FS Inox, right? With an extended barrel for increased accuracy and velocity. Nice.
Them's a Beretta 92FS Inox, and one's even a lefty conversion. Ya carry'em like their a parta yer hands...
What a gorgeous pair...I love watchin' them in action....They're both Beretta 92FS Inox, right?
While strippin guns: 
no additionall lines, but lines referencing the "clothing item" were removed
After stripping guns:
No, not the guns! They were innocent!
Hey, Revy, can I...Do ya mind if I field strip them? Just once. Just one?
A real gun-lover would sooner be naked than unarmed...
While Aimee must strip winning, normal, or losing, stage 3 (lost armbands) and Revy is naked: 
Oh Revy, ya really shoulda kept yer guns. Coulda taught ya a thing or two. 
Revy, ya don't know what yer missin with yer guns gone. You could be doin somethin like this for instance.

Rinkah:
Rinkah's chest is visible: 
Oh wow...yer totes darlin's type--he'd never say that, but if he saw this, he'd cream himself on the spot!
Hubba-hubba! If darlin were here he woulda flat ran away! He gets so bashful round girls like you.
Mmhmm! Yer the typa girl darlin trashtalks 'hind her back, but gets super bashful 'bout in person.
Chiaki must masturbate: 
Don't think there's an exact rule 'bout 8 items max, but more don't really seem fair.

Ruby: Multiple Times: 
Stripping belt (first strip):
The ammo on yer belt--That's 50 caliber anti-material rounds! Ya could penetrate a tank!
That ammo for yer rifle-scythe? I gotta rifle-ax with wings myself. 
Woowee, there's some big bullets. Specialty rounds, too, if I got my nose right.
Stripped belt: 
You and me? We're friends now. Friends with benefts. Benefits bein I get to see yer gun later. 
My gun and yer gun have got to meet. How bout we arrange a little play-date later?
Left Guncleaver at home--Too hard to model. Hey, I'll show ya mine if ya show me yers. 
Stripping panties: 
Heheh...Time to see Rube's pubes. 
And there goes the last of Red's threads. 
Time to see little red hood's goods!

Scarlet Witch: multiple times: 
as SW starts to masturbate:
Whoa! Ya can use magic for that? I'm know a witch, but her magic just blows yutz's up in new and interestin ways.
Wow, it's like ya got yer own harem! Ya can do that with magic!?
during masturbation: 
nothing added, but targetting was used to remove lines that wouldn't make sense.
finished masturbation: 
I know what I gotta give darlin for his birthday! You!
If that's what magic's all about, I should head off to school, too!

Twilight: multiple times:
When Twilight is removing panties: 
A-are ya serious? Yer not pullin our collective legs are ya?
Yer goin panties first!? 
after twilight has removed her panties: 
They say "don't look a gift horse in the mouth," but...
Also any lines from non-targetted list that make sense. 
after twilight has removed her skirt:
used targetting to remove lines that didn't make sense in this situation.
When Twilight provokes twilight_cutie_mark marker, Aimee responds when she has a good hand, okay hand, bad hand, is masturbating, is heavy masturbating, or is finished:
I can't quite tell, how boutcha bend over some?
Maybe it's between the cheeks? Ya better spreadem.

Weiss:
when weiss first must strip: 
I was hopin ya'd bring yer awesome revolver-sword with ya. Ya know, Murder-master. 
Ya RWBY molls know how to rock a weapon. Hey, where's yer revolver-sword? Ya know, Merge-a-burger.
Aw Jeez, and here I was hopin I'd get to see yer kickin revolver-sword. Ya know, More-die-nasty. 
when Weiss removes her jewlery:
To bad all that money can't buy ya skill.
When Weiss removes her jacket:
Think of it like Monopoly, Ice Queen. Yer the tophat, and I gotta hotel on Boardwalk. Time to pay up.
Think of it like Jumungi, Ice Queen. "Everytime ya lose a hand / another item falls like sand."
Think of it like D&D, Ice Queen. Yer playin an Elf Wizard, and I just sundered yer Cloak of Resistance +1.
Think of it like Yu-Gi-Oh, Ice Queen. Thought yer Blue-eyes was hot shit, but I flipped Man-Eater Bug. Discard to the graveyard!
When Weiss is removing her jacket:
Who needs money? I gotta gun. I could hunt, I could rob--In fact, I think I'd like yer bra. 
With all that money, ya could worn ten bras. But ya really wanted us to see yer titties, didn't ya?
What, so yer a slab of meat for sale? Ya think ya can just buy yer breast meat from us? 
When Weiss must strip her panties:
Yes, yes! Absolutely so! Yer doin this!
What, are yer panties frozen to yer snatch? Just drop them already!
When Weiss is stripping her panties:
Fine. I won't look at ya. Directly. For now. Lookin back in 3...2...1...
Fine, fine, I'll look away while ya defrost yer delicates. Some people...
When Weiss has stripped panties:
Ohoho! Looked at that shaved ice! Is that why ya were so frigid?
Ohoho! Yer primmed up nice and proper! Who'd ya shave that for?
Ohoho! A hairless harris! Uh, Airless heiress! ...Ugh--toungue tied.

Yang: Multiple times: 
Yang has removed scarf, Futaba is also playing:
Whoa! Shots fired! I hope yer as good at duckin' as ya look, Shorty!
Must strip stage 1 (after scarf, immediately before losing boots):
Wait a sec, those gauntlets...are they also guns? Ya have guns in yer gauntlets!? 
I just noticed...Yang, yer gauntlets...have guns in them, yeah? 
Wait...is that...! Yang! Do ya know yer gauntlets're...well of course ya...they're gun-gauntlets! Oh wow!
stripping boots:
Yeah, yeah, boots, whatever--Yang, what's the firin trigger? Is it by the thumb? Kinetic? Magic? Psychic?
Yeah, boots, sure--Yang, that uses shotgun rounds, right? Do ya use buckshot or slugs? What gauge?
Uh-huh. Boots. Cool. Yang, bout those gauntlets? How's the recoil? How're they braced? How're they cooled?
Stripped boots: 
...Uh...gotta little excited there. Sorry. 
Dang it, Aimee, way to blow the first impression. Now her gun-gauntlets think yer a spaz.
Oh...uh yeah, we're playin a game here. Sorry. 
stripping gauntlets: 
Yer gauntlets! Couldn't ya, like, loose yer jacket first?
Droppin her gauntlets...some people have no shame...
Yer gauntlets...and here I'd been thinkin we were kindret spirits...
Stripped gauntlets: 
Rest in peace, awesome gauntlet-guns. Yer shootin up angels now.
It's like the world just got a bit grayer...Rest in peace, awesome gauntlet-guns. 
Rest in peace, awesome gauntlet-guns. We hardly even knew ya. 

Zoey: must strip, when Zoey loses her sweater:
I notice ya keep shootin glares at peep's center of mass...ya a gunslinger, Zoey?
Zoey, ya got some residue on yer cuffs...ya fire a gun reciently?

Zone: 
while removing her boots:
Is it really for the foot fetishists if ya can't see the toes?
Ya say that Zonie-tan, but how's my darlin gonna lick tween yer toes wiith those leggins on ya?
Eh, yer cute, but yer not gonna drive my darlin wild till yer toes are out. 
After removing her leggings: 
Now, that's somethin darlin would drool for!
Ohoho! And the toes come into the picture!
♫ Them toes were made for stompin, and that's just waht they'll do! ♫
After Male has lost minor, while zone has lost sweater:
After this, Zonie-tan, I'mma get my hubby to feed ya a burger. Both literal and figurative.
Zonie-tan, swing by my darlin's pancake shop after this. Serves everythin yer cravin. Everythin.
Stop, Zonie-tan! Yer maken me hungry! It's bad enough darlin ain't here...
zone-tan's chest will be visible:
Psh--like ya don't have a closet full of them. I know how ya cartoon types work.
Ya know, I think I could turn that sweater into a virgin-killer. Yer loss, Zonie-tan.
Oh Zonie, Zonie, Zonie, tan, tan, tan. Ya know ya want a try. 
Aimee has started masturbating while Zone is not naked:
Yeah, well yer turn's comin up soon, Zonie-tan. 
Ya know, ya could pop an SP and take yer turn now if ya want, Zonie-tan.
Aimee has started masturbating while Zone is naked:
Yeah, well yer turn's comin up soon, Booty-tan. 
Ya know, ya could pop an SP and take yer turn now if ya want, Booty-tan.
Zone-tan is masturbating, in addition to normal lines:
Yer really in the zone, ain'tcha Booty-tan?
It's like there's an internet happinin right in front of me! An entire metric internet!