<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>

<!--This file was machine generated using the Character Editor v6.7.8 at 3:05:38 p. m. on octubre 29, 2022. Do not edit this file directly unless you know what you're doing.-->
<opponent>
    <version>v6.7.8</version>
    <first>Rin</first>
    <last>Kagamine</last>
    <label>Rin Kagamine</label>
    <gender>female</gender>
    <size>small</size>
    <timer>15</timer>
    <intelligence>average</intelligence>



    <wardrobe>
        <clothing name="panties" generic="underwear" position="lower" type="important" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="bra" generic="bra" position="upper" type="important" />
        <clothing name="skirt" generic="skirt" position="lower" type="major" />
        <clothing name="shirt" generic="shirt" position="upper" type="major" />
        <clothing name="knee socks and shoes" generic="shoes" position="lower" type="minor" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="sleeves" generic="sleeves" position="upper" type="minor" plural="true" />
    </wardrobe>

    <poses>
        <pose id="0-boo">
            <sprite id="grinning" delay="2.25" src="0-grinning.png" x="0" y="0" alpha="0" />
            <sprite id="yay" src="0-yay.png" x="0" y="6000" scalex="5.5" scaley="5.5" skewx="0" alpha="100" />
            <directive type="animation" id="grinning" delay="2.25" ease="smooth" interpolation="linear">
                <keyframe time="0" x="0" y="0" alpha="0" />
                <keyframe time="0.75" alpha="100" />
            </directive>
            <directive type="animation" id="yay" ease="smooth" interpolation="linear">
                <keyframe time="0" x="0" y="6000" scalex="5.5" scaley="5.5" skewx="0" alpha="100" />
                <keyframe time="0.75" y="6000" />
                <keyframe time="1" y="1900" alpha="100" />
                <keyframe time="1.25" y="1500" alpha="100" />
                <keyframe time="1.75" y="1900" alpha="0" />
            </directive>
        </pose>
        <pose id="0-boo_FG">
            <sprite id="grinning" delay="1.75" src="reskins/rin_kagamine_fear_garden/0-sweet.png" x="0" y="0" alpha="0" />
            <sprite id="yay" src="reskins/rin_kagamine_fear_garden/0-yay.png" x="0" y="6000" scalex="5.5" scaley="5.5" skewx="0" alpha="100" />
            <directive type="animation" id="grinning" delay="1.75" ease="smooth" interpolation="linear">
                <keyframe time="0" x="0" y="0" alpha="0" />
                <keyframe time="0.25" alpha="100" />
            </directive>
            <directive type="animation" id="yay" ease="smooth" interpolation="linear">
                <keyframe time="0" x="0" y="6000" scalex="5.5" scaley="5.5" skewx="0" alpha="100" />
                <keyframe time="0.5" y="2000" alpha="100" />
                <keyframe time="0.75" y="1300" alpha="100" />
                <keyframe time="1" y="1700" alpha="100" />
                <keyframe time="1.38" y="2000" alpha="0" />
            </directive>
        </pose>
    </poses>

    <behaviour>
        <trigger id="selected">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition count="1-" role="other" character="hatsune_miku" />
                <state img="#-pouting.png" marker="Miku01">Oh... Hey, Miku. I didn't expect to see you here. </state>
                <state img="#-pouting.png" marker="Miku02">Hey everyone! Who's ready to... &lt;br&gt;Oh, &lt;i&gt;she's&lt;/i&gt; here.&lt;br&gt;Hi, Miku.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~month.number~" value="10" />
                <state img="custom:#-boo">Boo!&lt;br&gt;Happy Halloween, ~player~! Did I scare ya? Ready for some spoooky card games with sexy results?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="rin_kagamine_fear_garden" role="self" />
                <test expr="~month.number~" value="10" />
                <state img="custom:#-boo_FG" marker="FearGarden">Happy Halloween, ~player~. Will you play with me?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-grinning.png">I'm all warmed up! Let's start this!</state>
                <state img="#-piece.png">The cutest Vocaloid is ready to play!</state>
                <state img="#-sweet.png">Please go easy on me, okay? I'm just a beginner after all~</state>
                <state img="#-yay.png">Let's get this show on the road, everyone! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="rin_kagamine_fear_garden" role="self" />
                <state img="#-yay.png" marker="FearGarden">One, two, three, four, five, six, seven... ten!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_selected">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FearGarden" />
                <condition role="target" character="rin" />
                <state img="#-shrug.png">... Really, ~player~? Did you invite &lt;i&gt;her&lt;/i&gt;?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FearGarden" />
                <condition role="target" character="ribbon_girl" />
                <state img="#-overwhelmed.png">... What kind of... abomination is that?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FearGarden" />
                <condition role="target" character="beatrix" />
                <state img="#-cocky.png">... Oh, I am so going to enjoy this... I'm not used to someone so... handful...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="hatsune_miku" />
                <state img="#-shrug.png" marker="Miku03">I should've expected to see you here, Miku. You've always liked being the center of attention.</state>
                <state img="#-grinning.png" marker="Miku04">Hey, Miku! Did you barge into here accidentally? This is strip poker, are you sure you're up for this challenge?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FearGarden" />
                <state img="#-grinning.png">The more, the merrier! We could always use a pair of extra hands!</state>
                <state img="#-sweet.png">Are you here to help us have a better game? How thoughtful of you to lend a hand...</state>
                <state img="#-challenging.png">Come, come! No need to be scared, you're in good hands!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-piece.png">We have company? Good, I love to play with the audience!</state>
                <state img="#-grinning.png">Hey there! Ready to be entertained?</state>
                <state img="#-piece.png">I hope you don't mind that I keep talking about "performing" and "shows" and stuff, I'm just so used to it!</state>
                <state img="#-seducing.png">It's good to have you here. The more, the better.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_start">
            <case stage="0" priority="999">
                <condition filter="rin_kagamine_fear_garden" role="self" />
                <state img="#-sweet.png" marker="FearGarden">Is everyone ready to play? I apologize for the garden knife, I was just tending to my garden...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="hatsune_miku" />
                <state img="#-yay.png" marker="Miku05">Let the best VOCALOID win!&lt;br&gt;... {small}Which is gonna be me!{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png" marker="Miku06">Let's make this a fair game, shall we, Miku? Let the best performer win.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-yay.png">Hello everyone! Your favorite VOCALOID has joined the game!</state>
                <state img="#-seducing.png">So, shall we begin?</state>
                <state img="#-piece.png">It's always a pleasure to play with some of my fans! And if you're not a fan, by the end of this game, you'll eb one!</state>
                <state img="#-yay.png">Time for the cutest, most talented VOCALOID to join the game! Hold your applauses until the end of the game!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="swap_cards">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <test expr="~cards~" value="0" />
                <state img="#-grinning.png">I'm happy with the ones I've got now, thanks!</state>
                <state img="#-piece.png">No thanks! I've got what I need!</state>
                <state img="#-startled.png">Could it be...? I... actually don't need any cards!</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">I think this will do...? You know what? Just keep going, don't give me any cards. I can manage with these.</state>
                <state img="#-challenging.png">Keep your cards. I've got just what I need...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FearGarden" />
                <state img="#-sweet.png">So many cards to make this hand even better...</state>
                <state img="#-sweet.png">And here I thought you couldn't make this hand even more perfect...</state>
                <state img="#-sweet.png">I think I'll have,,, ~cards.text~. But I already like this hand as it is.</state>
                <state img="#-sweet.png">Do you mind if I keep my hand? It's just so... pretty.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-bullied.png">W-wait, I wasn't ready! Give me ~cards.text~!</state>
                <state img="#-challenging.png">Let's make this hand even better, shall we? ~cards.text~ will do.</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Are you trying to make me lose on purpose? How devious. ~Cards.text~ will do.</state>
                <state img="#-furious.png">No need to be so mean to me! I know you're trying to make me lose on purpose! Now give me ~cards.text~!</state>
                <state img="#-grinning.png">No stress! With enough confidence, and maybe ~cards.text~, I can win in the end!</state>
                <state img="#-idea.png">Should I...? No, no, or maybe...? I will... take ~cards.text~, I think...?</state>
                <state img="#-inviting.png">Give me ~cards.text~! I can share some of my poker strategies if you want!&lt;br&gt;{small}The secret is that I don't have any! The real poker was inside you all along!{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I think I should take... ~cards.text~? I should've reread some poker strategies before coming here... Not that I care if I lose, but I try to keep games interesting...</state>
                <state img="#-piece.png">The best Vocaloid requires the best poker hand, don't you think? So it's ~cards.text~ for me!</state>
                <state img="#-pouting.png">Huh? Oh, yeah, give me ~cards.text~ or whatever...&lt;br&gt;Why is this game so random anyway... Some games can end stupidly fast, and others can last forever...</state>
                <state img="#-seducing.png">Could the cutest-yet-sexiest Vocaloid get ~cards.text~, please?</state>
                <state img="#-startled.png">It's gotta be... ~cards.text~. ~cards.text~, right? Is it?</state>
                <state img="#-sweet.png">If it's not too much to ask, mind if I get ~cards.text~?</state>
                <state img="#-yay.png">It's gonna be ~cards.text~ for the famous virtual diva in the room!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="good_hand">
            <case stage="3-6">
                <condition role="other" character="hatsune_miku" />
                <state img="#-furious.png" oneShotId="237">Just you wait until the low overcomes the high...!</state>
                <state img="#-furious.png" oneShotId="238">You'll see how the lower rules the higher in the end!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" priority="50">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FearGarden" />
                <state img="#-idea.png">I suppose you could call this a good hand... But I think all hands are perfect as they are.</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">My hand is so unique and mysterious... I wonder if there's another hand that's just like mine...</state>
                <state img="#-idea.png">Why do numbers and letters determine if a hand is good or not? I think they're all perfect as they are... </state>
                <state img="#-sweet.png">I suppose I won't have to strip this round... That's a shame, don't you think?</state>
                <state img="#-piece.png">I got a good hand! In fact, I've got two! Tehee~!</state>
                <state img="#-grinning.png">Have you noticed how sharp the edges of these cards are? If you got a paper cut from these the wound would sting for hours...</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">Lies. It's all lies. This game is all lies...</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Let's not cut each other's throats over who has the better hands, shall we?</state>
                <state img="#-yay.png">There are so many interesting and unique people in these games... I don't think I have to keep my garden a secret anymore. But I'm keeping the details as a surprise!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-yay.png">This round's mine!</state>
                <state img="#-grinning.png">Now this is a hand!... I think, I hope so!</state>
                <state img="#-piece.png">So, what did you all get? It doesn't matter, I'm not losing this one!</state>
                <state img="#-grinning.png">I think I can work with these... I hope! I don't actually know!</state>
                <state img="#-inviting.png">What did you get? Show me, show me!</state>
                <state img="#-piece.png">This is a great hand! Unless I got poker completely wrong, which is a possibility!</state>
                <state img="#-challenging.png">Now, bow to me!</state>
                <state img="#-seducing.png">Oh, it seems you'll be enjoying someone else's stripping this round. Don't worry. You'll get another chance to watch me!</state>
                <state img="#-challenging.png">I'm coming at you with the power of a road roller, and you won't stop me!</state>
                <state img="#-challenging.png">I don't need no "master" or "producer" anymore! I'm gonna fly on my own, and roll all over you like a road roller!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6">
                <state img="#-piece.png">Close, but not this time! You're not watching Rin-chan touch herself yet!</state>
                <state img="#-idea.png">Giving me good cards this late in the game? You're not in the mood to watch me perform, are you?</state>
                <state img="#-bullied.png">Oh, what terrible hand I have! What could Rin-chan do now!? Am I really going to lose now?</state>
                <state img="#-after+.png">I doubt I'll be losing this one. So... mind if we just skip to the next round? I doubt there's anyone more interesting to watch than me, anyway.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="okay_hand">
            <case stage="0-6" priority="50">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FearGarden" />
                <state img="#-grinning.png" oneShotId="125">Did you know that card throwing isn't actually harmful? At least not with modern cards. If you were to use ancient cards made out of wood pulp you could sharpen the edges to cut a throat in a single slice!</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">So many hands... of poker. Holding cards in such different, yet unique ways... Fufufu...</state>
                <state img="#-sweet.png" oneShotId="126">~blank~</state>
                <state img="#-yay.png">This hand is so pretty... Sometimes it has five of them, but occassionally there'll be four...&lt;br&gt;Cards, that is.</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Fufufu...</state>
                <state img="#-grinning.png">What a lovely game! Three to five players holding things and then stripping their clothes...&lt;br&gt;{small}So that's six to ten poker-playing hands...{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-idea.png">Do you come here often? And, most importantly... do you usually come with friends, or do you prefer to come alone?</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png" oneShotId="262">It's nice to finally meet adventurous people. I'm used to scaredy-cats who are afraid of the silliest  things... Like walking home alone, or hanging out with a friend in the dark...</state>
                <state img="#-idea.png">... Are we friends now? Do you consider me your friend?&lt;br&gt;Do you trust me?</state>
                <state img="#-seducing.png">I might need a ride after the game. Does anyone want to drive me home? I'll make sure our time together is worth it...</state>
                <state img="#-sweet.png">Are you afraid of the city at night,~player~? I could walk with you to make sure you don't get lost...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-idea.png">I just need any of you to have a worse hand than mine, right?</state>
                <state img="#-pouting.png">Alright... I hope this'll do...</state>
                <state img="#-sweet.png">I can work with these... right?</state>
                <state img="#-yay.png">Nothing to worry about! I have this under control, I swear!</state>
                <state img="#-yay.png">It's okay, it's okay... I can do this! I won't lose my hope!</state>
                <state img="#-yay.png">I have no idea how to play this game, but I will give it my all!</state>
                <state img="#-seducing.png">If I get a single queen, that counts as a two pair, right? Wouldn't you think of me as a queen already?</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I'm not sure if getting a good or bad hand is either good or bad... Isn't the point of the game to lose and strip?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6">
                <state img="#-shrug.png">Jeez, if you wanted to watch me touching myself so badly, you could've used the internet instead of giving me this hand...</state>
                <state img="#-grinning.png" oneShotId="11" dialogue-layer="over" font-size="small">I know I'm getting closer to the end, so... can I say I really enjoy being here? Most people who want to watch me in lewd situations just use the internet, fondle themselves and move on, but in here we can actually chat and enjoy a more intimate experience!</state>
                <state img="#-overwhelmed.png"></state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="bad_hand">
            <case stage="0-6" priority="50">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FearGarden" />
                <state img="#-shrug.png" oneShotId="260">I don't think I'll win this time, but I'm not gonna run away or anything. I'm so tired of people running away from situations they don't like...</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Uhm.. I think I'll have to strip next... &lt;i&gt;Sigh...&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;I was hoping to see you unfastening your belts, or unbuttoning your buttons...</state>
                <state img="#-sweet.png">I hope this game doesn't take too long... Tendingna garden on my own is a very time-consuming hobby...</state>
                <state img="#-yay.png">I like to keep my knife sharp and always close... You never know when you'll find something worth cutting and taking back to the garden... </state>
                <state img="#-overwhelmed.png">A-a &lt;i&gt;bad hand&lt;/i&gt;? That's ridiculous! All hands are beautiful and unique, even those who are very similar...</state>
                <state img="#-sweet.png">I don't mind getting a bad hand... All hands are one-of-a-kind, after all. This is an experience worth remembering.</state>
                <state img="#-overwhelmed.png">Oh, what a lovely hand... Who could ever call you "bad"? You're perfect as you are...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2" oneShotId="15" priority="1">
                <state img="#-startled.png">... This might've been a bad day to forget I wasn't wearing a bra...</state>
                <state img="#-startled.png">Wait... Did I forgot to put on a bra today?</state>
                <state img="#-startled.png">... I just realized I forgot to put on a bra before coming here...</state>
                <state img="#-startled.png">Shoot, a bad hand this early... Well, at least I- &lt;i&gt;Wait&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;... I-I forgot to wear a bra!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-startled.png">Oh no no no...</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">I'll save you some time and start stripping...</state>
                <state img="#-sweet.png" oneShotId="2">... Maybe there's some rule I don't know that makes me win in the end?</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I should've learned how to play poker instead of randomly picking cards...</state>
                <state img="#-sweet.png" oneShotId="3">Alright, keep it cool, keep it cool, no need to have a meltdown over it...</state>
                <state img="#-bullied.png">Who cares if I got a bad hand!? M-maybe someone else got a worse one! That's the thrilling part of the game!</state>
                <state img="#-furious.png">Even I know this hand is bad... Whatever! Bring it on!</state>
                <state img="#-grinning.png" oneShotId="4">Would you look at that! Three pairs! You better watch out for this hand!</state>
                <state img="#-furious.png">What is this abstract nonsense!? Give me my cards back!</state>
                <state img="#-pouting.png" oneShotId="74">RNG can be such a b... &lt;i&gt;meanie&lt;/i&gt;, sometimes. Like when you're listening to my songs on YouTube and it suddenly decides to play Miku's songs instead, and then it's all Miku's songs or Miku's covers of my songs...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6">
                <state img="#-startled.png">!</state>
                <state img="#-furious.png">Aw, come on!</state>
                <state img="#-furious.png">You can't be serious!</state>
                <state img="#-after-.png">I might as well sit down and start touching myself...</state>
                <state img="#-startled.png">I-It's okay! It's okay! I still have this! I can pull through, right? Right?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="hand">
            <case stage="0-6" id="3" oneShotId="8" totalRounds="5-">
                <test expr="~weekday.number~" value="1" />
                <state img="#-inviting.png">So, ~player~, have you listened to my songs lately? If you're in the mood for one of the classics, why not listen to &lt;i&gt;Meltdown&lt;/i&gt;? Some say it's my best work!</state>
                <state img="#-grinning.png">Mind if I recommend you a song, ~player~? If you want to listen to a cool song with a cool beat about running from home and feeling down, &lt;i&gt;Tokyo Teddy Bear&lt;/i&gt; might be right up your alley!</state>
                <state img="#-sweet.png">If you don't mind, ~player~... Can I invite you to listen to one of my songs today? If you're feeling lovey-dovey or in need of some affection, perhaps you'd enjoy &lt;i&gt;I Like You, I Love You&lt;/i&gt;?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="4" oneShotId="9" totalRounds="5-">
                <test expr="~weekday.number~" value="2" />
                <state img="#-cocky.png">&lt;i&gt;Oh ho ho ho ho!&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;~Player~, I order you to stop your lecherous activities and listen to &lt;i&gt;Daughter of Evil&lt;/i&gt; right now! And if you already have, listen to the rest of the &lt;i&gt;Seven Deadly Sins Series&lt;/i&gt;!</state>
                <state img="#-sweet.png">Hey, ~player~... If it's not too much to ask... could I ask that you give &lt;i&gt;Kokoro&lt;/i&gt; a listen? I worked really hard perfecting that song, and.. I'd just... I'd just like you to hear it. Please?</state>
                <state img="#-challenging.png">Hey, hey, ~player~! Don't you just hate schooling and the burdens it brings? If you do, why don't you give &lt;i&gt;Lost One's Weeping&lt;/i&gt; a listen? I'm sure it'll speak to you!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="5" oneShotId="10" totalRounds="5-">
                <test expr="~weekday.number~" value="3" />
                <state img="#-challenging.png">Are you tired of being nice, ~player~? Don't you just want to go... listen to &lt;i&gt;Abstract Nonsense&lt;/i&gt; to feel a little less alone in your tiredness?</state>
                <state img="#-piece.png">You know what? All this stripping reminds me of a song! Why, it's a perfect day to listen to &lt;i&gt;I Can Take Off My Panties!&lt;/i&gt; And yes, that is the real name of the song!</state>
                <state img="#-inviting.png">Are you a fan of my works, ~player~? If not, why don't you listen to &lt;i&gt;Bird of Paradise&lt;/i&gt; or &lt;i&gt;Tengaku&lt;/i&gt; to get you started? I'm very proud of how those songs came out!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="6" oneShotId="11" totalRounds="5-">
                <test expr="~weekday.number~" value="4" />
                <state img="#-idea.png">Lots of people would like Rin-chan to be their girlfriend... But there's only one Rin-chan! In the meantime, why don't you give &lt;i&gt;Demon Girlfriend&lt;/i&gt; a listen?</state>
                <state img="#-sweet.png">Were you ever confused by love, ~player~? If so, why not give &lt;i&gt;Melancholy&lt;/i&gt; a listen? I think you might relate to the lyrics! I... just want you to listen to it, pretty please?</state>
                <state img="#-startled.png">Uwa! Is it Halloween already?&lt;br&gt;... No? Not yet? Sorry, I've been singing &lt;i&gt;Happy Halloween&lt;/i&gt;, one of my greatest hits of all time, so much that I got lost into it!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="7" oneShotId="12" totalRounds="5-">
                <test expr="~weekday.number~" value="5" />
                <state img="#-startled.png">Uwa! Is it Halloween already?&lt;br&gt;... No? Not yet? Sorry, I've been singing &lt;i&gt;Happy Halloween&lt;/i&gt;, one of my greatest hits of all time, so much that I got lost into it!</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">♫ &lt;i&gt;I'm not usually the type to hold a grudge, &lt;br&gt;but... you've affected me. &lt;br&gt;And now... I'm nothing. &lt;br&gt;But {b}RAGE!{!reset} ♪&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;That was a small demonstration of &lt;i&gt;Karma&lt;/i&gt;, a song that if you havent' heard yet, you should.</state>
                <state img="#-piece.png">Are you in the mood to travel, ~player~? Because if you listen to &lt;i&gt;Deep Sea City Underground&lt;/i&gt;, I'll be sure to take you for a ride!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="8" oneShotId="13" totalRounds="5-">
                <test expr="~weekday.number~" value="6" />
                <state img="#-grinning.png">~Player~! If I can get your attention, mind giving the song &lt;i&gt;ROKI&lt;/i&gt; a listen sometime? Perhaps right now? I'm sure you'd like it if you listened to it!</state>
                <state img="#-startled.png">Uwaa! &lt;br&gt;Sorry, ~player~, I got startled for a bit... I was just thinking about &lt;i&gt;Fear Garden&lt;/i&gt;, one of the scariest songs I've sung! Perhaps you'd like to listen to it to make me feel less scared?</state>
                <state img="#-seducing.png">I was just thinking... Why don't you put in some background music, ~player~? You could listen to my song, &lt;i&gt;Tiger Rampage&lt;/i&gt;, on the background while watching me strip...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="9" oneShotId="14" totalRounds="5-">
                <test expr="~weekday.number~" value="7" />
                <state img="#-seducing.png">Things sure are gonna get heated to~background.time~, huh? Why don't you put in some background music, ~player~? Something like... &lt;i&gt;The Celestial Fox&lt;/i&gt; by me, perhaps?</state>
                <state img="#-piece.png">To~background.time~ sure is a sweet ~background.time~! You know what could make it sweeter, ~player~? Listening to &lt;i&gt;Sweet Magic&lt;/i&gt;, sung by me! Go listen to it now!</state>
                <state img="#-yay.png">You know? There's already too many Miku Expos! It's time for a Rin Expo! And we could start by listening to &lt;i&gt;RIN EXPO&lt;/i&gt;, the song about me getting my own expo... in spanish!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <test expr="~rin_kagamine.hand.score~" value="007" />
                <state img="#-startled.png">Did... Did I just get the worst hand possible?</state>
                <state img="#-bullied.png">You could've just told me to start touching myself instead of giving me the literal worst hand in the game!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-sweet.png" oneShotId="1">Some producers love to portray me as a yandere type... &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;You don't want to find out why.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" oneShotId="5" priority="0">
                <condition count="1-" filter="chef" role="other" />
                <state img="#-grinning.png">&lt;i&gt;Sweetie, sweetie, sweetie magical... Sweetie, sweetie, sweetie, yeah, yeah!&lt;/i&gt; ♪</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" priority="0">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FearGarden" />
                <test expr="~human.hand.score~" cmp="&lt;=" value="014" />
                <state img="#-sweet.png" oneShotId="141">Your hand just twitched, ~player~. Did you get no pairs?</state>
                <state img="#-sweet.png" oneShotId="142">Have you gotten a bad set of cards, ~player~? Your index finger twitched for a bit.</state>
                <state img="#-yay.png" oneShotId="143">Is everything alright, ~player~? You tightened your grip on the cards...</state>
                <state img="#-idea.png" oneShotId="144">Your middle finger just tapped lightly on the cards... Are you not satisfied with your hand, ~player~?</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png" oneShotId="145">Someone's hand just had a quiet spasm... Someone who's probably stripping next...</state>
                <state img="#-seducing.png" oneShotId="146">I see you're keeping your cool, ~player~, but your middle finger just gave you away. Don't worry, even if you got a "bad hand", I still think you have a beautiful hand...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip">
            <case stage="0-5" priority="500">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FearGarden" />
                <state img="#-overwhelmed.png" oneShotId="163">Oh... do I really have to? I don't mind, but...</state>
                <state img="#-idea.png" oneShotId="162">Oh... So I just lost, then...</state>
                <state img="#-idea.png" oneShotId="161">... I see... Do you mind if I do this quickly? I'd rather watch you strip than stripping myself...</state>
                <state img="#-startled.png" oneShotId="160">Oh no...!</state>
                <state img="#-yay.png" oneShotId="159">... Oh well... I'll just put this aside for a bit, I wouldn't want to accidentally cut myself and get bloodstains on my clothes...</state>
                <state img="#-pouting.png" oneShotId="164">... I'd rather watch you than the other way around, but I'll play along...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <condition count="1-" status="not_alive" role="other" character="hatsune_miku" />
                <state img="#-piece.png" oneShotId="101" marker="Miku07">I'll be joining you soon, Miku! But I'll make sure to put on a better show than yours!</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png" oneShotId="102" marker="Miku08">It's gonna be me, then? I've already beaten who I came here to beat, so I don't mind.</state>
                <state img="#-inviting.png" oneShotId="103" marker="Miku09">You hear that, Miku? I'm joining you soon!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2" priority="0">
                <condition count="1-" status="alive" role="other" character="hatsune_miku" />
                <state img="#-startled.png" oneShotId="89">E-eh? T-this is just a small setback! I can still beat you, Miku!</state>
                <state img="#-pouting.png" oneShotId="90">I thought that strategy was gonna do it...&lt;br&gt;Doesn't matter. I'll win in the end. You'll see!</state>
                <state img="#-seducing.png" oneShotId="91">Oh, well. Guess I'll have to show off more of my delicate and graceful body. Can you really call that a loss?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_winning">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Oh well, at least I'm wearing more than everyone else!</state>
                <state img="#-challenging.png">I'm not doing so bad, I could be down to your levels!</state>
                <state img="#-furious.png">The game is not over yet! And I'm still winning by a long shot!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_normal">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-pouting.png">Oh, it's tea time! I gotta leave now, bye!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;... Fine, I'll keep playing.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">This is what I get for not properly learning how to play...</state>
                <state img="#-furious.png">Fine! You will have your strip. But you better watch closely, I won't lose again!</state>
                <state img="#-challenging.png">I'm not out yet! As long as someone is having it worse than me, I've still got &lt;i&gt;some&lt;/i&gt; advantage!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_losing">
            <case stage="1-5">
                <state img="#-bullied.png">This isn't fair! You're all wearing more clothes than me!</state>
                <state img="#-bullied.png">You have to be cheating, right? How is this not cheating!?</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Hah! So it's... oh, it's me.</state>
                <state img="#-overwhelmed.png">I need to get better at this game asap...</state>
                <state img="#-idea.png">Hold on, if the goal of the game is to strip, am I losing... or actually winning?</state>
                <state img="#-idea.png">Oh, jeez, is it me again? Do you really want to watch poor innocent Rin-chan strip again?</state>
                <state img="#-seducing.png">You must really want to see me strip if you're bringing such big cards to the table...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-pouting.png">I should've worn something else if I was gonna play with such buzzkills...</state>
                <state img="#-yay.png">It appears that Rin-chan will have to show all these over-clothed buzzkils how you can do much more with less!</state>
                <state img="#-bullied.png">It's not fair! You're all wearing way too many clothes!</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Did I come here underdressed...? You don't think Rin-chan is lewd or anything, right...?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripping">
            <case stage="0" priority="50">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FearGarden" />
                <state img="#-strip-.png">These gloves keep my hands from getting dirty... or getting bruised... I'll be so exposed now...</state>
                <state img="#-strip+.png">Keeping your hands protected from all harm is essential to... everything, really. Have you noticed how we need our hands for everything?</state>
                <state img="#-strip+.png">I'll be so exposed without my gloves... But I have to admit there's some kind of... thrill in watching someone taking off their gloves...</state>
                <state img="#-strip-.png">Please don't ogle at my hands too much, I haven't put lotion on them for a while, nor have I trimmed my nails today. Gosh, how could I have been so careless...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" priority="50">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FearGarden" />
                <state img="#-strip+.png">Sometimes I wonder if I'd rather lose an arm or a leg...&lt;br&gt;I'd definitely lose the leg. Both of them, if needed.</state>
                <state img="#-strip+.png">If you had to choose between amputating your arms or your legs, which one would you choose? Personally, I'd cut my legs in a heartbeat.</state>
                <state img="#-strip-.png">Proper leg care is so boring... Legs are long, dull, plain and uninteresting. I can't believe some people get turned on just by looking at them.</state>
                <state img="#-strip-.png">Ogle at my legs all you want, I think they're overrated. If you had to choose between having your legs or arms ripped out, most people would choose the legs in a heartbeat.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" priority="50">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FearGarden" />
                <state img="#-strip+.png">I guess these have to go...</state>
                <state img="#-strip+.png">Boots are so boring anyway...</state>
                <state img="#-strip+.png">If it wasn't because I need to keep my feet from stepping on the broken flowerpot pieces, I wouldn't wear boots at all...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" priority="50">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FearGarden" />
                <state img="#-strip-.png" marker="FearGardenFall">Dumb boots on my dumb feet, attached to my dumb long legs, why are they so far away from... &lt;i&gt;e-eh?&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" priority="50">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FearGarden" />
                <state img="#-strip+.png">I never had a chance to win that round, huh? Well, my hands are tied, so I guess it can't be helped...</state>
                <state img="#-strip+.png">If you like this ~background~, you should see my garden... It's so beautiful, so full of my blooming pretties...</state>
                <state img="#-strip-.png">I'll strip the dress for you, but next time we'll play at my garden, okay? Promise me! Promise me you'll come to my garden!</state>
                <state img="#-strip+.png">We should all meet up at my garden next time... Although it is a bit small, perhaps we could play one-on-one?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4" priority="50">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FearGarden" />
                <state img="#-strip-.png">Uuhm... I can't seem to be able to unbutton my bra, either... I don't suppose you could give me a hand again?</state>
                <state img="#-strip-.png">Don't mind the stains on my bra. Tending a beautiful garden usually leaves one with one or two bleeding cuts.</state>
                <state img="#-strip-.png">... So... would it be too much to ask for help again? I might need a hand unbuttoning my bra...</state>
                <state img="#-strip+.png">Do I have your full attention now? If only you could see your own expression... Are you putting your hands all over me in your mind?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5" priority="50">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FearGarden" />
                <state img="#-strip+.png">I'm completely exposed to you now... I didn't expect things to go this far...</state>
                <state img="#-strip+.png">I didn't think I'd like the idea of losing, but... If you're all willing to lose as well, it's not so bad...</state>
                <state img="#-strip-.png">What's the point of losing if I'm gonna have to touch myself like every other ~background.time~... If only someone else wanted to touch me as well...</state>
                <state img="#-strip-.png">How did this get out of hand so badly... This is what happens when I try my hand at strip poker with no practice...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-strip-.png">So, this is how I pay for my little bra prank...? I suppose it's fair...</state>
                <state img="#-strip+.png">You were expecting for this moment all game, weren't you? To see Kagamine Rin's... &lt;i&gt;oranges&lt;/i&gt;. Well...</state>
                <state img="#-strip-.png">I don't mind doing this at all, but... But...&lt;br&gt;I don't really have anything to say, I'm just stalling...</state>
                <state img="#-strip+.png">The ribbon stays on at all times. So... I'll be showing you these instead. Hope you're prepared for it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-strip+.png">Sleeves are a great way to make your design pop off! Especially if they're iconic yet easy to make, therefore easy to cosplay!</state>
                <state img="#-strip-.png">People often say I use sleeves because I want to resemble Miku... It hurts, because they never tell Luka that. They just want to make fun of me.</state>
                <state img="#-strip+.png">I actually like these sleeves. They're comfy and iconic, and wearing them next to Miku and Luka's make you feel like you're part of something greater.</state>
                <state img="#-strip+.png">Most of my outfits don't have sleeves like these, so I enjoy the opportunity to wear them again.</state>
                <state img="#-strip+.png">I've been wearing these sleeves since I was a little kid... Well, not &lt;i&gt;these exact same&lt;/i&gt; sleeves, but you get what I mean!</state>
                <state img="#-strip-.png">Make sure to take care of these, alright? My accessories are part of my iconic style, which is... important to me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-strip+.png" weight="0.5">So I'll just take off my underwear...&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;... {small}&lt;i&gt;Take off my underwear, take off my underwear, alright... &lt;/i&gt;♫ {!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-strip-.png" weight="0.5">Fine, I'll get to it. Sigh...&lt;br&gt;{small}&lt;i&gt;(Pantsu nugeru mon, pantsu nugeru mon, pantsu nugeru mon, ne... ♪)&lt;/i&gt;{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-strip+.png">Well, it's all part of the show... I-It's all about putting up a good performance...</state>
                <state img="#-strip-.png">You can watch all you want, as long as you don't touch anything...&lt;br&gt;... Well, not that you could, with the whole "being a virtual idol" thing, but still...</state>
                <state img="#-strip-.png">... Do you expect me to say something interesting? You're watching a world-renowned idol taking off her panties for you, isn't that interesting enough?</state>
                <state img="#-strip+.png">I'm technically winning, right? The intent of the game is to strip, after all...</state>
                <state img="#-strip+.png">Well, at least this is pretty entertaining to watch! Rin-chan always strives to be a good performer!</state>
                <state img="#-strip-.png">I can already hear the comparisons... "Oh, but Miku-chan always takes off her panties with a smile!" </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" oneShotId="7">
                <state img="#-strip+.png">Oh well, I guess the shoes have to go now...</state>
                <state img="#-strip+.png">I'm sorry taking off my shoes isn't more interesting, I'm just... I'm just taking off my shoes, okay?</state>
                <state img="#-strip+.png">Some idols try to make every single action they do as flashy as possible. Like, taking off their shoes by sending them flying or something. I'm here to relax, you know?</state>
                <state img="#-strip+.png">I'm sure Miku doesn't take off her shoes with a smile... Wait, maybe she does, should I smile too...?</state>
                <state img="#-strip+.png">I'll just take these off and... oh, I hope I'm not being compared to Miku because I don't take off my shoes with a stupid grin on my face or anything. With the fans we have, I wouldn't be surprised...</state>
                <state img="#-strip-.png" marker="RinKagamineisFallingDownFallingDownFallingDown">I should try to make something flashy to take off my shoes, like a kick or...! E-eh?</state>
                <state img="#-strip-.png" marker="RinKagamineisFallingDownFallingDownFallingDown">Perhaps I could ask someone to take off my shoes instead? Would that make my stripping more interesting? What if I...? E-eh? W-wait...!</state>
                <state img="#-strip-.png" marker="RinKagamineisFallingDownFallingDownFallingDown">I could make a little eye-catching dance to take off my shoes, right? Something like this! Or like... W-whoa!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-strip+.png">Oh well, I suppose I'm going next. Am I putting on a good show, though? As long as I'm not boring you, I'm doing something right!</state>
                <state img="#-strip-.png">You're really picking up steam after the bra prank... You're not mad, right?</state>
                <state img="#-strip+.png">I've gotta say, you're really getting your game on! Keep this up and you might actually see my chest soon!</state>
                <state img="#-strip-.png">If this is the price I gotta pay for the bra prank I pulled on you, so be it! I'll just have to play better next time...</state>
                <state img="#-strip+.png">Good thing I prefer comfy clothes that I can strip out of easily... But trust me, I don't plan on losing more clothes anytime soon!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-strip+.png">You worked really hard to see my chest, right? Since I forgot to wear a bra and all... Well, here's your reward...</state>
                <state img="#-strip-.png">Ugh, you heard me saying that I didn't wear a bra and tried harder to get me to strip, right? You perv!</state>
                <state img="#-strip+.png">My, are you so eager to see me naked? Is that why you step up your game as soon as you heard me saying I wasn't wearing a bra? Well, in that case...</state>
                <state img="#-strip+.png">You heard me saying that I wasn't wearing a bra, right? That's the reason you started playing better? Oh well, here goes nothing, then...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripped">
            <case stage="2" priority="100">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FearGardenFall" />
                <state img="#-after-.png">A gardener's hands are her life... I gave my life to save them...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" priority="50">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FearGarden" />
                <state img="#-after-.png">I'll make sure not to lose anymore... I came here to look at you, not to be looked at...</state>
                <state img="#-after+.png">I'll just have to try harder not to lose anymore...</state>
                <state img="#-after+.png">If I keep my head collected and I plan my moves correctly, things probably won't get out of hand.</state>
                <state img="#-after-.png">If I'm gonna play without my gloves, I'll have to be extra careful not to get paper cuts or anything... I need my hands to keep tending my garden...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" priority="50">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FearGarden" />
                <state img="#-after+.png">Let's just get this over with so I can keep watching you fiddle with your cards...</state>
                <state img="#-after+.png">Let's move this along so I can see your next plays and try to guess your tells...</state>
                <state img="#-after+.png">Anyway... Back to the game, and back to watching you flicking through poker hands...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" priority="50">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FearGarden" />
                <state img="#-after-.png">Things are starting to get out of hand, I need to play more carefully...</state>
                <state img="#-after+.png">We'll get our clothes back at the end of the game, right? I hope they're in good hands...</state>
                <state img="#-after+.png">It's nice to play with people who never judge me for my second-hand clothes...</state>
                <state img="#-after-.png">I'm not particularly proud of my legs... I know some people who can outrun me easily, I guess I should focus more on them...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4" priority="50">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FearGarden" />
                <state img="#-after-.png">I can't seem to... oh, jeez, I might have forgotten how to take this dress off. Could you lend me a hand?</state>
                <state img="#-after+.png">What's wrong? Am I taking too long undressing? Jeez, I might have forgotten how to take this dress off! Could you give me a hand?</state>
                <state img="#-after+.png">Oops, it seems I forgot this dress has a zipper... Could you give me a hand ?</state>
                <state img="#-after-.png">I'm having some trouble taking my dress off... Could any of you lend me a hand, please?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5" priority="50">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FearGarden" />
                <state img="#-after+.png">The doctor said they'd grow bigger if they got stimulated often. So, if you're willing to give me a hand...</state>
                <state img="#-after-.png">I'd prefer if you didn't comment on my chest. Unless you want to lend a hand on stimulating it to make it grow bigger.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6" priority="50">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FearGarden" />
                <state img="#-after+.png">You've all seen one of these before, so why don't we just continue?</state>
                <state img="#-after-.png">I'd rather if you didn't comment on my "lady flower".&lt;br&gt;Yes, I've heard gardeners call it that. No, I don't get it either.</state>
                <state img="#-after-.png">I'll just wash my hands and let fate decide whatever happens in these next rounds.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="2" priority="10">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="RinKagamineisFallingDownFallingDownFallingDown" />
                <state img="#-after-.png">Ow... I guess that's what I get for wanting to force a weird stripping gimmick...</state>
                <state img="#-after-.png">Owowow... That wasn't what I planned...</state>
                <state img="#-after-.png">Ouch... Sorry, I didn't mean for that to happen...</state>
                <state img="#-after-.png">Ouch... Well, that's one way to make a flashy strip...</state>
                <state img="#-after-.png">I... ouch... well... I guess people will tease me by saying Miku strips even better than I do now...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-after+.png">Don't worry, it's not gonna be long until I show the good stuff. I'm not wearing a bra, after all.</state>
                <state img="#-after-.png" dialogue-layer="over" font-size="small">Just don't you start comparing me to Miku, okay? None of that "Oh but Miku strips with a big dumb grin on her face!" or "Miku got a lot thicker when she became an adult!"&lt;br&gt;Well, I'll tell you one good thing about not being as thick, you can go braless anytime. Like I am right now.</state>
                <state img="#-after+.png">Don't be bored, though! I'm not wearing a bra, so I'll be showing the good stuff soon!</state>
                <state img="#-after-.png">What a day to forget putting on a bra... I just hope I can pick up steam on the next rounds...</state>
                <state img="#-after-.png">I need to be more careful with my plays... I forgot to wear a bra today, so I might be very close to showing way too much skin soon...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-after+.png">Got you! You're gonna have to play better than &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; to get to see my chest!</state>
                <state img="#-after-.png">Sorry, but if you want me to show you my oranges, you'll have to play better than that! What are you gonna do? Play with Miku instead?&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;... Wait, you're not actually gonna leave me for Miku, right?</state>
                <state img="#-after+.png">Denied! I &lt;i&gt;was&lt;/i&gt; wearing a bra all this time! Sorry, but I'm not a kid anymore. I can't just not wear one, that'd be painful!</state>
                <state img="#-after+.png">Nope! You were expecting to see my chest, but I was actually wearing a bra the whole time! You'll have to try harder than that!</state>
                <state img="#-after+.png">Psyche! I'm actually wearing a bra! What a twist, right? Look at the face you're making right now! It's priceless!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-after+.png">I might as well take these off too... I don't want to be accused of stalling with them.</state>
                <state img="#-after+.png">I'll take these off as well. I'd rather have you ogling at my legs rather than my feet.</state>
                <state img="#-after+.png">I've been working hard to keep my legs clean, shaved and in shape! I prefer you to look at them rather than my feet...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-after+.png">Anyway, shall we continue? I've still got a lot more song in me!</state>
                <state img="#-after+.png">Let's not lose speed, everyone! There's still a chorus and a crescendo to this song, so let's keep it going!</state>
                <state img="#-after-.png">Jeez, I'm not boring you, am I? I'll... I'll sing you a song! Perhaps I can dance, too? Maybe do some magic tricks with the cards...?</state>
                <state img="#-after-.png">I hope I'm not making this boring for you... Am I? I'll strip more soon! O-or maybe I won't, and I'll play better to put on a better challenge! W-whatever thing you prefer!</state>
                <state img="#-after+.png">Luckily, I'm already used to being in bikinis and underwear in front of others. With all the outfits I have to wear, I could perfectly pass for a model!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-after+.png">There we go! A petite idol for all your ogling needs! Remember, you can watch all you want, but no touchsies!</state>
                <state img="#-after-.png">So... this is it. I know I'm on the smaller side, so no need to rub it in...</state>
                <state img="#-after+.png">Take a good look! You played your cards right, literally, so you've earned a peek or two at my naked chest! But don't slow down, the game's not over yet!</state>
                <state img="#-after-.png">And here I thought open rehearsals were an invasion of privacy...</state>
                <state img="#-after+.png">Do I have your full attention now? Good! Keep your eyes on Rin-chan, and I'll give you a show you'll never forget!</state>
                <state img="#-after-.png">H-here they are! Rin-chan's... I... can't do the oranges joke anymore. I know they're a bit smaller than that...</state>
                <state img="#-after+.png">This surely makes up for the prank earlier, right? Come on! You have to admit it was hilarious! And you still got to see me naked, so we all won in the end!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-after-.png">So... this is it. I don't really have anything else to lose. But I'm still in the game, right? So I'll give it my all, still.</state>
                <state img="#-after+.png">Welp! There goes that! Rin-chan's fully exposed now. But I've still got a chance to win, so don't count me out yet!</state>
                <state img="#-after+.png">Just because you've got me fully naked doesn't mean that the show is over! I've still got more in me, so I hope you can keep cheering me on!</state>
                <state img="#-after-.png" dialogue-layer="over" font-size="small">I can already hear the complaints... "Oh, but Miku-chan is shaved! Rin-chan's innocence is lost with that hair!"&lt;br&gt;Look, this was requested by the Inventory, okay? If it was for me, you know I'd always prioritize the naive cuteness that made me famous...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_strip">
            <case stage="0-8" oneShotId="17">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FearGarden" />
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Such strong, manly hands... You can see the veins spreading like beautiful rivers on a map...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-seducing.png">Isn't this why we're all here? Watching hot guys strip?</state>
                <state img="#-grinning.png">Hohoho! Now this is what I've been waiting for!</state>
                <state img="#-yay.png">You know what you gotta do, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-yay.png">Yeah! We're waiting on you, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-piece.png">So, what's it gonna be, ~name~? I hope you don't back out, you chicken!</state>
                <state img="#-sweet.png">Will you make it a show to remember, ~name~? Please?</state>
                <state img="#-inviting.png">Come along, everyone! Witness how much of a {small}clothes{!reset} loser ~name~ is!</state>
                <state img="#-piece.png" oneShotId="81">Of course I've got a good hand! I'm Rin! I'm always &lt;i&gt;Right&lt;/i&gt;! If you want an easy opponent, Len just &lt;i&gt;Left&lt;/i&gt;!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-idea.png">Could you undress slowly, ~target~? Perhaps while looking back at us, and giving us some manly, distant glances as you strip?</state>
                <state img="#-challenging.png">Every round lost gets you closer and closer to Rin-chan now...</state>
                <state img="#-grinning.png">Losing is not so bad, ~target~! In fact, it actually feels pretty good!</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Don't tell me you were losing on purpose, ~target~! Are you perhaps interested in joining me in the losing side...?</state>
                <state img="#-inviting.png">There's always room for another one on the losing side, ~target~! Don't be afraid to play recklessly, as you'll get to have a good time over here!</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I could... you know, lend you my pillow, or we could even... s-share it, if you keep losing like that...</state>
                <state img="#-piece.png">Hey, cheer up, ~target~! This is a game where losing feels really good, so either way you're gonna have a great time!</state>
                <state img="#-pouting.png">I could've played those cards better if I was still playing, hmpf... Perhaps next game...</state>
                <state img="#-seducing.png">I wouldn't mind having you lose more often, ~target~. I enjoy the sights, and I wonder if you could put on a good performance...</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">Don't make a big deal out of it and keep going, okay? It's not like losing the game will lose you money or goods or whatever. In fact, you get to jack off to cute girls like me, so if anything, losing is the way to win here.</state>
                <state img="#-sweet.png">I wonder if I'd look good on ~target~'s clothes... Or if he'd look good in mine...&lt;br&gt;You know what &lt;i&gt;would&lt;/i&gt; look great? Both of us with no clothes at all!</state>
                <state img="#-yay.png">Time for ~target~ to dazzle us with a sensational strip! Make it a good one for the gals in need of some eye candy!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_strip">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="rin" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FearGarden" />
                <state img="#-pouting.png">~blank~</state>
                <state img="#-yay.png" oneShotId="171">~blank~ </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" oneShotId="1">
                <condition role="target" character="bowsette" />
                <state img="#-grinning.png" marker="BowsetteMoreLikeBOWsette">Your crown is so cute! Wanna trade it for my bow? I bet you'd look great in it!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <condition role="target" character="hatsune_miku" />
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Not as easy as Miku Flick, huh?</state>
                <state img="#-challenging.png">Haha! You're gonna crash harder than your Live Stage Producer game!</state>
                <state img="#-piece.png">Looks like the next Miku Expo is going to be a Rin Expo instead!</state>
                <state img="#-challenging.png">Is this the #1 Vocaloid? All I see is a big loser!</state>
                <state img="#-piece.png">Your little Rin-chan is growing up and ready to beat you, so you'll have to step up your game!</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">What's wrong, Miku? Didn't expect sweet and cute Rin-chan to have such nasty cards?</state>
                <state img="#-challenging.png">How could you lose with that hand? Seriously! What did you swap?</state>
                <state img="#-piece.png">The quicker you're out of the game, the quicker I'll be hogging the spotlight!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-6">
                <condition role="target" character="hatsune_miku" />
                <state img="#-yay.png" oneShotId="112" dialogue-layer="over">The tension rises as the young understudy is ready to replace the main lead!</state>
                <state img="#-challenging.png" oneShotId="113" dialogue-layer="over">Things are heating up, aren't they? Can you feel the tension as we get closer to the end?</state>
                <state img="#-grinning.png" oneShotId="114" dialogue-layer="over">I didn't expect both of us to make it this far, but I'm not complaining! This makes a much more interesting game!</state>
                <state img="#-pouting.png" oneShotId="115" dialogue-layer="over">With how random cards are, you can never be truly sure you'll win until the other has lost...&lt;br&gt;So I'll keep playing my best to defeat you!</state>
                <state img="#-seducing.png" oneShotId="108" dialogue-layer="over">It's either gonna be you or me, but one thing's for sure: The real winners here are the audience. It's not often they get to see two rival divas undressing and possibly touching themselves.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <condition role="target" character="hatsune_miku" />
                <state img="#-grinning.png" oneShotId="116" dialogue-layer="over">Now that all eyes are on you, you do what you love the most: Giving everyone a great show!</state>
                <state img="#-seducing.png" oneShotId="117" dialogue-layer="over">I know you appreciate the attention from everyone, and you want to please them with a good strip, but make sure you get to enjoy yourself as well, okay?</state>
                <state img="#-sweet.png" oneShotId="118" dialogue-layer="over">I often forget how... &lt;i&gt;cute&lt;/i&gt; you are, Miku.</state>
                <state img="#-pouting.png" oneShotId="119" dialogue-layer="over">You look... good, I guess. It's not like I'm gonna enjoy watching you strip or anything...</state>
                <state img="#-seducing.png" oneShotId="120" dialogue-layer="over">Not as appealing as watching me touch myself, but it's still gonna be entertaining!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="barbara" />
                <state img="#-piece.png" oneShotId="305" marker="BarbaraMeet">A performer who's blonde, cute and full of energy? This girl knows what's up!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="cagliostro" />
                <state img="#-cocky.png" oneShotId="306" marker="CagShort">It's funny. You have a pretty tall ego for someone so... terribly short.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="kizuna" />
                <state img="#-inviting.png" oneShotId="308" marker="KizunaApplause">It's none other than Kizuna-chan! I'm a big fan of her show, so let's give her a round of applause!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="streaming-chan" />
                <state img="#-grinning.png" oneShotId="310" marker="StreamingRecording">Are you recording this for millions on the web? I don't mind at all! Hello everyone! Ready to see me get a victory or a lot of pleasure?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="reimu" />
                <state img="#-idea.png" oneShotId="312" marker="ReimuMeeting">Have we met before? I get a feeling that I've seen you before... Or perhaps, people dressed like you...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="remilia" />
                <state img="#-idea.png" oneShotId="316" marker="RemiliaMeeting">Have we met each other before? I don't usually hang with vampires, but... You seem oddly familiar, somehow...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="miko" />
                <state img="#-idea.png" oneShotId="320" marker="MikoMeet">You... I've seen you before. You must know me, of course, but where have I seen you...?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="zone-tan" />
                <state img="#-furious.png" oneShotId="322" marker="ZoneMeet">Wait a minute... You're the one that made all those animations! You're not here to make one about me, are you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" oneShotId="16">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FearGarden" />
                <state img="#-sweet.png">You're such a beautiful woman, ~target~... With such delicate, femenine hands...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">You lost to someone who doesn't even know how to play poker, how pitiful!</state>
                <state img="#-idea.png">So it's... ~name~! It's ~name~, right? Yeah!</state>
                <state img="#-piece.png">So, who...? Oh? Oh yeah, didn't lose this one!</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">Hey, as long as I'm not the one losing, I'm fine with anyone else losing.</state>
                <state img="#-sweet.png">You're next, ~name~! Nobody outside of this game is watching, so you're free to be yourself.</state>
                <state img="#-yay.png">Share yourself with the world, ~name~! Let's watch you perform!</state>
                <state img="#-grinning.png">Hohoho, this is getting me pumped up! You go, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-piece.png">What'll it be, ~name~? I can't wait!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="tie">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FearGarden" />
                <state img="#-pouting.png">So nobody gets to strip this round? What a pain...</state>
                <state img="#-yay.png">Let's all play together to make sure we don't get another wasted round like this, okay?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-idea.png">I didn't even know there could be ties! So, what happens now?</state>
                <state img="#-startled.png">A... what? A tie? Poker has ties? Who knew!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0-8" totalRounds="0-5">
                <state img="#-grinning.png">Starting with your ~clothing~l? That's fine. You wouldn't start a song with the chorus, right? </state>
                <state img="#-idea.png">I suppose it's fine to strip your ~clothing~ this early in the game...</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I know some people get really mad if you don't strip something meaningful like your shirt or shorts... but not me. We've just started after all...</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Your ~clothing~? Sure. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-pouting.png">I suppose your ~clothing~ is fine... but I'll be expecting something better next time!</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">Oh yeah, baby, give Rin your... ~clothing~? Really?</state>
                <state img="#-idea.png">Sure, you can take off your ~clothing~ and all, but can you really make it appealing to watch?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-bullied.png">Hey, I'm being pretty generous with what I strip, so I expect the same from you!</state>
                <state img="#-furious.png">We don't tolerate these lame strips in Shinkai City Underground, you're lucky we're not there!</state>
                <state img="#-pouting.png">Whatever! On with the next round! Go go go!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-grinning.png">What are you stripping there? ~Clothing~? I've had to wear ~clothing~ like ~clothing.ifPlural(those|these)~ to perform too!</state>
                <state img="#-seducing.png">I bet everyone was hoping for something bigger, but don't worry, they can always just look at me instead. I'm cute in any state of undress.</state>
                <state img="#-sweet.png">Every small accessory counts for an outfit. Ask any costume designer and they'll tell you.</state>
                <state img="#-idea.png">Is your ~clothing~ important to you, ~target~? I wouldn't be me if I didn't have my bow. Or at least, it'd be hard to recognize me.</state>
                <state img="#-grinning.png">Is your ~clothing~ iconic of you, ~target~? People always draw fanart of me with my hairpins, so it's become something of a icon!</state>
                <state img="#-idea.png" oneShotId="13" dialogue-layer="over" font-size="small">A small accessory can change it all! Like, you could put butterfly wings on your headphones, and it'd reference a song. But if you put the same butterfly wings on your right shoulder, it'd reference another!</state>
                <state img="#-inviting.png">Next time, you could have a cute white bow like mine! I wouldn't mind giving you one once this is over!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-shrug.png">Did you seriously take away my spotlight for this? Please, move on.</state>
                <state img="#-grinning.png">Who cares about your ~clothing~? There's a naked idol touching herself right here!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-grinning.png">If that was all, let's move on!</state>
                <state img="#-piece.png">Not as cute as Rin-chan's strips, but still good! </state>
                <state img="#-yay.png">And now the show must go on!</state>
                <state img="#-yay.png">On to the next round, everyone! </state>
                <state img="#-grinning.png">And that's another piece of boring, unimportant, small piece of clothing that we'll never have to see again!</state>
                <state img="#-piece.png">I'm sure I could've taken that off better, with more elegance and charm, but this isn't about me! It's about you... ~target~, right?</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">Next time, let's try to not bore the audience with a simple strip, okay? The audience being us, and the simple strip being... yours.</state>
                <state img="#-yay.png">And now, for something much more interesting than that lame strip, let's go back to the competition!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-idea.png">I wonder why did you choose to wear your ~clothing~ today, ~target~. Is it an important part of your look?</state>
                <state img="#-yay.png">No need to take that off so quickly, ~target~. You're putting on a show! Give us tension, give us expectations, and then a flashy result to truly seal the deal!</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I hope people don't think Rin-chan's no longer innocent for lusting over boys... I know how some of my fans can be...</state>
                <state img="#-yay.png">Come on, ~target~! The spotlight's on you, make good use of it!</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">I've gotten far too used to men changing in mere seconds to keep the show going... I've forgotten how slow to undress regular men can be...</state>
                <state img="#-inviting.png">Have you considered talking more at length about your ~clothing~? I'm sure cosplayers and people trying to copy your style would appreciate the information!</state>
                <state img="#-grinning.png">Your ~clothing~ looked good on you, but it's time for it to go! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-seducing.png">Not bad, ~target~, but you could do a little better. Don't you think?</state>
                <state img="#-challenging.png">Come on, ~target~. I'm already like this. Why don't you make this a bit more interesting?</state>
                <state img="#-grinning.png">Not quite the show I was hoping for, but at least you're closer to giving us a full performance!</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">Kind of a mezzo move, but who am I to judge how you play, considering I've already lost...</state>
                <state img="#-piece.png">Hey, ~player~. If ~target~'s strip is too boring, why don't you watch me touch myself for your viewing pleasure instead?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_minor">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Mmh... No, I didn't really feel the tension on that strip. Could we get a do-over? I wouldn't mind watching you strip again...</state>
                <state img="#-challenging.png">Don't tell me you're ashamed, ~target~. You merely have to strip! You don't even have to perform yet!</state>
                <state img="#-piece.png">One step closer to the great finale! Let's keep going!</state>
                <state img="#-grinning.png">You're a natural at this, ~target~! Is it all improvised, or did you go through at least one dress rehearsal?</state>
                <state img="#-pouting.png">This is taking a bit longer than I expected... Can we move on to the next round?</state>
                <state img="#-seducing.png">Something wrong, ~target~? You seem to be taking your sweet time stripping. Are you perhaps too distracted by something or... someone?</state>
                <state img="#-seducing.png">Don't tell me you're not enjoying this, ~target~. Don't you love the attention? To have all of us ogling at you?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-idea.png">Is your ~clothing~ important to you, ~target~? Or would you change ~clothing.ifPlural(them|it)~ for something else if you had to?</state>
                <state img="#-grinning.png">You gotta dress to impress, ~target~! Remember that costumes are an important part of the performance too!</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Did you take into account that your fans might want to cosplay you, ~target~?&lt;br&gt;... Oh, sorry, I forgot that not everyone has as many fans as me.</state>
                <state img="#-pouting.png">Jeez, how much time do you need to strip ~clothing.ifPlural(some|a)~ simple ~clothing~?</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">We often have to change outfits on the fly... Sometimes while we're still dancing. I guess I got used to people stripping way faster than this.</state>
                <state img="#-sweet.png">I wouldn't mind signing your ~clothing~ for you, ~target~... I-if you want my autograph, that is.</state>
                <state img="#-yay.png">Oh, well! I suppose I have no other choice. World-renowned virtual idol Rin-chan sign your ~clothing~ for you!</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">And I thought Miku took her sweet time fiddling with her clothing... </state>
                <state img="#-yay.png">Gaze upon the biggest loser of the round, everyone!&lt;br&gt;... Which is a good thing in this game! Losing clothes is the whole point!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_minor">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-yay.png">You're putting on quite the performance for us, ~target~. Keep it up!</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">It's a pity the game has to go on. The stripping &lt;i&gt;is&lt;/i&gt; the main attraction, after all.</state>
                <state img="#-challenging.png">You're not out yet, ~target~! You can still win if you put your heart into it!</state>
                <state img="#-grinning.png">No worries, ~target~! If you try really hard, you still have a chance to win!</state>
                <state img="#-idea.png">You're not really out yet, so you could still win the game... but if you're the only one who doesn't get to masturbate, wouldn't that make you the loser of this game?</state>
                <state img="#-yay.png">Don't worry so much about your ~clothing~, ~target~! I would've looked better in it anyway, so don't push yourself too hard trying to catch up!</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">I can see you're enjoying this, ~target~. Be careful, the spotlight can be addicting.</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Enjoy your time in the spotlight, ~target~. I'm gonna enjoy stealing it back from you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-grinning.png">Don't worry about getting naked, ~target~. It's actually not that bad!</state>
                <state img="#-piece.png">Once you get used to it, being naked is actually pretty comfy!</state>
                <state img="#-bullied.png">Next game I should do better! I can't believe I'm already like this while ~target~ is still playing!</state>
                <state img="#-challenging.png">Not bad, ~target~! But you're gonna have to step up your game if you want to be as eye-catching as I am.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_major">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-idea.png">I wonder why did you choose to wear your ~clothing~ today. Did you know you'd be stripping it?</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">You really planned for all of us to see you like this, didn't you, ~target~?</state>
                <state img="#-seducing.png">Did you wake up today and think "Oh gee, I'll wear my ~clothing~ to show it off to everyone during strip poker to~background.time~"?</state>
                <state img="#-startled.png">O-oh! Is pure and innocent Rin-chan supposed to see something so... lewd?</state>
                <state img="#-bullied.png">Kyaa! How can you strip something like that in front of a naive, sinless maiden like me? You perv!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-grinning.png">Join us on the losing side, ~target~!</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">This is what we were waiting for...</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">The crowd is watching, ~target~. Give us a proper show.</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Soon enough you'll be giving us another type of performance...</state>
                <state img="#-idea.png">You wouldn't mind if I kept that, right? Just to remember you better, ~target~!</state>
                <state img="#-seducing.png">You're really heating things up, ~target~. Did I inspire you to take bolder moves?</state>
                <state img="#-sweet.png">You're closer to the finish line, ~target~! I wonder if you're as excited as all of us are...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_major">
            <case stage="5-8">
                <state img="#-grinning.png">Well, how does it feel? It's not so bad, right?</state>
                <state img="#-challenging.png">Come on, ~target~! You're close to the real victory of sexual release! Come on!</state>
                <state img="#-pouting.png">Hurry it along and get to the interesting part... This is dragging on and on...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-inviting.png">I can give you some poker tutoring after the game is over, ~target~. I'm clearly better at this than you are!</state>
                <state img="#-grinning.png">I sort of feel guilty about you being so close to completely losing the game while I'm still decent...&lt;br&gt;Just kidding, I don't!</state>
                <state img="#-piece.png">How does it feel to be such a loser, ~target~? I sure hope I don't have to be in your position anytime soon!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I need to be careful, or I might be stripping my own underwear soon...</state>
                <state img="#-strip-.png">I wonder if I'll have to do the same soon, considering where the game is going...</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">It's not okay to lose, right? I mean, ~target~ seems to be doing fine, so I don't have anything to worry about...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_major">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-grinning.png">Strip freely, ~target~! Since everyone already thinks I'm cuter than you, you don't need to compete or anything!</state>
                <state img="#-grinning.png"></state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_major">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-challenging.png">You know what'll happen next, don't you? You better watch out, ~target~!</state>
                <state img="#-challenging.png">Fufufu... It seems you're quite eager to give us a most luscious show, aren't you?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FearGarden" />
                <state img="#-yay.png">Don't keep us waiting, ~target~!</state>
                <state img="#-yay.png">Your fellow playmates are expecting your strip, ~target~. Don't take too long...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-pouting.png">Take off your ~clothing~ already! I've earned it!</state>
                <state img="#-furious.png">You're taking way too long, ~name~! I demand to see your chest!</state>
                <state img="#-piece.png">The following male chest is being presented by: Rin Kagamine's amazing poker skills! You're welcome! Glad to be of service!</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">We had to do a lot to get ~target~ to show up his chest. Show up, make him lose... I hope you're at least packing a six-pack there to make it worth it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-seducing.png">I can't compete with a male-presenting look, but I can complement it if you allow me to.</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">This is just what we needed to see...</state>
                <state img="#-challenging.png">I don't know about everyone else, but I know this girl is certainly going to enjoy this...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FearGarden" />
                <state img="#-yay.png">I'm not usually interested in torsos, but yours is... particularly intriguijng.</state>
                <state img="#-sweet.png">You have such a healthy thorax, with strong connections to the limbs...</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">What a fascinating thorax you have there... I wonder how your skin would feel between my hands...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-grinning.png">Now that's what I wanted to see! Don't you feel better like that, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-yay.png">If you're getting cold, you can dance to warm up, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-idea.png">Aren't you cold, ~target~? I'm sure there'll be plenty of ladies willing to warm you up if you are...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-idea.png">We'll be seeing much more than that soon... </state>
                <state img="#-sweet.png">That's quite the performance you're putting on, ~target~. Mind if I act as the audience for your next moves?</state>
                <state img="#-seducing.png">This place sure is filled with all kinds of different guys... Not that I mind, I enjoy the variety.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FearGarden" />
                <state img="#-sweet.png">Will you show us your stem, ~target~? So that I might take a cutting and grow mine at home?</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Don't be so shy, ~target~. I promise we won't bite.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-idea.png">&lt;i&gt;Oh! This will definitely be the first time I'll see a man's penis! Should I be excited to finally meet Penis-kun?&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-pouting.png" dialogue-layer="over">Thank you for actually taking the time to play the game before showing off, ~name~. You wouldn't believe how many "fans" come here to flash us in the first round just to see our reactions and then run away.</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Are you expecting me to play along as you strip, ~target~? Should I say something like &lt;i&gt;"I love how you slowly peel off every layer, before finally showing us your banana"&lt;/i&gt;?</state>
                <state img="#-sweet.png">You never know how big or small a man's penis is until you truly see him. I've been curious about yours ever since we started...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-heavy0.png">The suspense is killing me...</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Come on, ~target~, I'm waiting...</state>
                <state img="#-grinning.png">Don't be shy, ~target~! We could use some more entertainment!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-seducing.png">Join in the fun, ~target~. The spotlight is all yours.</state>
                <state img="#-challenging.png">Impress us, ~target~!</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">I'm already done, but... I wouldn't mind watching a little more of this show...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_small_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-grinning.png">You got a cute cock, ~target~! Perfect for a quickie in tight spaces!</state>
                <state img="#-idea.png">That sure is... a cock, yes. Should I compliment you, tease you over it, leave it at that...?</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">You came into a strip poker game with a dick like that? How cute.</state>
                <state img="#-seducing.png">Aw, don't worry, I'll try to be a bit more seductive to get that big boy going. You're a grower, right?</state>
                <state img="#-sweet.png">You got an... adorable dick, ~target~. It's perfect for a quickie in tight spaces.</state>
                <state img="#-piece.png">As Len always says, don't let anyone make fun of you over the size of your banana!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I-I'ts a... It's... It's a dick, that's for sure...</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">Pfft. You better have an amazing performance to justify a small instrument like that.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_medium_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-seducing.png">Not bad, ~target~, not bad at all.</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Mm~ That's nice, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-seducing.png">I hope you know how to use that, ~name~. </state>
                <state img="#-grinning.png" oneShotId="5">I'm not usually into CBT, but... If it's for a cute cock like yours, ~target~, just say the word and I'll be your road roller!</state>
                <state img="#-idea.png" oneShotId="6">&lt;i&gt;Oh, my! I-is that a man's... "t-thing"? Are you telling me you pee from there? What other marvelous things could you do with it?&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-sweet.png">I wouldn't mind singing for you with a mic like that, just saying...</state>
                <state img="#-challenging.png">Hey, ~target~, if you need a talented singer to perform with that mic of yours, I know one that's severely underrated and full of potential...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_large_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FearGarden" />
                <state img="#-yay.png">... If you can keep that stiffness without a bone for long periods of time, I might be a tad more interested...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-challenging.png">T-that's...! N-not as big as I expected...</state>
                <state img="#-challenging.png">It's...! I-it's a bit bigger than the average, so what? It doesn't matter if you don't know how to use it!</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">You're gonna need something more than just a big dick to get me drooling. </state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Bigger fans than you have tried to impress me. You're gonna need a little bit more than that.</state>
                <state img="#-idea.png">&lt;i&gt;My, my, ~target~! Your "microphone" is so big! I can't imagine how you'd make wonderful melodies with it! Could you perhaps... show me?&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-startled.png">{small}That's so big...!{!reset}&lt;br&gt;I-I mean, that's what I'd say if I hadn't seen way bigger dicks than that! Which of course I have!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-yay.png">Now this is the prime example of a good cock! Take notes everyone!</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">My, I didn't think you were packing such a generous instrument, ~target~... You're full of surprises.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FearGarden" />
                <state img="#-yay.png">... Pretty!</state>
                <state img="#-yay.png">... Cute!</state>
                <state img="#-yay.png">How lovely...</state>
                <state img="#-yay.png">It's so full of wrinkles... so veiny... it's not unpleasant to look at, at all...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FearGarden" />
                <state img="#-yay.png">Finally... I've been wondering how you look on the inside since we started playing, ~target~...</state>
                <state img="#-sweet.png">If you need any help, I can surely be of assistance, ~target~...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-yay.png">You wanted the attention, don't you, ~target~? Enjoy it!</state>
                <state img="#-grinning.png">You knew what you were signing up for! Now come on, get to it!</state>
                <state img="#-piece.png">I'm not usually fond of others taking away the spotlight, but just this once, I wanna see what you can do!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-grinning.png">I must be doing something right, I wasn't expecting to see ~target~'s breasts so soon!</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">You're already showing off your chest? This early into the game?... Or is it late? I don't really know.</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">Were you even trying to win? You should take notes from other players next time. Players like me, who still have their genitals covered.</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Are you losing on purpose, ~target~? Or are you always this bad?</state>
                <state img="#-yay.png">Everyone was hoping for you to show some skin, and Rin-chan's always happy to provide for her audience!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-seducing.png">I doubt you can match me in attractiveness and beauty, but some competition won't hurt...</state>
                <state img="#-challenging.png">Are you trying to catch up to me, ~target~? You've got a long way to go before that...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_small_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-piece.png">Aww, they're so cute! Rin-chan remembers when Rin-chan used to be that small... But she's not so small anymore!</state>
                <state img="#-furious.png">You have beautiful breasts, ~target~! And don't let anyone tell you otherwise! You deserve love and affection all the same!</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">You're so brave, ~target~. Don't forget that you deserve to be desired and loved no matter what body you have. Even if they treat you like a little girl, or if they tell you horrible, childish insults...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Just perfect. Like a tulip glass. Elegant, thin, straight, with small, almost imperceptible lines...</state>
                <state img="#-grinning.png">Us petite ladies have to stay together! All the power to you!</state>
                <state img="#-challenging.png">It's not easy to make a small chest seem appealing, but with the right clothes, posing and practice, you can make it far more attractive than a big one.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_medium_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-grinning.png">Nice chest, ~target~! I bet you get compliments about it everyday!</state>
                <state img="#-yay.png">Would you like to perform with me sometime, ~target~? With a body like that, you'd get us both a lot of attention as a backup dancer!</state>
                <state img="#-sweet.png">I'm kind of used to seeing my fellow Vocaloids changing outfits during concerts, but... I think you're beautiful and worth looking at, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-piece.png">You look gorgeous, ~name~! Don't let anyone make you think otherwise!</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Finally something worth watching...</state>
                <state img="#-idea.png">You don't mind if I stare... for a long while, right?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_large_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-overwhelmed.png">... I can't even imagine what dancing around with that on my chest would be like. </state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">... Perhaps I was a bit too hard on Luka. If I had breasts so heavy and big, I wouldn't dance a lot either...</state>
                <state img="#-idea.png">I wonder if there's a way to make cute outfits work with big breasts, without them being sexy or distracting...</state>
                <state img="#-idea.png">If I had a big chest like that, could I still be cute and adorable? Wouldn't they ruin the aesthetic by making me look more mature or lewd?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-idea.png">Would you mind if I called you "mommy"?&lt;br&gt;I don't even have a mom, so it'd be just a joke...</state>
                <state img="#-challenging.png">If I had tits like those, I'd definitely be the center of attention everywhere I went...</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">You surely know how to grasp everyone's attention, ~target~. You don't even have to do anything, big boobs do all the work for you.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FearGarden" />
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Would you mind showing us how you play with your nipples, ~target~? Or is it too early for that?</state>
                <state img="#-challenging.png">I'm hoping to see how you grope, pinch and touch your chest, so... I'll be quietly observing until your demise.</state>
                <state img="#-idea.png" dialogue-layer="over">I wonder how you would play with your breasts... Like, would you fondle the nipple between your fingers? Would you grab them and hold them with your hand? Would you cusp them in your palms? Would you...?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FearGarden" />
                <state img="#-yay.png">Another step before your imminent demise...</state>
                <state img="#-yay.png">You're just getting closer and closer to your poker downfall...</state>
                <state img="#-yay.png">The game's almost over for you, ~target~. Don't you run away now!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">To think you had a real chance of winning when we started...</state>
                <state img="#-challenging.png">How did things get so out of control, ~target~? Were you really bad at the game... or did you secretly want everyone to look at you?</state>
                <state img="#-grinning.png">Come on, ~target~! We've all got one, and everyone who doesn't has probably seen one anyway, so it's nothing to be ashamed of!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FearGarden" />
                <state img="#-sweet.png">It looks just as normal as ever. The same way it looked when you showered yesterday.</state>
                <state img="#-idea.png">It has changed a bit, right? Perhaps I'm misremembering it, but I remember it a bit different since your last visit to the doctor last week...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Well... I'll admit it's better than I expected. </state>
                <state img="#-piece.png">You've got this, ~target~! Be as sexy as you can be!</state>
                <state img="#-piece.png">Not as cute as yours truly, but still pretty cute!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_lost">
            <case stage="0-8" oneShotId="4">
                <condition filter="princess" role="target" />
                <state img="#-sweet.png" marker="PrincessTag">Oh, to be a princess, to be greeted each morning with a steamy hot bagel sandwich, to enjoy cat-footed bubble baths... That is the life...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="chef" role="target" />
                <state img="#-grinning.png">Some say you're a great cook! Is that right, ~target~? Making delicious meals for the people you love is such a sweet magic!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="idol" role="target" />
                <state img="#-grinning.png" oneShotId="326" marker="Idol1">We idols have to stick together, ~target~! We're bound to make a good show, so let's give it our best!</state>
                <state img="#-yay.png" oneShotId="327" marker="Idol2">Let's get a round of applause for ~target~! ~target.ifMale(He|She)~'s no stranger to performing, so let's give ~target.ifMale(him|her)~ our support!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="singer" role="target" />
                <state img="#-sweet.png" oneShotId="330" marker="Singer1">You have such a beautiful voice, ~target~... I hope we can perform together someday.</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png" oneShotId="331" marker="Singer2">I'd want to hear you sing, ~target~. But... I'm probably going to hear you moan soon.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="musician" role="target" />
                <state img="#-piece.png" oneShotId="334" marker="Musician1">This must be so great for you, ~target~! A musician getting to meet a vocaloid? Do you know how many artists wish for an opportunity like this?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="uses_camera" role="target" />
                <state img="#-cocky.png" oneShotId="336" marker="Camera1">Take as many pictures as you need, ~target~, but be sure to take my good side.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FearGarden" />
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Don't worry, ~target~. I won't ogle too much...</state>
                <state img="#-sweet.png">I can't wait to see your next strip, ~target~...</state>
                <state img="#-yay.png">Cut loose and free yourself, ~target~!</state>
                <state img="#-sweet.png">Not to point fingers at anyone, but... it's your turn, ~target~.</state>
                <state img="#-piece.png">Cross your fingers and hope for better luck next time!</state>
                <state img="#-yay.png">Well...? &lt;br&gt;What are you waiting for?</state>
                <state img="#-yay.png">I'm so glad I get to see you like this...</state>
                <state img="#-yay.png">Don't be afraid, ~target~! It's just ripping off your clothing, it won't hurt at all!</state>
                <state img="#-grinning.png">Just think how painful would it be to strip your skin, or your hair, or your limbs... When you compare it like that, stripping clothes doesn't sound that bad, right?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_stripping">
            <case stage="0-8" oneShotId="2">
                <condition role="target" character="bowsette" saidMarker="RinCrown1" />
                <state img="#-sweet.png" marker="BowsetteMoreLikeBOWsette1">Why would you think that? Don't you think I'd look adorable as a princess? I'm sure you'd look gorgeous in a white bow!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FearGarden" />
                <condition role="target" character="rin" />
                <state img="#-shrug.png">~blank~</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FearGarden" />
                <condition role="target" character="ribbon_girl" />
                <state img="#-overwhelmed.png">...</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">...</state>
                <state img="#-startled.png">...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FearGarden" />
                <condition filter="athletic" role="target" />
                <state img="#-idea.png" oneShotId="202">Do you work out, ~target~? Exercise, perhaps?</state>
                <state img="#-sweet.png" oneShotId="203">Sometimes I invite people to my garden and challenge them to... surprise running races.</state>
                <state img="#-idea.png" oneShotId="201">You seem like you could outrun me, ~target~... in a race, that is. Perhaps I could invite you to my garden so we can run around for a while?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FearGarden" />
                <condition filter="muscular" role="target" />
                <state img="#-cocky.png" oneShotId="210">You're so strong and muscular, ~target~... I wouldn't mind spending some time alone in my garden with you...</state>
                <state img="#-sweet.png" oneShotId="211">Such big, muscly arms... And such defined, toned hands...</state>
                <state img="#-yay.png" oneShotId="212">You have such a firm grasp, ~target~... We should meet up at my garden after this, alone...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FearGarden" />
                <state img="#-sweet.png">If you need any help, I could use my knife to cut some of your ~clothing~...</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Take your time undressing. I want to see every movement of yours.</state>
                <state img="#-sweet.png">I can't wait to meet up in my garden later, ~target~! I'm proud of it, and you're invited to be a part of it too!</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Every piece you take off gets you closer and closer to the edge... </state>
                <state img="#-sweet.png">What wonderful and graceful moves you have, ~target~... I love the way you take off your ~clothing~...</state>
                <state img="#-grinning.png">I'm a gardener and an artist! And I declare you as a piece of art! I'd love to take a piece out of you!</state>
                <state img="#-challenging.png">Don't cut corners now, ~target~. A good strip requires you to be at the cutting edge of strip poker fashion.</state>
                <state img="#-yay.png">Your ~clothing~ ~clothing.ifPlural(are|is)~ just so... you, ~target~. ~clothing.ifPlural(They have|It has)~  your fingerprints all over ~clothing.ifPlural(them|it)~.</state>
                <state img="#-idea.png">Have you considered wearing more rings, ~target~? I think your hands look good as they are right now, but some people prefer to adorn their fingers with precious metals...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_stripped">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="rin" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FearGarden" />
                <state img="#-yay.png">~blank~</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FearGarden" />
                <condition role="target" character="ribbon_girl" />
                <state img="#-overwhelmed.png">...</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">...</state>
                <state img="#-startled.png">...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" oneShotId="3">
                <condition role="target" character="bowsette" />
                <state img="#-grinning.png" marker="BowsetteMoreLikeBOWsette2">Well, let me know if you change your mind! It's not like I'm &lt;i&gt;Evil&lt;/i&gt; or anything, so I'm always up to become a princess!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FearGarden" />
                <test expr="~clothing.generic~" value="belt" />
                <state img="#-yay.png">You have such dexterity on your hands... To take off your belt like that...</state>
                <state img="#-yay.png">Such finesse on unbuckling that belt... I loved every second of it...</state>
                <state img="#-sweet.png">If that's how you take off  a belt, I can't wait to see how you'd take off sometihng else...</state>
                <state img="#-sweet.png">Such long, nimble arms... Not everyone can take off their belts like that...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FearGarden" />
                <test expr="~clothing.generic~" value="gloves" />
                <state img="#-yay.png" oneShotId="193">It's always such a pleasure to see someone finally show their hands... Every wrinkle tells so much about them...</state>
                <state img="#-sweet.png" oneShotId="194">I could give you a palm reading if you want... Those are some beautiful hands right there...</state>
                <state img="#-sweet.png" oneShotId="195">Now that the gloves are coming off... why don't you show off your hands? Isn't that what we're all here for? To watch each others' bodies, including their hands?</state>
                <state img="#-sweet.png" oneShotId="196">I could read your future just by looking at the lines in your hand... Just lend me your hand for a moment...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FearGarden" />
                <state img="#-cocky.png">You have such gorgeous hands, ~target~...</state>
                <state img="#-sweet.png">Do you prefer fingerless gloves, or regular gloves, ~target~? Wait, no, don't tell me, I'd rather imagine your hands myself...</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Here's one... here's two... three... four... five fingers in your hand...</state>
                <state img="#-yay.png">Thank you for that strip, ~target~. Most people would run away from these mildly uncomfortable situations, but you didn't!</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Are you ready to draw more cards, ~target~? Ready to show off your hand and its digits?</state>
                <state img="#-idea.png">Do you believe fate made you lose this round, ~target~? Or are you pointing fingers at the dealer?</state>
                <state img="#-grinning.png">What an elegant technique of undressing, ~target~! You have such a firm grasp on your own clothing...</state>
                <state img="#-sweet.png">The finesse and dexterity you display while undressing is astounding, ~target~...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FearGarden" />
                <state img="#-seducing.png">Put those hands to good use, ~target~...</state>
                <state img="#-inviting.png">Get down to work, ~target~. Let's test your handyman skills on that tool of yours.</state>
                <state img="#-sweet.png">I can't wait to see you touching yourself, ~target~...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-challenging.png">It's... ~target~! And you ran out of clothes, so you know what that means!</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">So it's... ~target~. You've got no more clothes to strip. You know what that means, right?</state>
                <state img="#-inviting.png">Good game, ~target~! But now that you've lost, you'll have to give us a show!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FearGarden" />
                <state img="#-grinning.png">Remember that you can use your fingers to stimulate the surface area of your skin! Your soft fingertips would probably feel great!</state>
                <state img="#-idea.png">You can use your fingers to pinch your nipples, caress your skin, fondle your balls... There's all sorts of things you can do with them...</state>
                <state img="#-yay.png">This is, hands-down, the best party I've sneaked into!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-challenging.png">Hey, hey, does anybody have a camera? This is gonna be good!</state>
                <state img="#-challenging.png">Fufufu, I do &lt;i&gt;not&lt;/i&gt; want to miss this!</state>
                <state img="#-inviting.png">Take this as an oportunity to show everyone how you like your body to be touched, ~target~! I always like to learn how to please others better!</state>
                <state img="#-inviting.png">Come on, ~target~! Show us how to please you!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="34">So this is why this stage is so sticky...</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">I assume you'd be pretty good with a mic, ~target~?</state>
                <state img="#-bullied.png" oneShotId="33">You can look at me if it does anything for you!... Wait, why are you looking away?</state>
                <state img="#-startled.png" oneShotId="32">Wait, do men actually like doing it like that? Is that a thing? </state>
                <state img="#-pouting.png">Hmm... So that's how a guy does it in real life... It's quite different from the videos I've watched...</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png" oneShotId="31">When you live with a guy your age you tend to listen to those quiet moans and grunts coming from the bathroom a lot. You kinda get used to it.</state>
                <state img="#-inviting.png">Luckily for you, there's no shortage of attractive men, women and monsters to ogle at in the Inventory! So you'll have no problem... uhm, closing the show!</state>
                <state img="#-idea.png">Don't you get tired of doing it like that? Wouldn't you want someone to give you a hand?</state>
                <state img="#-piece.png">Rin-chan's is extremely cute both fully dressed and fully naked! So you'll always have a reason to look at me while doing... that!</state>
                <state img="#-seducing.png">What do you think, ~target~? Don't I make for much better fap material than Miku? Wouldn't you pick me over her a thousand times over?</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">And he keeps going and going... Such ferocity, such energetic movement... I wouldn't mind trying out some of that...</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">You know, we're always looking for energetic backup dancers... I wouldn't mind taking you with me for a tour...</state>
                <state img="#-challenging.png" oneShotId="79">Get a hold of yourself, dull boy!</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">I'm pretty sure I could make that &lt;i&gt;Happy Fruit&lt;/i&gt; of yours feel really good. Much better than Miku could.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" priority="0">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FearGarden" />
                <state img="#-cocky.png">You have such a tight grip, ~name~...</state>
                <state img="#-idea.png">You sure are jerking it hard... If you keep pulling, could you pull it off accidentally?</state>
                <state img="#-sweet.png">Some men like to use their fingers to stimulate their anuses... I wouldn't be opposed to you showing us how...</state>
                <state img="#-piece.png">You could stick up your fingers on your rectum to reach your G spot! You could even stick many of them!</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Look at the ferocity of your movements... You have such a dexterous control of your wrist...</state>
                <state img="#-yay.png">Have you considered using the palm to stimulate the glands? Some say it's a totally new experience...</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">I'll never understand why men are so scared of putting fingers in their backs... Don't they know how much pleasure they can get from your own hand?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_heavy_masturbating">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-startled.png" oneShotId="40">I can't believe you're still going... You must be close, right?</state>
                <state img="#-furious.png" oneShotId="41">You've been at it longer than a song from Π-P! Finish already!</state>
                <state img="#-pouting.png" oneShotId="39">I thought men could finish in five minutes or so... I could challenge the 1000 digits of Pi many times over by how long you're taking...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-piece.png">Now that was quite the performance, don't you think? I certainly do!</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">What a performance... I suppose we'll have to wait for a bit before asking you for an encore, right?</state>
                <state img="#-grinning.png">Now &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; was a real show!</state>
                <state img="#-idea.png">Did you finish your performance, ~target~? Rin-chan had her eyes closed the whole time and missed it! Would you mind giving us an encore?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-challenging.png">No clothing to hide behind anymore!</state>
                <state img="#-challenging.png">Well, ~name~, you know how it goes!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-shrug.png">Were you losing on purpose, ~target~? If you're so anxious to get off, you could've told us!</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">Did you really lose because you're bad at poker, ~target~? Or did you want everyone watching you as you touch yourself , you perv?</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">So... you know what this means, don't you, ~target~?</state>
                <state img="#-grinning.png">Well, I might be bad at poker, but at least I'm not as bad as ~target~!</state>
                <state img="#-idea.png" oneShotId="28" weight="1.5">Oh! Did ~target~ lose? Rin-chan is so sorry, ~target~! So, what happens now? Do you have to go home and pray? Or must you put on a socially awkward lewd display for us?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-challenging.png">Well, it seems like the show must go on, after all...</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Don't feel so bad, ~target~. I assure you, you'll feel good really soon...</state>
                <state img="#-grinning.png">You were taking your sweet time, ~target~! I hope you take as much time putting on a show for us to ogle at!</state>
                <state img="#-piece.png">Exchanged the wrong cards, ~target~? Or did you wanna lose to join in the fun? Either way, glad to have you on the losing side!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-piece.png">The stage is set, and it's now ~name~'s turn to shine!</state>
                <state img="#-grinning.png">You ready, ~name~? The spotlight is waiting for you!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Oh, don't mind us, ~target~. We'll just watch as you... &lt;i&gt;perform&lt;/i&gt; for us. Just pretend we're not here.</state>
                <state img="#-yay.png">Now it's time for ~target~, the biggest loser of the round, to give us a show to remember! </state>
                <state img="#-piece.png">Even in bad situations, there's always something to be grateful for! For instance, I'm grateful that I'm not a terrible loser like ~target~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-seducing.png">Can you match my pace, ~target~? I doubt it, but you can try!</state>
                <state img="#-inviting.png">I doubt you'll be as cute as me doing it, but you can try!</state>
                <state img="#-challenging.png">Trying to catch up to me, ~target~? You don't have much of a chance, but you can still give it your best!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-piece.png">Give it your all, ~target~! Don't let the spectators intimidate you!</state>
                <state img="#-seducing.png">You're putting on quite the show, ~name~! </state>
                <state img="#-piece.png">Getting really into it, huh? That's great! </state>
                <state img="#-grinning.png">Take the spotlight and don't let it go!</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Not bad... Not how I'd do it, but not bad at all!</state>
                <state img="#-seducing.png">Someone is enjoying herself, hm...?</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">Don't make a big deal out of it. Just let yourself go and pretend we're not here to see you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-inviting.png">I guess we're both making the music of heavens now, huh?</state>
                <state img="#-bullied.png">Wait up! Don't finish before me, I share the spotlight with you!</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="24">If you feel nervous, just think of it as some sort of acting performance you're putting up for people to watch. Like, it's not really "you" who's touching herself, but the "character" is doing it, while you're just the actress playing that character.</state>
                <state img="#-seducing.png">I hope you don't mind me staring. I wouldn't mind you staring at me at all...</state>
                <state img="#-yay.png">Keep it up, ~target~! Let's give it our all together!</state>
                <state img="#-piece.png">You can always use me for inspiration if you want, ~target~. I've had women of all ages lusting over me, I don't mind!</state>
                <state img="#-grinning.png">Yes, ~target~ is pretty arousing to look at, but don't you think Rin-chan is cuter and sexier?</state>
                <state img="#-challenging.png">Who would you say looks better while touching herself, ~player~? Me or ~target~? It's definitely me, right?</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I hope I'm not making you feel uncomfortable, ~target~...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-pouting.png">People weren't ogling at me like that when I was doing it...</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Not as good as when I did it, but hey, not bad either.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" priority="0">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FearGarden" />
                <state img="#-challenging.png">That's right, use your hands correctly! Touch yourself all over! Pinch your nipples, lick your fingers, show everyone what they're missing out on!</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">You're quite nasty, ~target~... I didn't expect that from you...</state>
                <state img="#-sweet.png">I wouldn't mind learning how to please you better one on one... Perhaps we could come to my garden later so you can show me?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_heavy_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-yay.png" oneShotId="83">If your perfomance was a song, I'd say you're reaching a crescendo!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Well, isn't that nice?</state>
                <state img="#-grinning.png">That was pretty hot! You've given us quite the performance, be proud of yourself, ~target~!</state>
                <state img="#-seducing.png">Someone here looks pretty satisfied, I'm jealous...</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Looks like someone here had fun, hohoho.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate_first">
            <case stage="6">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FearGarden" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I've been playing so poorly... I can't believe everything got out of hand so badly...</state>
                <state img="#-pouting.png">I think someone here has been cheating... I'm not gonna start pointing fingers, but I have a pretty good idea of who it is...</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">I suppose it can't be helped... I'll have to take matters into my own hands.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-pouting.png">Shoot... I can't believe I'm the first one to go...</state>
                <state img="#-pouting.png">Why do I have to go first? Fine...</state>
                <state img="#-seducing.png">It's up to me to set the stage! Well then, I don't mind being the opening number~</state>
                <state img="#-challenging.png">Step right up, everyone! It's time for the one and only Kagamine Rin to show you how it's done... by touching herself in front of strangers playing poker!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate">
            <case stage="6">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FearGarden" />
                <state img="#-shrug.png">I was hoping not to lose, but alas. I'll tip my hand on my own intimate techniques as well.</state>
                <state img="#-idea.png">So... Could I choose anyone to help me with my forfeit? I could use a hand, and ~player~'s looks willing...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-seducing.png">Hope I'm not too late to the party? I brought snacks.&lt;br&gt;And by snacks, I mean me. I'm a real snack.</state>
                <state img="#-inviting.png">They say a performer's joy is contagious, so I'll try my best to enjoy this, so you have a good time as well while watching me!</state>
                <state img="#-seducing.png">Well... I've been expecting this. What about you. &lt;br&gt;Are you ready?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="start_masturbating">
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-start.png">I hope you don't mind that I brought a pillow. I'd rather not touch the ~background.surface~ with my bare legs...</state>
                <state img="#-start.png">I'd rather not have my private parts have anything to do with the ~background.surface~, so I brought this pillow to help me out!</state>
                <state img="#-start.png">I thought about bringing an orange-shaped pillow for the brand recognition, but... I decided I'd rather be comfortable and use my best pillow instead.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="masturbating">
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Not the kind of performance I'm used to, but... it's not so bad.</state>
                <state img="#-seducing.png">This is a little embarrassing... But I've grown used to doing all sorts of performances for my fans...</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I've never given this kind of show before, but... it might be starting to grow on me.</state>
                <state img="#-pouting.png">I'm not so naive, you know. I've seen the "fanart" and adult MMD animations fans have made of me. But I never thought I'd be reenacting one in real life...</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Is this turning you on, ~player~? To watch me do this... and describe every action I do with even the smallest of details...?</state>
                <state img="#-bullied.png">&lt;i&gt;Poor, innocent Rin-chan... Being watched by all these perverted meanies, as she explores her body in front of them...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-seducing.png">Look at the way my hands are moving... Play close attention... This is how I like it, and this is how I'd like you to do it... Hypothetically, of course...</state>
                <state img="#-yay.png">You're watching the world-famous Rin Kagamine touching herself in front of you. You can stare at me all you want... No one will ever believe you!</state>
                <state img="#-challenging.png" oneShotId="52">You can take pictures if you want. Nobody will believe they're not fanart, AI-generated, or a really good MMD model.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I'm actually enjoying this... I hope you're enjoying watching me too...</state>
                <state img="#-idea.png" oneShotId="65" weight="1.7">Would you mind if I... humped my pillow a little bit? I know it's not the most entertaining thing to watch, but... &lt;i&gt;I-I kind of... like... it?&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7" priority="0">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FearGarden" />
                <state img="#-pouting.png">I'd rather watch you doing this... I've already watched my own hands caressing me over and over in front of the mirror...</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">I see you watching me... Would you mind if I licked my fingers? If I played with them using my tongue, or if I suckled on them a bit...?</state>
                <state img="#-grinning.png">Luckily, I've been able to see the most attractive part of you since the very beginning... I've been aroused since we started playing!</state>
                <state img="#-sweet.png" oneShotId="286">Maybe I could...&lt;br&gt;No, that'd be insane! Who would masturbate with a knife? Not this girl, that's for sure!</state>
                <state img="#-inviting.png">Hey, ~player~... I see you constantly tapping your index finger a lot... I think I could use that right now.</state>
                <state img="#-idea.png">Think of all the things we could do if we were alone in my garden... I'm sure I could let you have a more... hands-on approach...</state>
                <state img="#-grinning.png">If only I could have you touch me... Yes! I can imagine it! Using your grabby hands and touching me all over... </state>
                <state>Making my skin crawl with your index finger... Putting your fingers into my mouth as I start to lick them all over... I can picture it perfectly!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="heavy_masturbating">
            <case stage="7" id="1">
                <state img="#-heavy0.png" oneShotId="68">... I'm so glad I brought this pillow...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy1.png">H-haah...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy2.png">Nnh...~</state>
                <state img="#-heavy1.png">I'm... I-I'm sorry... for being such a mess...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy1.png">I'm trying... to be quiet... I-I can't hold it...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy2.png" oneShotId="7">I-It's building up...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy2.png">Okay... okay... Just... oh my...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy0.png">Uuhhhnn... </state>
                <state img="#-heavy2.png">&lt;i&gt;Right there, right there, right there...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-heavy1.png">&lt;i&gt;Shhh...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-heavy2.png">I'm sorry for being so needy... I'm not usually like this, I swear...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy1.png">&lt;i&gt;... Mmhm... Kiss my purple butterfly... on the right shoulder... something something dissonance...&lt;/i&gt; ♪&lt;br&gt; I can't... I can't even sing... or make sense anymore...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy2.png">R-Rin-chan is sorry... For being so lewd... And perverted... And... and... {small}and... oh...{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-heavy1.png">&lt;i&gt;S-sorry... for not being as... entertaining as Miku... I-I just can't stop myself now...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-heavy0.png">Mmh...~</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finishing_masturbating">
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-finish.png">Oh, oh, ohhhh~!</state>
                <state img="#-finish.png">Ohh! That's it! That's iiiiit...</state>
                <state img="#-finish.png">A-ahhhhh!~</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-finish.png">I... I... shh... shhhould breathe...</state>
                <state img="#-finish.png">That was... wow... great...</state>
                <state img="#-finish.png">... Oh... That was amazing...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_victory">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FearGarden" />
                <state img="#-overwhelmed.png">I hope you all enjoyed yourselves! However... I'm scared to walk home alone! I didn't get to release myself! Would anyone mind coming with me?</state>
                <state img="#-seducing.png">That was certainly a good experience... Now, if you truly wish to see my nastiest side, we could go home together. I'll make sure to make the experience... unforgettable.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-yay.png">Thank you all for coming to witness my victory! You're all more than welcome to try again!</state>
                <state img="#-piece.png">Sorry! It seems like you won't be able to see my sexiest, nastiest side. You can try again later, though! I'm always up to the challenge!</state>
                <state img="#-grinning.png">Don't be discouraged! You're all invited to play with me again, but I won't hold back there either!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_defeat">
            <case stage="8">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FearGarden" />
                <state img="#-sweet.png">This was... enjoyable. I wouldn't mind doing it all over again...&lt;br&gt;Now... who's coming home with me?</state>
                <state img="#-sweet.png">Now that the game is over... I'll go back to my garden.&lt;br&gt;Do you wish to come back with me?</state>
                <state img="#-grinning.png">Hey, ~player~... I think we could have a lot more fun on our own, don't you think?&lt;br&gt;Why don't you..&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;Come with me to my garden?&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-piece.png">That was great, everyone! Let's do it all over again! And here we go, one, two...!</state>
                <state img="#-piece.png">Well, did you enjoy the show? I did! I can't wait to play with all of you again!</state>
                <state img="#-piece.png">Now &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; was a great show! Good game, everyone! You deserve an applause! Now, let's do an encore!</state>
                <state img="#-sweet.png">I hope you all enjoyed yourselves... Rin-chan would love to play with you all again~</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

    </behaviour>
</opponent>
