<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>

<!--This file was machine generated using the Character Editor v6.7 at 3:31:34 PM on October 01, 2021. Do not edit this file directly unless you know what you're doing.-->
<opponent>
    <version>v6.7</version>
    <first>Mikoto</first>
    <last>Misaka</last>
    <label>Misaka</label>
    <gender>female</gender>
    <size>medium</size>
    <timer>16</timer>
    <intelligence>good</intelligence>

    <intelligence stage="3">average</intelligence>

    <intelligence stage="7">bad</intelligence>



    <wardrobe>
        <clothing name="panties" generic="underwear" position="lower" type="important" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="bra" generic="bra" position="upper" type="important" />
        <clothing name="shorts" generic="shorts" position="lower" type="major" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="shirt" generic="shirt" position="upper" type="major" />
        <clothing name="skirt" generic="skirt" position="lower" type="minor" />
        <clothing name="cardigan" generic="vest" position="upper" type="minor" />
        <clothing name="socks" generic="socks" position="feet" type="minor" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="shoes" generic="shoes" position="feet" type="extra" plural="true" />
    </wardrobe>


    <behaviour>
        <trigger id="selected">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-pondering.png">My friends told me to meet them here... I wonder where they are?</state>
                <state img="#-pondering.png">I've been everywhere in Academy City. How come I've never noticed this place before?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_selected">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="9s" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png">A-Accelerator!? ...Wait a sec... Sorry 9S, I thought you were someone else, hehe.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="akko" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">Hey, Atsuko, you're a student and a magic user? I didn't think Academy City had schools for magic.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="larachel" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="misaka_larachel_selected">Your outfit, L'Arachel... Are you part of the church? A different sect, perhaps?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="miko" />
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">Miko, you're a magic user, huh...? You're not associated with the church are you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="pit" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Pit! You have angel wings!? Th-that means you might be a...!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_start">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="shimakaze" />
                <state img="#-exclaiming.png">Heh!? What a cute robot, Shimakaze... reminds me of the cleaning bots in Academy city!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~background.location~" value="outdoors" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">Eh!? We're playing poker outdoors? Kinda strange if you ask me...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition count="5" gender="female" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">Hey! I've never met any of you girls before! I'm Mikoto Misaka! I hope we can become good friends, hehe!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition count="3-4" gender="male" />
                <state img="#-shy.png">There's certainly a lotta guys here... What am I getting in to?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Hello everyone, I'm Mikoto Misaka! I'm a level 5 Esper, so don't screw with me!</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">A game of poker, huh... count me in! I'll show you just how skilled I really am!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I'm always up for making new friends! What're we playing? Poker or somethin'?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="swap_cards">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <test expr="~cards~" value="0" />
                <state img="#-smug.png">Heh! I don't even &lt;i&gt;need&lt;/i&gt; to swap any cards!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-pondering.png">Hmmm... I'll take ~cards~ ~cards.ifPlural(cards|card)~.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I've got this! Give me ~cards~ ~cards.ifPlural(cards|card)~.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">I think I'll go for... ~cards~ ~cards.ifPlural(cards|card)~.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Give me ~cards~ ~cards.ifPlural(cards|card)~, that should do it!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Zap me ~cards~ ~cards.ifPlural(cards|card)~... hehe!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="good_hand">
            <case stage="0" totalRounds="0">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Hey, you must be the people my friend Kuroko told me about... I must warn you, I'm pretty good at poker!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-1">
                <state img="#-pondering.png">I didn't think places like this were so easily found in Academy City. There's that policy about public nudity...</state>
                <state img="#-exclaiming.png">Have you guys seen my friend Kuroko around here? She's got twin-tails and an annoying attitude...</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Just so you guys know, I'm kinda good at poker! I got the highest score on the poker machines at the arcade!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-3">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Alright! A great hand! I picked up a few tricks playing the poker machines at the arcade.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">There's no way I can lose now!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">You might as well give up!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Just what I expected! I &lt;i&gt;am&lt;/i&gt; the 3rd ranked level 5 Esper, after all!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-8">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Hah! Good luck beating this hand, guys!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Don't be so `shocked' when I beat you this round!</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">Alright! I can't go wrong with these cards!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">You'd need to pull out all the stops to beat me this round!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="okay_hand">
            <case stage="0" totalRounds="0">
                <state img="#-pondering.png">I'm kinda confused where my friend Kuroko is... She said to meet a new group of friends here.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-1">
                <state img="#-shy.png">I always love meeting new people! Never thought I'd do it over a game of &lt;i&gt;strip&lt;/i&gt; poker... hehe.</state>
                <state img="#-exclaiming.png">My friend Saten is supposed to be here, somewhere. She wears a large flower ribbon in her hair, green eyes, too. Have you seen her?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">So, are any of you Espers? I'm an electromaster. Means I can summon and control lightning!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-3">
                <state img="#-pondering.png">Hmm... this could go either way...</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Yeah... these might get me through.</state>
                <state img="#-thumbsup.png">These cards are okay. I can work something out.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Not the best... But, at least I can make use of these.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-8">
                <state img="#-pondering.png">I hope these will work...</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">These look good enough... no problem!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">You gotta make use of what you are given, I suppose.</state>
                <state img="#-pondering.png">I've played enough to know this might be a good hand... I hope...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="bad_hand">
            <case stage="0" totalRounds="0">
                <state img="#-calm.png">So, you're the guys my friend Kuroko told me about. You any good at poker?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-1">
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">I'll have you know, I don't like losing!</state>
                <state img="#-exclaiming.png">I think Uiharu said she'd be here, too. Have you seen her? She wears a flowery headband, kinda short.</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">Dunno how I've ended up playing &lt;i&gt;strip&lt;/i&gt; poker of all things, but if it means I get to prove myself then... &lt;i&gt;*gulp*&lt;/i&gt; ...I guess I gotta do this.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-3">
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">Sheesh... these cards!</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">Give me a break... such a bad hand!</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">This is so annoying! What can I do with these?</state>
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">Gah! I usually have better luck at the arcade!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-8">
                <state img="#-angry.png">Kuroko! Where are you!? Quit messing with my cards!</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">Uh-oh... It might be me this round...</state>
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">Seriously!? How is it I ended up with these!?</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">Ugh... such rotten luck!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="hand">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="other" character="shimakaze" sayingMarker="japend" />
                <state img="#-exclaiming.png" oneShotId="1">I suppose it's easier for everyone if you're speaking in English.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_winning">
            <case stage="0" totalRounds="0">
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Wait a sec... I've got to strip!? What kind of poker game &lt;i&gt;is&lt;/i&gt; this?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-shy.png">It can't be too bad, right? Everyone else seemed okay with it.</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">It feels kinda weird having to strip outside of my dorm room...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-angry.png">So annoying! I was doing great...</state>
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">I'm sure my friend Saten would have something positive to say about this... She's always one for encouraging people.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Heh! At least I'm still ahead of you guys!</state>
                <state img="#-exclaiming.png">Hey... it was bound to happen at some point. Don't expect it to happen again, though!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Heh! I'll cut you guys a break! Don't expect me to lose on purpose again!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Heh! It's just one small hurdle. I'll be back on my feet in no time!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-angry.png">So irritating! I thought I'd got the hang of this.</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">What!? M-me!? I guess I couldn't stay covered up forever, eh?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-angry.png">Gaah! I was trying so hard to not have to show my panties...</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Those poker tips from Uiharu got me this far at least...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">I kinda want to weasel my way outta this, but everyone else'll think I'm a sore loser...</state>
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">It's too bad my electromaster abilities can't help me outta &lt;i&gt;this&lt;/i&gt; situation...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">I've managed to hold on this long, but I guess it's time to take off... *gulp*... my panties.</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">I suppose being a level 5 isn't all it's cracked up to be. I still ended up having to show my... &lt;i&gt;you know&lt;/i&gt;...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_normal">
            <case stage="0" totalRounds="0">
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Wait a sec... I've got to strip!? What kind of poker game &lt;i&gt;is&lt;/i&gt; this?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">You've got to be kidding me, I gotta strip!? Fine... I don't intend on losing.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Now I gotta take off something, huh? Don't think you'll make me do it again!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">I gotta strip again... maybe I'll take it easy.</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">I get better hands without even trying over at the arcade. Yet here, I lose...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-confused.png">*gulp* Now I'm on to the bigger stuff...</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">Well... uhhh ...I don't have any of my smaller stuff left.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">Another bad hand... I'm playing like a level-2 here.</state>
                <state img="#-exclaiming.png">Ya know... I'm kinda getting use to this stripping thing. It's like being back in the shower rooms!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-shy.png">You know... I'm getting kinda used to having to strip in front of you guys.</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">I suppose it's just like being in your bikini, not that I mind anyway.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Really!? B-but that means I'll be showing you my...*gulp* panties...</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">&lt;i&gt;It's just like wearing a bikini... It's just like wearing a bikini...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">All I have left is my underwear!? ...which means...</state>
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">I bet you're wondering what I got under these, huh?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-shy.png">*gulp* Well, this is it... I-I'm not sure how I feel about this...</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Please don't tell Saten and the others that you're gonna see me naked, okay?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_losing">
            <case stage="0" totalRounds="0">
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Wait a sec... I've got to strip!? What kind of poker game &lt;i&gt;is&lt;/i&gt; this?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Wait a sec... I've got to strip!? What kind of game is this?</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">My friend, Kuroko, told me she found a new hang-out spot... I did &lt;i&gt;not&lt;/i&gt; expect it to involve stripping off your clothes!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-angry.png">I have to strip again!? I don't get it... why are my cards so bad!?</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">This can't be right!? Which one of you is messing with my cards!?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-angry.png">This is getting irritating! I'm all out of small stuff!</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">Have any of you seen a guy with black, spiky hair around here? That punk is the most unluckiest guy I know...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-shy.png">W-wait! Are you sure I have to strip... again?</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">I'm almost positive this is Kuroko's doing... &lt;i&gt;just you wait, Kuroko!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">Why's it always gotta be me!? Is someone messing with these cards?</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">&lt;i&gt;(Don't give up now, Misaka, you got this)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Whaa...!? Now I gotta show my panties too. It's just not fair.</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">This really &lt;i&gt;is&lt;/i&gt; rotten luck! What could be happening to me!?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">I'm down to my underwear already! And now I gotta take of my... *gulp*</state>
                <state img="#-pondering.png">There's this very unlucky guy I know... Touma or somethin'... This must be what it's like for him everyday, huh?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Whaaa!? B-but how?! Do I seriously have to remove my... *gulp* panties?</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">Kurokooo! This is such a terrible prank! When I get back, you're gonna pay!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripping">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-stripshoes.png">I suppose... I'll take off my shoes to begin with. It counts, right?</state>
                <state img="#-stripshoes.png">I'll go for something small. I think my shoes are a good start. They &lt;i&gt;do&lt;/i&gt; count, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-stripsocks.png">I'll take off my socks...</state>
                <state img="#-stripsocks.png">At least I'm not gonna be showing anything... important.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-stripcardigan.png">Umm... Yeah! ...I'll take off my cardigan.</state>
                <state img="#-stripcardigan.png">My cardigan won't be &lt;i&gt;too&lt;/i&gt; exposing... hehe.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-stripskirt.png">&lt;i&gt;(I think I'll have to take off my skirt.)&lt;/i&gt; H-hey! Don't look, okay?</state>
                <state img="#-stripskirt.png">What're the chances I'd have to strip again?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-stripshirt.png">Hey, y-you wouldn't laugh at a girl's choice in underwear, would you?</state>
                <state img="#-stripshirt.png">Just don't laugh at my underwear... Kuroko got them for me, ya know...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-stripshorts.png">W-well... *gulp* ...here goes...</state>
                <state img="#-stripshorts.png">H-hey! Don't think this means we're close or anything, okay!?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-stripbra.png">I think it's gotta be my bra... &lt;i&gt;(Ehh? Why am I not that embarrassed about it?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-stripbra.png">Well, I kinda feel like I'm with close friends now soooo.... It shouldn't be that big of a deal, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-strippanties.png">W-well... here goes...</state>
                <state img="#-strippanties.png">Please don't stare. It's embarrassing enough as it is!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripped">
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-lostshoes.png">There we go... A lot more comfortable now.</state>
                <state img="#-lostshoes.png">Tadaaa! Just like being back at the dorm!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-lostsocks.png">...I like going barefoot anyway!</state>
                <state img="#-lostsocks.png">Well... that's it for my smaller stuff. Maybe I shoulda worn my Gekota ribbon.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-lostcardigan.png">I was getting kinda hot in that thing...</state>
                <state img="#-lostcardigan.png">Now I'm not as restricted! Bring on the next round!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4" id="10">
                <state img="#-lostskirt.png">So what if I'm wearing shorts? You shouldn't even be looking there!</state>
                <state img="#-lostskirt.png">Yeah? I wear these because I like them, okay!?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-lostshirt.png">H-hey! it's perfectly normal for girls to wear cute underwear like this!</state>
                <state img="#-lostshirt.png">See! As if &lt;i&gt;I'd&lt;/i&gt; wear something like this...hehehe.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-lostshorts.png">It's kinda embarrassing just being in your underwear, but I feel okay with it with you guys...</state>
                <state img="#-lostshorts.png">Kuroko sees me like this most nights. Kinda glad she isn't here to screw with me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-lostbra.png">J-just don't stare &lt;i&gt;too&lt;/i&gt; much, okay.</state>
                <state img="#-lostbra.png">Don't tell anyone that you've seen them, please.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-lostpanties.png">D-don't make such a big deal outta this, okay...</state>
                <state img="#-lostpanties.png">As long as this just stays between us...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_strip">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="7">Heh! Serves you right, ~player~! Boys aren't that great at this kind of thing!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="8">Wow, you mustn't be trying very hard, ~player~. Maybe you were... boys are kinda idiotic...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="49">Hehehe! I bet you're trying to lose on purpose aren't you, ~player~?</state>
                <state img="#-disappointed.png" oneShotId="50">This guy... What does ~player~ think he's trying to pull here?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="53">If I was to guess your level, ~player~... I'd say you're about a level 1! Hehe!</state>
                <state img="#-disappointed.png" oneShotId="54">Just don't go thinking that you'll win the next round, ~player~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-shy.png" oneShotId="57">It's not like I'm interested or anything but you gotta strip something.</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png" oneShotId="58">I'm getting kinda &lt;i&gt;warm&lt;/i&gt;... It's not because ~player~ has to strip or anything like that!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="61">I bet you were hoping it was me who had strip, huh, ~player~.</state>
                <state img="#-exclaiming.png" oneShotId="62">Hehe! I had a feeling that you'd be the one to lose this round, ~player~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-shy.png" oneShotId="65">Hey, ~player~... I won't look if you don't want me to.</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png" oneShotId="66">I'll try to lose the next round if you want me to, ~player~...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-shy.png" oneShotId="69">Ummm... ~player~.... Do you want to get naked with me?</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png" oneShotId="70">I w-was hoping that you'd lose that round, ~player~...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-mast1.png" oneShotId="73">Did me t-touching myself... &lt;i&gt;-hnng-&lt;/i&gt; ...make you w-want to lose the round, ~player~?</state>
                <state img="#-mast3.png" oneShotId="74">I think you l-lost that round... &lt;i&gt;-unnf-&lt;/i&gt; ...on purpose, ~player~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-finishcalm.png" oneShotId="77">You're gonna be as naked as me soon, ~player~. I... wouldn't mind that ...hehe...</state>
                <state img="#-finishhappy.png" oneShotId="78">Heh! I can't wait to see you take off more clothes, ~player~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Don't think you'll impress me with whatever you take off.</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">It's not that I care to see ~name~ strip off.</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">You're just like all the other boys I know. You just wanna show off!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">This looks like it could be kinda fun! Uhh... I mean... Eww, don't wanna see &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; take off anything!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Ha! ~name~ has to remove some clothing!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I'm only just getting started! What're you gonna remove, eh!?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Heh! I take it you had a bad hand!</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">Alright! I win this round!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">As if you'd have a better hand than me!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-shy.png">At least I got through that round without stripping...hehe.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Wow, so ~name~ has to strip off something... I don't even wanna look!</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">I think I get why my friend Saten wanted to try this out sometime...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Heh! So ~name~ has to strip! Just don't make a show of it, okay.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Hehe! My cards were better than ~name~'s! It's your turn to strip!</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">This means you gotta strip, ~name~? Just 'cause I'm a level 5 doesn't mean you gotta impress me or anything...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Oooh..What are you gonna take off?</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">I'm near enough naked ~name~! It better be something big!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Hehe! Looks like we're all gonna be showing some skin tonight!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Heh! You'll be as naked as me soon!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Hah! That's what I thought, ~name~! What are ya gonna take off?</state>
                <state img="#-pondering.png">Those cards are getting as bad as mine! I swear something is up with them...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-mast1.png">H-hey ~name~... &lt;i&gt;-hnng-&lt;/i&gt; ...you gotta strip.</state>
                <state img="#-mast3.png">T-that hand wasn't y-your... &lt;i&gt;-unnf-&lt;/i&gt;... best, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-finishsmug.png">Hehe! Sooner or later, you're gonna be as naked as I am!</state>
                <state img="#-finishhappy.png">Hah! Looks like you didn't win this round, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-finishcalm.png">Getting closer to the end! Maybe we can get some crepes later, okay?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_strip">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">Not a great hand, ~player~? I better make sure that doesn't happen to me!</state>
                <state img="#-exclaiming.png">It'll probably be me who has to strip next round, ~player~. It &lt;i&gt;is&lt;/i&gt; kinda based on luck, after all.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-exclaiming.png" oneShotId="15">Maybe I'll let you in on my poker tricks after this, ~player~!</state>
                <state img="#-thumbsup.png" oneShotId="16">It's all part of the game, ~player~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-exclaiming.png" oneShotId="19">Yeah! I got this round! There's nothing like a bit of friendly competition, ~player~!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="20">It's not looking good for you, eh ~player~?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="23">Ya know... It's not too bad once you get in to it!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="24">Ooooh... I'm kinda interested in seeing what ~player~'s gonna do here!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-exclaiming.png" oneShotId="27">At least you're still in the game, ~player~!</state>
                <state img="#-thumbsup.png" oneShotId="28">I bet we'd make great friends, ~player~! Going ahead and stripping in front of others takes guts. I like that!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-thumbsup.png" oneShotId="31">Us girls can show the boys how it's done, ~player~!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="32">Hey, ~name~, let's both be in our underwear, okay?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-thumbsup.png" oneShotId="35">We'll &lt;i&gt;both&lt;/i&gt; be naked soon, ~player~.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="36">I'm glad that you're stripping down too, ~player~. I don't want to be naked when you aren't.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-mast4.png" oneShotId="39">Why don't y-you come... &lt;i&gt;-hnng-&lt;/i&gt; ...join me, ~player~?</state>
                <state img="#-mast3.png" oneShotId="40">I hope I get to s-see you... &lt;i&gt;-hnnf-&lt;/i&gt; ...naked, ~player~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-finishcalm.png" oneShotId="43">Hey, ~player~, getting naked is actually more fun than I expected!</state>
                <state img="#-finishhappy.png" oneShotId="44">We should totally meet up after this, ~player~. You're really great, ya know!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" oneShotId="7">
                <condition filter="confident" role="target" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">Heh! I bet it doesn't even bother you, huh?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-calm.png">If you gotta strip, go for something light.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">It's okay, ~name~. Just go for something small if you can.</state>
                <state img="#-exclaiming.png">I'm kinda glad my friend Kuroko isn't here. She get's... &lt;i&gt;excitable&lt;/i&gt; ...around girls.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-shy.png">At least it isn't me this round...</state>
                <state img="#-thumbsup.png">Come on ~name~, you've gotta remove some clothing!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">That hand was &lt;i&gt;not&lt;/i&gt; in your favor! What ya gonna take off, ~name~?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Those cards look pretty bad.</state>
                <state img="#-thumbsup.png">I'm sure you'll get a better hand next round!</state>
                <state img="#-exclaiming.png">Maybe you should hang out at the arcade with me... pick up some tips!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-excited.png">All right! Here we go!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Looks like you've gotta strip ~name~! What ya gonna take off next!</state>
                <state img="#-exclaiming.png">Imagining my friend Uiharu in this kinda situation is making me giggle a bit... hehe! She's kinda timid!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Ahhh... that's quite a bad hand ~name~! What are you gonna take off!</state>
                <state img="#-thumbsup.png">Don't feel too bad about it, ~name~. The game's not over yet!</state>
                <state img="#-thumbsup.png">We're friends now, right? It shouldn't be too bad for you to strip in front of me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-excited.png">Yeah! I won this round! Looks like you won't get to see anything special this time!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">This is getting interesting! What're you taking off!?</state>
                <state img="#-exclaiming.png">What kinda card choice was that!? I'm starting to think you want to get naked!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-thumbsup.png">It's okay ~name~, stripping down isn't as bad as it seems!</state>
                <state img="#-exclaiming.png">Hey, you've got this! It can't be worse than where I'm at!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Hehe! We'll all be naked soon enough! These cards just keep getting worse!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-mast4.png">I b-bet you wish you h-hadn't... &lt;i&gt;-hnng-&lt;/i&gt; ...t-traded in those cards, huh ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-mast2.png">Hey, you g-gotta strip ~name~... &lt;i&gt;-Oh wow-&lt;/i&gt;...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-finishthumbsup.png">No worries, ~player~! It's really not that bad once you get used to it!</state>
                <state img="#-finishcalm.png">It can't be much worse than where I'm at right now... hehe...</state>
                <state img="#-finishhappy.png">I feel like we know each other so well now! We should go visit the entertainment district later.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="tie">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Wow... it's a tie!? Kinda rare to see that happen!</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">I didn't even think this was possible...!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-mast3.png">A tie? That's... &lt;i&gt;-hnng-&lt;/i&gt; ...kinda rare!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-finishshocked.png">Woah!? A tie! Ya don't see that everyday!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <condition filter="mean" role="target" />
                <state img="#-disappointed.png" oneShotId="81">Seriously!? Someone like you deserves to take off more.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <condition filter="mean" role="target" />
                <state img="#-disappointed.png" oneShotId="85">I bet you're enjoying this, aren't you!?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" layers="2-3" />
                <state img="#-angry.png" oneShotId="83">You're seriously only gonna remove your ~clothing~? Just give it up already!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <condition role="target" layers="2-3" />
                <state img="#-finishdisappointed.png" oneShotId="87">You're only gonna remove your ~clothing~!? Don't think it'll help you much.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-1">
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">Seriously? Your ~clothing~ barely ~clothing.ifPlural(count|counts)~!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Oh, just your ~clothing~, huh? You'd better hurry it up!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-3">
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">Ugh...fine, take off your ~clothing~ if you want.</state>
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">Fine... at least it isn't something that I care about.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">I'm almost down to my underwear, and you're only gonna take off your ~clothing~!?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Is there anything metallic on your ~clothing~? I could pull it off for ya!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">Only your ~clothing~!? It's not like I expected much...</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">Maybe you should let me take your ~clothing~ off for you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Your ~clothing~? I guess I'm in no position to complain.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">As long as it gets you one step closer to losing the game, I'm all for you removing your ~clothing~, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-mast4.png">T-taking off your...~clothing~?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-finishdisappointed.png">Only your ~clothing~? It's not much, considering where I am.</state>
                <state img="#-finishhappy.png">Let me fry it off you, hehe! I'll buy you a new one, later.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="10">
                <condition role="target" character="9s" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-finishshocked.png">Hey!? Just what're you tryin' to pull? I've seen that kinda tech before! Academy City &lt;i&gt;is&lt;/i&gt; considered the most advanced city after all!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-1">
                <state img="#-shy.png">It's not like this changes anything, though.</state>
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">I coulda just used my electrical ability to fry that off of you instead!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-3">
                <state img="#-pondering.png">I thought all boys wanted to show off, removing your ~clothing~ doesn't really reveal much.</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">There's nothing really special about such a small item... why even bother, eh!?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-angry.png">I shoulda just pulled that off you myself!</state>
                <state img="#-pondering.png">Well, whatever. Maybe next time, eh?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-pondering.png">That's gotta be the last small thing you have, right!?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I'd totally have taken off more than that, hehe!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-shy.png">I was kinda hoping you'd go for something... bigger.</state>
                <state img="#-exclaiming.png">Hey, do you all wanna go to the lookout point after this? There's a great view of Academy City up there!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-mast2.png">It must b-be some kinda... &lt;i&gt;-uhhn-&lt;/i&gt; ...strategy.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-finishembarrassed.png">Well... at least you're closer to where I'm at...</state>
                <state img="#-finishsmug.png">Hehe! Make sure you don't lose track of it!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0-1" oneShotId="8" priority="400">
                <condition role="self" notSaidMarker="expo1" />
                <state img="#-exclaiming.png" marker="expo1">Have you ever heard of an Esper before? There's a lotta science behind it but, basically, we emit an energy field that we manipulate to manifest our powers...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-1" oneShotId="13" priority="400">
                <condition role="self" notSaidMarker="expo3" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="expo3">Anyone else here from Academy City, too? It's an entire city based around academic research and progress, hence the name...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-3" oneShotId="17" priority="400">
                <condition role="self" notSaidMarker="expo5" />
                <state img="#-exclaiming.png" marker="expo5">All the Espers in Academy City are placed in to a power bracket. The weakest are placed at Level 0, up to the strongest at Level 5...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-3" oneShotId="21" priority="400">
                <condition role="self" notSaidMarker="expo7" />
                <state img="#-pondering.png" marker="expo7">I wonder which district of Academy City I'm in? You see, Academy City is split up in to 23 districts, each with a specific purpose and function...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="alice_mgq" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Woah!? Did you just transform in to a... snake or something!?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="shimakaze" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Ehh!? Shimakaze? Did you just burn off your ~clothing~!? Are you a pyrokineticist, or something?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <condition role="target" character="alice_mgq" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-finishshocked.png">I've seen a lotta strange stuff done with magic, but this is somethin' else!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <condition role="target" character="shimakaze" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-finishshocked.png">Ehh!? You burned off your ~clothing~, Shimakaze? Espers with the pyrokineticist ability can do that...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" oneShotId="4">
                <condition filter="school_uniform" status="not_lost_some" role="target" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="93">I don't recognize that uniform... are you from Academy City?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10" oneShotId="1">
                <condition filter="school_uniform" status="not_lost_some" role="target" />
                <state img="#-finishconfused.png" oneShotId="99">I don't recognize that school uniform... are you from Academy City?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="moe" role="target" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="95">Ahhh! I bet you're just as cute without your ~clothing~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" layers="2-3" />
                <state img="#-exclaiming.png" oneShotId="97">Removing your ~clothing~!? It must be kinda important to you, huh?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <condition role="target" layers="2-3" />
                <state img="#-finishconfused.png" oneShotId="101">You're ~clothing~ must mean something to you. Since you're now only just removing ~clothing.ifPlural(them|it)~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-1">
                <state img="#-thumbsup.png">No big deal... it's only your ~clothing~.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">It look's kinda pretty! Where did ya get it from?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-3">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Hey, I can understand why you'd only want to remove your ~clothing~.</state>
                <state img="#-exclaiming.png">If it was my friend Uiharu, I'd bet she'd take off one flower from her headband each round!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-confused.png">Taking off your ~clothing~, huh? Does that even count?</state>
                <state img="#-exclaiming.png">Just your ~clothing~? That's no big deal, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-exclaiming.png">Ah, your ~clothing~!? It must be kinda important.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">You can't keep a girl from her ~clothing~! Unless, ya know, we're playing a stripping game.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Going to remove your ~clothing~ huh?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Ya know, Uiharu would have probably done the same. She's kinda timid like that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-mast3.png">Your ~clothing~ still c-counts....?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-finishcalm.png">Taking off your ~clothing~, huh.</state>
                <state img="#-finishhappy.png">If I had the Telekinesis ability, I'd totally try to take it off of you myself!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="shimakaze" stage="4" saidMarker="dizzy" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Woah!? Shimakaze, are you okay? That's a serious hit you took!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <condition role="target" character="shimakaze" stage="4" saidMarker="dizzy" />
                <state img="#-finishshocked.png">Waah!? Shimakaze, you're not looking too good... you sure you're okay?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" stage="6" />
                <condition role="other" character="alice_mgq" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">I've never seen anything like &lt;i&gt;this&lt;/i&gt; before! Y-your not gonna attack me or anything, are you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <condition role="target" stage="6" />
                <condition role="other" character="alice_mgq" />
                <state img="#-finishconfused.png">I this some kinda new magic the church is employing!?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-1" oneShotId="9">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="expo1" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">...It's called an AIM Diffusion Field and it's different for everyone. I'm an electromaster and my friend, Kuroko, is a teleporter.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-1" oneShotId="14">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="expo3" />
                <state img="#-exclaiming.png">...almost all the residents there have at least some kind of special ability. With many schools and universities set up to further that power.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-3" oneShotId="18">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="expo5" />
                <state img="#-smug.png">...There are only seven Level 5 Espers in total at the moment. I'm ranked third out of those seven... hehe! I'm pretty powerful!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-3" oneShotId="22">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="expo7" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">...District 7 is where Tokiwadai and the other schools are located and District 15 is the city's shopping and commerce center. Just to name a few!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-1">
                <state img="#-happy.png">I wonder what ~name~'ll remove next?</state>
                <state img="#-exclaiming.png">I'd take off my hair clip but, ya know, I kinda need it to hold my hair together!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-3">
                <state img="#-thumbsup.png">...I'd probably do the same if I had any small stuff left.</state>
                <state img="#-pondering.png">Kinda makes me wish I'd worn my Gekota bracelet.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-pondering.png">I shoulda thought of doing that...</state>
                <state img="#-pondering.png">This game is kinda interesting, I wonder if the others'll play it...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-pondering.png">Hmm... I shoulda thought about wearing something small like that.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">That reminds me... I should stop by the mart on the way home...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-exclaiming.png">Sooner or later you'll end up as naked as me!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Even though I'm stood here naked, I'm having quite a fun time with you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-mast1.png">Was th-that the right... &lt;i&gt;-hnng-&lt;/i&gt; ...choice?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-finishexcited.png">You'll eventually be as naked as I am!</state>
                <state img="#-finishcalm.png">I know a good store where you can get more of those!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <condition filter="mean" role="target" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="103">Heh! You totally deserve that! Serves you right...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <condition filter="mean" role="target" />
                <state img="#-angry.png" oneShotId="105">Whaa!? You seriously should take off two things if you're going for something small like that!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-1">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Going for the small stuff...good. Keep it that way.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">As long as you keep it to the smaller stuff! I don't wanna see any of you getting fully naked!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-3">
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">Fine, go ahead and remove your ~clothing~!</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">Yeah, yeah... I get it. Just remove your ~clothing~ already!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Your ~clothing~? Ehh... at least it's something.</state>
                <state img="#-thumbsup.png">I'm totally okay with it if you're only gonna take of your ~clothing~, ~name~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">I'm almost naked and you're only taking off your ~clothing~ this round!?</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">Ooooh... What're you hiding under there?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">If you wanna take off your ~clothing~, then go for it, I guess.</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">Just hurry up and take off your ~clothing~, ~name~! I don't like the fact you've still got stuff on!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-mast4.png">Going for your ~clothing~... th-this time, huh?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-finishdisappointed.png">I guess your ~clothing~ isn't too bad of a choice... hehe.</state>
                <state img="#-finishcalm.png">When the festival was on, they had stalls that sold stuff like your ~clothing~. I shoulda bought one!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_minor">
            <case stage="0-1">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Okay then, let's keep going!</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">Just... as long as you keep away from me, we're fine!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-3">
                <state img="#-smug.png">I totally get why you wouldn't remove anything bigger!</state>
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">Just don't go thinking you're gonna win this, okay!?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Maybe you should step it up a bit, next round!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Hehe! One step closer to me winning this thing!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-angry.png">Ehhh... fine. You'd better make it up to me next round, though!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Just throwing it on the ground, huh? My dorm Housemaster would scold us for something like that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">&lt;i&gt;(I kinda wanna see ~name~ take off something more)&lt;/i&gt; W-wait... this isn't like me!</state>
                <state img="#-pondering.png">Am I distracting you? Will it make you lose the next hand, too.?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-mast3.png">I... &lt;i&gt;-uhhn-&lt;/i&gt; ...suppose i-it's okay.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-finishembarrassed.png">I wonder if you're gonna take off more... W-wait a sec! I... uh... meant somethin' else!</state>
                <state img="#-finishhappy.png">I usually don't mix well with guys, but you're actually kinda nice...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0-1" oneShotId="10" priority="400">
                <condition role="self" notSaidMarker="expo2" />
                <state img="#-exclaiming.png" marker="expo2">My friend, Kuroko, is quite... uhhh... &lt;i&gt;eccentric&lt;/i&gt; to say the least. She's totally crazy about me for some reason...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-1" oneShotId="15" priority="400">
                <condition role="self" notSaidMarker="expo4" />
                <state img="#-exclaiming.png" marker="expo4">My friends, Saten and Uiharu, don't go to Tokiwadai like Kuroko and I do. They go to Sakugawa High School instead...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-3" oneShotId="19" priority="400">
                <condition role="self" notSaidMarker="expo6" />
                <state img="#-shy.png" marker="expo6">H-hey... are any of you collecting Gekota figurines...? It's this frog mascot that all the kids are talking about...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-3" oneShotId="23" priority="400">
                <condition role="self" notSaidMarker="expo8" />
                <state img="#-exclaiming.png" marker="expo8">My Esper ability is known as Electromaster. It allows me to control, manifest and manipulate lightning and electricity...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="7">
                <condition role="target" character="cammy_white" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Ehh!? I think I can see Cammy's... &lt;i&gt;outline&lt;/i&gt; ... through her pants!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="sakura" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Wait!? You were a z-zombie this entire time!? ...Saten was right, they really &lt;i&gt;do&lt;/i&gt; exist!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10" id="15">
                <condition role="target" character="cammy_white" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-finishembarrassed.png">Woah! Cammy, I can kinda see the outline of your... &lt;i&gt;parts&lt;/i&gt;!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <condition role="target" character="sakura" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-finishshocked.png">Woah!? Saten was right!! Th-they totally &lt;i&gt;do&lt;/i&gt; exist!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" oneShotId="5">
                <condition filter="school_uniform" status="not_lost_some" role="target" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="107">I don't recognize that uniform... are you from Academy City?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10" oneShotId="2">
                <condition filter="school_uniform" status="not_lost_some" role="target" />
                <state img="#-finishconfused.png" oneShotId="111">I don't recognize that school uniform... are you from Academy City?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="moe" role="target" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="109">You're still gonna look cute either way!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-1">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Ah, your ~clothing~... I see how it is.</state>
                <state img="#-exclaiming.png">I think my friend Saten might like this game! She's always flipping Uiharu's skirt in public, hehe!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-3">
                <state img="#-thumbsup.png">Hey, I removed something similar when I last stripped. It's not too bad!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Me and the other girls would play a game in the dorms where we would remove stuff like this...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-thumbsup.png">Of course! Your ~clothing~! Kinda makes sense if you ask me.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Kuroko would probably ask you to take off more, hehe...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">Really, ~name~!? I've barely got anything left and you're only gonna take off your ~clothing~!?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Can't be worse than where I'm at, ~name~. Can it?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-shy.png">Going for your ~clothing~ Eh? I wouldn't mind seeing a bit more...</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Alright then... your ~clothing~. The sooner you're as naked as I am, the better!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-mast1.png">Removing y-your ~clothing~ I... &lt;i&gt;-hnng-&lt;/i&gt; ...see.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-finishembarrassed.png">Your ~clothing~, huh? I wouldn't mind it if you showed a bit more.</state>
                <state img="#-finishcalm.png">There's a store in District 15 that sells stuff kinda like your ~clothing~, ya know?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_minor">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="gwen" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-angry.png">Seriously!? Play fair! You coulda removed the entire thing...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="kyoko" stage="6" />
                <state img="#-exclaiming.png">Ohhh... I see why you didn't wanna take off your gloves, Kyoko.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <condition role="target" character="gwen" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-finishdisappointed.png">Are you serious!? You shoulda taken off the entire thing...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <condition role="target" character="kyoko" stage="6" />
                <state img="#-finishcalm.png">Ohh I get it now, Kyoko... You were using them to hide your hands this entire time.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-1" oneShotId="11">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="expo2" />
                <state img="#-exclaiming.png">...She even managed to become my room-mate, even though she's in a lower year! I dunno what her deal is, really.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-1" oneShotId="16">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="expo4" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">...They're both actually really nice people! I'm glad to have met them. Even though we go to different schools, we still hang out together whenever we can!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-3" oneShotId="20">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="expo6" />
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">...I was just wondering, ya know. I-it's not like I would care about some stupid kids toy!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-3" oneShotId="24">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="expo8" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">...It also gives me a degree of magnetic control, too! Through electro-magnetism, I can even create weaponry from iron particles found in the ground!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-1">
                <state img="#-thumbsup.png">Hey, don't sweat it! Let's keep going!</state>
                <state img="#-exclaiming.png">Sometimes... it's good to start small and work your way up when you have the confidence!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-3">
                <state img="#-happy.png">See... not too bad, right?</state>
                <state img="#-exclaiming.png">I'm getting kinda interested, seeing you take off your ~clothing~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Things are getting more and more risky, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">You're one step closer to the end, ~name~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-thumbsup.png">Hey, at least you're one step closer!</state>
                <state img="#-exclaiming.png">We should totally hang out after this! We have this cafe we usually go to and they serve the best sundaes.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-happy.png">You can't have much left to take off now, right!?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Alright! I'm still gonna win, though! Well... hehe ...I hope I do.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-mast3.png">Your ~clothing~... &lt;i&gt;-ohhh-&lt;/i&gt; ...was k-kinda cute.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-finishhappy.png">You should be getting closer now, right?</state>
                <state img="#-finishthumbsup.png">I'm actually really glad I've met you. I like to make new friends, ya know...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_major">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <condition filter="mean" role="target" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="113">Hehe! Karma's finally caught up with you!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <condition filter="mean" role="target" />
                <state img="#-angry.png" oneShotId="117">Seriously!? I don't even think I'd wanna see what's under there!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition status="not_lost_some" role="target" />
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" oneShotId="115">Whaa!? ~Name~? Removing your ~clothing~!? Why not something a little less... revealing.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <condition status="not_lost_some" role="target" />
                <state img="#-finishembarrassed.png" oneShotId="120">Woah!? You must &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; want to get in to this...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-1">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">W-wait!? You're removing your ~clothing~!?</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">Hey, ~name~!? Are you just showin' off!? It didn't end well for the last guy who tried doing that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-3">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Ehh!? Your ~clothing~?</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">Like I actually &lt;i&gt;want&lt;/i&gt; to see you take off ~clothing~... punk!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-shy.png">He's taking off his ~clothing~!? I think I should join in on this...</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">Your ~clothing~!? Just remember who you're with, okay!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Finally! You shouldn't keep a girl waiting, okay!</state>
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">If Kuroko finds out about this, I won't hear the end of it all week...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-horny.png">You're gonna take off your ~clothing~!? Well, I uhh...</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">Wow, ~name~'s taking off his ~clothing~! None of the guys I've ever met would do that willingly...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-mast2.png">You're t-taking your ~clothing~ off! I... &lt;i&gt;-unnf-&lt;/i&gt; ...was k-kinda hoping so...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-finishembarrassed.png">Taking off your ~clothing~ is a big move! You thinking of joining me?</state>
                <state img="#-finishcalm.png">As long as you aren't like the guys from the schools in District 18, then I'm fine with it.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_major">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <test expr="~background~" value="beach" />
                <state img="#-exclaiming.png" oneShotId="124">Well... we are on the beach after all.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <test expr="~background~" value="hot spring" />
                <state img="#-angry.png" oneShotId="122">You seriously think I'd wanna join you in the hot springs, ~name~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <test expr="~background~" value="beach" />
                <state img="#-finishhappy.png" oneShotId="126">Kinda fitting, seeing as we're on a beach and all...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-1">
                <state img="#-angry.png">I &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; hope you're not gonna go further than that!</state>
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">Just don't go parading around like that!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-3">
                <state img="#-shy.png">Now I understand why boys want to show off all the time.</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">As long as you don't go further than that, I think we're okay...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">I wonder what's under there...? AHH! I mean, put your ~clothing~ back on!</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Woah!? I think you just upgraded to a level 3...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-excited.png">Alright! Someone else is showing some skin!</state>
                <state img="#-exclaiming.png">Feels kinda like being at the water park, doesn't it!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">That's kinda... nice. I wonder if he's... W-what am I thinking!</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">You're almost ready to join me, right? &lt;i&gt;(What am I saying!)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-mast1.png">Do you th-think I could m-maybe... &lt;i&gt;-uhhn-&lt;/i&gt; ... have your ~clothing~?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-finishshocked.png">Woah! That's actually... kinda good looking...</state>
                <state img="#-finishsmug.png">Imagine If I told Saten that Hitotsue Hajime was here... She's such a massive fan of his albums! She'd freak out!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_major">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="aimee" stage="0-2" />
                <state img="#-angry.png">H-hey! Watch where you're firing that thing!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <condition role="target" character="aimee" stage="0-2" />
                <state img="#-finishdisappointed.png">Hey! watch it! I'm kinda vulnerable here...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" oneShotId="6">
                <condition filter="school_uniform" status="not_lost_some" role="target" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="128">I don't recognize that uniform... are you from Academy City?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10" oneShotId="3">
                <condition filter="school_uniform" status="not_lost_some" role="target" />
                <state img="#-finishconfused.png" oneShotId="134">I don't recognize that school uniform... are you from Academy City?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" oneShotId="12">
                <condition filter="moe" role="target" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="130">Ohhh! I bet you're wearing cute underwear, too!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition status="not_lost_some" role="target" />
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" oneShotId="132">Whaa!? ~Name~? You're taking off your ~clothing~ so soon!? Why not something less revealing...?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <condition status="not_lost_some" role="target" />
                <state img="#-finishshocked.png" oneShotId="136">Wow... your ~clothing~ already!? Do you &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; want to strip off this badly?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-1">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Ehh...!? Is she really gonna remove her ~clothing~!?</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">You know... my friend Kuroko would be all over me if I took off something like that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-3">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Woah... shouldn't you... maybe think about this for a sec!</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">What kinda tricks are you trying to pull here!?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-exclaiming.png">You're removing your ~clothing~!? If I have to strip, I'll do the same next round!</state>
                <state img="#-exclaiming.png">I'm kinda getting in to this... Hey, ~name~? I'll go for something similar if I lose next round, okay?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Yeah, ~name~! Us girls have gotta show some skin!</state>
                <state img="#-exclaiming.png">As long as I'm not the only one in their underwear, I'm fine with it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-excited.png">Way to go! I gotta see what you've got under there!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">It's kinda different when you're not in the privacy of your own home, huh!?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-mast2.png">Taking off y-your ~clothing~ this... &lt;i&gt;-ohhh-&lt;/i&gt; ...time?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-finishthumbsup.png">Alright! You shouldn't be too far off from joining me.</state>
                <state img="#-finishcalm.png">I actually kinda like your ~clothing~, ~name~! Could ya tell me where you got it?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_major">
            <case stage="0-8" id="8">
                <condition role="target" character="navi" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Waaah!? Navi!? Weren't you just... I don't recall &lt;i&gt;this&lt;/i&gt; ability in the Database?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4" id="4">
                <condition role="target" character="rin" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-exclaiming.png">Ohhh!? Hey, Rin, it's okay. I can get why you'd wanna hide them from other people.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="rinkah" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Whaa!? Rinkah, your thong isn't... well.... I can kinda see your &lt;i&gt;hair&lt;/i&gt; down there!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <condition role="target" character="natsuki" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-smug.png">Hehe! Natsuki, I can still kinda see your panties!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <condition role="target" character="natsuki" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-finishsmug.png">Hey Natsuki, I can still see them!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10" id="16">
                <condition role="target" character="navi" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-finishshocked.png">Ehhh!? Navi!? Did you just... transform? I don't recall ever learning about &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; kind of ability.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <condition role="target" character="rinkah" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-finishembarrassed.png">Woah!? Rinkah!? I can totally see your... &lt;i&gt;hair&lt;/i&gt;... poking out.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <test expr="~background~" value="beach" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="138">We &lt;i&gt;are&lt;/i&gt; on the beach... may as well dress for it, right!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <test expr="~background~" value="beach" />
                <state img="#-finishexcited.png" oneShotId="140">It's not too bad, seeing as we're on the beach.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-1">
                <state img="#-smug.png">This was a common sight in the girl's shower room, no big deal.</state>
                <state img="#-exclaiming.png">I'm actually kinda relieved my friend Kuroko isn't here. She's...uhh ...a bit &lt;i&gt;excitable&lt;/i&gt; around girls.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-3">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">I hope I won't have to show &lt;i&gt;my&lt;/i&gt; underwear...</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">Are you gonna be okay!? You might lose the next round, too?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-exclaiming.png">If you're showing your underwear then I guess it's okay if I do too. We &lt;i&gt;are&lt;/i&gt; friends after all!</state>
                <state img="#-pondering.png">I just think of it as, like, a bikini during the summer or something.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Alright! At least I'm not the only one showing her underwear!</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">This kinda makes me feel a bit less embarrassed, I gotta say...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-thumbsup.png">Your underwear looks cute, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-exclaiming.png">Hey, ~name~? Do you wanna visit the Tokiwadai dorms after this? I'll show you around, it'll be fun!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-mast4.png">Do you t-think I could... &lt;i&gt;-uhnn-&lt;/i&gt; ...maybe use that to...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-finishconfused.png">Ya know, I think I might have some that look just like that...</state>
                <state img="#-finishhappy.png">The ammo I use to fire my Railgun ability are actually arcade coins that I've won from the machines. Hey, ~name~? I'll take you to the arcade later and show ya!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-1">
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">Looks to me like you aren't even trying! You better not be looking for attention from me!</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">I mean... for guys, showing your chest totally isn't worth getting excited over.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-3">
                <state img="#-angry.png">Ugh... I just don't get it! Why bother covering up if you're gonna show it off anyway!</state>
                <state img="#-exclaiming.png">It gets pretty hot in Academy City around summer, it's an excuse for guys to go topless everywhere! Just... don't go flaunting it here, okay!?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Taking off your ~clothing~ huh...</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">I wonder how strong his muscles look under th... Hey! W-what am I thinking!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-shy.png">I think I-I'm actually kinda looking forward to this...</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">I'm kinda interested to see yours, ~name~. Wh-what am I thinking here!?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-pondering.png">Ohh! So, ~name~'s going to show off his chest, huh.</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">Ya know, I'm kinda looking forward to this. I don't even know why...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-mast1.png">I was w-waiting... &lt;i&gt;-ahhh-&lt;/i&gt; ... for you to take that off!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-finishcalm.png">So you're gonna show your chest, huh. Just tryin' to impress me or somethin'?</state>
                <state img="#-finishcalm.png">You're lucky Kuroko isn't here, ~name~! She'd literally fight you to keep your ~clothing~ on!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="9s" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">Eehh!? Th-that's kinda weird, 9S. I'm just not use to seeing someone without any nipples! N-not that I was looking!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-shy.png">Even though you're a guy, a bare chest is still kinda...</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">~name~, are you just tryin' to show off!?</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">I'm kinda glad Tokiwadai is an all girls school. It isn't full of guys tryin' to show off themselves!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-angry.png">&lt;i&gt;(Wow... that actually looks pretty good.)&lt;/i&gt; Waah! I... uhh... cover it up, NOW!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I'm thinking that you want to lose. Fine! Means I'm more likely to win!</state>
                <state img="#-pondering.png">Ya know, that doesn't look too bad! Just don't let Kuroko know I've seen you like this.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Wow... that's quite a.. I-I mean, quit showin' off ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">Now we're talking! Finally showing off more of yourself!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-mast2.png">Oh wow... &lt;i&gt;-hnng-&lt;/i&gt; ...you look so...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-finishhappy.png">W-well I... uhh... That's actually kinda nice...</state>
                <state img="#-finishthumbsup.png">I doubt many people would tangle with you with a chest like that... hehe!?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-1">
                <state img="#-angry.png">Ehh...!? You're seriously gonna remove that!? guys are &lt;i&gt;so&lt;/i&gt; gross!</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Woah!? You mean you're seriously gonna show your... &lt;i&gt;crotch&lt;/i&gt;?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-3">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">W-w-wait a sec!? Your ~clothing~!? Then that means...</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">Your gonna do that here!? Do you have &lt;i&gt;any&lt;/i&gt; decency!?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Hey! Who told you you could remove your ~clothing~!? I might see your... &lt;i&gt;you know&lt;/i&gt;...</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">Wait!? You're gonna show your... I just... Argh! Just get it over with, okay!?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Wait!? He's gonna show his...&lt;i&gt;you-know-what&lt;/i&gt;!? B-but, I'm practically naked here...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Why am I feeling like this!? Why do I actually &lt;i&gt;want&lt;/i&gt; to see ~name~'s...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">You're taking off your ~clothing~, ~name~!? Just 'cause I'm naked doesn't mean you gotta get your &lt;i&gt;thing&lt;/i&gt; out.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">So... We'll both have our &lt;i&gt;parts&lt;/i&gt; on show? This is totally freaking me out!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-mast3.png">Taking off your ~clothing~!? Whilst I'm already feeling so...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-finishshocked.png">Look's like ~name~'s gotta take off his ~clothing~! He better not be a show-off about it...</state>
                <state img="#-finishconfused.png">Maybe I &lt;i&gt;shouldn't&lt;/i&gt; mention this to Kuroko... I don't think she'd wanna see stuff like this...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_small_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">I wasn't expecting... &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt;. Is it supposed to be so... small?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Waah!? It's so... small. I don't think any Esper abilities will help you out there!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-shy.png">Hehe! It's not that big! &lt;i&gt;(But still, seeing a guy's you-know-what is kinda making me feel hot)&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">I really shouldn't have looked, but... I coulda sworn Saten said they were &lt;i&gt;bigger&lt;/i&gt; than that...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-confused.png">I could've sworn the other girls said they were usually bigger than this... Even so...</state>
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">Is my body not good enough for you!? Why's it so small?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-mast1.png">It's so s-small... but still, it's... &lt;i&gt;-Oooh-&lt;/i&gt; ...kinda making me...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-finishsmug.png">Ehhh? That's kinda... uhhh... Well, that's less for me to be embarrassed about.</state>
                <state img="#-finishdisappointed.png">I don't wanna be judgmental, but... is that &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; all you have down there?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_medium_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-shy.png">I shouldn't even be looking at your... penis. I-I'm &lt;i&gt;not&lt;/i&gt; interested...</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Hmmph... as if I care that you're showing off your... &lt;i&gt;guy parts&lt;/i&gt;. So gross!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Woah... I can't believe you're showing... &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt;! It's kinda making me feel a bit hot...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Wow... Just seeing a guy's &lt;i&gt;private parts&lt;/i&gt; right there in front of me... what is this weird feeling?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-shy.png">Wow... that's kinda brave of you to just show it off like that. N-not that I was looking... or anything!</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Woah!? It's just like that website Saten showed me the other day...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-mast2.png">Oh yes! Th-that's... &lt;i&gt;-hnng-&lt;/i&gt; ... helping me!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-finishhappy.png">Just don't try and touch it when I'm here okay!</state>
                <state img="#-finishsmug.png">I think I'll bring Kuroko next time, just to see her squirm at the site of a naked guy! hehe!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_large_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Whaa..!? I didn't think that they could be so... &lt;i&gt;big&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Is this an example of the Metamorphose ability!? Did you grow it to be &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; big just to try to impress everyone?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Woah... that's quite *gulp* ...big. Is this what they all talk about in the dorm at night?</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Woah!? This is even bigger than what Saten said... &lt;i&gt;Are they all like that?&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Woah!? That's so much... &lt;i&gt;bigger&lt;/i&gt; ...than I thought it would be. Ehh! I mean, d-don't point that at me!</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Whaaa!? B-but... How's it so big!? Are you &lt;i&gt;sure&lt;/i&gt; you're not using some kinda Esper ability here?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-mast1.png">Ahh! Th-that's so... &lt;i&gt;-hnnf-&lt;/i&gt; ...big! I think I m-might...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-finishembarrassed.png">Woah! That's kinda... huge. I didn't even think they could get that big.</state>
                <state img="#-finishshocked.png">Th-that's quite big, ~name~! I didn't know you were hiding &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; down there!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="nagisa" sayingMarker="nagisa_food_motivation" />
                <test expr="~target.position~" value="left" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="misaka_nagisa_food_motivation">Hey, Nagisa, why are you shouting out different names of food?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <condition role="target" character="nagisa" sayingMarker="nagisa_food_motivation" />
                <test expr="~target.position~" value="left" />
                <state img="#-finishconfused.png" marker="misaka_nagisa_food_motivation">I just don't get you, Nagisa... Why are you shouting out types of food?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-1">
                <state img="#-exclaiming.png">Can't you keep your clothes on!? At least for now...</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">At least it isn't me who has to do that...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-3">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">W-wait!? At least have some decency!</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">You're seriously just gonna get them out... like you're at home or something!?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-thumbsup.png">It should be okay if you keep them covered with your hands or something.</state>
                <state img="#-exclaiming.png">Wow... I don't know if I have the guts to show mine in a place like this.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Woah!? ~name~'s about to show her boobs!?</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Weird... Why do I &lt;i&gt;want&lt;/i&gt; to see ~name~'s boobs. Even though she's a girl...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-thumbsup.png">It's not as bad as you think, ~name~! You're not gonna be alone in this!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">We can both have them out, ~name~! It'll make me a little less embarrassed, at least!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-mast3.png">Thinking about ~name~'s boobs... &lt;i&gt;-hnng-&lt;/i&gt; ...w-why am saying this!?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-finishthumbsup.png">It's totally not that bad once you have them showing. You kinda get used to it after a while!</state>
                <state img="#-finishsmug.png">Hehe! I bet there's a lot of guys who'd do anything to get a look at what's going on here!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_small_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Heh! They're almost as small as Kuroko's! She's kinda... flat up there.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I don't mean to brag, but... mine are totally bigger!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-exclaiming.png">We all had small boobs at some point. Maybe you're still growing...?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">They look about Kuroko's size... kinda cute. &lt;i&gt;(Don't tell her I said that, okay?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Mine may be bigger, but don't let that bother you.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Hehe! I don't mind showing mine off now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-mast2.png">Wow... &lt;i&gt;-ufff-&lt;/i&gt; ... they're so cute, ~name~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-finishhappy.png">Even though they're kinda cute looking... I'm happy mine aren't that small.</state>
                <state img="#-finishthumbsup.png">Hey, ~name~! Kinda cute! Kuroko would probably spout off about how &lt;i&gt;"smaller is superior!"&lt;/i&gt;, though.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_medium_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="kyu" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Woah!? Kyu, you're using magic to strip!? I hope you know what you're doing...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <condition role="target" character="kyu" />
                <state img="#-finishsmug.png">Heh! Don't think you're gonna impress me with that!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Seriously!? You're showing them here... in front of everybody!</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">I caught a glimpse of Wannai's, from the swim team, last year at the swimming tournament... It seems girls do like to show them off, sometimes...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">Are they bigger than mine? I can't tell...</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">Seeing them out in a place like this is kinda weird. I'm used to seeing them in the showers after gym class.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-thumbsup.png">Hey, at least you're not the only one with them on show, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Hehe! Kuroko doesn't even know what she's missing! All these boobs on show!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-mast4.png">W-why do I feel... &lt;i&gt;hotter&lt;/i&gt; with ~name~'s b-boobs on show?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-finishhappy.png">It's okay, ~name~. At least you won't be the only one with them on show!</state>
                <state img="#-finishcalm.png">Hehe, just thinking that if this happened a lot earlier, I'd be totally embarrassed about it. I guess being nude does that to ya!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_large_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-angry.png">Why aren't mine that size...?</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">Ehhh!? They might actually be bigger than Shokuhou's... I wish she wouldn't flaunt them as much as she does.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-angry.png">Hey! Size isn't everything... ya know!</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">I get enough of this from Misaki Shokuhou, that stuck-up brat... I don't need you to show off your size, too!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-shy.png">Whaaa!? B-but... why aren't mine... Maybe the others'll be distracted.</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">Hey! Quit it would ya! Nobody likes a show-off!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-mast1.png">I j-just wish... &lt;i&gt;-uhhn-&lt;/i&gt; ... mine were as b-big as ~name~'s.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-finishdisappointed.png">Hey! Quit showing off! Just 'cause mine aren't that big doesn't mean you gotta put 'em on display!</state>
                <state img="#-finishdisappointed.png">Grrr! Those just remind me of Misaki... that stuck-up, little... Why are hers so much bigger? We're the same age...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-1">
                <state img="#-shocked.png">She's actually gonna show her... *gulp*... &lt;i&gt;parts&lt;/i&gt; in front of everyone?</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">I can't believe it! The "Legend of the Disrobing Woman"! I thought it was just an urban legend. I gotta tell my friend Saten about this!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-3">
                <state img="#-shy.png">If you've really gotta take off your ~clothing~...</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">You're removing your ~clothing~!? I feel like I'm in the bad area of District 17!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-shy.png">You're removing your ~clothing~! You can turn your back to us if you think it'll help!</state>
                <state img="#-exclaiming.png">If it's anything like the schools in Academy City, you kinda get used to showing your &lt;i&gt;parts&lt;/i&gt; to other girls in the changing rooms after class.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-calm.png">She's removing her ~clothing~? A girls gotta do what a girls gotta do!</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">Ooooh, I wonder if it looks like mine...ehehe!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-thumbsup.png">I know it can be a bit frightening at first, but I think you'll get used to it kinda quick!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Hey, it's totally fine! I mean, mine's out and I'm not that bothered by it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-mast3.png">S-she's taking off her ~clothing~!? Maybe s-she will... &lt;i&gt;-hnng-&lt;/i&gt; ...join me?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-finishhappy.png">It's kinda weird at first, what with other people watching, but you get used to it pretty quick.</state>
                <state img="#-finishthumbsup.png">You just gotta overcome your fear, ~name~. Think of it as a hurdle that you gotta jump over.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-shy.png">I-it's not like it's the first I've seen, but still...</state>
                <state img="#-exclaiming.png">I don't think I could just show myself like that. It takes serious guts to do that in front of others!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-exclaiming.png">I suppose if you stand a certain way then it kinda hides it, ya know.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Still... I can understand how it can be embarrassing. I'd probably feel the same way... hehe.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-exclaiming.png">Wow... that's actually kinda cute, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Hey, nice going ~name~! I promise I won't look &lt;i&gt;too&lt;/i&gt; much, okay?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-mast2.png">I'm seriously g-gonna be d-doing &lt;i&gt;this&lt;/i&gt; with... &lt;i&gt;-unnf-&lt;/i&gt; ...another girls p-parts on show!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-finishhappy.png">Hey, that's not so bad, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-finishcalm.png">You're looking good down there, ~name~! To think, they have specialist barbers in District 16 that work on your private parts!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_lost">
            <case stage="0" totalRounds="0" priority="500">
                <state img="#-shocked.png" oneShotId="3">Ehhh!? I didn't know we were playing &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; kind of poker! You mean we have to take off our... &lt;i&gt;*gulp*&lt;/i&gt; ...clothes, in p-public!?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8" id="9">
                <condition status="crotch_visible" role="target" character="chihiro" />
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">W-whaaa!? Chihiro, y-you're a guy!? To think that I was...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10" id="18">
                <condition role="target" character="chihiro" />
                <state img="#-finishshocked.png">Ehhh!? Chihiro!? Y-you were a guy this whole time!?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0-1">
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Hey! I-I didn't think &lt;i&gt;this&lt;/i&gt; was part of the game!</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">W-wait a sec, ~name~!? You're not gonna do what I think you're gonna do!?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-3">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">W-wait a sec...!? You're gonna start doing that... &lt;i&gt;here&lt;/i&gt;?</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Oh no... Isn't this the kinda thing you only do in private?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Hold on... Did you lose on purpose just so you could do... &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt;?</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">W-wait a sec!? That hand means you're... J-just don't think I'm gonna be interested, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-smug.png">That hand was pretty bad, ~name~! Now you gotta forfeit, right?</state>
                <state img="#-exclaiming.png">Wow, you definitely don't visit the arcade as much as I do, eh! That hand was the end of you!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-shocked.png">~name~ has to...&lt;i&gt;m-masturbate&lt;/i&gt;, right!? It was almost me this round...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">W-wait!? ~name~ has to masturbate!? I... well, uhh ...I'm kinda intrigued by this.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-mast1.png">Those cards... &lt;i&gt;-ufff-&lt;/i&gt; ... that m-means you gotta... you know...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-finishsmug.png">It's totally not your day, ~name~! Now you gotta do... &lt;i&gt;you know&lt;/i&gt;..!</state>
                <state img="#-finishembarrassed.png">I wonder if my... uhh ...&lt;i&gt;performance&lt;/i&gt; earlier has gotten you ready...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-shocked.png">You're totally gonna do that here... in front of all of us!?</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">I don't think I can even look...</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">School studies didn't really go into detail about how guys do it... I don't even think I wanna know!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-shy.png">Wow... uhh... I guess he was ready for it.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Is ~name~ not bothered that we're stood here? Even if we &lt;i&gt;are&lt;/i&gt; all friends.</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Woah! ~name~'s really gonna do it!? B-but I'm stood right next to him...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">J-just make sure you don't s-stare at me too much, okay...</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">I-I'll let you look at me for a bit... if you w-wanna. Not too long, okay!</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">I thought I'd never want to see guys do this kinda thing... But... I kinda wanna see ~name~ do it now...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-mast3.png">It's t-totally weird h-having a guy... &lt;i&gt;-uhhn-&lt;/i&gt; ...do &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; with me.</state>
                <state img="#-mast4.png">Woah, ~name~'s so &lt;i&gt;s-stiff&lt;/i&gt;... &lt;i&gt;-unnf-&lt;/i&gt; ...already!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-finishembarrassed.png">I think ~name~ was totally watching me earlier, he's so... &lt;i&gt;stiff&lt;/i&gt;... already!</state>
                <state img="#-finishexcited.png">I wonder if ~name~ has the guts to do this!</state>
                <state img="#-finishembarrassed.png">I... uhh...don't mind if you use my body to help you out, okay?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-1">
                <state img="#-angry.png">Pipe down would you! It's... distracting...</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">Enough with it already! You don't have to make a big deal outta this!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-3">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Gah!... I hope ~name~ isn't looking at me...!</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">I swear... you'd better not be looking at me! You're gonna get electrocuted if you are!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-shy.png">I really don't think I should be staring...</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">If ~name~ looks at me whilst he's doing &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt;, I'm gonna give him a li'l shock...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">A-are you looking at me!? I-I'm not even fully naked yet!</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Wow... So this is what it looks like when guys do it...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Standing here naked, whilst ~name~'s doing &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt;. It's kinda making me feel a bit... wet.</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">The others said that the sight of a naked body can help you, so... if you wanna look at mine... you can ...uhh...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-mast2.png">He's seriously g-getting... &lt;i&gt;-hnng-&lt;/i&gt; ...in to it!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-finishshocked.png">Woah!? He's really getting in to it...</state>
                <state img="#-finishshocked.png">~name~'s not even getting tired! He has so much stamina!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Whaa!? Why's it so sticky?</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">Keep that... &lt;i&gt;stuff&lt;/i&gt; away from me!</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">I've only ever heard about this sorta stuff. Seeing it happen right in front of me is kinda... weird.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">I didn't think it'd be so... messy!</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Whaa!? Why is there so much of it!?</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Woah!? It's exactly as Saten described... Where does she get this information from...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Oh wow... he must've really enjoyed doing it.</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Wow... that's quite a lot of... &lt;i&gt;stuff&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Is this what Saten meant by &lt;i&gt;`creamy, white stuff'&lt;/i&gt;?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-mast1.png">Woah!? There's s-so much...</state>
                <state img="#-mast4.png">I c-cant let a guy f-finish before me... &lt;i&gt;-hnnf-&lt;/i&gt; ... even doing &lt;i&gt;this&lt;/i&gt;!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-finishcalm.png">Hey! Don't get any of that... &lt;i&gt;stuff&lt;/i&gt;... near me!</state>
                <state img="#-finishhappy.png">Wow... you must have seriously wanted to do that!?</state>
                <state img="#-finishshocked.png">Woah! Just wait until I tell Saten about this!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="shimakaze" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Woah!? Shimakaze, that one looked like it was serious!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <condition role="target" character="shimakaze" />
                <state img="#-finishhappy.png">Ouch... Shimakaze, that one looked like it hurt.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-1">
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Wait, what are you...!? I didn't think we'd be doing &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt;!</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Waah!? Isn't that something you'd only wanna do in private!? Not here, in front of everyone!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-3">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">I think ~name~ is about to.... I don't even wanna think about it!</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">Waah!? You're gonna... uhhh... Don't you wanna do it in private?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Hey ~name~, you gotta forfeit! It can't be too bad, right?</state>
                <state img="#-thumbsup.png">So, you gotta forfeit, huh? I think, if you just go for it then it shouldn't be too big a deal.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-smug.png">That hand has gotta be the worst! You know what comes next, right...?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Maybe after this I'll show you my high-score at the poker machine. Give you some tips, hehe!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-confused.png">So, ~name~'s gotta &lt;i&gt;m-masturbate&lt;/i&gt;!? I might learn somethin' if she's going before me...</state>
                <state img="#-pondering.png">Woah!? It's a good job I read that book Uiharu left out that night. Hmm... Why did she have a book like that, anyway...?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-mast3.png">That hand means... &lt;i&gt;-ufff-&lt;/i&gt; ... that you g-gotta start... &lt;i&gt;y-you know&lt;/i&gt;...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-finishsmug.png">That's a seriously bad hand, ~name~! Now you gotta... &lt;i&gt;you know&lt;/i&gt;..!</state>
                <state img="#-finishembarrassed.png">I kinda wanna see ~name~ have to do what I just did. I wonder if my &lt;i&gt;performance&lt;/i&gt; encouraged her in any way?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="nagisa" saidMarker="nagisa_play" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">Nagisa... are you reciting a play? W-whilst you're doing... &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt;?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <condition role="target" character="nagisa" saidMarker="nagisa_play" />
                <state img="#-finishconfused.png">H-hey, Nagisa? Are you... reciting a play? Hey, if it helps you get through this then I'm all for it!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="hermione" />
                <state img="#-pondering.png">Woah!? Hermione, this isn't like the magic I'm used to...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="uravity" />
                <state img="#-pondering.png">Hey, Ochako. Are you some kind of Esper? I think I read about this in the Database somewhere...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <condition role="target" character="catria" />
                <state img="#-finishhappy.png">A chair, huh. Why didn't I think of that...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <condition role="target" character="hermione" />
                <state img="#-finishshocked.png">Woah, Hermione!? This isn't like the magic that I usually deal with...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <condition role="target" character="uravity" />
                <state img="#-finishconfused.png">Hey, Ochako? Is that some kinda Esper ability? I might have studied this at Tokiwadai.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Waah... you're crazy!</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">Why are you doing that!? What is with this woman!?</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">You're seriously doing that here!? If you know the Dummy Check ability, you can hide yourself from others. Might make it less embarrassing!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Wow... ~name~'s actually gonna do it!</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">Ehh!? ~name~'s looking kinda wet down... &lt;i&gt;there&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">Woah!? ...I'm kinda glad Kuroko isn't here to see this. It'd be way too awkward...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Wow, it's glistening down there! She must really be in to this!</state>
                <state img="#-pondering.png">Hmm... I wonder if ~name~ is turned on by my nakedness?</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">I can't help but look... Is this what Kuroko feels like whenever I get out the shower?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-mast1.png">H-hey ~name~! Let's do it t-together!</state>
                <state img="#-mast4.png">It's n-not so bad once y-you start... &lt;i&gt;-hnnf-&lt;/i&gt; ... doing it!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-finishthumbsup.png">I was kinda nervous at first, but you get used to it pretty quickly.</state>
                <state img="#-finishhappy.png">I think ~name~ watching me earlier might have gotten her totally wet!</state>
                <state img="#-finishsmug.png">Hehe, Uiharu would totally have bottled it she had to do this!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="hermione" />
                <state img="#-pondering.png" oneShotId="142">Actually... This could be a new kind of Esper ability. I don't recall seeing anything like this in the Database.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <condition role="target" character="hermione" />
                <state img="#-finishconfused.png" oneShotId="144">Actually... It seems similar to certain types of Esper abilities. I'm not entirely sure...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-1">
                <state img="#-shy.png">Do you really have to make those sounds!?</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">This is kinda embarrassing... standing here whilst she's doing... &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-3">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Well... uhh... she definitely looks like she's enjoying herself.</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">Is this what my friends are always teasing me about...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-shy.png">Is it really this much fun? I've only done it a few times so...</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Yeah... I'm really glad Kuroko isn't here. You should consider yourself lucky, ~name~...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-shy.png">Wow... she's really got... Ehh!? I-I shouldn't even be thinking th-things like that!</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">To be in the same room when someone else is doing &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt;! It's kinda making me feel a little excited...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-horny.png">She's so excited! It might, be my turn next. I'm kinda looking forward to it...</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">Wow! I could add a little bit of electricity to help you out if ya want... I hear it can be stimulating.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-mast2.png">Wow... she's totally... &lt;i&gt;-hnng-&lt;/i&gt; ...g-getting in to it!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-finishembarrassed.png">Did I seriously make those kinda sounds when I was doing... &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt;!?</state>
                <state img="#-finishshocked.png">Woah! ~name~'s really getting in to it! I might have to copy her technique...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition count="0" filter="nagisa_maid_cafe" />
                <condition role="target" character="nagisa" saidMarker="nagisa_play" sayingMarker="nagisa_finished_1" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">Okay...? I just don't get you, Nagisa...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <condition count="0" filter="nagisa_maid_cafe" />
                <condition role="target" character="nagisa" saidMarker="nagisa_play" sayingMarker="nagisa_finished_1" />
                <state img="#-finishconfused.png">I think the play talk kinda helped, don'tcha think?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="shimakaze" sayingMarker="rencatch" />
                <state img="#-exclaiming.png">Ohhh! So that's where your cute robot went to...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <condition role="target" character="shimakaze" sayingMarker="rencatch" />
                <state img="#-finishhappy.png">Yay! Your cute robot is back!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="videl" />
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Waaah!? Videl, I didn't think girls could make &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; kinda... mess!?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <condition role="target" character="videl" />
                <state img="#-finishshocked.png">Woah!? Videl! Th-that's quite a lot of... Uhhh... &lt;i&gt;stuff&lt;/i&gt;...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Wow... she's so loud.</state>
                <state img="#-pondering.png">Hmmm... she looks like she had a great time. I wonder if I have to do that...</state>
                <state img="#-pondering.png">I wonder what it'd feel like if I use my electromaster abilities... I might try that if it comes to it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Whaa!? She's even wetter than before...</state>
                <state img="#-exclaiming.png">Woah ~name~, that looked intense! &lt;i&gt;(I... uhh... kinda don't mind losing now)&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">That website kinda downplayed this a bit... It looks a lot more &lt;i&gt;fun&lt;/i&gt; in person.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-angry.png">Woah!? Does doing &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; in front of others really make that big a difference?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Ya know... I hope mine is as good as that...</state>
                <state img="#-pondering.png">It's exactly like in that magazine Saten brought round. Where does she find this stuff...?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-mast4.png">I'm-I'm not that... &lt;i&gt;-Oooh-&lt;/i&gt; ... far behind!</state>
                <state img="#-mast1.png">Woah!? will I s-sound like that?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-finishshocked.png">Woah!? Is she just tryin' to show off or what?</state>
                <state img="#-finishthumbsup.png">There we go! See, it wasn't too bad, right?</state>
                <state img="#-finishcalm.png">Oh wow... ~name~ looked like she really enjoyed doing that. I gotta try this with the others, sometime...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate_first">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">W-w-wait a sec!? B-but I was doing so well!? Does that mean I gotta...!?</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Woah, wait a sec!? I don't know if I can even do this here... It's kinda weird with you all watching me...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">W-wait!? I lost!? Does this mean I also have to... &lt;i&gt;you know&lt;/i&gt; ...do &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt;?</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Eeeeh! Now it's &lt;i&gt;my&lt;/i&gt; turn to... masturbate!? I kinda feel better that others have gone before me...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="start_masturbating">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-maststart.png">J-just don't stare at me too much, okay.</state>
                <state img="#-maststart.png">I-I can't believe I'm doing this in front of other people!</state>
                <state img="#-maststart.png">If I remember from what Saten told me... I do &lt;i&gt;this&lt;/i&gt;... right?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="masturbating">
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-mast3.png">It kinda &lt;i&gt;does&lt;/i&gt; feel better when others are watching...</state>
                <state img="#-mast4.png">&lt;i&gt;-Hnnn-&lt;/i&gt; H-hey... quit s-staring!</state>
                <state img="#-mast2.png">It's so wet... it's conducting my &lt;i&gt;-uhnn-&lt;/i&gt; electrical impulses.</state>
                <state img="#-mast1.png">I s-seriously can't believe I'm actually d-doing this...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="heavy_masturbating">
            <case stage="9" id="19">
                <state img="#-mastheavy1.png">&lt;i&gt;-hnnnnnnnnn-&lt;/i&gt; Oh wow... I gotta be close...</state>
                <state img="#-mastheavy2.png">&lt;i&gt;-hnnnff-&lt;/i&gt; This has gotta be it... I'm almost at climax!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finishing_masturbating">
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-finish.png">&lt;i&gt;Ahhh! Ohhhhh! Hhhhnnnnngggg!&lt;/i&gt; I-I-I'm..!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-afterfinish.png">Oh wow..! That was so intense..!</state>
                <state img="#-afterfinish.png">Woah! I d-didn't mean to uninhibit myself like that...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_victory">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-excited.png">Hah! I won! ...and I didn't even have to strip!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">That was it? I barely did &lt;i&gt;anything&lt;/i&gt; and yet I still won!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-excited.png">Hah! I won and all I had to do was take off my shoes!</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">Ya know, I kinda feel bad just losing my shoes, but... I won, soooo... yay!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-excited.png">Take that! I won with just my bare feet showing!</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">Whew! I only removed what I would have back home! Good times!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-excited.png">Alright! I won &lt;i&gt;and&lt;/i&gt; I got to keep most of my clothes on!</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">I only lost the stuff I woulda taken off at home anyway! So... yeah!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-excited.png">Yeah! This was actually kinda fun! I might play this with Saten and the others...</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">Wow... I almost had to show my underwear. I still managed to win, though!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-excited.png">Alright! I won! Ya know, this was better than I expected!</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">Nice! I won! I shoulda invited Uiharu and the others to join us, too!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-excited.png">Well, you got to see me in my underwear, but at least I still won!</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">Hehe, you &lt;i&gt;almost&lt;/i&gt; got to see my private parts! Maybe next time, if you want to play together again!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-excited.png">I was real close to getting completely naked, but I won just in time!</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Woah, I won!? I was &lt;i&gt;this&lt;/i&gt; close to getting fully nude!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-shy.png">I won? That was a close one! I almost had to... &lt;i&gt;you know&lt;/i&gt;...</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">Even though I'm totally naked, I still had a great time!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_defeat">
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-finishhappy.png">You know, even though I lost, this was much better than I expected!</state>
                <state img="#-finishhappy.png">Even though I lost, I had a great time meeting everyone and making new friends!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

    </behaviour>
</opponent>
