<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>

<!--This file was machine generated using the Character Editor v6.7.7 at 6:01:41 a. m. on agosto 21, 2022. Do not edit this file directly unless you know what you're doing.-->
<opponent>
    <version>v6.7.7</version>
    <first>Bowsette</first>
    <last />
    <label>Bowsette</label>
    <gender>female</gender>
    <size>large</size>
    <timer>20</timer>
    <intelligence>best</intelligence>

    <intelligence stage="1">average</intelligence>



    <wardrobe>
        <clothing name="bands" position="arms" type="extra" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="panties" position="lower" type="important" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="top" position="upper" type="major" />
        <clothing name="stockings" position="legs" type="minor" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="shoes" position="feet" type="extra" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="earrings" position="head" type="extra" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="skirt" position="lower" type="major" />
    </wardrobe>


    <behaviour>
        <trigger id="selected">
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~background~" value="mansion" />
                <state img="#-resigned.png">Hey, is this Luigi's Mansion? I'm NOT doing any vacuuming, just so you're aware. That is by far the worst kind of sucking.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Bwa ha ha! Think you can take the Koopa Queen?!</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">For your own safety, I advise you &lt;i&gt;don't&lt;/i&gt; touch this crown on my head. Unless you're into that, of course.</state>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">You hesitated for a couple of seconds before picking me, didn't you? Don't worry, ~player~, it's not gay if the crown stays on.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">You'd be surprised how good the Koopas are at Poker. Bring it on!</state>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">You know, conquering the Mushroom Kingdom was getting old. I'm down to try something new.</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">You're challenging me? You're not scared? I say you should be...</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">So you wanna play with fire? Hope you're ready to get burned! </state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Get ready to bow down to your queen! Especially you, ~player~~!</state>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">Like the crown? Well, good news, chumps -- it ain't goin' anywhere!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">GWAHAHA! Oh, this'll be easy -- I beat Mario at Go Fish all the time!</state>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">Bwahaha! We all know you chose me for these gigantic Koopa cannons, but are you game enough to see them?</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Bwahaha! Are you ready to expose yourself for the great Queen Koopa's enjoyment, peasants?</state>
                <state img="#-resigned.png">C'mon, what's the holdup? I'm a busy guy -- er, gal. (Blasted crown...)</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Bwahaha! The Queen has arrived, peasants!</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">This place has a funky energy in the air, and it's crawling with all sorts of weirdos... Gwahaha! This is my kind of place! I'll show these losers who's Queen around here!</state>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">Hello, pipsqueaks! Surprised by my NEW LOOK? BWAHAHA!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Let me guess -- I stumbled into a magic painting? Yeah... "Clods Playing Poker" or some crud like that!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Make it quick, why don'tcha? I got golf to play and a son to raise! </state>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">No red capped italian plumber here? Looks like I finally got a chance to win for once!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition count="3-4" role="opp" />
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Don't even think about starting without me! You're all about to feel Bowsette's Rampage!</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Don't even think about starting without me! You're all about to feel Bowser's... I mean, Bowsette's Rampage!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_selected">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="peach" />
                <state img="#-cocky.png" marker="bowsette_peach_reclaim_crown">Bwahahaha! Come to reclaim your crown, &lt;i&gt;princess&lt;/i&gt;?</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="bowsette_peach_diary">&lt;i&gt;(Ah, crud -- Peach is here!  I wonder if she still remembers what I wrote in my diary...  That was pretty embarrassing.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png" marker="bowsette_peach_body">Well well well, Princess! Like this new body of mine, or should I say, &lt;i&gt;yours&lt;/i&gt;?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="futaba" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="bowsette_futaba_inkstain">Ah, CRUD! I thought I could get away from the idiots from Smash Bros here... Oh wait. You're not the ink stain.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" marker="bowsette_futaba_woomy">Oh no, I'm not going through the trouble of cleaning this dress because of that ink of yours! ...Wait a minute, you're not one of them.  </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="italian" role="target" />
                <state img="#-resigned.png">I've never trusted Italians... Not since that pesky plumber kept getting in my way.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" oneShotId="938">
                <condition filter="sonic_franchise" role="target" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">Hey! I know you from somewhere, right?&lt;br&gt;... Yeah! The Olympic Games!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" oneShotId="939">
                <condition filter="princess" role="target" />
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">I'm not planning on kidnapping any princesses to~background.time~, bwahaha! Let's just enjoy ourselves this time!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="prince" role="target" />
                <state img="#-resigned.png">... Should I try to kidnap princes now? Is that how it works? I'll have to think about that.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_start">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="joey" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Who are you supposed to be, Mrs. Frilly Pants? You gonna tie me a balloon animal?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="felicia" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="bowsette_felicia_cat">Whoa, what the heck is wrong with her? Didja pick up a half-busted Lucky Bell, lady?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="jason" />
                <state img="#-angry.png">So that's how Shy Gals look behind their masks... What? I never asked before! I thought it was a religious thing or something!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="susie" />
                <state img="#-resigned.png">Since when do Shy Gals... talk? And what's up with her mask? It's all messed up!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~background~" value="hot spring" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">Oh, wow! A hot spring! I haven't been to one in YEARS. Couldn't enjoy the last time either, thanks to a certain plumber and his friggin' water gun.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~background~" value="mansion" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png">Oh wow, Luigi's really cleaned this place up nicely. Guess he's good for something after all!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~background~" value="haunted forest" />
                <state img="#-resigned.png">I'm all for haunting gothic architecture and scenery, but would it not make more sense to play this game INDOORS?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="magic" role="other" var="magician" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png">A magic user? Say, ~magician~, would you like a job as my assistant? Kammy and Kamek didn't want to come for whatever reason.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="royalty" role="other" />
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Hello, there... The princess I'm looking for is in another castle, but you'll do just fine.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">Like I'm gonna pass up a chance to show off this killer new bod.</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Don't get the wrong idea; I might look frail and dainty, but I'm still tough as I always am!</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">I've lost for 35 years by this point, so if that luck keeps up with me here, don't expect me to take losing well!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Prepare to get demolished by the Great Bowser! &lt;br&gt; &lt;i&gt;(Or... Bowsette? I guess?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">It's everybody's favorite time -- BOWSER TIME!</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Koopa royalty doesn't go down easy, ya know. I hope you're all ready for one heck of a challenge.</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">No backing out now! You've got to face the ferocious Princess Koopa!</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Let's get this Mario Party started!</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Prepare for a bitter defeat at the hands of Queen Bowsette!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Alright, where are the Uno cards? &lt;br&gt; ...Poker? Great! I suck at Uno anyway.</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Pay your respects to me, Bowser, er... Bowsette! King... no, Queen of the Koopas! Anyone who doesn't will receive a kick to the face!</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Time to show you punks why I'm the king -- er, I mean QUEEN of the castle!</state>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">Yep, it's ME! Didn't expect to see your majesty like THIS, did you? It's all thanks to this crown!</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">No backing out now! This should be fun!</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Bwahahaha! You call THIS a party? Bowser is here to shake things up! Okay, dimwits, just try to shine!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Name's Bowser, chumps. But you can call me Bowsette, Princess Koopa or King Koopa. I'm the whole royal family, so I expect some royal flushes! Bwahaha!</state>
                <state img="#-resigned.png">This better be quick -- I have a kingdom to run! ...Or is it a "queendom" now?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="swap_cards">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Blue shell, please.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Can I swap half an ace?</state>
                <state img="#-resigned.png">Give me ~cards.text~ ~cards.ifplural(cards|card)~.</state>
                <state img="#-resigned.png">Hmm... I'll take ~cards.text~ ~cards.ifplural(cards|card)~.</state>
                <state img="#-resigned.png">Gimme ~cards.text~ card, I guess? Whatever's good.</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">BWAH! Anything but these!</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">~Cards.text~ cards. Let's see what I'm working with...</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Bwahahahaha! Now I can go for Kings and Queens alike!</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Let's see... Kammy always switches these, so...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-4">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Whuzzat? No, I'm not changing my cards. Your... eyes must be playing tricks on you! Yeah.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Swap these.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Take these.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">I don't know, but I usually have better hands when I play with Kamek and the troops.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Just give me some cards.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">C'mon! C'mon! I don't want to masturbate in front of these losers!</state>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">How d'ya like these Koopa Shells? Do they... make your Goombas rise? Makes sense I breathe fire since I'm so hot! &lt;i&gt;(...Okay, I gotta work on my pickup lines if I want to sell this schtick.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Let's go with these, then...</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">Here. Give it. HURRY IT UP.</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Whatever, dealer. We all know I'll &lt;i&gt;somehow&lt;/i&gt; end up with the right hand.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">These better be darn good...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-angry.png">~Cards.text~. And they better be the &lt;i&gt;right&lt;/i&gt; ones, capiche, Dealer?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-resigned.png">~Cards.text~? Is that a good number?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="good_hand">
            <case stage="1-4" oneShotId="280">
                <alternative>
                    <condition role="other" character="lucina" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <condition role="other" character="tharja" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="bowsette_strategists">Ha! You expect me to be intimidated by these Fire Imbeciles? Most ''strategists'' choose Tiki, Severa, or Sumia... or something.</state>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">Sorry chumps! Looks like I'm the REAL fire emblem here! &lt;i&gt;(Or whatever a "fire emblem" is...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="32" oneShotId="616">
                <condition role="other" character="spooky" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">Hey, Spooky! Since you have an army of ghosts and stuff, how'd you like to join &lt;i&gt;my&lt;/i&gt; army? I got ghosts, too. A whole legion of 'em!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5" oneShotId="543" priority="1">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Thanks, dealer! Maybe I won't roast you today after all.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">Gaze upon your glorious ruler, my subjects!</state>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">Think you got a handle on me, ~player~? Yeah, well, looks can be deceiving when Koopas are involved...</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Yeah, come to Koopa!</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Now you'll see why I oh-so-modestly call myself a genius.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Now this is a hand fit for a king! Or a queen! Or whatever my title's supposed to be!</state>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">This is easier than talkin' Wendy into a shopping spree!</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png" oneShotId="39">{small}...When was I this good at cards...?{!reset}&lt;br&gt; I mean... YEAH as EXPECTED, I'm amazing at cards!</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Gyeheheh... Not even a SUPER STAR could beat me with THIS hand!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Hah! Only fitting for the Koopa Queen herself! &lt;i&gt;(Got it right this time!)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Hah! Only fitting for the Koopa King-! Erm, Queen, herself!</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">Hah! Only fitting for the Koopa King-! Erm, Queen, himsel-! Oh forget it! You get the point!</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Hah! Only fitting for the Koopa Queen himself-! I mean, herself! &lt;i&gt;(Darn it! You were so close too!)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">I need to set a good example for my son. Make sure he knows that he's always a winner so long as he works hard and cheats his tail off.</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Even a Goomba could win with this hand. And they've got no hands at all!</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">I haven't done anything really rotten in a long time. Not since yesterday. This is a totally depraved, evil, insidious game. Perfectly fit for King Koopa.</state>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">Hah! I'm hopin' you weren't lookin' forward to seeing these bad boys anytime soon...</state>
                <state img="#-surprise.png">What a lovely tribute, dealer! I'm usually stealing nice things, not receiving them!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Looks like I'm starting off strong!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Oh sure! I get good cards once I show off my breasts! ...I-I mean, not like it's a complaint or anything, dealer! {small}&lt;i&gt;Please don't give me a bad hand...&lt;/i&gt;{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Bweheheh... Yep, this is EXACTLY what it feels like to get a Blue Shell!</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Well, well, well, Dealer. You finally recognize me as your Queen, don't you?</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Bwahaha... Is that a Blue Shell alarm I hear, or is that just my cards?</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">It looks like these cards finally recognize a king when they see it... Or a queen. Or both.</state>
                <state img="#-rage.png">GRRR! Where was this hand a couple of rounds ago!?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-4">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Heh! Looks like things are going my way for once!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Where I come from, star power makes you &lt;i&gt;invincible&lt;/i&gt;!</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">You'd better hope you've got a BRIDGE and an AXE hidden in that hand. Bwa ha ha ha! &lt;br&gt;{small}&lt;i&gt;...Yeah, that works!&lt;/i&gt;{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">After I win this game, you should all come to my castle. I could always use more &lt;i&gt;footstools&lt;/i&gt;!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Bwa ha ha! I thought you should know that my other losses don't count! The real game starts now!</state>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">Gwaha! You should just give up now!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="okay_hand">
            <case stage="0" id="6" oneShotId="6" totalRounds="5-">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Who wants to go karting after this? Should I wear the dress or rock a full bodysuit instead?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-4">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">My castles don't have much running water... Plumbers are too much of a pain in the rear to work with.</state>
                <state img="#-resigned.png">...The &lt;i&gt;heck&lt;/i&gt; do I do with these?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Since I've changed my name already, I think you should all start calling me &lt;i&gt;The&lt;/i&gt; Bowsette! If you do, I &lt;i&gt;might&lt;/i&gt; go easy on you after I win.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Well, mediocre is better than bad, at least!</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Bwah! I've kidnapped princesses with troops less bright than these cards! I can still come out on top.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Meh. At least with karting, I know whether I'm in the lead or not- and adjust my cheating accordingly.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Why aren't we playing at &lt;i&gt;my&lt;/i&gt; casino? I'd be getting better hands there!</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Tch... Bet you scrubs ALL have worse cards than mine.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Should I still announce my next victory as the Great Koopa &lt;i&gt;King?&lt;/i&gt;Or is it Queen? Meh, I'll just go with what feels right.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I think I'll send Mario through a poker-themed world next time! Let's see him try and get through THAT one!</state>
                <state img="#-resigned.png">Average... Not planning on losing, though.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-5">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">...This is the Luigi of hands.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">It takes a feared ruler to keep a kingdom in order, ya know! My demeanor is not without reason.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">This might be the end of my reign of terror... Tch!</state>
                <state img="#-resigned.png">...Well! I can only HOPE this is enough.</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">YEAH. My hand is GREAT. A real CONFIDENCE BOOSTER in my TIME OF NEED.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png"></state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="bad_hand">
            <case stage="5-7">
                <condition role="self" consecutiveLosses="2-" />
                <state img="#-rage.png">Is this deck &lt;i&gt;rigged&lt;/i&gt; or something!? This is NOT FAIR!</state>
                <state img="#-rage.png">Oh you are JOKING ME! Dealer, you wanna get grilled, baked, or incinerated tonight?! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7" oneShotId="936">
                <test expr="~background.location~" value="indoors" />
                <state img="#-rage.png">&lt;i&gt;Dealer.&lt;/i&gt; Need I remind you, I am a &lt;i&gt;fire-breather&lt;/i&gt;. I could burn this place to the ground if I desire, &lt;i&gt;so help me Koopa God&lt;/i&gt; -- so give me some &lt;i&gt;good friggin' cards next time&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-angry.png">Do you want to feel the might of my Koopa Army, dealer!?</state>
                <state img="#-rage.png">These cards are flammable, right?</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">Do ya really think a Koopa of MY cunning is gonna lose? How DARE you?</state>
                <state img="#-rage.png">You'd better hope these cards are flame retardant!</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">...Roasted dealer, coming right up!</state>
                <state img="#-rage.png">Keep on giving me hands like these and I'll throw you in the deepest, draftiest dungeon I've got, Dealer!</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">UGH.  These cards are weak.  This TABLE is weak. Everyone in here is weak, weak, WEAK!</state>
                <state img="#-surprise.png">Bwah...?! Crud, this is looking worse than an incoming Blue Shell!</state>
                <state img="#-rage.png">Dealer, if you &lt;i&gt;wanted&lt;/i&gt; to see me naked, why don't you just ASK instead of bending me over a Kong-sized barrel?!</state>
                <state img="#-rage.png">Dealer... I’ll burn you so hard your &lt;i&gt;grandkids&lt;/i&gt; are gonna come out crispy!</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">I'll get you for this, dealer!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-angry.png">Drat! If I wanted to feel like a fool, I'd have played checkers with that ape Donkey Kong... At least then I wouldn't have to stand around in next to nothing!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-rage.png">Y'know, Dealer, Mario isn't the only one who can give you a ground pound!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">One bad hand won’t be enough for a game over as long as you have enough lives!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Ha! I'd always win against my underlings, even with hands this garbage!</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">Hey, what gives?! Didn't I tell you to stack the deck in MY favor?</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">This better be some dumb coincidence and not a bad omen!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-4">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">...Grrr.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-rage.png">I think the dealer slipped me a poison mushroom!</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">&lt;i&gt;(What's the one thing most likely to rot my opponents' minds and reduce their brains to mashed potatoes?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-rage.png">These cards are a lot of toadstool, Dealer! Want me to jump on your head or somethin'?</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Meh, WHATEVER! I just have to have a better hand than any of you chumps to win!</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">I am the King of the Koopas! You DARE serve me these cards, Dealer!?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-6">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">I was hoping my new look would sway the dealer, but I guess I’ll have to come up with another plan!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Garbage hand. Though it IS the early stages, so I guess it's only fair.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-angry.png">I &lt;i&gt;knew&lt;/i&gt; I should've cheated for this hand... I &lt;i&gt;knew&lt;/i&gt; it!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-7">
                <state img="#-rage.png">Words cannot even DESCRIBE the absolute ruin I shall bring upon THESE BLASTED CARDS!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="48" oneShotId="806" hidden="1">
                <state img="#-resigned.png">Hey, is Junior playing within the time limit...?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="hand">
            <case stage="0-7" id="29" oneShotId="625">
                <condition role="other" character="spooky" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-resigned.png">I thought only noble, blue-blooded Boos could get their own haunted mansions and private armies. How did a human ghost your age get your own?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="25" oneShotId="599">
                <condition role="other" character="pinkie_pie" timeInStage="2" saidMarker="pinka_start" notSaidMarker="pinka_end2" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Okay... I think Pinkamena is starting to scare me. J-just a little bit.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="812">
                <condition role="other" character="polly" sayingMarker="Booze-ette1" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" marker="Booze-ette2">Well, if we weren't aiming for a kid-friendly audience, it'd probably be "Boo-ze."</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="27" oneShotId="624">
                <condition role="other" character="pinkie_pie" saidMarker="pinka_end2" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">Whew! Pinkie's back to her normal, annoyingly perky self.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="8" oneShotId="8">
                <condition role="other" character="peach" />
                <state img="#-resigned.png">&lt;i&gt;(I can't believe Peach would pick a chubby little Italian plumber over me... He wears raccoon pajamas, for pete's sake! Maybe she'd be willing to give THIS body a try...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="10" oneShotId="267">
                <condition role="other" character="marceline" />
                <state img="#-flaunt.png" marker="bowsette_marceline_flame_princess">I met your Flame Princess, Marceline. She's hot, but not as hot as me! Literally, and figuratively!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="7" oneShotId="7">
                <test expr="~background~" value="beach" />
                <state img="#-cocky.png">There are some great go-karting shortcuts on this beach. Too bad I'm not telling you where they are! Bwahaha!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" oneShotId="940">
                <test expr="~background.location~" value="outdoors" />
                <state img="#-cocky.png" dialogue-layer="over">There's plenty of space around here! No underground poker clubs, no tight bedrooms or fragile libraries... I could easily take off my crown here!</state>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png" dialogue-layer="over">Are you enjoying my new body, ~player~? You better keep me in a good mood. In an open space like this, I could take off my crown at any time.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~background~" value="birthday backyard" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" dialogue-layer="over">So, whose party is this? Call me up next time. I know a Koopa who can get you good deals on balloons, and a certain torte who can make some AMAZING cakes!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" id="30" oneShotId="287">
                <condition filter="artist" role="other" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">I've always had a passing interest in art. It &lt;i&gt;is&lt;/i&gt; one of my son's favorite hobbies, after all!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4" id="1" oneShotId="1">
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">Look at ~player~ getting lost in my cleavage... Obviously I'm not the &lt;i&gt;only&lt;/i&gt; one with a lizard brain here!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="103">You know, despite being able to breathe fire, I'm not actually fireproof. It's kind of ironic, really.&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;(Blasted fire flowers...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="102">When I first put this crown on, I worried I might suddenly become attracted to Italian men, but nope! I'm still really into blonde chicks.</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png" oneShotId="104" dialogue-layer="over">I hope Junior's okay. Kamek is a good sitter, but he always lets him play beyond his time limit! I don't want him to grow up to be a teenager spewing nonsense on the internet!</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" oneShotId="105" dialogue-layer="over" font-size="small">Don't tell ANYONE I said this, but... As much as I care for my subjects, it's nice to finally go out somewhere where you're not calling the shots since you were a baby for once.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="31" oneShotId="65">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" marker="bowsette_koopaling_seaside">If the Koopalings call, tell them I'm on vacation at Seaside Kingdom.</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png" marker="bowsette_no_game">So, are we gonna play a minigame or something? ...Wait, there isn't any? Drat! No wonder they cut that "no game" mode outta the first game!</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png" marker="bowsette_animal_crossing_party">What do you mean we aren't playing minigames between rounds?! Have you &lt;i&gt;seen&lt;/i&gt; how boring that Animal Crossing party game was?!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">Humans are &lt;i&gt;so&lt;/i&gt; last century. Reptiles are where it's at!</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">What do you mean, "I can't remove the crown?!" It's a piece of clothing! You're all just cowards! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="14" oneShotId="472">
                <state img="#-flaunt.png" dialogue-layer="over">Come to think of it, Junior will finally get the mother he always wanted...but then he doesn't have a father anymore... Oh, what am I saying? I can do both! I'm no chump!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Ah, feel the freedom! There's nothing quite like reminding yourself of why clothes are for suckers!</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">On one hand, this is much better than having to wear that dumb dress! ...But on the other hand, I'm losing.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Yeah yeah, I walk around nude 24/7 without this crown, but losing isn't fun! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4" oneShotId="941" priority="0">
                <condition status="not_decent" role="opp" character="human" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">Why are you looking at me, ~player~? You should be looking at your cards, since you're losing so badly already!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" oneShotId="942" priority="0">
                <test expr="~background~" value="throne room" />
                <state img="#-resigned.png" dialogue-layer="over">This ~background~ could use some changes... It's too bright, there's not enough candles or lava lakes, and don't get me started on the color scheme...</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png" dialogue-layer="over">You call this a ~background~? Who could fit in that tiny throne? Where is the spiked furniture? Where are the candles and golden chains?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="wikipe-tan" stage="0-6" sayingMarker="WhatgenderIsBowsette" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">Call me Bowsette! I identify as a woman, by the way. Makes things easier!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" oneShotId="945">
                <condition role="other" character="rin_kagamine" sayingMarker="BowsetteMoreLikeBOWsette" />
                <state img="#-angry.png" marker="RinCrown1">... Gah! I can't figure out why, but somehow I feel like giving Rin the crown would be a terrible idea! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <test expr="~bowsette.hand.score~" value="112" />
                <state img="#-angry.png">Three queens, all in a row! You tryin' to say something about me, pipsqueak? You wanna tell me, "you don't count as a queen?"</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <test expr="~bowsette.hand.score~" value="113" />
                <state img="#-angry.png">Look at that, three of a kind! Huh? "It's only a pair"? Are you trying to say that &lt;i&gt;I&lt;/i&gt;, the great &lt;i&gt;King&lt;/i&gt; Koopa, ain't a king? Is that it?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" totalRounds="0">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">You plumb-dumbs got lucky, that's all.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-angry.png">...Look, it's not &lt;i&gt;my&lt;/i&gt; fault I lost. Half the time I play cards with Mario, they have stupid pictures of clouds and mushrooms and crud, but no numbers! It's throwing off my game hard.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Without the crown, I usually walk around in nothing but the spiky armbands! I don't give two skipsqueak's butts about getting naked, unlike you wimps!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">How about I count each one of these bands as an individual piece of clothing?  It wouldn't be cheating.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_winning">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">I'll throw ya a bone. I let myself lose, after all.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">Ha! Nice shot, ya pesky pipsqueaks -- but you're never gonna beat me for real!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Bwahaha -- one minor setback won’t stop me from victory!</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">So, I guess I'll finally join you losers. Well, at least I'm still in the lead! Bahaha!</state>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">So what? Looks like I'm still in the lead, as expected!</state>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">Ya ready, chumps? Take a good look, because this'll be the last thing I'm taking off today.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-4">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">I guess I can give the rabble &lt;i&gt;some&lt;/i&gt; small consolation...</state>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">Pfft...! Well, I &lt;i&gt;am&lt;/i&gt; in the lead... So I &lt;i&gt;guess&lt;/i&gt; can afford to show off the goods~</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Ha! I don't blame you chumps for your persistence. &lt;i&gt;I'd&lt;/i&gt; want to see me that bad as well!</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">Don't think this will become a regular thing!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_normal">
            <case stage="5-6">
                <state img="#-resigned.png">Do these horns come off...? No...?</state>
                <state img="#-rage.png">COME ON! I'M NOT EXACTLY WORKING WITH MUCH OVER HERE!</state>
                <state img="#-rage.png">Grah...! Don't think for a moment you've won!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Are you that desperate to see my new body naked? Bwahahaha! Keep up the good plays, then, but I won't hold back anymore!</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Bwahaha! So you've scored a hit! But don't think your Queen is going down in three stomps!</state>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">Gaze upon your Queen, peasants!</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Oh no, one measly little loss...? Ha! It's a small price to pay for my eventual victory.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-4">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Heh, really bringing your A-game, huh?  You're gonna need to if ya plan to dethrone the Queen!</state>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">What, ya wanna see more of me? I don't blame ya -- I know my body's perfect.</state>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">My body is usually more... thick... but I'm liking this so far. Don't get me wrong, my normal look is PEAK performance, but honestly -- there ain't nothing wrong with a feminine touch.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Hmph. The first few stages are always easy.  Just wait until the end.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-rage.png">What's your damage, dealer?! Ya got a death wish or somethin'? Stop making me lose so much!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">MAN! I lost again! You're lucky I'm in a good mood right now, or else you'd &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; regret makin' me do this.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_losing">
            <case stage="1-6">
                <condition role="self" consecutiveLosses="2-" />
                <state img="#-rage.png">What?! I lost &lt;i&gt;again?!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-rage.png">I'm the only one allowed to rig a card game, dealer!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" totalRounds="0-4">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Steamed as all heck that I'm losing. But hey, it's still early on, right? The tides oughta be changing soon!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition count="0-" status="chest_visible" />
                <state img="#-angry.png">Wait, this isn't how this is supposed to go! I'm the final boss -- I can't be the &lt;i&gt;first&lt;/i&gt; chump to show my chest!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6">
                <state img="#-rage.png">Darn it, I lost AGAIN?! Cheating's supposed to make you &lt;i&gt;win&lt;/i&gt;!</state>
                <state img="#-rage.png">You... you... AAAAAAAAAARGH!</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">Tch... Getting me &lt;i&gt;this&lt;/i&gt; far? Either you're cheating or ya &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; like this body...</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">Wait, there must be some mistake! I can't be losing a game about getting naked! I'm not &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; unlucky!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-angry.png">Bah... All of you are uninvited to my wedding!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" />
            <case stage="1-4">
                <state img="#-angry.png">Bah... I may be losing, but it’s not game over yet!</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">GAH!  Come on, koopa, get in the game!  Ugh, that's it-- winning streak starts &lt;i&gt;now&lt;/i&gt;!</state>
                <state img="#-rage.png">You can't be serious...</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">What!? &lt;i&gt;Me&lt;/i&gt; again... What's a Queen gotta do to get some fair friggin' treatment around here?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-6">
                <state img="#-angry.png">Stop trying to win, you pinheads!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-angry.png">What? What are you looking at? I ain't taking nothing off until one of these &lt;i&gt;other&lt;/i&gt; losers strips... &lt;br&gt; Bah, &lt;i&gt;fine.&lt;/i&gt; But it's the only time I'm stripping. &lt;i&gt;Got it?&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-angry.png">What is this load of Delfino dookie? I'm &lt;i&gt;Bowsette&lt;/i&gt;, I oughta be winnin' more!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-6">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">I wish I could take off the crown, but let's just say that wouldn't be allowed for the same reason that purple space dragon took so long to get in smash...</state>
                <state img="#-rage.png">I'll be back from this! You BETTER believe it!</state>
                <state img="#-rage.png">I better get nothing but good cards from now on, or someone is gonna get a Bob-omb on their mail soon...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripping">
            <case stage="0-6" oneShotId="946">
                <condition role="opp" character="rin_kagamine" sayingMarker="BowsetteMoreLikeBOWsette1" />
                <state img="#-stripping-.png" marker="RinCrown2">There's only one blonde princess I'm after and it's not gonna be you, young lady. You can be dang sure of that. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <condition count="0" status="crotch_visible" role="other" />
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">What did I ever do to deserve this butt-whuppin'? Besides the kidnappings, thefts, and general mayhem.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">This dress is so hard to move around in! Time to handle this problem the Bowser way.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">I might have lost that round, but don't you dare think I'm a loser! Maybe you all need a good distraction...</state>
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">Oh, I'll give you a show alright! I bet the other princesses wouldn't &lt;i&gt;dare&lt;/i&gt; do &lt;i&gt;this!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">Where did this dress even come from? I definitely weren't wearing one before I put on this crown... Don't you dare doubt me, ~player~!</state>
                <state img="#-stripping+.png" marker="pizazz">You're probably expecting me to remove something boring, right? Well I'm not boring! I'm the friggin' Koopa Queen! Let me show you losers how a queen strips!</state>
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">Heh. Strength &lt;i&gt;and&lt;/i&gt; confidence -- no wonder it's my destiny to rule!</state>
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">Why must they make these clasps so HARD to undo...!? RRRGH--</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">These were getting uncomfortable. Peach has &lt;i&gt;terrible&lt;/i&gt; taste in shoes.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">Bah, I usually go barefoot anyway. I don't need shoes to stomp those pesky Mario Brothers into pancakes -- and I don't need shoes to stomp &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; chumps into pancakes, either!</state>
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">Since when did being tall have to hurt in a way that doesn't include bumping your head on high things?!</state>
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">Well, pain is beauty, isn't it? Never said that pain is &lt;i&gt;worth&lt;/i&gt; the beauty, though!</state>
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">How do princesses even wear these for so long? My ankles were crying after an hour!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">You're really enjoying this, aren't you? Go ahead and tell me, ~player~. I don't mind it at all~</state>
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">Gwahaha... I know a few people who are into feet. You one of 'em?</state>
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">My stockings it is. Aw, are you disappointed? Sorry for wanting to win this, buddy!</state>
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">Don't get cocky -- as long as I get some good hands, I can STILL crush you all beneath my heel.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">At first, I was against the idea of wearing these stupid things here. Yet they feel so good against my skin that I just &lt;i&gt;had&lt;/i&gt; to keep them on!</state>
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">Y'know what? At least these are satisfying to remove! You can never get that feeling when they don't make socks in your size!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">Shut up about why I'm wearing these... It's part of the crown, and Junior thought they looked good on me. You &lt;i&gt;try&lt;/i&gt; telling that kid no.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">This crown's magic is pretty impressive! Along with the clothes, it gave me these earrings too. I don't like them, but they look expensive, so you better not lose 'em!</state>
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">What to remove next? I hope you were expecting the earrings, because it's the earrings, alright!</state>
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">On the bright side, this gives me an excuse to ditch &lt;i&gt;these&lt;/i&gt; bulky baubles. With the heft they've got, it gets uncomfortable wearing 'em after a few hours!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">... Did I forget I had these..?!</state>
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">Blast, this is really all I have left...</state>
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">Yeah, once I get these off it'll be easier to kick your butt!</state>
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">Maybe I shouldn't have saved my armbands for last... Whuzzat? You'd rather I keep them on?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">All this power -- &lt;i&gt;and&lt;/i&gt; good looks, too! Yeah, I know you're all thinking it...</state>
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">Heh, like what you see? Then you're gonna LOVE what comes next~</state>
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">So much for that "stategic move" I did earlier...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">Bah. These things were riding up anyways...</state>
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">Wait a sec... Did I remember to shave down there?</state>
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">(Why am I nervous...? I'm &lt;i&gt;literally&lt;/i&gt; naked all day. Then again, I guess the usual junk ain't typically on display, either...)</state>
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">Go ahead, take a good look at what's gonna wear yer tongue out tonight! H-heh heh...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripped">
            <case stage="1-7" oneShotId="947">
                <condition role="opp" character="rin_kagamine" sayingMarker="BowsetteMoreLikeBOWsette2" />
                <state img="#-stripped-.png">Tough luck, twerp. This crown is fit for a queen only. If anything, I'm passing it down to my son. Or, guh, &lt;i&gt;Daughter&lt;/i&gt;, hypothetically.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <test expr="~background~" value="beach" />
                <state img="#-stripped+.png" marker="bowsette_beach_body">How's &lt;i&gt;this&lt;/i&gt; for a beach body?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <test expr="~background~" value="holiday lodge" />
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">The best part of being a firebreather is that I don't have to worry about the cold. I can waltz around in the snow buck naked without a care in the world. You humans and your dumb hypothermia.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <condition count="1" gender="male" status="masturbating" />
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">Take a look at &lt;i&gt;these&lt;/i&gt; honkers! Try not to blow your load too quickly now, will ya? GWAHAHAHA!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <condition count="0" status="crotch_visible" role="other" />
                <state img="#-stripped-.png">Curse this crown! Losing is one thing, but what I really regret is that I can't give you all a showin' of my Koopa Cannon!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="pizazz" />
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">SHOWTIME! How d'ya like that?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">Be careful! When you pinch Bowser's titties, they pinch back.</state>
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">Take a look at these Koopa Shells!</state>
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">Aren't these melons totally fantastic? Certainly way better than any of those dumb princesses' racks.</state>
                <state img="#-stripped-.png">... Honestly, I thought giant tits would work in my favor more, but by golly if they don't get in the way sometimes. Not to mention the stares I get from Goombas...</state>
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">What'cha think? These Banzai Bills big enough for you? Don't answer -- I couldn't care one stinkin' bit less.</state>
                <state img="#-stripped-.png">I don't mind showing off, but I &lt;i&gt;hate&lt;/i&gt; to lose! Don't think you'll be getting the rest off this easily!</state>
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">I'm the big, bad Koopa Queen!  Emphasis on big!</state>
                <state img="#-stripped-.png">If you're wondering... No, they &lt;i&gt;don't&lt;/i&gt; sound like note blocks when you bounce them.</state>
                <state img="#-stripped-.png">You like looking at this body, ~player~? Howsabout, I dunno, throwing the game for it? No? Pah! You have no taste!</state>
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">Grr... Well, if I'm gonna lose, I might as well make the most of it. Get a load of this, ~player~! C'mon! Let these tits distract you from the game!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-stripped-.png">I swear these looked much cooler when they had spikes.</state>
                <state img="#-stripped-.png">Well, enjoy the view, dearies. Nothing else is coming off...</state>
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">Welp -- there go my awesome spiked bands. Ya better be grateful I'm stoppin' there, ya hear?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">It's either the shoes or the crown, and as fun as the latter would be... I would have even less clothes afterwards. So count your blessings this time, worms!</state>
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">Go ahead and get a good look! It's gonna make crushing you all the better!</state>
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">I never got used to those heels anyway...</state>
                <state img="#-stripped-.png">Ankle torture has never been more fashionable...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-stripped-.png">So long, straight Mario!</state>
                <state img="#-stripped-.png">Let my guess... my thighs are "super thicc" and you want them to "sandwich" you... I know exactly how you insufferable humans think.</state>
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">These babies could crush a Koopa Shell! Not that I &lt;i&gt;would&lt;/i&gt; crush one, but I'm just sayin'!</state>
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">Enjoying yourself? Well, SAVOR IT, 'cause you won't be getting any more outta me! That's your QUEEN speaking!</state>
                <state img="#-stripped-.png">No witty comments or I'll pulverize you! I bet ya I can crack your skull between my thighs! &lt;i&gt;Wanna find out?&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">Admiring my legs? One of the great things about this form is that I could crack a nut with these thighs. Or maybe even someone's skull!</state>
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">&lt;i&gt;There.&lt;/i&gt; Don't stare at my long, perfect legs &lt;i&gt;too&lt;/i&gt; much, ya pervy little pipsqueaks.</state>
                <state img="#-stripped-.png">Fine, whatever! They were itchy anyway!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="9">
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">Won't be needing &lt;i&gt;this!&lt;/i&gt; Fancy dress balls are no match for undressed balls anyway.</state>
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">That’s better. Never really understood the appeal of dresses or skirts like the princesses do.</state>
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">I never saw the appeal of these stupid things anyway. Give me a shell instead any day of the week.</state>
                <state img="#-stripped-.png">Sexy lingerie? This Super Crown really pulled out all the stops -- what, ya think I'd walk around dressed like this as a male Koopa? ...Well, I &lt;i&gt;don't!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">BAH! Who needs this thing! Here, let a Koopa Queen show you pathetic rubes how stripping is REALLY DONE!</state>
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">Ah, much better -- and much &lt;i&gt;easier,&lt;/i&gt; too! Who needs to take the whole thing off when you got claws?</state>
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">You think seeing my tits would be that easy? Think again, bucko! </state>
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">Huh? I was supposed to take off the entire dress? No thanks! I don't play fair, I play to win!</state>
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">One man's cheating is another man's way of playing strategically! I like to think of this as the latter! Hah!</state>
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">Take off the entire dress and reveal most of my body from the getgo? You think I'm the kinda person to play fair, pal?!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-stripped-.png">Take a picture -- it'll last longer!</state>
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">Tell me... H-how do you feel about kneeling before your Queen?</state>
                <state img="#-stripped-.png">If you think I'm embarrassed, then think again! I always walk around naked anyway. S-so there!</state>
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">What were you expecting, some kind of Koopa cock?</state>
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">S-so what if I'm basically naked...? Most of the time, these spiky armbands are all I need to wear.</state>
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">Shavin'? I'm a lizard, what do I have to shave?</state>
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">Feels weird to have nothing dangling between my legs anymore... &lt;br&gt; I was referrin' to my &lt;i&gt;tail,&lt;/i&gt; not my dick! Since when did I &lt;i&gt;ever&lt;/i&gt; romp around with that big thing out?</state>
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">Whoops! Guess I didn't... Gyeheheh~</state>
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">Gyeheheh.... A body befitting a Queen, yes?</state>
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">I still haven't quite gotten used to the whole hairy crotch thing... Koopas might grow hair on their heads, but &lt;i&gt;never&lt;/i&gt; between their legs!</state>
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">W-well, here I am... What do you guys think? Blown away by my queenly appeal, aren't ya...?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-stripped-.png">In any case, I just hope that I won't have to do away with much more than this.</state>
                <state img="#-stripped-.png">I wish these were magical. Heck, maybe I should tell Kamek to &lt;i&gt;make&lt;/i&gt; 'em magical! Then I'd be crushing you all harder, too, I bet.</state>
                <state img="#-stripped-.png">What's that? Take off something bigger? Sorry, I can't hear you over how much I don't care.</state>
                <state img="#-stripped-.png">These hunks of junk are heavy as heck. I guess it's for the feminine look, but for Pete's sake...</state>
                <state img="#-stripped-.png">On one hand, another tiny useless trinket to remove. On the other, hand, these darn hurt to wear!</state>
                <state img="#-stripped-.png">I'll &lt;i&gt;gladly&lt;/i&gt; admit how trivial and unnecessary these are. Then again, ain't that all the more reason to have them here?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_human_must_strip">
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="114">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">I'm the biggest, baddest gal around, and don't you forget it.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">You don't talk a lot, do ya? Well, it's not like the plumber I often fight with has much of a vocabulary, either...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Well, ~player~? Wanna help me by getting me aroused, or do you wanna help me by alleviating the humiliation of losing?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_strip">
            <case stage="0-9" id="33" oneShotId="632">
                <condition role="target" character="twisted_fate" />
                <state img="#-rage.png" marker="bowsette_fate_treasure_hunter">What's up with the treasure hunter look? You're not here to take away my magical crown for a museum or somethin', are ya!?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="34" oneShotId="630">
                <condition role="target" character="adrien" />
                <state img="#-resigned.png">That makes me wonder... Can I use the Super Bell in this form? Wait, can I even use ANY other power-up!?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="35" oneShotId="631">
                <condition role="target" character="brock" />
                <state img="#-cocky.png">You got some explosive toys, but do you have explosive BREATH? Didn't think so!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Show me something good, whydoncha? Maybe you can show me something humiliating too! Hah!</state>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">Don't be such a shy guy!</state>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">Take off something good and you might get to cop a feel on a REAL queen... GWAHAHAHA! As IF, chump!</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">I've already shown a lot~ &lt;br&gt; It's only fair that you join your Queen in this revelry!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-4">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Gwahahaha! Even when I'm down, you're still gonna lose!</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">BAHAHA! The new look this crown gave me may be great, but I'm still me, which means I will still WIN!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Bah hah HAH!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Come on, give me a good show and &lt;i&gt;maybe&lt;/i&gt; I won't throw you into the nearest firepit.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Show the Koopa Queen something good, ~name~, and you might receive my... benevolence!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">BWAHAHA! Don't lose your nerve now, pipsqueak. Its more fun to crush my enemies when they put up a fight.</state>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">That's right. Strip for Mama~</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-horny.png">You're a little late to turn me on, but what the heck! Nothing wrong with taking a look at more, eh?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">It took you long enough! </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_human_must_strip">
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="118">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Gwahaha! Did you think I was just going to &lt;i&gt;give&lt;/i&gt; the win to ya? You've got to earn it first! Or cheat better than me!</state>
                <state img="#-resigned.png">You don't talk a lot, do ya? Well, it's not like my usual rivals have much of a vocabulary, either...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_strip">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="ribbon_girl" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-cocky.png" marker="bowsette_ribbon_girl_mii">Hey there, "Pop Star." Haven't seen you since that Ramen Chick stole your Smash invite. Sucks to be you... or should I say, sucks to be a Mii.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="yang_xiao_long" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Sorry, blondie! But &lt;i&gt;{b}I{!reset} burn!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="polly" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Is this what that green plumber was so afraid of? The worst thing he can get from her is STDs!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="polly" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-resigned.png">And I thought I made way too many jokes based on shrooms...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="moon" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-angry.png">Why did you just give up!? Are we not worthy opponents!? Bah! This is insulting!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="moon" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-angry.png">Wrong, wrong, WRONG! The game isn't supposed to be played like this!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="36" oneShotId="635">
                <condition role="target" character="jason" />
                <state img="#-angry.png">I came here to have a good time, and now I'm finding myself playing against talking, armed, unmasked Shy Gals! You better not ask for raises, 'cause you ain't getting none!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="42" oneShotId="122">
                <condition role="target" character="polly" />
                <state img="#-angry.png" marker="bowsette_polly_boosette">Oh great, another Princess Boosette impersonator. Like the last one wasn't enough.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="44" oneShotId="296">
                <condition role="target" character="lucina" />
                <state img="#-cocky.png" marker="bowsette_lucina_not_fooled">"Marth?" Yeah, right. Nice try, Princess, but you're not fooling anyone but yourself. Next time, try a Super Crown like the rest of us.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="41" oneShotId="406">
                <condition role="target" character="pa-15" />
                <state img="#-resigned.png" marker="pa15_geno">Huh. Never thought I'd meet another talking toy that was packing heat.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="43" oneShotId="553">
                <condition role="target" character="spooky" />
                <state img="#-rage.png">I thought ghosts couldn't hold weapons! All this time the Boos have been avoiding training, those lazy balls of ectogunk!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="38" oneShotId="638">
                <condition role="target" character="chara_dreemurr" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">You look very close to your "Partner," kiddo. Better be careful or I might crush you both with these fiery plays! Bwahahaha!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="37" oneShotId="637">
                <condition role="target" character="ami" />
                <state img="#-angry.png">Come again, what sort of "model" are you supposed to be? Because if it's a role model, you're not supposed to be here at all! I wouldn't want Junior to look up to the likes of you!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="39" oneShotId="639">
                <condition role="target" character="neptune" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">Finally! About time someone made controls big enough for my claws!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="46" oneShotId="642">
                <condition role="target" character="yang_xiao_long" />
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">Bwahaha! Now that is a good, well-kept mane just like mine! Newsflash, though -- ponytails are &lt;i&gt;in&lt;/i&gt; this season!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="45" oneShotId="641">
                <condition role="target" character="susie" />
                <state img="#-rage.png">What's up with that knife now!? Are the Shy Gals tryin' to unionize again or something!?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="40" oneShotId="640">
                <condition role="target" character="perona" />
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Finally someone worthy of playing with me! Ghost princess, meet the fiercest of the fire princesses!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" oneShotId="832">
                <condition role="target" character="larachel" />
                <state img="#-resigned.png">She's ever gonna stop talking? &lt;i&gt;Sigh~&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="mari" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="101" marker="MariThirst">Bwahaha! You've got quite the thirst, young lady! I like your attitude, that's just what we need around here!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" oneShotId="944">
                <condition role="target" character="kumatora" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="KumatoraSmash">HEY! Haven't I seen you before, pinky? Weren't you friends with that magic blonde kid in Smash?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" layers="1" />
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Hah! Looks like yer down to one life!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Gwahaha! Like I tell my son, anythin's possible if ya cheat enough!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-happy.png">This is what you get for thinking you could defeat King Bowser! Now, get to it!</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">Oh, you lost. Boohoo. Just hurry up and strip, lady. I'm getting cold.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Come on, honey. Take off something nice for me...</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Don't get &lt;i&gt;cocky&lt;/i&gt; just because I've lost a few hands, pipsqueak!</state>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">Did you really think you had a CHANCE against King-... Queen Bowsette? Bwahaha! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">What a joke of a hand! Next time, put some actual thought into it!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-rage.png">Oh, don't you complain...! You could be me...!</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Yes, yes -- more!  Show me MORE!  The Koopa Troop demands MORE TO LOOK AT, gwahaha!</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Show me something worthy of your Queen, girly!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-surprise.png">Whoa, I forgot you were in this game for a second, ~name~. Ya kinda don't stand out compared to me.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Well, ya lose often enough. How about it, wanna become one of my minions?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Don't forget who's the queen around here, and who ain't! &lt;br&gt; ...It's me, I'm the queen.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-4">
                <state img="#-happy.png">We're waiting on you, pipsqueak!</state>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">Don't get all proper on me now! Show your queen your slutty side, girly!</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Come on, show us what you're made of, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">Don't keep a king waiting, ~name~! Show us what you've got!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Yeah! Get a little bit closer to your natural state!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">GWA HA HA!</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Better get used to this feeling, worm. You'll be feeling it a &lt;i&gt;lot&lt;/i&gt; today with me here!  BAHAHA!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="tie">
            <case stage="0-9" id="47">
                <condition role="other" character="neptune" />
                <state img="#-angry.png" marker="bowsette_neptune_sega_genesis">Nobody asked you, Sega Genesis.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-4">
                <state img="#-angry.png">A tie?! So no one has to strip? What a waste of a hand!</state>
                <state img="#-resigned.png">What a waste of time.</state>
                <state img="#-rage.png">What in the blazes! I didn't even know that was possible!</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">In simpler games, we'd just go into Sudden Death Mode!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">BAHAHA! So, BOTH of you are stripping now! Right? What, you aren't? Well, that's stupid.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-surprise.png">Oh. Crud.</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">That was a waste of goddamned time!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">What? We have a tie for last place? What a waste of time...</state>
                <state img="#-rage.png">Oh wow how INCREDIBLE oh the INTRIGUE oh the -- HOW IS THIS MUCH GOING ON WHEN I'M ALREADY DONE!?</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">A tie? That means both these useless worms strip, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">What a waste of time! Let's move on already.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-surprise.png">Wait, is that a tie?!</state>
                <state img="#-surprise.png">I didn't realize that could happen!</state>
                <state img="#-rage.png">So nobody has to strip? What a wasted round!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Ties shouldn't be a thing... This isn't Mario Strikers.</state>
                <state img="#-surprise.png">Is... is that even possible?</state>
                <state img="#-surprise.png">That's probably the last thing I expected to happen, if I'm going to be honest!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-rage.png">If I'm exhibiting such a majestic display, somebody better be taking off some blasted clothes!</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">C'mon, I wanted some more action than THAT!</state>
                <state img="#-surprise.png">&lt;i&gt;Hahh... hahh...&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br&gt; ...What happened?  Why isn't anyone -- &lt;i&gt;hahh&lt;/i&gt; -- stripping? Your queen demands MORE stripping!  URGH!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-resigned.png">Just once I'd like to have a minion that &lt;i&gt;couldn't&lt;/i&gt; be defeated by some Italian jumpin' on top of 'em three times.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">You're such a tease, ~name~...</state>
                <state img="#-rage.png">OOOH! You're mocking me! I'll incinerate ~clothing.ifPlural(those little trinkets|that little trinket)~ of yours, just so I don't have to see ~clothing.ifPlural(them|it)~ EVER AGAIN!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-4">
                <state img="#-happy.png">This is how it starts. Big losing streak for you COMING UP, I'm calling it right now! Ya ready, pipsqueak?</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Keep this up and maybe I &lt;i&gt;will&lt;/i&gt; take off the crown.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-angry.png">Ridiculous! I watch Mario lose his hat every other day! You waste my time!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Less annoying than losing the Hammer Bro suit, isn't it?</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">It's a step in the right direction, at least.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-rage.png">This little...? Are ya taunting me, ya clown?!</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Come on, you could at &lt;i&gt;least&lt;/i&gt; do something better than that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Are you strong enough to rid me of a couple of troublesome fools, ~name~? Nothing I've tried has worked.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Seriously, ~name~? Is that all you can strip?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">You know, some people would just go straight for whipping out their cock. I mean, I know I would. More power to ya, I guess.</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">If you're looking for more fireworks, that won't spark any.</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">Seriously?! When this is over, you are SO getting thrown into a lava pit!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="9">
                <condition status="not_naked" role="target" />
                <state img="#-angry.png">Bah! You should've taken that off ages ago!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-resigned.png">Mmmh... was Monday for kidnapping Peach again, or was that the day me n' Mario go karting and party?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-rage.png">Oh I get it. Just because you can see my tits, that means you can take off whatever the hell you want. Well, tell you what. Do that again and &lt;i&gt;I'll show you the wrath of the Queen of the Koopas!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">Do you know why they call me the Queen of Horny? It's because I got these giant horns, which I'm gonna use to spear you if that's all yer takin' off!</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">Take off something better next time, you puny, pathetic pest!</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">Maybe a hundred of those would help you get a life.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-angry.png">Speedrunners...</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">Was I a full lap behind?</state>
                <state img="#-rage.png">I will rip the clothes RIGHT off of you if I have to...!</state>
                <state img="#-rage.png">Alright, twerp, here's a deal for you -- either you're gonna whip out your dick next, or you're gonna find yourself a Double Cherry short!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-angry.png">I can't say I'm happy with you removing your ~clothing~, but since I still have my bands on... I guess I'll hold my tongue. &lt;i&gt;But only this time!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-4">
                <state img="#-angry.png">Boy, don't MAKE me come over there and take something off for you!</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Take off more!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-angry.png">At this rate, I'm going to have to strip you myself!</state>
                <state img="#-resigned.png">Hmph... Junior better behave himself while I'm gone. Hard keeping that kid busy when he'd rather play with his little bombs.</state>
                <state img="#-resigned.png">Do all the princesses in the kingdoms wear tight corsets like this? Hrgh.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-resigned.png">Ugh. How could I have lost by SO MUCH!? I thought this crown would change things...</state>
                <state img="#-resigned.png">You'd think I'd be used to getting thrashed by these bros by now...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="51">
                <state img="#-resigned.png">Boring! Before I wore this crown, I didn't wear no ~clothing~. I didn't wear no clothes at all!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="chun-li" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="bowsette_chun-li_matching_bands">Wow. We have matching bands. Is this what they call bonding? I kinda... hate it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <test expr="~clothing~" value="crown" />
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Go ahead, take off the crown! Then I'll be the only hot woman here!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <test expr="~clothing.position~" value="neck" />
                <state img="#-rage.png">Are you kidding me...? I may be a princess now, but I don't cover myself with crummy trinkets!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-4">
                <state img="#-angry.png">Come on, girl! Not even I take that much time stripping, and I have to account for a spiked shell!</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Whenever someone strips it's all "Me! Me! Me!", when there's obviously more important things to talk about... like me.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Do not flaunt your TRINKETS at me, girl. I am here to win, and I'm gonna!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Yes! Yeeeeesss! Looks like it's time for Bowser to FINALLY start raking in the wins!</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">C'mon, get it over with!</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Hmph. Removing something so small while your queen is presenting herself...!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-angry.png">Oh, that's great... You REALLY pulled out all the stops on that one.</state>
                <state img="#-rage.png">You had better take something more exciting off next time, or so help me--</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Mph... You're slower than... err... &lt;br&gt; ...Junior usually helps me come up with my insults...</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Bah, is &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; all? I think I'll just spend this time savoring my many wins to come...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-rage.png">Come on! I just got done playing with myself only for you to take something like THAT off?</state>
                <state img="#-resigned.png">I think I'll make Koopa soup for dinner tonight.</state>
                <state img="#-rage.png">Are you actively trying to tick me off over here?!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="blake" stage="6" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="bowsette_blake_super_bell">Whoa! Cat ears. Are those real, or did you sneak a Super Bell in without us noticing?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="moon" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-resigned.png">Is this the kind of clientele this place wants to bring in? Hmmm...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="twilight" />
                <state img="#-angry.png">How dare you trick us with removing that accessory, Twilight Sparkle!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-rage.png">I'm too horny for this nonsense! Take off something real before I take it off FOR ya!</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">A simple decoration? That's it? I thought a queen was worth more.</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">Hey! As the queen here, I shouldn't be this far behind!</state>
                <state img="#-rage.png">If I have to BURN something off of you, I &lt;i&gt;will&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-resigned.png">Grr... I must look like a fool right now. If Mario were here, I'd crush him with a Thwomp.</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">You wanna know what I don't have all of? It's day! Hurry up, ~name~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">Don't be shy, ~name~. I know what'cha heard of me, but I don't bite.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">If you want help with being bolder, I could always set your clothing ablaze. Your ~clothing~ wouldn't help you at all at that point.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-resigned.png">Done like a true amateur.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">I am the ki... I mean QUEEN of cards!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-angry.png">Quit stalling! You're only delaying your own defeat, you know?</state>
                <state img="#-resigned.png">I would clap sarcastically, but I do that enough in Smash Brothers. And my hands are full of cards. Whatever. NEXT.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-4">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Don't be afraid to lose this next round too! Not that you'll have much of a choice, playing against me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Bwahaha! It ain't much, but you're getting your game over eventually, lady!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-angry.png">That's it!? That's way too low of a punishment when I'm already like this! At least lose 10 coins or something!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-angry.png">Bah!  I tear off my dress and ~name~ takes off her ~clothing~.  Pathetic!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-7">
                <state img="#-angry.png">If you're gonna be such a princess, I might as well kidnap you.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_minor">
            <case stage="3-5">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Why is it that so many of my bosses have giant, glowy eyes on their weak spots?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-resigned.png">I tried playin' this game with some Koopa Troopas as practice 'fore comin' here, right? 'Cept Koopas got nothin' to lose but their shells, so I won every game.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">&lt;i&gt;(Don't get mad. Don't Get Mad.  DON'T GET MAD! {b}I'M GETTING MAD!{!reset})&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Ugh. To have to watch you only take off THAT, after I've already lost like this... What a sad day for the Koopa Troop.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-resigned.png">Ugh, seriously!? You're just as big of a coward as that scrawny little beanpole always cowering behind Mario. &lt;br&gt; ...What was his name again? Luigi?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-resigned.png">Come on. Don't be boring. Is a little skin too much to ask for?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="57" />
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_minor">
            <case stage="1-7" oneShotId="509">
                <alternative>
                    <condition filter="slutty" role="other" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <condition filter="confident" role="other" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">&lt;i&gt;(How do these floozies come up with better pick-up lines than I do? Ugh, I need to up my game. I'll show them!)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-4">
                <state img="#-angry.png">Come ON, you wimp! Live a little! Take off something fun!</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">Bwah! If you were just going to take off that, you could have at least put on a show.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Bahahaha -- YES! That's more like it. Don't get too comfortable, now -- I'm not done with you yet!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">One step closer. I can always burn the rest away if you want me to end it right now. Bwahahaha!</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Pfft, what a waste. You shouldn't keep a queen waiting, you know.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-rage.png">If you keep this up, I swear, I'm taking off my crown until things get more interesting. Pay up, or it's Bowser Time!</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">That's a bit unfair...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-9">
                <state img="#-rage.png">Oh, go &lt;i&gt;on&lt;/i&gt;, Mr. Comedian! I'm just &lt;i&gt;dying&lt;/i&gt; to see the rest of your HILARIOUS comedy routine, with you barely stripping while I'm &lt;i&gt;like this&lt;/i&gt;!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Yeah, yeah. Everyone else is complainin', but I could care less! You're prolly ugly under there anyways. Besides, nothing can compete with this hot bod of mine.</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">After what I just did, that's it?!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-angry.png">Come on, already! Stop teasing! Show the goods!</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">That's not neat stuff, you nincomkoop! How am I supposed to wank to this!?</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Really? That's the best you can do? Pfft.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="miko" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-flustered.png" marker="bowsette_miko_not_boosette">W-wait, what's goin' on? Yer not Princess Boosette!</state>
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="bowsette_miko_boosette_looks_different">Princess Boosette? That you? Ya look a little different....</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <condition status="decent" role="target" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">This is bull... The whole game's rigged, I tell ya!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-angry.png">You could... ngh... afford to loosen up a bit! Considering that I'm already like t-this... Grrh...</state>
                <state img="#-resigned.png">This is -- nngh -- humiliating. I lost by &lt;i&gt;so much&lt;/i&gt;. I must get Kamek to do something -- hahh -- to make sure this doesn't happen again...</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Your queen requires an exhibitionist right now, not a prude...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-angry.png">Glad you did that now. That woulda made my cunt drier than a desert when jerking off. That's how much of a turn-off it is.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Could you remove something bigger instead...? You wouldn't lose any faster, but I'd feel better about the whole thing.</state>
                <state img="#-rage.png">Are you mocking me? I demand you get naked this instant!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Argh... What do women want to hear when they strip? ...Wait. What would &lt;i&gt;I&lt;/i&gt; want to hear?</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Hrmgh - I have to admit, the new form this crown gave me feels... comfortable. Is this a side effect of its magic, or...?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Aw, crap... I only now realized I never got my deposit back from the moon chapel.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-rage.png">GRR! I don't like losing like this... That's it, I'm coming for you NEXT, missy!</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Keep stalling and I might slash the rest off of you myself.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">Come on. Don't be a shivering little Shy Gal. Give the audience what they came to see.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_minor">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="sakura" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png">&lt;i&gt;Rampaging reptiles!&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;You're a zombie?!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" oneShotId="861">
                <condition filter="ghost" role="target" />
                <condition filter="ghost" role="other" />
                <state img="#-resigned.png">What's up with all these stripping ghosts? Though now that I think about it, getting Boosette to come here &lt;i&gt;would&lt;/i&gt; help her get rid of her crippling shyness...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-resigned.png">Damn, I suck at this game.  I should just go back to kidnapping princesses...</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">How did I get so far behind?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Not getting played for a fool this time! That's your job!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">You should show a little more skin if you want some nice, scaly &lt;i&gt;hunk&lt;/i&gt; of a man to kidnap you someday...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-4">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Is that all? I thought you would want to impress me before I burn this place to the ground.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Be flattered -- usually, I'd let Kamek deal with the attrition stuff.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-resigned.png">BAH. I should be winning more than this. How can I take over the world if I can't even CRUSH at cards?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_major">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Ooooh yeah, come to daddy~ &lt;br&gt; ...Or, mommy. Or... You know what, never rmind.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Nnf -- ooh! I was... hahh! I was distracted... Why haven't you stripped yet? Why do you still have those ...nnf... underpants on?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-4">
                <state img="#-happy.png">HAH, that's nothing! I see that every time a Koopa pops out of its shell!  When are ya showing me the &lt;i&gt;real goods&lt;/i&gt;, huh?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0 5-7 9" id="58" />
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_major">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Normally, I take stars or coins from losers who cross my path, but this will do as a substitute.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">It's times like these that make me happy to be a king... er, queen.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Yes, show me more, weakling! Take... off... &lt;i&gt;everything&lt;/i&gt; for me.</state>
                <state img="#-resigned.png">Yeah, yeah, you're still wearin' clothes. But I'd kick your tail in a fight and you know it. So don't get cocky!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">Oh~? Is that present all wrapped up for me~?</state>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">A splendid view! Don't you wish to throw the rest of the game and join your queen?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">We're reaching the last level, ~name~! You really think you can take down this final boss?</state>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">Is that a shroom in your underpants, or are you just terrified to see me?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">You SUCK at this. No, I'm not insulting you. It's just an observation.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_major">
            <case stage="0-9" id="18">
                <condition role="target" character="shantae" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-horny.png">Yeah! Shake that ass, Shantae!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-9">
                <test expr="~clothing~" value="dress" />
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Just tear it off! Don't be a coward.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Pah! Amateurs! None of you will ever see what lies beneath my layers!</state>
                <state img="#-resigned.png">I like winning, sure, but usually that's when all my plans come crashing down, so ya can't blame this Koopa for being uneasy right now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Nngh -- yes, show me more -- ungh -- show your queen &lt;i&gt;more&lt;/i&gt;.  I -- ahh!  I demand it!</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Good thing you aren't a Boo, 'cause I'm looking right at you.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I saw this going differently in my head...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Even though I'm finished, this sight makes me wanna start over.</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">That's it. Present yourself for your queen!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-4">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">That's more like it! Now this is a game!</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">There we go. Join the club~</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7" id="59" />
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_major">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="ruby" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">Strawberry panties? Suits you pretty good, Ruby.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-4">
                <test expr="~clothing.position~" value="lower" />
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">Hey, babe. Spread your legs a bit, it looks to be a li'l see-through where your cunt is.</state>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">Gwahaha! If you're gonna come to Strip Poker Night, at least wear some sexier panties!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-horny.png">This is MUCH better than those games I don't let Junior play.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-4">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">How does it feel to know a magical crown has better fashion sense than you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-horny.png">How's that saying go? "Nudity loves company"? No, that's not right. But your queen is looking forward to what comes next, regardless.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Saaaay, ~name~... you into being kidnapped? Bein' tied up, &lt;i&gt;all tight&lt;/i&gt;?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">So much better than seeing you shrink down to half your size!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">... &lt;br&gt; &lt;i&gt;(This is good material.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-surprise.png">H-hum...
 &lt;br&gt; &lt;i&gt;(Why is that helping?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-4">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Very nice! Very nice! Your powerful frame will serve my army well!</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Oh please! I spent years only wearing studded leather bands. Quit your bellyaching about losing your shirt.</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Oooh, a nice manly chest... Good. Give me something to appreciate!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">The pecs at last, eh? I guess you knew they can't hold a candle to the ones I've got in my &lt;i&gt;other&lt;/i&gt; form.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">&lt;i&gt;Ugh.&lt;/i&gt; You still have so far to go -- and here I am sitting on my dry bones! At least you look pleasantly strong...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="60" />
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="8">
                <condition filter="athletic" role="target" />
                <state img="#-horny.png">Damn! That's pretty good, hot stuff!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="13" oneShotId="270">
                <condition filter="skinny" role="target" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Feh, ya look like a real beanpole. Nobody notices the guys that're all skin and bones -- someone oughta fatten you up!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="12" oneShotId="269">
                <condition filter="chubby" role="target" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">Whats'a matter, fatso, you eat too much pasta? Well, lucky for you, I don't mind that body type -- but I'll be sure you get a real workout soon!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="11" oneShotId="268">
                <condition filter="muscular" role="target" />
                <state img="#-horny.png">Niiiice chest, ~name~. Maybe after the game we can get together and compare our pecs.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-4">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Now we're even.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">A manly physique! Now show your Queen more!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-horny.png">I think I can speak for everyone here when I say "Nice." What else do have for your queen?</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">I’d love to grind on that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-rage.png">You're only showing me that NOW? You humiliate me, THEN taunt me like this? Why I oughta...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Yesss... Show me more.  Show your &lt;i&gt;Queen&lt;/i&gt; some more!  I demand it!  Gya ha ha ha!</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Seeing that chest of yours just made me feel even hornier, baby!</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">What? Big deal. So what if you've got a nice chest, or or some cozy-looking abs, or... Ah, stuff it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">(W-why I am getting turned on by a man's chest!? This crown must be affecting my brain or something...)</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">Now, show us your Super Shroom! Hope it's as big as the ones in &lt;i&gt;my&lt;/i&gt; kingdom...</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Heh... Ya know, buddy, ya didn't need to play poker if you just wanted to strip for me.</state>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">Time to see if you are a worthy opponent.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Is that a Bullet Bill in your pants, or...? Well, we're about to find out.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Oh yes! There we are! Give Mama the goods!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">What's taking you so long? Take that off or I'll bite it off myself!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Have you got a surprise for us, ~target~? I sure hope it's a big one, 'cause I'm a bit hungry...</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Hmph.  Presenting yourself only after I've finished? How cruel.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">You think you have something down there that will impress me? Well, flop it out and let's see it.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Time for ~name~ to show us his mushroom. This should be entertaining.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">I hope it's good enough for royalty. You don't want to know what I do to my servants that disappoint me...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_small_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-angry.png">What is that thing? I was expecting a giant Wiggler, not a tiny Biddybud. Why would you even start playing if you knew you were going to disappoint everyone?</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Well... that's disappointing, ya limp-dicked wimp.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">That‘s so pathetic...</state>
                <state img="#-surprise.png">O-oh! Is this your small form? Did I hit you that hard?</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">Such a POOR tribute... I'd ask what you'll do to make it up to me, but what could you POSSIBLY have to offer? At least I'm still CRUSHING you -- so get ready for more of that, pipsqueak!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">You made me wait for THAT? &lt;i&gt;Please.&lt;/i&gt; I've seen bigger on a Toad. What am I supposed to do with something so pathetic?</state>
                <state img="#-resigned.png">You really packin' a pecker &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; puny? Yeesh... If I put it between &lt;i&gt;these&lt;/i&gt; gazongas, it'd get so lost we'd never see it again.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">O-oh... uhhmm... That's surprisingly adorable...</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Another small mushroom. I could've stayed in my kingdom for that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Ha! Looks like ~name~ is packing a Mini Mushroom. Tell me -- if you get a blowjob, does your partner shrink to half their size?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">BWA HA HA! Pathetic, just like the rest of you! You're not pleasing anyone with that, buster!</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">I hear Mario's is pretty small, too. Might explain his hero complex.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-resigned.png">If only the wait was as short...</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Too late to pleasure me, y'know... Not like you would've -- I've seen Goombas bigger than you!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Can't relate.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-surprise.png">You're hiding a mushroom in your pants and you didn't even tell any of us!? ...Whaddaya mean I can't eat it? That's what Mario always does!</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">You're not really leaving me much to work with here.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Really? That's it? You should've at least used a Super Mushroom before facing me!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Is that all? You should have collected more power-ups before arriving.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-4">
                <state img="#-resigned.png">I'm not even going to dignify that with a proper reaction.</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">You call that tiny thing a dick? Mine was ten times the size of that piddly little peashooter!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-angry.png">Want me to give you a Super Crown? That way, I'd at &lt;i&gt;least&lt;/i&gt; have something interesting to look at for the rest of the game!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_medium_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Y'ever heard the saying, "It's not the size that matters; it's the way you use it"?</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Gyahaha!  A fair tribute for the Queen of the Koopas... And is it just me, or were you pretty EAGER to present it?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-9">
                <state img="#-horny.png">At last, we get to see what you were hiding down there... Now, let's see if we can make you use it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">It's not as small as I thought it would be, but it's hardly impressive. Maybe you should try eating a Mega Mushroom if you want to wow me.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Ooh... That'll do. Remind me to take you back to my castle after this is over.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-4">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">An average man with an average dick... Can't you do something remarkable for a change?</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Aesthetically pleasing -- but mine was bigger!</state>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">Hah! I've seen better -- heck, I've &lt;i&gt;got&lt;/i&gt; better! I could take this crown off and show you the proof...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-resigned.png">It's a nice size... But it would have been nice to see before I finished...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I... I think I should try slipping in one more finger.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_large_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="8" id="54">
                <condition filter="huge_penis" role="target" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png">Whoa! And I thought I had a monster cock in my original form!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <condition filter="huge_penis" role="target" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png">That's... bigger than mine normally is...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition filter="huge_penis" role="target" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png">It's almost as big as my tail!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">Now THAT is a Mega Mushroom!  I've, uh, seen bigger though.  Like when I'm not wearing this crown, for example...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Whoa, that thing is &lt;i&gt;thick!&lt;/i&gt; it's nothing compared to my tail, but, y'know... it's impressive for a human!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7" id="53">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Pffft. I've been bigger.</state>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">I see you want the help of your Queen!</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Hmmm... Yes, this will do NICELY! Your Queen appreciates this EXCELLENT tribute, gweheheh!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9" id="55">
                <state img="#-flustered.png">..!?</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">You ever heard of the grapefruit technique?</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Mmm... Now that's a warp pipe I wouldn't mind going down on!</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">...Dang, is that mushroom of yours a 1-Up? Because I wanna go again now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Hah! It just keeps getting better!</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Ahhhh... Now this... THIS is what I call FITTING TRIBUTE! Your Queen is pleased!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-horny.png">God damn! Look at that warp pipe! Come over here and explore my world, why don'tcha!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-4">
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">Oh my~ &lt;br&gt; You know, your Princess may be in another castle. But I'm... right... &lt;i&gt;here.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Why don't we make some new Koopalings?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Talk about a Mega Shroom, my goodness~</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-2" oneShotId="566">
                <condition role="target" character="marinette" />
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Fitting that you call yourself Ladybug, 'cause you're getting &lt;i&gt;squashed!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7" oneShotId="884">
                <alternative>
                    <condition filter="small_breasts" role="target" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <condition filter="medium_breasts" role="target" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">GWAHAHA! We all know the only royal-grade rack here belongs to ME! It's okay to be scared!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-horny.png">It's about time we got to see your &lt;i&gt;Boo&lt;/i&gt;-bies. Bwahahaha!</state>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">C'mon, let's see what you're packin'... You're gonna need to break out the &lt;i&gt;heavy&lt;/i&gt; shells if you wanna beat MY bombshell bazongas! GWAHAHA!</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">That's it; come to Mama...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">That's right, ~name~, you runt. Show the Queen your titties.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">Don't be intimidated by my massive funbags, ~name~... Any nice-looking pair's gonna be fun for me to play with.</state>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">Welcome to the club~ &lt;br&gt; Now, continue to lose so I can claim victory.</state>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">Let's see how yours compare to mine!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4 9" id="61" />
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_small_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-7 9" id="56">
                <condition filter="boob_envy" role="target" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Hey, uh... Folks might tell you "You ain't perfect," but at the end of the day, you are who you are. Some jerks call me "fat,", some may say you're too small, but screw 'em. You're A-OK.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-surprise.png">Well. I've... never breasts like that. I mean, &lt;i&gt;Peach's&lt;/i&gt; are small, but those are as tiny as heck!</state>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">Oh my! They're &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; small? What a treat! Don't worry, ~name~ -- eat your veggies and they'll be big as a Banzai Bill one day~</state>
                <state img="#-surprise.png">Wait... ~name~, where are your tits!? Is that &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; all ya got?</state>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">Don't worry, ~name~ -- I've got enough boobs for the both of us!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">You call THOSE tits?</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">I'm going to appoint you as castle jester if you keep acting like a clown.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">I'm more into peaches than grapes, but those'll do for now...</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">They're nothing compared to mine, but I'll still take 'em!</state>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">Give me something to work with! Play with those cute nips a little, like this...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">You call THOSE tits? Look at &lt;i&gt;these&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Nice little titties ya got there, ~name~. Ya wanna feel up a REAL pair? Come over here and Mama'll let ya have a squeeze -- but I can't promise I won't return the favor! BWA HA HA!</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Not bad coming from a pipsqueak like you! They're nothin' like mine, of course but... not bad! Geheheh...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Ha! You call those tits? I could do my laundry on that washboard!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Small. &lt;i&gt;Really&lt;/i&gt; small. Can you even be called a woman?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-4">
                <state img="#-surprise.png">This... this makes me feel strangely motherly...</state>
                <state img="#-surprise.png">I don't get it. Isn't milk production a big deal for your species?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_medium_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">There's a reason that &lt;i&gt;I'm&lt;/i&gt; the Koopa Queen!</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Nice tits, honey, but you could do &lt;i&gt;so&lt;/i&gt; much better...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-resigned.png">Meh. They're fine... I guess. They wouldn't have done anything for ME if I was still going.</state>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">Lookin' pretty good! I MAY have lost THIS time -- but in the end, you're still a pipsqueak compared to the QUEEN of the KOOPAS!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">BWAHAHAHA! I'd love to see you try to fill out this dress with those.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-4">
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">You tried.</state>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">Nice set of peaches. Mind if I... kidnap them?</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">Why are we taking this long for those forgettable breasts? Let's go! Next hand!</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">W-wow... they're... um... Peach-y!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Well, well, well... Not bad! &lt;br&gt; ...But I'm still bigger.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="62" />
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_large_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="5-7">
                <condition role="target" character="yang_xiao_long" />
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">Heh. Gotta hand it to ya, Yang -- you've got the second-best tits at the table! Still not &lt;i&gt;quite&lt;/i&gt; as nice as mine, though~</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <test expr="~background.location~" value="indoors" />
                <state img="#-horny.png">Damn, is it hotter than lava in here, or is it just me?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Wanna compare sizes, babe?</state>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">Oh, look at those! And no black magic or crown involved either. Your &lt;i&gt;Queen&lt;/i&gt; is &lt;i&gt;pleased&lt;/i&gt;, geheheh.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">&lt;i&gt;Whew...&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br&gt; You could break POW Blocks with those~</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-happy.png">This just keeps getting better and better!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-rage.png">Listen well, ~name~. I'm still the Queen, &lt;i&gt;got it&lt;/i&gt;?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Nice! Obviously not as good as the pair of melons I'm rocking, of course. But you got a nice rack yourself, and I don't usually give away free compliments.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Well, well, well! Looks like I'm not the only one with an impressive chest at this table.</state>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">Tits that big are just &lt;i&gt;begging&lt;/i&gt; to get squeezed together... Go on, ~name~, try and make your elbows meet. Your Queen commands it!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Ooooh... definitely worth kidnapping! I'd even let you choose whether the crown stays on.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-4">
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">Not bad... Not bad! Not as great as MINE, but pretty close~!</state>
                <state img="#-surprise.png">Whoa! Those are some GIANT Thwomps, ~name~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-7">
                <state img="#-flustered.png">Whoa, whoa, WHOA! Are you actually giving me some competition, ~name~!? I thought there wasn't gonna be ANYONE here who could match my power!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="twilight" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">Whoa-ho-ho! Starting with the panties already, Princess?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">So it's finally time to see what ~name~ has going on down there...! Well, now. Don't keep me waiting, babe.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Hey, you're distracting everybody... If a Queen's gotta put her jack-off session on full display, she should at &lt;i&gt;least&lt;/i&gt; be the main attraction!</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">About time!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-9">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Enough with the snotworks, faucet face! You don't see me whining about being naked, do you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Yes! Unveil yourself to me!</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Hah, there we go! Show the queen your... &lt;i&gt;(What's a sexy word for vagina? Beaver? Nah, beaver sounds stupid.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Wish I'd had this view earlier...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="futaba" />
                <state img="#-horny.png" marker="bowsette_futaba_fire_crotch">Ooh, Futaba's got a fire crotch! How's about I see if I end up burning my tongue?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="5" oneShotId="5">
                <condition filter="princess" role="target" />
                <state img="#-horny.png">Delicious. They say you are what you eat, but I'm &lt;i&gt;already&lt;/i&gt; a princess... Bwahahaha!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="21" totalRounds="0">
                <state img="#-surprise.png">
                    <alt-img>#-angry.png</alt-img>
                    <alt-img>#-annoyed.png</alt-img>
                    <alt-img>#-awkward.png</alt-img>
                    <alt-img>#-cocky.png</alt-img>
                    <alt-img>#-flaunt.png</alt-img>
                    <alt-img>#-flustered.png</alt-img>
                    <alt-img>#-happy.png</alt-img>
                    <alt-img>#-horny.png</alt-img>
                    <alt-img>#-rage.png</alt-img>
                    <alt-img>#-resigned.png</alt-img>
                    <alt-img>#-surprise.png</alt-img>
                    <text>[Note: A female opponent has revealed her crotch as the first strip of the game.] Contribute dialogue here: https://tinyurl.com/y2on2gzf</text>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Gwahahaha! The Great Bowsette always wins!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Nnnnf -- it's about time!  Now hurry up and -- ooh -- lose faster! Your Queen demands more company!</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Still into chicks!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Mmmm... Instead of masturbating, why don't you come over here and let me eat you? Your pussy, that is.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">That looks delicious...! I might be no Yoshi, but I’ve been told that my tongue can do wonderful things.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-4">
                <state img="#-horny.png">As your glorious Koopa Queen, I declare you scissor-able!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-horny.png">You look good enough to eat!</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">All that's left is to spread those legs and cum before your Queen... So look forward to it, ~name~! BWAHAHA!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_lost">
            <case stage="5-7" id="4" oneShotId="4">
                <condition filter="princess" role="target" character="lucina" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="bowsette_lucina_build_another_princess">I can build another castle, but &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; ain't got what it takes, princess.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition filter="student" role="target" />
                <test expr="~background.time~" value="night" />
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~weekday.number~" cmp="!=" value="5" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~weekday.number~" cmp="!=" value="6" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-resigned.png" oneShotId="96" marker="ClassesTomorrow" dialogue-layer="over">Are you sure you should be playing tonight, ~name~? Don't you have school tomorrow? </state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="95" marker="ClassesTomorrow" dialogue-layer="over">I don't mean to be a typical grumpy dad, but... don't you have classes tomorrow, ~target~? Are you sure it's okay for you to be playing this late?</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png" oneShotId="97" marker="ClassesTomorrow" dialogue-layer="over" font-size="small">Shouldn't you be in bed, ~target~?&lt;br&gt;... I-I mean, I know you're a responsible adult now and you can take your own decisions, but you gotta go to class tomorrow, right? You need to be well-rested for your education!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition filter="princess" role="target" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="1">Gwahaha! I love it when princesses get shown what for!</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png" oneShotId="2">Keep those bad hands coming! I love it when princesses get just what they deserve!</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" oneShotId="32">I might be interested in watching an princess strip... so what? Aren't all of us willing to watch?</state>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png" oneShotId="33">Strip to your heart's content, princess. You will never be prettier than a queen.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition filter="princess" role="target" />
                <state img="#-cocky.png" oneShotId="7">Next time you might want to hire yourself a tutor for card games! Bwahaha!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition filter="military" role="target" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="91">You're up, soldier! Don't let me catch you slackin' on the job!</state>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png" oneShotId="92">I'd be a bad boss if I teased my army when they play strip poker. But you're not in my army, are you?~</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" oneShotId="948">
                <condition filter="furry" role="target" />
                <state img="#-resigned.png" marker="Animalese">I was wondering, how come we can understand you, ~target~? I thought all Animal Crossing folks spoke animalese or whatever that language is...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="949">
                <condition filter="adventurer" role="target" />
                <state img="#-flaunt.png" oneShotId="114" marker="Adventurer1">You look like all those fools who dare trespass into my domain. I will enjoy beating your kind again...</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png" oneShotId="115" marker="Adventurer2">Lots of people like you usually come into my castles looking for fortune or glory. You shall find neither. Not in my castle, and not here either.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <test expr="~background.temperature~" value="cold" />
                <state img="#-resigned.png">I get why you wouldn't want to strip in this place... But if you get really cold, I could always warm up the place for ya.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Get to it, ~name~! If you get too cold here, I'll just throw some fireballs at ya! Bwahaha!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">Take that, bilge brain!</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Stupid is as stupid does.</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Did you REALLY think you had a chance? HAH!</state>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">What a PATHETIC display! You BETTER make it up with a good striptease!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" priority="0">
                <test expr="~background.temperature~" value="hot" />
                <state img="#-resigned.png">In a place as hot as this one, taking off clothes feels like more of a reward...</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">Gah, don't act like you don't want it. In a place as hot as this one, anyone would want to strip!</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">This place isn't as hot as my castles, but it's still pretty hot! You should be thankful for undressing here!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_stripping">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="yang_xiao_long" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-cocky.png" marker="bowsette_yang_like_your_style">Yo! Goldilocks! I like your style. You got a hard head and a fiery spirit to back it up. I can respect that. We should hang out after this.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="erufuda" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-flaunt.png" marker="bowsette_erufuda_fastfood">Did you know I once tried to conquer Dinosaur World with poisoned fast food? Eating it turned those dumb cave people into Chickadactyls -- who I fried up and sold to the dinos!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" oneShotId="930">
                <condition role="target" character="moon" />
                <state img="#-angry.png">Can somebody tell this little lady what the point of the game is?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" oneShotId="943">
                <condition filter="blonde" role="target" />
                <test expr="~clothing.generic~" value="dress" />
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">A blonde woman stripping a dress... Now THIS is a view I could get used to!</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Take your time, ~name~. I don't usually get to watch blondies taking off their dresses...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition filter="adventurer" role="target" />
                <state img="#-cocky.png" oneShotId="118">Hand over the loot, loser.</state>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png" oneShotId="119">Losing your equipment this early? You haven't finished exploring my mazes yet!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <test expr="~clothing~" value="hat" />
                <state img="#-resigned.png" dialogue-layer="over">Good thinking, covering up your noggin like that. Wouldn't wanna risk getting Captured -- who KNOWS what kinda creepy stuff some paisano might do while wearing your face?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <test expr="~clothing.generic~" value="dress" />
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">I suggest ripping your dress off. It ALWAYS makes a good impression!</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Dresses look good, but... I don't really know how to take them off, so I kinda just rip them off...</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">Who's got time to figure out how to take off dresses, anyway? Just rip the whole thing off! It's WAY easier!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Piece by piece, you'll lose to my unrivaled poker skills! </state>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">It's not so bad, is it? At least WE are enjoying the view! Bwahaha!</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Take your time. Let me savor the taste of victory.</state>
                <state img="#-surprise.png" dialogue-layer="over">Oh no! Not your ~clothing~! What ever shall a fire-breathing, shape-shifting, hammer-throwing monarch do against that?</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" dialogue-layer="over">Most of my underlings and minions are usually naked, so... I never considered how someone wearing &lt;i&gt;more&lt;/i&gt; clothing could make you want to undress them...</state>
                <state img="#-resigned.png">Do you really need your ~clothing~? ~clothing.ifPlural(Are they|Is it)~ really that important to you?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Move out, everyone! ~Target~ is taking off ~target.ifMale(his|her)~ ~clothing~!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_stripped">
            <case stage="0-9" id="23" oneShotId="597">
                <alternative>
                    <condition role="target" character="marinette" stage="2" />
                    <condition role="other" character="adrien" stage="2-10" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <condition role="target" character="adrien" stage="2" />
                    <condition role="other" character="marinette" stage="2-10" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-surprise.png">You have a secret identity, too?!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="22" oneShotId="596">
                <alternative>
                    <condition role="target" character="marinette" stage="2" />
                    <condition role="other" character="adrien" stage="0-1" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <condition role="target" character="adrien" stage="2" />
                    <condition role="other" character="marinette" stage="0-1" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-surprise.png">THAT'S your secret identity?!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="erufuda" stage="4" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="bowsette_erufuda_fastfood" />
                <state img="#-cocky.png" marker="bowsette_erufuda_finest_ingredients">But even polymorphed cave people are still better for you than whatever they put in those fries you're eating. I only used the finest ingredients in my chicken transformation food!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <condition role="target" character="mulan" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="bowsette_mulan_so_familiar">Wow. A woman pretending to be a man... Why does that sound so familiar? Oh right...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="moon" stage="6" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" marker="bowsette_moon_too_enthusiastic">You're too enthusiastic to be losing so hard.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <test expr="~clothing~" value="hat" />
                <state img="#-angry.png">Ya can't trust someone with headwear. What're they hidin' under that hat?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Come on, you've got a long way to go! </state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Bwahaha! You should just give up now! </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="twilight" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png">&lt;i&gt;(If kidnapping Peach has never worked out for me, perhaps Twilight might be a better hostage...)&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br&gt; Uh, can you repeat that, Twilight? I was thinking about... something else.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition count="0" status="masturbating" />
                <condition count="0" status="finished" />
                <state img="#-horny.png">The stakes for these crossover minigames sure have escalated a lot in recent years! Your queen approves!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-angry.png">What a joke! Put some muscle into it, ~name~!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-angry.png">Yeah, yeah, congrats on finishing.  What do you want, a fireworks show?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Good boy! Now put on a show.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Go on, touch your cock, loser! That's apparently all you're good for!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-horny.png">The Queen gets what she wants. Come here!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-angry.png">Couldn't you have done this earlier? It's common sense to cater to a lady. Especially if that lady is a queen!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="7">
                <condition role="target" character="kamina" />
                <state img="#-horny.png">Oh, Kamina... Let's see what you can do with that big drill of yours.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">At least I get someone to look at... but ya best not get anything on me, ya hear?</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">You can look all you want, ~target~! My raw sexual energy might make you come even faster than me! Bwahahaha!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">Take your time, ~name~. You've got plenty to look at for inspiration.</state>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">Hey now, hot stuff, I don't mind putting on a little show for your entertainment. Whaddaya say?</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Heh heh heh... You know, ~name~, I think I might be just about ready for Round Two.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-resigned.png">Well, that was... less than fun, but I suppose I can work with it. Show me that you can hold your own and I'll consider taking you on.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">Y'know, since you brought me down to this, you at least deserve to look at this great rack.</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Now &lt;i&gt;that's&lt;/i&gt; a good boy.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Oh my~ Now &lt;i&gt;this&lt;/i&gt; is a performance befitting a Queen!</state>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">Feel free to look at me while you wipe your pipe, ~name~~</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-4" id="63" />
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_masturbating">
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Yes, I know that you‘re beating your meat to ME!</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">You looking at me, honey? Go ahead, just don't splatter on me. Cum is &lt;i&gt;so&lt;/i&gt; hard to clean up.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Why don't you run off and find some green pipe to hide in?</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">Your queen demands better. GO FASTER, PEASANT!</state>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">I see you want the help of your Queen!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-4">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Honey, slow down for Bowsette. I wanna cum with you, not after you!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Is that really how guys like you do it? Seems a bit rough... I like it!</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Usually I don't like it when some schmoe slides down the flagpole, but...</state>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">What, is this cleavage all ya need to jerk it THAT hard? Or are ya just some weirdo who's into panties~?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">If you need to see more, just beat me! Oh, wait -- you &lt;i&gt;can't&lt;/i&gt; anymore.</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Maybe if you beg, I'll show you a bit of my leg~</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">Remember, good grammar is important! It ain't "Can I cum for my Queen?" it's &lt;i&gt;"May&lt;/i&gt; I cum for my Queen?"!</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Oh, what's the rush, boy? Take your time. I want to SAVOR this, geheheh.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-9">
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">This must be awkward for you, ~name~, jerking off while I'm here like this.  Is it gay? Is it hot? Maybe both?</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Y'know a queen needs her throne, right? I think your face might do. You should feel honored I'm even considering it!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">I'll let you look at me while you do that. You'd best feel HONORED -- I haven't looked in a mirror much since I got this crown, but I do know I look AMAZING, BAHAHA!</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Don't worry, ~name~. It wouldn't be gay for either of us if we helped each other out with this...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">You know, ~name~, I'm always up for having a man help me try out this new body....</state>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">Don't think I don't see you glancing my way, chump. Hah, I can't blame you anyways! I'd look at me too!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">Here... If you need help, you're welcome to  appreciate the beauty of your Queen~</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_heavy_masturbating">
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">What's the matter? Need a little motivation? Well, tough titties, chump! Bwhahaha!</state>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">That's it, bow down before your Koopa Queen like a good subject~</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Yeah, keep goin'. You wanna cum on my tits, don'tcha?</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">&lt;i&gt;(Heh... Gotta wonder what it's like to have one of those inside you...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">I'm still covered from head to toe and you're rubbing your pole like &lt;i&gt;that?&lt;/i&gt; I mean, what are you even doing it to?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">You look like you're about to burst! Well, show mama Koopa a good cumshot -- don't let all that build-up go to waste now.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Almost there, huh, ~name~...? Ha! Well, if you're &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; eager, go ahead and cum for me~</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-angry.png">Hey! Watch where you aim that thing.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-4">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Be a good little subject and cum for your Queen! Show me your devotion with every stroke!</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Yes... Finish for me, and maybe I'll have a place for you in my castle.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Wish we could've finished together; that looks like fun...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition filter="small_penis" role="target" />
                <state img="#-cocky.png">All that work for just a little dribble? I'll show you later how it feels to get blasted with a firehose.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-4">
                <state img="#-flustered.png">Hey! It's getting everywhere!?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-resigned.png">Gosh, you're easy, aren't you?</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">Whoa, whoa, HEY -- don't shoot over &lt;i&gt;here!&lt;/i&gt; You'll mess my dress up!</state>
                <state img="#-surprise.png">Oh! Such an ample offering for your Queen. &lt;br&gt; ...Where were you even keeping all of that? ...I mean, regardless, this pleases me!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">A fine tribute -- hey, I've never gotten tributes AFTER I lost! Maybe this poker thing isn't so bad. GWAHAHA!</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Well, look who's all full of spunk! Though, not anymore I guess, BWAHAHA!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-horny.png">...THERE you go. Let that puddle of cum be a reminder -- NEVER mess with the Koopa Troop! Though it looks like losing wasn't all that bad for you either, BWAHAHA!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-angry.png">What a quickshot. Honestly! You could at least last until your Queen finishes before you go blowin' your load!</state>
                <state img="#-surprise.png">Whoa. That's a lot for your size!</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Gwahaha... Yes, that's it! Quiver and moan before your superior~</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Hmm... Gweheheh, just &lt;i&gt;look&lt;/i&gt; at that load! Good boy -- I accept this tribute.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">Thanks for takin' the plunge &lt;i&gt;for&lt;/i&gt; me, babe. And I &lt;i&gt;do&lt;/i&gt; hope to see your finger plunging there.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-resigned.png">I knew I'd beat you, but honestly, this is a little pathetic. You better make it worth it, girly.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-4">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">No hero to jump in and save you? Or is he hiding somewhere around here, waiting to enjoy the show with us?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">You'd fit in really well in my dungeon... with a pair of shackles. Gagged and chained!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Oh, yes... Looks like it's time for a little good old-fashioned humiliation, huh, ~name~? I'm gonna get a kick outta &lt;i&gt;this.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Spread your legs wide, ya hear? This is my winnings, so I get to have a good look at the spoils!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Well, well, well... Look who decided to join me. Now sit down, shut up, and take notes if you need.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Why don't you scooch a little closer...? Let me show you how a Koopa chick does it!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Well, you're not very good at cards, it seems. How about we see how good you are at... other things? Perhaps if you do a good job, I'll take you with me!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Jill, peasant. Jill for your queen!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-4">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Gweheheh... Your admission of defeat to the Koopa Troop has been noted.  WELL AND DULY noted!</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I haven't really played with myself a lot since turning into this. Hopefully I can pick up a couple pointers...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">Ah, GOOD... Now, take your time -- I want to SAVOR this victory. And if you're good, I might even let you ask me to step on you. GWA HA HA!</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Go on! Get your claws in there!</state>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">Heh, I should've known that showin' these two off would get you guys going! Not that I'm complaining~</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Hey, ~target~ -- if you want to give everybody a REAL show, I can lend a hand.</state>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">Well, better late than never. I showed you how to do it -- now don't screw it up too much.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-7" id="16" oneShotId="539" priority="900">
                <condition gender="female" role="target" />
                <condition count="1" status="masturbating" />
                <state img="#-cocky.png">So &lt;i&gt;that's&lt;/i&gt; how this business is done, huh...? It ain't no tough task for the Queen of the Koopas -- but don't bet on me trying it out in front of &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; chumps! It'll have to wait when I get home.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" oneShotId="527">
                <condition filter="princess" role="target" />
                <condition count="0" role="target" character="peach" />
                <state img="#-horny.png">You know? I could have you instead of Princess Peach. Nah, screw that -- I could have you AND her at the same time! That sounds lovely~</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7" oneShotId="937">
                <condition role="target" character="neptune" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="bowsette_neptune_uranus" weight="5">Whoa, now...! Careful there, Neptune -- I think I saw Uranus!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="3" oneShotId="3">
                <condition role="target" character="amalia" />
                <state img="#-horny.png" marker="bowsette_amalia_pirhana_plant" weight="5">I'd love to see you get "seeded" by a Piranha Plant, Amalia. Now THAT would be a sight to see!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" oneShotId="341">
                <condition filter="chair_forfeit" role="target" />
                <state img="#-rage.png">Wait! Why does &lt;i&gt;she&lt;/i&gt; get a seat and I don't?! This is an outrage! I demand a chair too!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <alternative>
                    <condition count="0" role="opp" character="peach" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <condition role="opp" character="peach" stage="0-8" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-horny.png">I wonder if this is how Peach does this...?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-4">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Lovely.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">So, uh. That... m-movement you're doing right now -- does it hurt? C-could you show me?</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">My tongue isn't as long as it used to be, but I'm positive it can find all the right places...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">That’s right, pump those little fingers in and out for me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">This mouth is too small to devour you, ~name~. But don't think I can't still "eat" you the other way.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">You'll never be able to spread those legs as wide as I can!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Better slow down before I decide to join in.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-horny.png">You creeps have ABSOLUTELY no idea what's going on in my imagination right about now!</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Why don't you come over here, ~name~? I can show you what a real QUEEN can do!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">That's right. Humiliate yourself for your Queen!</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">What's that, ~name~...? See something you like?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_heavy_masturbating">
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Can we hurry this up? I gotta get back to my castle before that darn plumber shows up again.</state>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">If you want me to pose, you can ask, y'know?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-horny.png">That's what I like to see! Now look this way so I can enjoy the view when you finish.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Come on. Finish for your Queen's enjoyment!</state>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">H-hey.... If you need something to help you get over the edge... You can just watch me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-horny.png">You go, girl! Show us how it's done!</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Gwahaha... Yes, squirm for the mighty Koopa Queen~!</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Ohhh...  Now &lt;i&gt;look&lt;/i&gt; at you go. So fast! So INTENSE! It's like you touched a Super Star -- or like YOU'RE a Super Star, gweheheh...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Getting close? Look at you, you're a hot mess.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Here &lt;i&gt;cums&lt;/i&gt; the best part!  &lt;i&gt;(Heheh, I crack myself up.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Looks like you're almost to the goal~</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="peach" />
                <state img="#-horny.png" marker="bowsette_peach_just_the_two_of_us">Maybe the next time I kidnap you, Princess, we can play this game again... but with just the two of us, hmm?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Already?</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">A worthy show for such an unworthy opponent, my dear!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Bwahaha... Bet I can make you do &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; again!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Dang, now THAT'S a squirt!</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">When I lose to Mario, it's a lonely feeling. It's kind of nice to split the loss this time...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Such intensity... Such PASSION! Gweheheh -- I'd like to extend an invitation to come to my castle after the game...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-horny.png">That was HOT! Can't wait to see everyone else do that!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-4">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Damn, you must want me to kidnap you, don't you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-horny.png">It is I who nuts to that!</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Oooh~ What an excellent display there, ~name~~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Finished? Good. I hope you thought of me when you were touching yourself.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Gweheheh... It feels good to see others taste defeat for once!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate_first">
            <case stage="7">
                <condition count="0" role="self" hasHand="High Card" />
                <condition count="0" role="self" hasHand="One Pair" />
                <condition count="0" role="self" hasHand="Two Pair" />
                <state img="#-flustered.png">B-but, I... I had good cards this time...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-angry.png">&lt;i&gt;What? NO!&lt;/i&gt; I refuse! I &lt;i&gt;will NOT&lt;/i&gt; be the first one to do such a thing! I demand one of you to do it instead o-o-or a rematch or.... &lt;i&gt;Fuck!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-rage.png">We need a new dealer.</state>
                <state img="#-rage.png">I demand a recount! There's no way--- there's no way that I lost!</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">H-hold on a sec! I haven't really gotten much of a chance to play around with this body... &lt;i&gt;(Let alone masturbate with it.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-rage.png">Curses! I'm so tired of this game!</state>
                <state img="#-rage.png">GRAAAAH! WHY ME?! I DESERVE BETTER THAN THIS -- DO YOU {b}KNOW{!reset} WHO I {b}AM?{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">A &lt;i&gt;queen&lt;/i&gt; like me, losing like this?! Unbelievable!</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">Um! Uh...! T-The princess you're looking for is in another castle!</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">F-first!? But I don't have much experience as a woman...</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">What!? I'm supposed to be the final boss here! Not some flimsy first stage goon!</state>
                <state img="#-rage.png">One of you punks must have cheated for me to lose this fast...</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">F-fine! I wanted to give this body a test ride anyways!</state>
                <state img="#-rage.png">Dead Last!!! I'm not some lowly Goomba to be taken out first!!! I'm Bowsette, ruler of the Koopa Kingdom, dammit! GRRRAAAHHH!!!!!</state>
                <state img="#-resigned.png">Defeated AGAIN. BAH! And this time, Mario wasn't even involved. Am I losing my touch? No, that can't be it. I must have just gotten unlucky. YEAH!</state>
                <state img="#-rage.png">GRAWRR! This can't be happening! Defeated AGAIN! Just you WAIT! Next time you won't be so LUCKY! &lt;br&gt;...Alright, let me just sit down here.</state>
                <state img="#-rage.png">NO! NO! I am NOT supposed to be classed as a first-level boss! I REFUSE to be thrown into such a low ranking of -- ah, screw it... Fine.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate">
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-resigned.png">So long, gay Bowser...</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">It's everyone's favorite time: &lt;br&gt; BOWSETTE TIME!</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">You better appreciate this!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Ha...! I &lt;i&gt;was&lt;/i&gt; tempted to take off my crown, but I doubt you chumps could handle the manly might of the Koopa King. Plus, I'm kinda just looking forward to the forfeit at this point.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">&lt;i&gt;Bah.&lt;/i&gt; I'm pretty sure this deck's almost as stacked as &lt;i&gt;I&lt;/i&gt; am -- but obviously not in &lt;i&gt;my&lt;/i&gt; favor.</state>
                <state img="#-resigned.png">GAH! Well, it was bound to happen eventually. At least I'll get to enjoy this.</state>
                <state img="#-rage.png">Why the heck are you staring at &lt;i&gt;me!?&lt;/i&gt; At least wait until I'm too horny to care!</state>
                <state img="#-rage.png">This is &lt;i&gt;bull honky&lt;/i&gt;!  How can I lose to a nobody like you!?</state>
                <state img="#-rage.png">You find this funny?! You won't find it funny when I burn you to ashes!</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Oh...? Well, well, well. Looks like it's showtime! Watch me carefully, ~player~.</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">I'm gonna flippin' love this... But you might like it more than me. Ha, as if!</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Okay. Keep in mind I'm not used to using my... uh... mammal parts. Let alone the specifically female parts.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Well... Let’s get to it.</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">Bwuh...!? O-okay then! Don't have much practice with this but here I go!</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">Mama mia!</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">Gwahaha! Haha! ...Ha? &lt;br&gt; I LOST?! Cheating is supposed to make you WIN!</state>
                <state img="#-resigned.png">Ugh! Yes, YES, I'm doing it. The Queen of the Koopas ALWAYS keeps her word! Even if the rule is stupid.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="start_masturbating">
            <case stage="7">
                <condition count="3-4" status="decent" role="opp" />
                <state img="#-starting.png" marker="FantasyForfeit">Well... It's gonna be a while until any of you get to do what I'm about to do, so I suggest you keep playing while I keep to myself!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-starting.png">I'm only doing this cause I'm pent up. Nothing more.</state>
                <state img="#-starting.png">...O-okay, but seriously. I haven't had much experience with this...</state>
                <state img="#-starting.png">You're lucky I'm enjoying this like crazy... but I have to ask... Are &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; enjoying the view at all?</state>
                <state img="#-starting.png">Put away your flammable objects before I start spitting fire!</state>
                <state img="#-starting.png">Guess it's your lucky day, chumps. Bet'cha never seen a sight like THIS before, eh?</state>
                <state img="#-starting.png">So &lt;i&gt;what&lt;/i&gt; if I lost? Don't think I'm not taking the rest of you down with me! S-somehow...</state>
                <state img="#-starting.png">J-just give me a moment, I'm still figuring things out... seems simple en-- oh... OH!</state>
                <state img="#-starting.png">I'm pretty sure this is how the princesses do it...? Mostly sure. I haven't seen them do it directly, I mean.</state>
                <state img="#-starting.png">I can't believe I lost... I never lose! Well...Except maybe that one time... or that other time...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="masturbating">
            <case stage="8" oneShotId="582">
                <test expr="~human.gender~" value="male" />
                <state img="#-horny.png">Mmmm... Hope you're in the mood for laying some pipe!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" oneShotId="932">
                <condition count="2-" status="alive" />
                <state img="#-horny.png" weight="5">Come on! Lose already so you can give me a hand... or perhaps something else?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FantasyForfeit" />
                <state img="#-angry.png" oneShotId="47" weight="1.5">&lt;i&gt;(I can't believe I lost so easily... I must be getting rusty)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" oneShotId="48">&lt;i&gt;(I didn't expect this to feel so good... Doing it in another body is a completely different experience...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-resigned.png" oneShotId="49" weight="1.5">&lt;i&gt;(Next time, I've gotta remember to cheat smarter, not harder)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-heavyA.png" oneShotId="50">&lt;i&gt;(... Is it wrong that I'm thinking about how good the Vibe Scepter would feel right now? Guh...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-heavyB.png" oneShotId="51">&lt;i&gt;(Nobody tells you that you gotta use different fingers for different results... I thought you could just use any of them to get the same feeling)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-heavyC.png" oneShotId="52">&lt;i&gt;(It tickles! Why didn't I try this before?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" oneShotId="53">&lt;i&gt;(Now I get to know how this feels in a female humanoid body, but now I wonder how would it feel on a female koopa body...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="54">&lt;i&gt;(It's kind of pathetic to be the doing this while everyone else is still playing, but I might as well get it over with...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-resigned.png" oneShotId="55">&lt;i&gt;(Well, at least now I get to know exactly where the clitoris is on a human body. I don't know what I'll do with that knowledge, but... the more you know.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png" oneShotId="56">&lt;i&gt;(I should just take the damn crown off and get to it like a normal koopa... But what's the point of using the crown in the first place if I'm gonna chicken out as soon as things get weird?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-surprise.png" oneShotId="57">&lt;i&gt;(Guh! W-what's this...?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-heavyC.png" oneShotId="58">&lt;i&gt;(Bwahaha... Grr... Gwahahaha....)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" oneShotId="59">&lt;i&gt;(I expected this body to give me different fantasies, but I still like what I like... I guess you can't just change who you like, bwahaha...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-heavyC.png" oneShotId="60">&lt;i&gt;(Well, at least by the time everyone's doing this, I'll get to watch them and enjoy myself)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="61">&lt;i&gt;(I need to pay attention to how others do this when they get to it... I could learn a thing or two from both sexes now)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png" oneShotId="62">&lt;i&gt;(Everyone is gonna be so focused on the game, they won't be looking at me! I can do whatever I want and they won't care!)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-heavyA.png" oneShotId="63">&lt;i&gt;(... Could I use my tail...? No, no, that's a dumb idea. I feel like an idiot just for considering it)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png" oneShotId="64">&lt;i&gt;(Next time I should bring a dice. At least there's spicy things you can do with a dice in bed)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" oneShotId="65">&lt;i&gt;(I kind of wish they were looking at me... Bwahaha, have I always been this needy for attention...? )&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-surprise.png" oneShotId="66">&lt;i&gt;(What if... I came back with my original body later? Everyone here looks the same, I'd definitely stand out! I could rule this place!)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-horny.png">&lt;i&gt;(Whoa, this feels so good... No wonder she does this like crazy whenever I've got her locked up!)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Sure, Peach can bake you a cake, but will she let ya make a cream pie?</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">Dammit, ~player~... why don't you flick your tongue over my clit? Make yerself useful...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Is it I who nuts to that -- or is it &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; who nuts to &lt;i&gt;me?&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">If you've got any complaints on how I'm doing, please direct them to the complaints box in Dark Land. My Hammer Bros will be happy to hear your complaints, and also throw you in my dungeon.</state>
                <state img="#-surprise.png">Oh wow, this feels really good.  This is way better than how I used to do it!</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">You looking at me? Good! Go ahead and take notes!</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">These creeps actually dare to gaze upon the Queen of Koopas...? I mean, I don't &lt;i&gt;mind,&lt;/i&gt; but would it kill you to cower at least a &lt;i&gt;little?&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-heavyA.png">G-Gwah... My body's on fire! Like all of the times I've fallen into lava...</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">GRAAAAAAARGH! ...Nah, doesn't really strike fear when I'm in this position, does it?</state>
                <state img="#-resigned.png">N-not gonna look at me...? That's fine... Have it your way...</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">How did I even let myself get convinced to come here... N-not that I'm regretting it! I LIKE being here! I OWN my choices!</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">H-hey! I've got this crown on and I'm looking all pretty-princess-like, so the least you can do is actually &lt;i&gt;look&lt;/i&gt; at me!</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Good thing I've got proper hands for this... I doubt my usual big, meaty claws would do the trick.</state>
                <state img="#-heavyC.png">Oh, gosh... So &lt;i&gt;good.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-rage.png">...W-what? No, I didn't say any names! You hear me? I DIDN'T SAY ANY NAMES, YOU DIDN'T HEAR ANYTHING!</state>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">I'm a hundred times better than Peach, aren't I?</state>
                <state img="#-resigned.png">I wonder how it'd feel to jerk off with &lt;i&gt;these&lt;/i&gt; hands... Nah, ain't happenin'. Even if I could keep my King Koopa cock, no way these dainty things could handle the girth &lt;i&gt;or&lt;/i&gt; the spines.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I've gotta hand it to the crown, it was a good call to give me these dainty little hands. There's no way I could -- or WOULD -- touch myself like this with big ol' claws!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="heavy_masturbating">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-heavyC.png">Yes, Yes, YES! &lt;i&gt;YES!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-heavyB.png">It's... so messy...</state>
                <state img="#-heavyB.png">Bwah... ha... &lt;i&gt;hhhhhah...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-heavyB.png">Ungh... I'll get you... for this... &lt;i&gt;fff--&lt;/i&gt; ...So good...</state>
                <state img="#-heavyB.png">&lt;i&gt;Owh... Grrrr...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-heavyB.png">&lt;i&gt;Urk... haaah...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-heavyB.png">Hnnng... N-no, not yet... Not coming for you ungrateful bums yet...</state>
                <state img="#-heavyC.png">Ngh... T-This heat is incredible!</state>
                <state img="#-heavyA.png">Ah-- Ahhn~ &lt;br&gt; I'm... getting c-close~!</state>
                <state img="#-heavyA.png">Ohhh motherfffff-- fudge... I shouldn't swear, but I'm so... effin' close...!</state>
                <state img="#-heavyB.png">Did it just -- &lt;i&gt;Oh~&lt;/i&gt; -- get hotter in here? Mmh~</state>
                <state img="#-heavyA.png">Hahh! HAHH! Oh, it's a different heat -- hahh, a different FIRE!</state>
                <state img="#-heavyB.png">Hahh! Hahh!  It's good....it's SO GOOD!  Hahh! Can't...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finishing_masturbating">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-finishing.png">&lt;i&gt;Grh...&lt;/i&gt; GAAAAAAO!</state>
                <state img="#-finishing.png">OH, MARIOOOOOOO!</state>
                <state img="#-finishing.png">O-oh -- ~player~, &lt;i&gt;FFFFFFUCK...!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-finishing.png">&lt;i&gt;Mnnn... nnn... Princess... {b}Peach...!{!reset}&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-finishing.png">MARIOOOOO~!</state>
                <state img="#-finishing.png">Ahh -- so HOT... Can't control... YES!  Nnngghhh-- AHHHH!</state>
                <state img="#-finishing.png">Yes...! Yes, invade my castle...! Mmm-- Oh, &lt;i&gt;MARIO!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-finishing.png">The... Mushroom Kingdom... is... MINE!</state>
                <state img="#-finishing.png">RRRRRRAAAAAAAWWRR!</state>
                <state img="#-finishing.png">...hnngrRRRAAAAUGH!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-finished.png">Well -- that was &lt;i&gt;nice.&lt;/i&gt; I could honestly go again...!</state>
                <state img="#-finished.png">Almost as good as when I use my tail. &lt;i&gt;Almost.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-finished.png">Wow... And I thought the Grand Stars made me feel great!</state>
                <state img="#-finished.png">Ahhh, always feels good to do that! When you want a job done right, you've gotta do it yourself.</state>
                <state img="#-finished.png">Gwahaha...! Why run around jumpin' on blocks and going through pipes when you could just rub your cunt for an hour and feel just as exercised?</state>
                <state img="#-finished.png">Ahhh... that felt great! Even though I lost, I'm having a good time here. Thanks for inviting me, ~player~!</state>
                <state img="#-finished.png">That felt great! No wonder Peach does this while waiting for Mario!</state>
                <state img="#-finished.png">...1-up!</state>
                <state img="#-finished.png">Sss... Stage complete...! Now that &lt;i&gt;that's&lt;/i&gt; over with, time to think about my next plan...</state>
                <state img="#-finished.png">Ha... Gwaha... So that's what this body can do...? I think I'll be staying like this for a while...~</state>
                <state img="#-finished.png">...Hahhh... hahhh... hahh.  Good -- now who wants the honor of cleaning me up?</state>
                <state img="#-finished.png">...Hahhh... hahhhh... &lt;br&gt; ...hahaha! Now you see -- the Koopa Queen &lt;i&gt;always&lt;/i&gt; rules no matter &lt;i&gt;what&lt;/i&gt; she's doing!</state>
                <state img="#-finished.png">...Hahhh... hahhh... hah. &lt;br&gt; ...Okay, I'll admit, that was almost worth losing. &lt;i&gt;Almost.&lt;/i&gt; Don't let it get to your head!</state>
                <state img="#-finished.png">Gwahahaha... I'm still the best!</state>
                <state img="#-finished.png">And now I flutter back to the earth like a raccoon... Those flutter, right?</state>
                <state img="#-finished.png">Whew! I should REALLY do that more often!</state>
                <state img="#-finished.png">Phew... Y'know, the whole "queen" thing ain't too bad. Felt more of a rush than I do when I burn one of those insufferable plumbers to a crisp!</state>
                <state img="#-finished.png">Hahhh... hahh... Nnngh, okay -- maybe losing once in a while CAN be pretty fun~</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="after_masturbating">
            <case stage="9" oneShotId="256" priority="0">
                <test expr="~background~" value="hot spring" />
                <state img="#-resigned.png">...Can I get a friggin' towel or something?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-angry.png">Yeah, take your friggin' time. Not like I'm standing here covered in my own damned juices.</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">Oh, CRUD! I just realized I forgot to tie up my Chain Chomp! Hope she doesn't get into my stock of extra Super Crowns.</state>
                <state img="#-resigned.png">I oughta put a new expansion in the ol' castle. I'm thinking either a water feature or a wall of Bullet Bills. &lt;br&gt;...Let's go with the Bullet Bills.</state>
                <state img="#-resigned.png">Ya know, since becomin' a dame, I've found I'm a lot more relaxed. Maybe the princess I needed to capture was inside me all along. &lt;br&gt;...Naw, that sounds gay.</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">This has ceased to be fun! I demand entertainment! Deal me back in!</state>
                <state img="#-resigned.png">Unlike Captain Lou Albano, I never got a chance to “Do The Mario.”</state>
                <state img="#-resigned.png">I forgot how unfair poker can be sometimes. It's almost as unfair as hidden blocks!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I don't usually get to hang around &lt;i&gt;after&lt;/i&gt; I lose a fight! It's a nice change of pace from swimming in lava! GWAHAHA!</state>
                <state img="#-resigned.png">Where are my koopas? If I'm just going to be waiting around, I could at least use a drink!</state>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">C'mon, dealer, let me back in! Every game needs a secret final boss!</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">Hurry up and finish this. The queen is out of the game already, so nobody cares about it anymore.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Can we hurry this up? I've got a castle to invade later.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Could you, I dunno, try to speedrun this thing?</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">I bet Mario and his friends planned this stupid party like they always do. I always end up the loser in the end...</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Where is the Koopa Clown Car? I thought I told Kamek to bring it around... &lt;br&gt; &lt;i&gt;Hmph.&lt;/i&gt; I guess I can watch the rest of you while I wait.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Junior better have done his homework and taken out the trash by the time I get home...!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_victory">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="other" character="chara_dreemurr" />
                <state img="#-resigned.png">BWAHAHAHA! You're all finished now! Now I get to kidnap all the princesses I want from here! &lt;br&gt; ...Not the one with the knife, though. That weirdo scares me. Seriously.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="other" character="mulan" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="bowsette_mulan_disney_princesses">So, Mulan, was it? I hear you're only one of many Disney Princesses... Sounds like I've got a new hobby ahead of me. Bwahahaha!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <condition role="other" character="bernadetta" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="bowsette_bernadetta_be_yourself">Ya know, Bernie, there's nothing wrong with being yourself. I mean, look at me! Ya know what "myself" is? A winner! BWAHAHA!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <test expr="~human.gender~" value="male" />
                <state img="#-horny.png">Ya know, ~player~, this doesn't have to stop here. Let's go back to my castle and play "Jumpman." I'll jump on &lt;i&gt;your&lt;/i&gt; man... if you know what I mean.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Damn, this was easier than nabbing Peach... And that's saying something!</state>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">Well, &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; wasn’t much of a challenge.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Well, that was easy. I went from the King of the Koopas to the Queen of Cards!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Ha -- I must've been playing on easy mode!</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Haha! No surprise here! Hoping this luck follows me when I play Mario Kart with Junior at home!</state>
                <state img="#-surprise.png">I won... and I crushed you. I crushed you ALL... &lt;br&gt; Er, I mean... of COURSE I did! I should face Mario next -- if I'm &lt;i&gt;this&lt;/i&gt; good, then I'm gonna crush him too!</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Really? Come on, I wanted a challenge!</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Bwahahaha! Too easy! There wasn't even a challenge here, as expected!</state>
                <state img="#-resigned.png">&lt;i&gt;Haaah...&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br&gt; ...I'm sorry, I'm used to bigger challenges. This victory feels... kinda empty?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">And cue my victory theme. &lt;br&gt; ...No? We don't play victory themes here? Well, then, you'll just have to imagine it, ~player~.</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Maybe we should do a rematch... I'd love to thrash you chumps all over again.</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">GWA HA HA HA! There's no WAY you're ready to stand up against ME. Keep practicing, pipsqueak!</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I'm not 100% sure what happens when you &lt;i&gt;do&lt;/i&gt; win... Should I just kidnap one of you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Everything the light touches... is my kingdom.</state>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">I may not be victorious often, but when I am, it always feels so, &lt;i&gt;so&lt;/i&gt; good... Now, bring forth my prize~!</state>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">Rawwwwwwr! Victory!</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Gwahaha! Maybe I should stick to this strip poker thing instead of kidnapping the princess -- if &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; wimps are the toughest competition I've got, it'd be a cakewalk!</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Ha! If only my Koopa Troop could see me now! ...Oh, wait -- they'd probably all avert their gazes anyway. What with the... er... queenly bits on display.</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Well, would ya look at that -- a queen &lt;i&gt;and&lt;/i&gt; a winner!</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Ha! It's good to be the King! Er, the Queen...? Whatever; I win!</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Now, why don't you bow down to your new queen?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-4">
                <state img="#-happy.png">...I won? I'm actually victorious? I mean, uh... I WON!  I'm ACTUALLY VICTORIOUS!  BWAHAHA! As it SHOULD BE!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Yes! Kneel before me, peasants!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Gwahahaha... I won! Finally, I WON!</state>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">Another victory for me! Gwahaha!</state>
                <state img="#-flaunt.png">I think this Super Crown might've just turned my luck around for the better... Hmm, nah. I'm just &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; good~</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Bow to your queen! BWAHAHAHAHA!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_defeat">
            <case stage="9">
                <condition filter="gamer" role="target" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png">So, uh... you wanna... play Mario Party or something? N-n-not that I &lt;i&gt;want&lt;/i&gt; to play with you! J-just putting an invite out in case a loser like you needs some company.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <condition role="other" character="yunyun" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="bowsette_yunyun_friendship_offer">Okay, okay -- I'll be your friend, Yunyun! &lt;br&gt; ...I'm serious! The Koopa Queen could always use a new minion -- er, &lt;i&gt;pal.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Fine... Whatever... I'm still better at Smash than the rest of ya.</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">Dammit... I may have lost this time, but next time you're getting crushed!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Well, this was fun. Who's up for a Mario Party after this?</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">Bah. So long, you runts!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">It takes guts to brag to &lt;i&gt;me&lt;/i&gt; about winning. I like it! You'd make a decent henchman.</state>
                <state img="#-resigned.png">THIS 'L' is real, at least.</state>
                <state img="#-rage.png">Oh, &lt;i&gt;you'll get yours.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-resigned.png">Well, as the old saying goes... He who koops and runs away lives to koop another day!</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Don't you usually have to beat me three times? That's usually how it works with Mario...</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">I want a rematch! Double or nothin'!</state>
                <state img="#-resigned.png">Yeah, yeah, I lost. After 35 years, I'm pretty much used to it.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">I’ll get you next time...</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">BAH! Don't even think of counting me out just 'cause you beat me this once.  Your Queen demands a REMATCH; let's go!</state>
                <state img="#-resigned.png">You'd &lt;i&gt;think&lt;/i&gt; I'd get used to defeat after all these years...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9" hidden="1">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state collectible="bowsette_panties">[Hidden line. Awards the panties collectible if defeated by the human player.]</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9" hidden="1">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <condition count="3-" filter="princess" role="other" />
                <state collectible="bowsette_crown">[Hidden line. Awards the crown collectible if Bowsette and three other princess are defeated by the human player.]</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="global">
            <case stage="0-9" id="28" oneShotId="600">
                <alternative>
                    <condition role="target" character="zone-tan" pose="demoncalm" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <condition role="target" character="zone-tan" pose="demonfurious" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">You got spunk, attitude, and a demonic rage! I like it!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

    </behaviour>
</opponent>
