<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<collectibles>
    <collectible id="mitama_haiku" status="online" img="opponents/mitama/mitama_haiku.png" thumbnail="opponents/mitama/mitama_card.png">
        <title>Haiku For You</title>
        <subtitle>Who knows what the future holds?</subtitle>
        <text>After the game, Mitama gave you one of her cards, with this poem written on its back. It's up to you whether it becomes true or not...</text>
        <unlock>Play a game with Mitama. The outcome does not matter.</unlock>
        <hide-details>true</hide-details>
    </collectible>
    <collectible id="mitama_masterseal" img="opponents/mitama/PriestessMitama.png" thumbnail="opponents/mitama/Mitama_Master_Seal.png">
        <title>Master Seal</title>
        <subtitle>Useful for when you have to give yourself a promotion.</subtitle>
        <text>As a reward for your efforts, you received a Master Seal. According to Mitama, it ''allows  you to enter a more advanced class, allowing for unprecedented skill.'' She also sends a picture of how she looks in her advanced class...

How will your own clothes look after using it? Maybe it's more convenient than going shopping...</text>
        <unlock>See a small amount of Mitama's haiku. &lt;br&gt;You who seek a prize; &lt;br&gt;
rather than mindlessly grind,&lt;br&gt; 
walk alternate paths. &lt;br&gt;

(No, this one doesn't count - Mitama)</unlock>
        <hide-details>true</hide-details>
        <counter>75</counter>
    </collectible>
    <collectible id="mitama_heartseal" img="opponents/mitama/nohr_noble_mitama.png" thumbnail="opponents/mitama/hseal.png">
        <title>Heart Seal</title>
        <subtitle>Sometimes, you have to follow your heart.</subtitle>
        <text>After the game, Mitama handed you a spare Heart Seal that was in her possession. Similar to the Master Seal, it allows the user to change class. However, whereas the Master Seal advanced your class, this is merely a horizontal change. &lt;br&gt; The class depends on the user; on the right, Mitama provides an example of how she would look, were she to use a Heart Seal.

</text>
        <unlock>See a moderate amount of Mitama's haiku. &lt;br&gt; Should you find yourself&lt;br&gt;pressed for more haiku to find,&lt;br&gt;targets are worth more.</unlock>
        <hide-details>true</hide-details>
        <counter>125</counter>
    </collectible>
</collectibles>
