<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<metadata>
    <owner>shimakaze</owner>
    <noteworthy>
        <case name="Dizzykaze" min="4" max="4">
            <description>Shimakaze has taken a blow to the head, and will be very dizzy for the round.</description>
            <trigger tag="stripped" saidMarker="dizzy" priority="999">
                <state img="dizzy.png">-aaaaAAAAAR-! I-I think I'm gonna be sick...</state>
                <state img="dizzy.png">-aaaaAAAAAR-! I feel like I just sailed through a typhoon...</state>
                <state img="dizzy.png">-aaaaAAAAAR-! My head's still spinning..!</state>
                <state img="dizzy.png">-aaaaAAAAAR-! Awawawaw...</state>
                <state img="dizzy.png">-aaaaAAAAAR-! T-t-that one really shook me up...</state>
                <state img="dizzy.png">-aaaaAAAAAR-! T-the world just turned upside down all of a sudden!</state>
            </trigger>
        </case>
        <case name="Japanese" min="4" max="4">
            <description>Shimakaze's speech had temporarily reverted to Japanese, and has only just come back.</description>
            <trigger tag="good_hand" timeInStage="0" saidMarker="japanese" notSaidMarker="japend" priority="500">
                <state img="stumped.png" marker="japend">$%^#(*! -llo? Am I coming through clearly now?</state>
                <state img="stumped.png" marker="japend">:"_!(@+/ -erstand me now? Ah, we're back.</state>
                <state img="stumped.png" marker="japend">`%{|;&lt;.| -tion systems are back up now, I think.</state>
                <state img="stumped.png" marker="japend">\{].'_=@* -ower's never been damaged like that before. I'll have to be more careful.</state>
            </trigger>
        </case>
        <case name="Explosion" min="8" max="8">
            <description>Shimakaze explodes. Literally, not sexually.</description>
            <trigger tag="must_masturbate">
                <state img="damaged.gif">!!!</state>
            </trigger>
        </case>
        <case name="Rensouhou Returns" min="10" max="10">
            <description>Shimakaze's little robot friend, who disappeared at the start of the game, returns.</description>
            <trigger tag="finished_masturbating" notSaidMarker="rencatch" priority="200">
                <state img="rencatch.png" marker="rencatch">&lt;i&gt;Haah, haah.&lt;/i&gt; Oh, Rensouhou-chan. C'mere.</state>
                <state img="rencatch.png" marker="rencatch">&lt;i&gt;Haah, haah.&lt;/i&gt; Rensouhou-chan? Were you worried about me?</state>
                <state img="rencatch.png" marker="rencatch">Oh, Rensouhou-chan. &lt;i&gt;Haah,&lt;/i&gt; I'm okay. Just a bit tired.</state>
                <state img="rencatch.png" marker="rencatch">Didn't I ask you to wait outside, Rensouhou-chan? Well, doesn't matter anymore.</state>
            </trigger>
        </case>
        <case name="Rensouhou Leaves" min="0" max="0">
            <description>Shimakaze's little robot friend is sent away.</description>
            <trigger tag="game_start">
                <state img="portrait2.png">Rensouhou-chan! Don't wander too far away from the room, or you'll get lost again.</state>
                <state img="portrait2.png">We'll have some races when we return to the base, okay, Rensouhou-chan?</state>
                <state img="portrait2.png">Rensouhou-chan, don't get into any fights, okay?</state>
                <state img="portrait2.png">Rensouhou-chan, even if someone makes you mad, you can't open fire on them.</state>
                <state img="portrait2.png">I'll finish up as quick as a flash, Rensouhou-chan, so wait patiently outside.</state>
            </trigger>
        </case>
        <case name="Shimakaze Stripping" min="0" max="0">
            <description>Shimakaze's gloves burn away instead of being stripped off. The rest of her clothing will disappear in a similar fashion.</description>
            <trigger tag="stripping">
                <state img="damaged.png">A little bit of damage here and there, but I'm still fine!</state>
                <state img="damaged.png">No damage to anything vital. I can keep playing!</state>
                <state img="damaged.png">Just gotta wait for the damage control fairies to do their work.</state>
                <state img="damaged.png">I won't even need time in the docks to repair something like this.</state>
                <state img="damaged.png">If it's just this, Akashi will have me fixed up in no time.</state>
                <state img="damaged.png">It's pretty generous to call something like this a hit.</state>
            </trigger>
        </case>
    </noteworthy>
    <hidden />
    <responses />
    <notes />
    <nextId>0</nextId>
</metadata>
