<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<metadata>
    <owner>rosa</owner>
    <noteworthy>
        <case name="Present offer" id="29" priority="Prompt" min="9" max="9">
            <description>Rosa says that she'll give a present to the winner of the game. </description>
        </case>
    </noteworthy>
    <reviewed>true</reviewed>
    <responses>
        <response id="7" opponent="arash" opponentId="1" />
        <response id="18" opponent="ae86" opponentId="1" />
        <response id="0" opponent="mavis" opponentId="25" />
        <response id="19" opponent="ae86" opponentId="4" />
        <response id="20" opponent="amy" opponentId="259" />
        <response id="27" opponent="chazz" opponentId="22" />
        <response id="28" opponent="yuelia" opponentId="6" />
        <response id="30" opponent="nami" opponentId="13" />
        <response id="0" opponent="nami_szs" opponentId="7" />
        <response id="0" opponent="saki_zls" opponentId="12" />
        <response id="32" opponent="mister_clean" opponentId="1" />
    </responses>
    <notes>
        <note id="2">Rosa mentions that she doesn't remember the rules for Poker.</note>
        <note id="36">I'm actually curious about this: can a person with no balls be considered a biological male? Don't they make, like, hormones and stuff like that? Oh shit, maybe Bi and Trans are the same person and the Bi lore is even more profound than we all imagined...</note>
    </notes>
    <labels>
        <label id="26" label="TM 11" folder="" sort="0" />
    </labels>
    <nextId>39</nextId>
    <markers>
        <marker scope="Public" name="" />
        <marker scope="Public" name="AE-86_Moveset">Rosa wonders about the moveset that AE-86, a car, would have.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="aoba_france">Rosa says that France is not a familiar place; naturally, as it doesn't exist in the Pokémon World.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="beach_pokémon">Rosa comments on the fact that there are a lack of Pokémon in the beach, which is unusual to her.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="bi_is_a_futa">Rosa theorizes that Bi is actually a woman without a vagina, rather than a man with no balls.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="bobobo_bee">Response to Bobobo's line when Ochako starts masturbating. Since she doesn't know what a bee is, she is confused about it.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="cynthia_stronger">Rosa asks Cynthia whether she or Iris is a stronger Pokémon Trainer.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="cynthia_verity">Responses to Cynthia's line about her not-daughter.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="ghost_clothes">Rosa wonders about the nature of a ghost's garments.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="ghost_encounter">Rosa mentions having seen a ghost before.</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="inevitable_end">Rosa thinks about the inevitabilty of having to strip in a strip poker game.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="may_favpokémon">Answer to May's question of who is your favorite Pokémon.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="may_livearoundhere">Answer to May's prompt about living around here.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="may_livearoundhere_holidaylodge">Special variation of the answer to May's prompt about living around here.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="miko_desires">Answer to Miko's prompt about desires. Is a simple life the key to happiness?</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="misaka_powers">Rosa wants to know how Misaka's electric powers work.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="misty_dates">Rosa asks Misty how does she have time to go on dates.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="misty_parallel_universes">If both the new and old Misty are present at the table, Rosa will comment that they might be from parallel universes.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="misty_stage1loss">Rosa's line when Misty loses for the second time. It's pretty generic tbh.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="misty_typematchups">If Misty starts stripping first, she makes a remark about having a type advantage, since she specializes in Grass-type Pokémon and Misty specializes in Water-type Pokémon.</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="N_left">N has left the game, because you are a bad person.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="nickname" />
        <marker scope="Public" name="nopkmn_life">If she's in a table with no other Pokémon characters, Rosa will remark that it is odd to her that there are people who don't live alongside Pokémon.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="roof_musing_1">If she has a bad hand while playing on the rooftop, she complains about the lack of plants. These markers also serve as setup for a chain, so that each line is said in order, and isn't said more than once.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="roof_musing_2" />
        <marker scope="Public" name="rosa_incentive">Rosa says that she'll give a present to the winner of the game. It's her tm collectible, so it's what tvtropes calls gameplay and story integration.</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="RosaSeesTie">A tie happened.</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="RosaSeesTie2">A tie happened for the second time.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="school_uniform_filter">Filtered line to those with the school_uniform tag; there are two of them, maybe I should do separate markers?</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="succubus_filter">Filtered line to those with the succubus tag; Rosa is unsure about the word ''succubus''.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="weapon_filter">Filtered line to those with the weapon tag; Rosa asks why would you bring a weapon to a cards game.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="winged_filter">Filtered line to those with the winged tag; Rosa mentions that the wings remind her of a certain pokémon. Which pokémon depends on the characters, but she'll probably have a more detailed answer if you ask her.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="witch_filter">Filtered line to those with the witch tag; Rosa is comparing the target with the witch from one of the movies she has starred in.</marker>
    </markers>
    <recipes>
        <recipe key="ab63638e-fcc5-44e9-b020-a677785bb36f">
            <cases>
                <id>3</id>
            </cases>
        </recipe>
        <recipe key="93fb1799-f582-4f08-a53c-49d5e56f6278">
            <cases>
                <id>5</id>
            </cases>
        </recipe>
        <recipe key="352366df-ef02-4874-a2eb-0fdc4c210fbd">
            <cases>
                <id>6</id>
            </cases>
        </recipe>
        <recipe key="670e7368-4059-4a56-8171-65d18d43ebff">
            <cases>
                <id>8</id>
            </cases>
        </recipe>
        <recipe key="b90f559d-7557-4180-989e-63b583b9a82d">
            <cases>
                <id>10</id>
            </cases>
        </recipe>
        <recipe key="dba5778a-dbed-4079-9052-d204275d6f93">
            <cases>
                <id>14</id>
            </cases>
        </recipe>
        <recipe key="cc28d236-6b17-48ce-a010-48a75ded118c">
            <cases>
                <id>15</id>
            </cases>
        </recipe>
        <recipe key="9181b912-d7db-4c2a-8f23-c2ddea3aa7ee">
            <cases>
                <id>23</id>
            </cases>
        </recipe>
        <recipe key="95241bd5-5ee1-4979-ae3c-aad1384050d9">
            <cases>
                <id>24</id>
            </cases>
        </recipe>
        <recipe key="15f3a04f-8e03-40e0-b426-dcba8b4f5b3b">
            <cases>
                <id>25</id>
            </cases>
        </recipe>
        <recipe key="0adf072a-3183-4a01-a5d8-1068634734fb">
            <cases>
                <id>31</id>
            </cases>
        </recipe>
        <recipe key="f43ccc1b-701f-4f7e-9738-617802c9b5e0">
            <cases>
                <id>34</id>
            </cases>
        </recipe>
        <recipe key="db2db8d0-8c32-4724-aa3c-627605e58119">
            <cases>
                <id>35</id>
            </cases>
        </recipe>
        <recipe key="3f8ada94-88ef-4fdd-8448-2a2705e15029">
            <cases>
                <id>38</id>
            </cases>
        </recipe>
    </recipes>
</metadata>
