<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<collectibles>
    <collectible id="collectible_underwear" img="opponents/jessie/collectible_underwear.png" thumbnail="opponents/jessie/collectible_underwear.png">
        <title>Jessie's Bra</title>
        <subtitle>A remarkably large bra</subtitle>
        <text>You took Jessie's bra after winning against her for the first time. She knows that you took it, but she doesn't mind. Besides, how often do you encounter a used bra this big, anyway? You weren't going to let such a rare opportunity go by without a souvenier.</text>
        <unlock>Win a game against Jessie while she's wearing her default outfit.</unlock>
        <hide-details>true</hide-details>
        <wearable>true</wearable>
        <clothing name="Bra" generic="bra" position="upper" type="important" img="opponents/jessie/collectible_underwear.png" />
    </collectible>
    <collectible id="collectible_munie" img="opponents/jessie/collectible_munie.png" thumbnail="opponents/jessie/collectible_munie.png">
        <title>HuniePop Munie</title>
        <subtitle>Not a valid currency</subtitle>
        <text>Not "money", but munie. It's some sort of currency that you received by grinding through Jessie's Q&amp;A. It's not clear where it came from, and it's unlikely to be a usable currency, but it's better than nothing, maybe.</text>
        <unlock>Listen to 30 responses to Jessie's Q&amp;A</unlock>
        <hide-details>true</hide-details>
        <counter>30</counter>
    </collectible>
    <collectible id="collectible_implants" img="opponents/jessie/collectible_implants.png" thumbnail="opponents/jessie/collectible_implants.png">
        <title>Breast Implants</title>
        <subtitle>Saline-solution-filled model</subtitle>
        <text>Poor Jessie. After her unfortunate encounter with the dark mage Tharja, she's going to need these from now on. Breasts implants are common in the porn industry anyway, so it's not like Jessie would be different for having them.</text>
        <unlock>Have Tharja permanently (not temporarily) shrink Jessie's breasts. (Hint: Tharja must win against Jessie)</unlock>
        <hidden>true</hidden>
        <hide-details>true</hide-details>
    </collectible>
    <collectible id="collectible_crown" status="offline" img="opponents/jessie/collectible_crown.png" thumbnail="opponents/jessie/collectible_crown.png">
        <title>Christmas Crown</title>
        <subtitle>A Christmas-themed crown</subtitle>
        <text>The Christmas crown that was part of Jessie's Christmas Queen outfit, given to you as a gift from her. For some reason, you can't shake the feeling that you've seen a crown of this design before. Maybe you've seen in at a pop-opera concert you've watched? You also note that it's way lighter than it looks, almost as if it's floating in zero gravity.</text>
        <unlock>Win a game against Jessie while she's wearing her Christmas Queen outfit.</unlock>
        <hidden>true</hidden>
        <wearable>true</wearable>
        <clothing name="Christmas Crown" generic="hair decoration" position="head" type="extra" img="opponents/jessie/collectible_crown.png" />
    </collectible>
</collectibles>
