<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>

<!--This file was machine generated using the Character Editor v6.7.8 at 4:11:12 PM on November 25, 2022. Do not edit this file directly unless you know what you're doing.-->
<opponent>
    <version>v6.7.8</version>
    <first>Anatoly</first>
    <last />
    <label>Anatoly</label>
    <gender>male</gender>
    <size>small</size>
    <timer>20</timer>
    <intelligence>average</intelligence>

    <stylesheet>styles.css</stylesheet>


    <wardrobe>
        <clothing name="briefs" generic="underwear" position="lower" type="important" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="pants" generic="pants" position="lower" type="major" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="belt" generic="belt" position="waist" type="extra" />
        <clothing name="shirt" generic="shirt" position="upper" type="major" />
        <clothing name="socks" generic="socks" position="feet" type="minor" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="shoes" generic="shoes" position="feet" type="minor" plural="true" />
    </wardrobe>

    <poses>
        <pose id="paskaleaves">
            <sprite id="shocked" src="5-shocked.png" x="0" />
            <sprite id="paska_run" src="Paska/paska_run.png" x="-260" y="559" scalex="0.27" scaley="0.34" alpha="100" rotation="-3" />
            <directive type="animation" id="paska_run" ease="smooth" interpolation="linear">
                <keyframe time="0" x="-260" y="559" scalex="0.27" scaley="0.34" alpha="100" rotation="-3" />
                <keyframe time="0.81" x="-352" y="559" alpha="0" />
            </directive>
        </pose>
        <pose id="standinghere">
            <sprite id="0-bashful" src="#-bashful.png" x="13" y="0" />
            <directive type="animation" id="0-bashful" ease="linear" interpolation="none">
                <keyframe time="0" src="#-bashful.png" />
                <keyframe time="2.5" src="#-embarrassed.png" />
            </directive>
        </pose>
    </poses>

    <behaviour>
        <trigger id="selected">
            <case stage="0" id="248">
                <condition filter="human_male" status="crotch_visible" role="other" character="human" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Geez-- You're way too forward!</state>
                <state img="#-scared.png">Can't you put some pants on before we start?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="129" oneShotId="82">
                <condition role="other" character="fluttershy" sayingMarker="Anatoly_selected" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">Eh? Paska has grabbed your attention? Wow, she is already popular! &lt;br&gt;{paska}Squeak squeak!{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="110">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Erm... Hello there, ~player~. My name is Anatoly, and this is my squirrel, Paska.</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">Poker? Well, taking a break from my studies does sound nice. Don't you think so, Paska?</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Hello there, ~player~. I am... uh... Anatoly. So... &lt;br&gt;{paska}Squeak, squeak!{!reset}&lt;br&gt;Don't be rude, Paska.</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">{uk}Привіт ~player.ifMale(пане|пані)~{!reset}-- Er, I mean... &lt;br&gt;{small}Sorry...{!reset} H-Hello there!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_start">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition count="0" gender="male" role="opp" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png">O-Oh, just ladies...? That's a bit disappointing. But, um, if you want me to play as a friend, I'll stay.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Ah, I was hoping to see some guys tonight, but... Uh, this works too! {small}Friendly games are still fun.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="249">
                <condition count="3" status="alive" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I-I'm not an expert on poker, but, uh... Shouldn't there be more people here?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-smug.png">I've read up extensively on poker strategies, so do not think you'll see my loss!</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">{small}Um, h-hello everyone...{!reset}&lt;br&gt;{paska}Squeak!{!reset}&lt;br&gt;Huh? I am not mumbling!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="swap_cards">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <test expr="~cards~" value="0" />
                <state img="#-conversational.png">No new cards, thank you.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I will not need any new cards, thank you.</state>
                <state img="#-knowledge.png">A hands perfection! I will not need anything new.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Ah, n-no new cards, thank you...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <test expr="~cards~" value="1" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I think one card will be enough...</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Um, just one card, please.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Can I have one new card?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-conversational.png">May I gain ~cards.text~ cards, please?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Just ~cards.text~ new cards will win.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Can I have ~cards.text~ new cards?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-calm.png">~Cards.text~ cards, please.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Uh, ~cards.text~ new cards...</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">{paska}Squeak!{!reset}&lt;br&gt;Yeah, ~cards.text~ fresher cards.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Erm... Just ~cards.text~ new cards, please.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Uh, just ~cards.text~ new cards will be strong, right?</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I-I will take ~cards.text~ new cards...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="good_hand">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Have you ever tried blackthorn berries? I found many and many when I last went foraging. They're so delicious!</state>
                <state img="#-petting.png">When I was a kid, I met my best friend, Gregor. I showed him all the butterflies I caught, and he was excited to grasp them. I've known him for so long now...</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">These are great! {small}I think.{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">There's nothing better than viewing the sunset. Hues of red, orange, even a little purple... Oh, it's beautiful!</state>
                <state img="#-knowledge.png">Simply crushing some &lt;i&gt;fragaria vesca&lt;/i&gt;, also known as strawberries, can make a great tasting jam! Optional is sugar, despite what Karin thinks.</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">It's so funny to me that people go "camping" with all their prepackaged food and tents. There's plenty of tasty things in the forest, you just need to use your eyes!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">This is good, right?</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">(&lt;i&gt;Should I celebrate? What if these cards read doom, and I end up looking like a fool...?&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Heheheh!</state>
                <state img="#-knowledge.png">Ukraine has a rich and colorful history, not to mention fantastic meals. I'll tell you about it, if you'd like! Just call me teacher, okay?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I may be skinny, b-but I exercise every day! You know, I'm a very strong swimmer.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I-I can't remember... Cards with faces are good, right? </state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png" oneShotId="8" marker="crickets">Many people include bugs in their diet. In fact, there are cakes made with cricket flour! Who knows, maybe you'll like it?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">These are perfect! My research is paying off, I'm sure of it!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I know they sell food here, but are there many good vegetarian options? And how cheap are they?</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">I'm so used to living in a cabin that it confuses me to see others rely on electricity. We had a radio, but it broke down early enough.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">So many people gathered from many different places just to play. It's really exciting! I would like to travel...</state>
                <state img="#-petting.png">Ah, I should have brought some treats for you, Paska. Sorry, I'll be sure to find you some lettuce.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">M-My mama always said: Лише коли їсте таргана, ви цінуєте суп. "Only when you have eaten a cockroach do you appreciate the soup." S-So, don't steal good cards for granted!</state>
                <state img="#-cute.png">Um, I-I find it hard to focus on reading my cards when you look at me...</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Oh, that's a relief! </state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Did you know?  The odds are 649,740 to 1 of getting a royal flush. So... Y-Yeah!</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Um... Sorry, I'm not the best at small talk, heheh... How about these cards, huh? &lt;br&gt;(&lt;i&gt;That was awful.&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">My friend made the best vegetable stew when we first came to our cabin. It... t-took a lot of our stored rations, but it is worth it!</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">It gets so cold in the mountains at night. I-It seems to me that I am overheating here.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="okay_hand">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I grew up in Ukraine, but recently I had to... um... leave. My friends and I are staying in a cabin along the Tatra Mountains now.</state>
                <state img="#-conversationalalt.png">I do not go to events like this often. In the cabin, I have to ask to be left alone. It's hard to focus on reading when people are trying to talk to you.</state>
                <state img="#-petting.png">Winter in Ukraine is incredibly harsh. I found Paska outside, hurt in the snow when I was younger, and she hasn't left my side since.</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">P-Paska! Don't nibble on the cards like that!&lt;br&gt;{paska}Squeaaak!{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">{big}&lt;i&gt;A-Achoo!&lt;/i&gt;{!reset} &lt;br&gt;S-Sorry! My allergies are acting up...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Did I forget to bring money with me? Oh well... &lt;br&gt;(&lt;i&gt;It's not like I have any extra to spend anyway.&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I really have to arrange what food we keep in the cabin ... W-We don't have the money to just go and buy groceries.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Mediocrity won't deter me. My mind is busy thinking about important things! Like how many seeds a strawberry has.</state>
                <state img="#-knowledge.png">T-There is no way I would be lackluster in something as simple as cards. Do not forget that!</state>
                <state img="#-petting.png">{uk}з вами все гаразд?{!reset}&lt;br&gt;{paska}Chitter chitter...{!reset}&lt;br&gt;{uk}Хороший. Я радий почути це, мила дівчинка.{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-scared.png">The cabin holds a basement, it's locked behind this old door. Oh, just thinking about it makes me tremble!</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Eep! S-Sorry, I didn't mean to make eye contact, ~player~... Or, uh, is that rude of me to say?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Are people still making beds? I always do this every morning, but all my friends make fun of me for it.</state>
                <state img="#-petting.png">Are you doing alright, Paska? I know how scary meeting new people can be. </state>
                <state img="#-conversationalalt.png">I can't say I've played too many cards in my life. I mostly just ran outside when I was a kid.</state>
                <state img="#-knowledge.png">Getting food yourself is &lt;i&gt;so&lt;/i&gt; much better than relying on a supermarket. Fresh blueberries are incredibly useful, as well as delicious.</state>
                <state img="#-petting.png">I wish I knew--- Er... &lt;i&gt;Had time to&lt;/i&gt; fix that radio we found. I'd love to listen to some music again, if only for a bit.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Oh, I'm hungry... I wish to bring bread with me...</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I've been sleeping badly lately. A shared bedroom is one thing, but when it snores louder than a lumberyard, it becomes especially difficult.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">It is interesting what everyone is doing in the cabin. I hope they all get along with each other without me.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I-Is it normal to come here in search of a... a {small}b-boyfriend?{!reset} I-I'm asking just out of curiosity.</state>
                <state img="#-scared.png">(&lt;i&gt;How long can I continue to pretend before they realize I can't even read...?&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Nothing interesting to say about these cards... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Oh, I can't remember any of the tips Gregor told me! You'll go easy on me, won't you...?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I wonder where Paska ran off to? Knowing her, she's probably hiding from everyone else.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I hate being uncertain... Oh, hopefully I do alright this round.</state>
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">P-People can be so wasteful. There's bound to be some treasure on the ~background.surface~, right?</state>
                <state img="#-cute.png">Um, just so you know, ~player~... I-I really appreciate you having me here. Uh... So... yeah.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Did you know? N-Nuts and seeds are known to improve the erm... sex lives... o-of whoever eats them. {small}Should I have said that?{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">The other day, Mariah told me a very interesting fact about deer. Did you know that they are... U-Uh... {small}I don't remember...{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">I'm sorry... I'm sure I'm nothing impressive to look at, ~player~. </state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">Oh... Sometimes I feel like a hopeless romantic. Who would ever want a nerd like me? &lt;i&gt;Sigh...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Why did the chicken molt his feathers? Because he lost the poker match! &lt;br&gt;Heheheh! G-Get it?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Oh, I could really go for a drink... It's been so long since I've gone to a bar.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">&lt;i&gt;Yawn...&lt;/i&gt; O-Oh, excuse me...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="bad_hand">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-sad.png">Are you hungry, Paska?&lt;br&gt;{paska}Squeak...{!reset}&lt;br&gt;Yeah, me too...</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Oh, these are awfu--- Eek! I mean... I'm doing great!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Ah, yes... Perfect! &lt;br&gt;(&lt;i&gt;I have no idea what these cards say.&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Um... To be honest, I don't have many friends. I'm not used to talking to so many people. So...</state>
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">A vegetarian diet is great for your body. B-But people keep coming up with excuses! Is meat really that important?</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">Before Gregor, my only true friend was a family dog. Even now... I only know four people. M-Maybe I'll make new friends while I'm here.</state>
                <state img="#-scared.png">I can't remember a thing Gregor taught me about cards! Erm-- I mean... All is good here!</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">D-Does anyone have any advice on standing up to others? Karin... I think picking on me is one of her favorite activities.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Um, just so you know, I'm not short. I'm just "fun-sized", o-okay?</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Good...! N-No, these are bad...? Uh...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Erm... I haven't been annoying, have I? S-Sorry... Sometimes I just...</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I used to love the rain. But after the floodwaters rose so high around our cabin, I can't help but be scared now.</state>
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">Just because I left food in the bedroom rather than the kitchen doesn't make me an idiot. I-I just forgot to move the rations, that's all...</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Um, I hope I don't look too pale. I spend a lot of time outdoors, but I always get sunburn instead of those tans.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" oneShotId="215">I-I'll admit, English isn't my first language. I'm not used to speaking it for so long, honestly. {small}Although, I suppose ~player.ifMale(he|she)~ only speaks English too...{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-scared.png">Eep! T-This is bad, isn't it?</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Ah, I'm trying to think of hobbies to talk about. That's what people do to "break the ice", r-right? Heh...</state>
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">In case you're curious, most people &lt;i&gt;don't&lt;/i&gt; consider honey to be vegan. Some beekeepers terribly mistreat their little friends. Oh, it makes me so mad!</state>
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">The girls at home always stare at Gregor. He's so big and strong, I guess it's natural. I get a bit jealous, though...</state>
                <state img="#-petting.png">Thank you, Paska. Whenever I grow too anxious, you are there to calm me.&lt;br&gt;{paska}Squeak!{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6" id="6">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">E-Even I can tell these are bad!</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">I miss Paska... Oh, hopefully she isn't stirring up trouble. She used to bite at my friends, until I taught her to stop.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" marker="losttemper">{uk}Це... Дилер! Я покажу тобі де раки зимують!{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-conversationalalt.png">Misfortune never gives peace... This morning I slipped in a puddle of mud outside.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Ah, so these mean I'll...?</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Ah, don't panic, Anatoly... I'll be fine, I-I think.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I'm getting jittery... I hope I don't drop my glasses.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Why do I care so much about winning? This is not like many other prizes.</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">M-Maybe a loss will be good for me. </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="hand">
            <case stage="0-6" id="21" oneShotId="26" totalRounds="2-">
                <condition role="other" character="mari_setogaya" sayingMarker="Self_Odd_drinks" />
                <test expr="~background.location~" value="indoors" />
                <state img="#-scared.png" marker="mari_diet">What kind of unholy diet do you have...? Can't you just eat a salad?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="168" totalRounds="3-">
                <condition role="other" character="mari_setogaya" stage="0-4" sayingMarker="Self_whyBotherWithStudies" />
                <state img="#-sad.png" marker="mari_whystudy">Because you are incredibly fortunate to be able to attend school, Mari. N-Not everyone... has the opportunities you do.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="22" oneShotId="25" totalRounds="4-">
                <condition role="other" character="revy" stage="0-7" sayingMarker="killing" />
                <state img="#-frustrated.png" marker="revy_killing">Never. I would never harm a person, or an animal! Actually, did you know how corrupt the meat industry is? Really, going vegetarian isn't that hard!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="25" oneShotId="24" totalRounds="5-">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" stage="0-6" sayingMarker="TheVoiceOfHair=1" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png" marker="bobobo_voiceofhair">M-My hair? Should I be scared?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="75" totalRounds="4-">
                <condition role="other" character="hilbert" stage="0-5" sayingMarker="truth-ideals" />
                <state img="#-conversationalalt.png">The truth, of course! My ideals aren't law, but truth is forever... The truth has consequences!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" oneShotId="105" totalRounds="4-">
                <condition role="other" character="hilbert" stage="0-5" sayingMarker="anatoly_cheren" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="hilbert_cheren">Eh? Should I be happy, Hilbert? I certainly hope this is a good friend.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4" id="234" oneShotId="165">
                <condition role="other" character="dunban" />
                <test expr="~dunban.position~" value="right" />
                <state img="#-conversationalalt.png" marker="dunban_idleinsecure">{small}Psst! Paska! Be on your best behavior, okay? You're right next to the handsome man!{!reset}&lt;br&gt;{paska}Hmf...{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5" id="87" oneShotId="85">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="paskaleaves" />
                <condition role="other" character="mari_setogaya" stage="0" saidMarker="Self_wonderingWherePaskaWent" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Hm? You're thinking of Paska? She'll be alright, Mari. I think she was frustrated around so many people, and decided to go hide. Always a queen of drama...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6 8" id="242">
                <condition role="other" character="dwight" stage="0-7" sayingMarker="pizzatoppings" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">Mushrooms and onions are perfect for pizza. Really, I like any vegetables on mine.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6 8" id="243">
                <condition role="other" character="dwight" stage="0-7" sayingMarker="nervoushabits" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I really wish I didn't stutter... It must get annoying to listen to.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4" id="105">
                <condition gender="male" status="alive" character="human" layers="0" />
                <condition count="2" status="alive" />
                <state img="#-smug.png">Eh? Impress me, ~player~... We will see who wins this!</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">N-No matter who wins... I had fun with you, ~player~. I hope you did too.</state>
                <state img="#-knowledge.png">Your charms will not deter me, ~player~! I-I'm incredibly focused. Do not underestimate a boy and his squirrel!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6" id="106">
                <condition gender="male" status="alive" character="human" layers="0" />
                <condition count="2" status="alive" />
                <state img="#-smug.png">Eh? Impress me, ~player~... We will see who wins this!</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">N-No matter who wins... I had fun with you, ~player~. I hope you did too.</state>
                <state img="#-knowledge.png">Your charms will not deter me, ~player~! I-I'm incredibly focused. Do not underestimate a boy from Ukraine!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="107">
                <condition gender="female" status="alive" character="human" layers="0" />
                <condition count="2" status="alive" />
                <state img="#-smug.png">We will see who the true winner is... Fight hard, ~player~!</state>
                <state img="#-knowledge.png">Hehehe! You will see, ~player~... I really am a smart boy!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" totalRounds="4-">
                <condition count="2-" gender="female" />
                <condition count="0" filter="lesbian" gender="female" />
                <condition role="other" character="mari_setogaya" sayingMarker="Self_FavoriteWayToHaveSex" notSaidMarker="Self_FavoriteSexPosition" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="mari_pleasingaman">W-Well, there are many ways that are fun for both! I enjoy-- &lt;br&gt;{big}O-Oh!{!reset} Wait! You, um... You were just asking the girls. I... I knew that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-1" oneShotId="170" totalRounds="0">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="introductions" />
                <condition role="other" character="eichi" saidMarker="anatoly_paskaeichi_reaction" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png">You've never seen a squirrel before? Well, Paska is a &lt;i&gt;red squirrel&lt;/i&gt;, which are only found in Europe... But, still!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="169" oneShotId="117" totalRounds="4-">
                <condition role="other" character="mari_setogaya" sayingMarker="Self_FavoriteSexPosition" notSaidMarker="Self_FavoriteWayToHaveSex" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="mari_sexposition">I do not know what the slang term is for it... T-That one where you sit on someone's lap, and you... You jump up and down. &lt;br&gt;{small}I like doing that one.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="49" oneShotId="34" totalRounds="4-">
                <condition role="other" character="twisted_fate" />
                <state img="#-shy.png" marker="fate_idle1">O-Oh, wow! I've never heard of an accent like yours, Fate. It's really quite charming...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="50" oneShotId="35" totalRounds="3-">
                <condition role="other" character="twisted_fate" />
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" marker="fate_idle2">{paska}Chitter chitter!{!reset}&lt;br&gt;P-Paska, cut it out! Why do you want to embarrass me in front of Fate?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="126" oneShotId="106" totalRounds="4-">
                <condition role="other" character="ahri" />
                <state img="#-conversational.png" marker="ahri_idle">I thank you for compressing your tails, Ahri. Paska constantly swings hers in my face... It gets old fast.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5" id="200" oneShotId="141" totalRounds="4-">
                <condition role="other" character="nagatoro" />
                <state img="#-frustrated.png" marker="nagatoro_idle">I'm not going to be pushed around by some pathetic school girl bully. Not anymore!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-4" id="233" oneShotId="164">
                <condition role="other" character="dunban" />
                <condition filter="seductive" role="other" var="flirt" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png">(&lt;i&gt;I really stand no chance with ~flirt~ here... Besides, why would Dunban ever choose me?&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" oneShotId="179" totalRounds="3-">
                <condition role="other" character="dwight" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="dwight_idle">&lt;i&gt;D... Dight... Doot... Duh...&lt;/i&gt; Uh, Ukrainian does not have that "w sound" in your name. I'm having some difficulty...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6" id="68" oneShotId="54">
                <condition gender="male" character="human" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="peptalk" />
                <state img="#-analtoly.png" marker="butt">Eh...? S-Something is in the distance, right? I'll just turn around to see.</state>
                <state img="#-analtoly.png" marker="butt">W-What is that? You saw Paska for a second...? I should turn around and be sure she isn't causing trouble!</state>
                <state img="#-analtoly.png" marker="butt">Have you dropped a coin, ~player~? I can b-bend down to pick it up for you!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="other" character="okino" sayingMarker="okino_piningblues" />
                <state img="#-sad.png">You have to stay strong, Okino! There are guys for both of us, waiting... I-I'm sure of it! One day we won't be single...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="42" oneShotId="5">
                <condition role="other" character="pit" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png" marker="anatolypit_idle">P-Pit, you can't read? Who knew? I'm not the only one!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6" id="206" oneShotId="148">
                <condition role="other" character="dunban" />
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" marker="dunban_idlenaked">Mm... D-Dunban, I will be blunt! I think you're... {small}really, really h-handsome...{!reset}&lt;br&gt;It has been chewing at my brain all game...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-4" id="223" oneShotId="149">
                <condition role="other" character="dunban" />
                <state img="#-sad.png" marker="dunban_idleinsecure">(&lt;i&gt;Oh, why am I bothering? Dunban could do so much better than me.&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png" marker="dunban_idleinsecure">(&lt;i&gt;Why am I even trying? Dunban could do much better than a scrawny nerd like me...&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6" id="228" oneShotId="150">
                <condition role="other" character="dunban" />
                <state img="#-shy.png" marker="dunban_idledating">(&lt;i&gt;Ah... I really wish I was brave enough to ask him out...&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="1" oneShotId="1" totalRounds="0">
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="introductions">Excuse me, have I introduced Paska correctly yet? She's a squirrel right on my shoulder. Behave yourself, okay, Paska?&lt;br&gt;{paska}Squeak squeak!{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png" marker="introductions">Did I introduce you all to Paska yet? She's the squirrel on my shoulder. Say hi, Paska. &lt;br&gt;{paska}Squeak squeak!{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-petting.png" marker="introductions">A-Allow me to introduce you to Paska. She's the squirrel on my shoulder.&lt;br&gt;{paska}Squeak squeak!{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="41" oneShotId="22">
                <condition filter="has_food" role="other" var="foodie" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Hm...? I smell food... If you hear my stomach growl, it isn't my fault.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4" id="40" oneShotId="21">
                <condition filter="has_food" role="other" var="foodie" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Paska, I know you're hungry... But you can't go running off to pick around for other people's food!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="104">
                <condition count="0" status="not_lost_all" />
                <condition count="1" status="alive" role="opp" var="opponent" />
                <state img="#-smug.png">A-Are you scared, ~opponent~? Do not worry, my win will be painless.</state>
                <state img="#-knowledge.png">Y-You've doubted my smarts, haven't you, ~opponent~? Well now, I will win! Hehehe...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4" id="217">
                <condition filter="has_companion" role="other" var="owner" />
                <state img="#-conversational.png">Say hi, Paska. ~Owner~ brought their own friend too!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Hm? Is ~owner~ here with another as well? Well, why don't you say hello, Paska?</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">Ignore her frown, ~owner~. I assure you that Paska is very excited you came with someone as well!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-5" oneShotId="2">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="crickets" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I didn't gross anyone out with that cricket fact, did I? Got carried away again! Haha...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6" oneShotId="4">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="losttemper" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I-I'm sorry. Sometimes my patience goes thin...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4" oneShotId="7">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="annoying2" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png">(&lt;i&gt;Oh my god. Why did I yell "yippee"!?&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5" id="2">
                <state img="#-frustrated.png" oneShotId="1" marker="karin2">Karin is one of the friends I'm "living" with. She's smart, but... I don't know. She keeps calling me "pipsqueak", a-and interrupting me! Sometimes she's so rude...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5" id="3" oneShotId="55">
                <state img="#-cute.png" marker="gregor2">Oh, um, have I mentioned Gregor yet?  He's my best friend. "Big Guy" and "Little Guy", that's what we've called each other. </state>
                <state img="#-shy.png" marker="gregor2">Oh, um, have I mentioned Gregor yet?  He's my best friend. He's so gentle, even if he's much bigger than most. Really, he's sweet as pound cake...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5" id="4">
                <state img="#-bashful.png" oneShotId="5" marker="mariah2">Mariah is the smartest girl I know! Oh, and she's so sweet, too... She helped me look for berries the other day. She's taught me all sorts of wonderful things.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5" id="5">
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="7" marker="mc">There's someone in the cabin I'm staying with. ~player.ifMale(He's|She's)~ nice, but... I don't know. ~player.ifMale(He|She)~ kinda freaks me out. Though ~player.ifMale(he|she)~ does make some delicious vegetable stew.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="121" oneShotId="3" priority="0">
                <test expr="~background.location~" value="outdoors" />
                <state img="#-smug.png">Oh, I'm so happy to be outside! With over 450 mosses, 900 fungi and 70 slime moulds, there's bound to be treasure out here!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" oneShotId="116">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">My accent isn't too thick, is it? I'd like to think my English is pretty good, but sometimes I slip up.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I'm sorry if I phrase things a bit weird at times. My English isn't perfect, but I do my very best!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="178">I'm so sorry, ~player~. W-Whenever I get embarrassed, my stutter comes out... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6" id="69" priority="0">
                <condition gender="male" character="human" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="218" marker="peptalk">(&lt;i&gt;Be sexy and teasing... That's how you win over a man, Anatoly! Turn around... get ~player~'s interest!&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="207" priority="0">
                <condition filter="chef" role="other" var="chef" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="1052">Oh, I can tell... ~Chef~, you cook, don't you? Don't be shy!</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png" oneShotId="1053">Of course, no two chefs will ever look the same. Just compare me to ~chef~!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="1054">Cooking and art are similar, if you think about. I would say no two cooking styles are exactly the same.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="1076">I haven't been able to speak with that many chefs, actually. I-It's exciting!</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png" oneShotId="1122">From what I know, most chefs get their ingredients from other people. You should try foraging for your own, ~chef~!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="1123">Haev you considered including foraged ingredients in your cooking, ~chef~? Most wouldn't even think to...</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="1138">Oh! ~Chef~ cooks? I wonder what their signature dish is? It can say a lot about a person!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="1139">Cooking takes a lot of patience and practice, you should be proud of your talent, ~chef~!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip">
            <case stage="0-3" id="202" oneShotId="142">
                <condition role="other" character="nagatoro" />
                <test expr="~human.gender~" value="male" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="nagatoro_competition">A man does not want constant nagging and insults. Isn't that correct, ~player~? I'll be extra sweet for you.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="nagatoro_competition">No man wants to be insulted like that. Isn't that right, ~player~? I promise to be extra sweet, just for you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="67" oneShotId="53">
                <condition role="other" character="jura" stage="0-6" sayingMarker="anatoly0" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" marker="jurareply_ms1a">{paska}Squeak squeak! Chitter...!{!reset} &lt;br&gt; Jura, don't yell things like that! Ouch... Paska, you're grinding your claws into my shoulder! &lt;br&gt;{paska}Hiss!{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="66" oneShotId="52">
                <condition role="other" character="meia" stage="0-5" sayingMarker="anatoly0" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="meiareply_ms1a">Oh, yes! But, uh, I don't know how normal it is to keep a pet on your shoulder like I do. She's just clingy.&lt;br&gt;{paska}Squeak!{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="64" oneShotId="50">
                <condition role="other" character="revy" stage="0-7" sayingMarker="anatoly0" />
                <state img="#-frustrated.png" marker="revyreply_ms1a">{uk}Дурна дівчисько...!{!reset}&lt;br&gt;W-What, are you scared of her? You must jump and scream at the sight of a cockroach, huh?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="65" oneShotId="51">
                <condition role="other" character="revy" stage="0-7" sayingMarker="anatoly1" />
                <state img="#-sad.png" marker="revyreply_ms2a">I-I just... Well, I can read! I swear I can, okay!? Uh, so... Stop trying to humiliate me and Paska!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="139" oneShotId="64">
                <condition role="other" character="kumatora" stage="0-7" sayingMarker="anatoly_greet" />
                <state img="#-knowledge.png" marker="kumatorareply_ms1a">I'm lucky to have her, she really does complete me!&lt;br&gt;{paska}Squeak squeak!{!reset} &lt;br&gt; Oh, you've flattered her! Paska, don't get a big head.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="88" oneShotId="80">
                <condition role="other" character="fluttershy" stage="0-6" sayingMarker="Anatoly_why_bring_Paska" />
                <state img="#-conversational.png" marker="fluttershyreply_ms1a">She won't admit it, but she's a clingy girl. If I try and leave the cabin without her, she'll start crying. There was no choice.&lt;br&gt;{paska}...{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="89" oneShotId="81">
                <condition role="other" character="fluttershy" stage="0-6" sayingMarker="Anatoly_cooking_question" />
                <state img="#-sad.png" marker="fluttershyreply_ms2a">My... My family is very poor. After an experience as a boy, I learned how to forage in the woods. I needed to support my parents, so I learned how to cook with anything I found.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="91">
                <condition role="other" character="yuno_uno" stage="0-6" sayingMarker="yuno_anatoly_strip0a" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="yunoreply_ms1a">"Drip"...? Is that some American thing I'm missing? Er, yes, I'm Ukrainian, where "drip" is not a thing, I guess.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="92" oneShotId="91">
                <condition role="other" character="yuno_uno" stage="0-6" sayingMarker="yuno_anatoly_strip1a" />
                <state img="#-knowledge.png" marker="yunoreply_ms2a">Oh, it would have to be borscht! It's a beet stew, served with sour cream (or without if you're vegan, like Mariah). You're missing out if you don't try proper Ukrainian borscht!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="128" oneShotId="107">
                <condition role="other" character="arueshalae" stage="0-2" sayingMarker="Anatoly0a" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png" marker="arueshalaereply_ms1a">{paska}{big}Hissssss!!{!reset} &lt;br&gt;W-Woah, Paska, what's wrong? Arueshalae just wanted to say hello!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="147">
                <condition role="other" character="nanoko-chan" stage="0-7" sayingMarker="nanoko_anatoly0" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="nanokotreply_ms1a">Y-You want my advice...? Really!? Oh, yes! Okay... I have been cooking since I was little, all homemade and full of love! Is there anything in specific you wish to talk about?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5" id="188" oneShotId="138">
                <condition role="other" character="polly" stage="0-5" sayingMarker="Polly_Anatoly_Russian" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" marker="polly_ukraine">{uk}Дай мені спокій, дівчино!{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5" id="189" oneShotId="135">
                <condition role="other" character="polly" stage="0-5" sayingMarker="Polly_Anatoly_Reading" />
                <state img="#-scared.png" marker="polly_illiterate">O-Of course I can read! Who can't read nowadays? Anyone who can't must be s-some type of idiot!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5" id="190" oneShotId="133">
                <condition role="other" character="polly" stage="0-5" sayingMarker="Polly_Anatoly_Snack" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" marker="polly_snack">A "snack"...? I am no food, Polly. G-Ghosts do not eat people, right, ~player~?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5" id="191" oneShotId="136">
                <condition role="other" character="polly" stage="0-5" sayingMarker="Polly_Anatoly_Paska" />
                <state img="#-frustrated.png" marker="polly_paska">I will have you know she is quite smart! Paska, have you anything to say to Polly? &lt;br&gt; {paska}Squeak squeak!{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5" id="192" oneShotId="137">
                <condition role="other" character="polly" stage="0-5" sayingMarker="Polly_Anatoly_Herbs" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="polly_herb">Heh... Silly Polly. Such a thing doesn't exist! Uh, and if it did, {small}or something{!reset}, I wouldn't need it at all!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5" id="193" oneShotId="134">
                <condition role="other" character="polly" stage="0-5" sayingMarker="Polly_Anatoly_ReadItTogether" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png" marker="polly_read">Oh! Um, yes... I read something about, uh, m-mountain climates, recently. It was really interesting, but it'd be better if you read it on your own!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5" id="194" oneShotId="139">
                <condition role="other" character="polly" stage="0-5" sayingMarker="Polly_Anatoly_CookingCompanion" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="polly_cannibalismfunny">I'm not sure I can trust that look in your eyes, Polly...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" oneShotId="159">
                <condition role="other" character="dunban" stage="0-4" sayingMarker="dunban_anatoly_cooking1" />
                <state img="#-shy.png" marker="dunbanreply_ms1a">Oh, you w-want my advice? Um... A good start for new chefs would be homemade bread. It teachs you patience, and the importance in measuring.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="208">
                <condition role="other" character="nagatoro" stage="0-5" sayingMarker="anatoly3" />
                <state img="#-stripping-.png" marker="nagatororeply_ms1a">I am not sure I should trust her with you. She is a fiery girl, what would you do if she scratched you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" oneShotId="169">
                <condition role="other" character="eichi" stage="0-3" sayingMarker="anatoly_impressed" />
                <state img="#-bashful.png" marker="eichireply_ms2a">Hehehe! Oh, you flatter me! I doubt it's as glamorous as that, though. Sometimes I'll worry Gregor, returning home covered in mud...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" oneShotId="171">
                <condition role="other" character="eichi" stage="0-3" sayingMarker="anatoly_1" />
                <state img="#-conversational.png" marker="eichi_replyms1a">I have been foraging since I was a little boy. I do enjoy it, it's nice to be out in the sun for so long. If you aren't careful, you'll get burned though!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <condition role="other" character="aoba" stage="0-5" sayingMarker="Aoba-Anatoly_Squirrel" />
                <state img="#-petting.png" marker="aoba_replyms1">What about her? She never leaves my shoulder.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" oneShotId="104">
                <condition role="other" character="hilbert" sayingMarker="anatoly_hunger" />
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" marker="hilbertreply_ms3a">I-I'm fine! I have lots of food in my cabin, and in my stomach! I-I don't need your pity, boy!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" oneShotId="103">
                <condition role="other" character="hilbert" sayingMarker="anatoly_survival" />
                <state img="#-conversationalalt.png" marker="hilbertreply_ms2a">Survival skills are all I need, my friend. Ukrainian wilderness is not all flowers and bees, but it is not a deathwish... Regardless, I know my way around the outside!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="hilbertreply_ms2a">The forests I frequent are not all rainbows, but they are certainly no deathwish. I know my way around, I am fine with the animals.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" oneShotId="102">
                <condition role="other" character="hilbert" sayingMarker="anatoly_ukraine" />
                <state img="#-knowledge.png" marker="hilbertreply_ms1a">It certainly is! Ukraine is home to beautiful sights and fantastic cooking, if I do say myself... Are you interested in some authentic meals?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="70" oneShotId="58">
                <condition role="other" character="mari" sayingMarker="Anatoly_Misunderstanding1=1" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="marireply_ms1a">I-I thank you for the encouragement, but I'm misunderstanding. Why would I be looking at you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="146" oneShotId="63">
                <condition role="other" character="petra" sayingMarker="petra_anatoly_strip1a" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="petrareply_ms2a">R-Really? I have worried that I'd stand out because of it... But we are similar, I'm not alone! Petra, where are you from?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="145" oneShotId="62">
                <condition role="other" character="petra" sayingMarker="petra_anatoly_strip0a" />
                <state img="#-conversationalalt.png" marker="petrareply_ms1a">Ah, no no no... Paska and I never want to hunt another. We're vegetarians, through and through!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="71" oneShotId="57">
                <condition role="other" character="mari" sayingMarker="Anatoly_Friends1=1" />
                <state img="#-conversational.png" marker="marireply_ms2a">My friends? Well, Mariah and Gregor have stayed with me since we were all kids. Karin was there as well, but, er... I don't know if she likes me much.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="157" oneShotId="84">
                <condition role="other" character="mari_setogaya" sayingMarker="Anatoly_understandPaska_question" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="marireply_ms1a">Nope. Paska and I are emotionally connected. We don't need words. Isn't that right, Paska? &lt;br&gt;{paska}...{!reset}&lt;br&gt;{small}P-Paska, you were meant to squeak or something...{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="93" oneShotId="92">
                <condition role="other" character="rosa" sayingMarker="rosa_anatoly_strip0a" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="rosereply_ms1a">M-My clothes? What is wrong on them, Rosa...? My mama gave me this old shirt, and I tailored these pants myself, you know...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="133">
                <condition role="other" character="gloria" sayingMarker="gloria_anatoly_strip0a" />
                <state img="#-conversational.png" marker="gloriareply_ms1a">You refer to Paska, yes? &lt;br&gt; {paska}...{!reset}&lt;br&gt;She is my squirrel, and companion! Say hi to Gloria, Paska. &lt;br&gt;{paska}Tch.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="140" oneShotId="109">
                <condition role="other" character="turandot" sayingMarker="anatoly_0" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="turnandotreply_ms1a">W-Wow! &lt;i&gt;Sciurus vulgaris...&lt;/i&gt; Yes, she certainly is! You really know your animals, Turandot. {small}Isn't that cool, Paska?{!reset}&lt;br&gt;{paska}Squeak!{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="174" oneShotId="118">
                <condition role="other" character="sly_cooper" sayingMarker="AnatolyShoes1" />
                <state img="#-bashful.png" marker="slyreply_ms1a">S-Smart...? Er-- Yes, I certainly am! L-Lots of studying, reading... Um, {small}yeah...{!reset}&lt;br&gt;Ahem! B-Bentley, hm? Is he another raccoon you know?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" oneShotId="121">
                <condition role="other" character="takatoshi" sayingMarker="AnatolySocks1" />
                <state img="#-conversational.png" marker="takatoshireply_ms2a">Protein is common in more than just meat, Takatoshi. Many people cry out on what they cannot eat as a vegetarian, and ignore how much there is that they can.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" oneShotId="122">
                <condition role="other" character="takatoshi" sayingMarker="AnatolyShoes1" />
                <state img="#-sad.png" marker="takatoshireply_ms1a">{small}You poor man, living on the streets...{!reset} Foraging all depends on the area. In the city, I used to look in the trash for food.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="186" oneShotId="127">
                <condition role="other" character="gloria" sayingMarker="gloria_anatoly_men01" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="gloriareply_ms4a">Oh! Y-Yes, that is true. What is it you would like to ask me...?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="twisted_fate" sayingMarker="Anatoly_Animals_0A" />
                <state img="#-conversational.png">Sadly, I do not speak squirrel. Paska does not speak Ukrainian either, but it's okay! We have an understanding, if that makes sense.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="okino" sayingMarker="anatoly_wishgaypplwerereal2" />
                <state img="#-conversational.png" marker="okino_reply1a">Yes... I-It is a bit difficult to flourish in. But, hey, at least we have each other now, right? Maybe our luck will turn around, and we'll find our very own princes here!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="okino" sayingMarker="anatoly_wishgaypplwerereal1" />
                <state img="#-sad.png" marker="okino_reply1a">Ah, y-yes... It is a bit difficult, I'll admit. And with so many other people, most of the men are taken or interested in someone else!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="joey" sayingMarker="Anatoly_Candy1" />
                <state img="#-conversational.png" marker="joey_replyms1">Yes, actually! On Valentine's day, I made my best friend a batch of honey hard-candies... I even gathered the honey myself!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" oneShotId="181">
                <condition role="other" character="trixie" sayingMarker="anatoly0" />
                <state img="#-frustrated.png" marker="trixie_replyms1">Don't baby me! I am scared of nothing, girl. Do you think I cannot make it through a simple game of poker!?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="steve" />
                <state img="#-conversational.png" marker="stevereply_ms1a">I am afraid I am not Russian. I was born and raised in Ukraine, you see? {uk}Це правда.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <condition role="self" consecutiveLosses="3" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Are you serious? I'm doing awful!</state>
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">There's no way I'd misunderstand something as simple as poker!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5" id="14" totalRounds="0">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Oh, oops... Well, I'm new to this, okay? </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_winning">
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-shy.png">O-Okay... I won't give up now! Yes, I'm still winning...</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">What's with that look, ~player~? I-I'm still winning, you know...!</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I-I'm kind of nervous. Uh, sorry... Just give me a moment.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-conversational.png">No big deal. It's just a small dent in my winning streak, after all.</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Oh, oops! I wasn't paying much attention...</state>
                <state img="#-cute.png">Even in the lead, it's a bit embarrassing... Uh, I'll get to it, though.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-smug.png">It's no big deal. I'm winning regardless!</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">Yes, it's only fair I lose something as well. I'll stay winning, though!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Sorry, everyone. I've kept you waiting.</state>
                <state img="#-knowledge.png">Hmm... Good job beating me! My poker skills are pretty good, aren't they? </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_normal">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-conversationalalt.png">Hmm... Well, it's no big deal. I won't deny that it will likely be boring.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Meh... Not winning, not losing, early in the game... Oh well.</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">Oh, this is fun! Just what will I remove next, hmmmm?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">No big deal, r-right? Yeah, I'm just fine...</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">R-Really? Oh, I thought I could pull through... Well, rules are rules.</state>
                <state img="#-conversationalalt.png">The chance of getting a simple pair is only 50%, so I'll take my wins with my losses.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Well, things could be going worse.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">G-Gregor, those strategies you taught me are completely useless!</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I-I thought I was smarter than this...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_losing">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Is there something I'm misunderstanding? Please tell me if I'm playing incorrectly.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">This is my first time playing poker, okay? C-Can't you go easy on me?</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Eep! My allergies are really acting up... O-Oh, I lost?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Yes yes, laugh at my loss... Hehehe, I'll win in the end, you know!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">W-Wow... I really don't know how to play...</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Oh, I'm a little embarrassed... But I've kept you all waiting, so...</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">D-Don't pity me. I'll make a great comeback, okay?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Each time I lose, I get more flustered... It's made it hard to focus!</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Am I simply unlucky? It would explain a lot, actually.</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">{small}&lt;i&gt;Ahhh...&lt;/i&gt;{!reset}{big}&lt;i&gt;Achoo!!&lt;/i&gt;{!reset} &lt;br&gt;Ah, e-excuse me! Oh, what!? I lost? </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripping">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="okino_reply1a" />
                <condition count="0" character="takatoshi" />
                <condition gender="male" role="other" character="okino" stage="0-7" sayingMarker="anatoly_gaypeople2b" />
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">The same guy? Oh... I know how it is, Okino. It's hard, and frustrating... It's like they never pay attention to anything.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="132">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="fluttershyreply_ms2a" />
                <condition role="other" character="fluttershy" stage="0-6" sayingMarker="Anatoly_cooking_cont" />
                <state img="#-stripping+.png" marker="fluttershyreply_s2a">Thank you, Fluttershy... I'm appreciating that. Actually, you seem like you'd be interested. Are you vegetarian?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="131">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="fluttershyreply_ms1a" />
                <condition role="other" character="fluttershy" stage="0-6" sayingMarker="Anatoly_why_bring_Paska_cont" />
                <state img="#-stripping+.png" marker="fluttershyreply_s1a">You're experienced with all types of animals, hm? No wonder Paska is so calm right now! She's usually quite jealous towards girls. &lt;br&gt;{paska}Squeak...{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="nagatororeply_ms1a" />
                <condition role="other" character="nagatoro" stage="0-5" sayingMarker="anatoly02" />
                <state img="#-stripping+.png" marker="nagatoro_replys1">Really? Well, maybe if she's okay with it... What do you say, Paska?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" oneShotId="130">
                <condition role="other" character="nanoko-chan" stage="0-7" sayingMarker="nanoko_anatoly1" />
                <state img="#-stripping-.png" marker="nanokotreply_s1a">Hm... Well, you are likely putting too many of your noodles into the water. You understand, starch will get into the water and end up expanding, causing that water to rise.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" oneShotId="168">
                <condition role="other" character="eichi" stage="0-4" sayingMarker="anatoly_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping+.png" marker="eichireply_s1a">&lt;i&gt;Never?&lt;/i&gt; Oh, are you a city boy? Ukraine's wildlife can be quite intimidating. Here, I promise I'll protect you, okay?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="76" oneShotId="73">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="marireply_ms2a" />
                <condition role="other" character="mari" saidMarker="Anatoly_Friends1" sayingMarker="Anatoly_Friends2A=1" />
                <state img="#-stripping+.png" marker="marireply_s2a">Oh, he's the best! Always considerate and helping... Not only that, but he's real big and strong as well. If I ever need to get something off a shelf, he's always there to lift me up!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="77" oneShotId="75">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="marireply_ms2a" />
                <condition role="other" character="mari" saidMarker="Anatoly_Friends1" sayingMarker="Anatoly_Friends2C=1" />
                <state img="#-stripping-.png" marker="marireply_s2c">Karin... She likes to exploit people, truthfully. I guess I'm the easiest to pick on out of our friends. Mariah will yell back, and Gregor is so strong you wouldn't dare make fun of him. I'm just a weakling...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="83" oneShotId="74">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="marireply_ms2a" />
                <condition role="other" character="mari" saidMarker="Anatoly_Friends1" sayingMarker="Anatoly_Friends2B=1" />
                <state img="#-stripping+.png" marker="marireply_s2b">You two would get along, I think! She's a hard worker, smart, and incredibly kind. B-But she'll grow fiery if you wrong her. She's like... a beaver.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" oneShotId="72">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="marireply_ms1a" />
                <condition role="other" character="mari" saidMarker="Anatoly_Misunderstanding1" />
                <state img="#-stripping-.png" marker="marireply_s1a">Mari... I like men. Only men.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="137" oneShotId="77">
                <condition role="other" character="kumatora" sayingMarker="anatoly_greet2" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="kumatorareply_ms1a" />
                <state img="#-stripping+.png" marker="kumatorareply_s1a">Hear that, Paska? A dynamic duo! And people say dogs are a man's true friend. &lt;br&gt;{paska}Chitter chitter!{!reset}&lt;br&gt; Eh, you want to say something to Kumatora...?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="150">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="marireply_ms1a" />
                <condition role="other" character="mari_setogaya" sayingMarker="Anatoly_understandPaska_cont" />
                <state img="#-stripping-.png" marker="marireply_s1a">{paska}...{!reset}&lt;br&gt;Paska... Come on, be nice to her...&lt;br&gt;{paska}Tch.{!reset}&lt;br&gt;Er... Ignore her, Mari. She is quite hostile towards girls.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="arueshalaereply_ms1a" />
                <condition role="other" character="arueshalae" sayingMarker="Anatoly0b" />
                <state img="#-stripping-.png" marker="arueshalaereply_s1a">Just ignore her, Arueshalae. She can be quite mean to ladies we encounter. {small}And she is likely not happy you thought she was a boy...{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" oneShotId="131">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="petrareply_ms1a" />
                <condition role="other" character="petra" sayingMarker="petra_anatoly_strip0b" />
                <state img="#-stripping+.png" marker="petrareply_s1a">She is so talented! My eyes are not perfect, you see, so her help in locating nuts and herbs is always appreciated.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" oneShotId="132">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="petrareply_ms2a" />
                <condition role="other" character="petra" sayingMarker="petra_anatoly_strip1b" />
                <state img="#-stripping+.png" marker="petrareply_s2a">Brigid... I--- I um, have definitely read about such a place! I am sure of it. Famous for your... uh...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="185" oneShotId="128">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="gloriareply_ms1a" />
                <condition role="other" character="gloria" sayingMarker="gloria_anatoly_strip0b" />
                <state img="#-stripping-.png" marker="gloriareply_s1a">Paska thanks you, a-and I do too. But, um... What is a Pokémon...?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="187" oneShotId="129">
                <condition role="other" character="gloria" sayingMarker="gloria_anatoly_men02" />
                <state img="#-stripping+.png" marker="gloriareply_s4a">Uh, I guess m-my "go-to" would simply be my mouth. A man goes crazy at the sight of you on your knees! It took some practice, but now I'm really good at uh... {small}&lt;i&gt;y-you know...&lt;/i&gt;{!reset} </state>
                <state img="#-stripping+.png" marker="gloriareply_s4a">U-Uh... heheh... I guess my "go-to" would be using my mouth. Men go crazy at the sight of someone on their knees. Besides, I've gotten very good with uh... m-my mouth.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="takatoshi" sayingMarker="AnatolyShoes2" />
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">Yes, it is really quite humiliating. Hunger will do crazy things to the brain...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="steve" sayingMarker="AnatolyShoes2" />
                <state img="#-stripping+.png" marker="steve_replys1">It is beautiful! Um, very cold, though. It's quite different from America, I think. I lived in a small village, at least.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="119" priority="0">
                <condition gender="male" character="human" />
                <condition count="0" filter="straight" character="human" />
                <state img="#-stripping+.png" marker="boyfriendmaterial">M-Men value someone who can cook, right? Well, I have quite the talent for it! And Gregor says I look adorable in my apron, too!</state>
                <state img="#-stripping+.png" marker="boyfriendmaterial">Men want a partner who is talented in cooking, y-yes? Well, I am quite talented! Besides, Gregor said I look adorable in my apron.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">Things have been difficult, but I've had my friends with me through it all. Even if I like to be alone, I'm thankful for their company.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">I didn't know many people growing up, and even now I only know... four others. </state>
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">Have you heard of the works by Franz Kafka? I'm a huge fan! He's famous for his works of horror, if you're curious!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-stripping+.png" marker="mariah">Last summer, I worked as a lifeguard. My friend Mariah would splash around in the water, smiling as I watched.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">I used to be quite the swimmer, actually. It's... been a bit since I've felt like going in the water. </state>
                <state img="#-stripping+.png" marker="womenshirt">If the buttons on a shirt are on the right side, then it's a man's shirt - if it's on the left, it's a woman's. Why? I have no idea!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">Resourcefulness is vital to living. So many people rely on factories or stores... Whatever happened to hand washing your clothing in a river?</state>
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">(&lt;i&gt;Ah! There's a five kopiyok coin on the floor! I'll slip this into my pockets when they aren't paying attention...&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">Ukraine is home to many animals, but cats outnumber dogs by a lot! They don't interest me, though. Not when I have Paska!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-stripping+.png" marker="gregor">Er... I hope Gregor is doing alright, even if I'm only out for a bit. He's told me the same dream since we were young.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">One time, I was walking around town, and a bully went and pantsed me. The look on my papa's face when I shuffled home with my pants down...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">Agh! T-The zipper got stuck! Oh, my nerves are getting the better of me...</state>
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">H-Hey, be careful with these, okay? I can't really afford to get new pants...</state>
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">A-At least my briefs aren't some embarrassing pattern. L-Like strawberries, or something...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">Ahh... O-Okay. I trust you, so...</state>
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">Eek! O-Okay, but only if you avoid staring!</state>
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">Very well... Just... P-Please do not stare too much.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripped">
            <case stage="2" id="155" oneShotId="110">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="fluttershyreply_s2a" />
                <condition role="other" character="fluttershy" stage="0-6" sayingMarker="Anatoly_cooking_end" />
                <state img="#-conversational.png" marker="fluttershyreply_as2a">You care so deeply about animals, I can tell! There is no way you would purchase meat. I am happy to see such a thing, Fluttershy!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="156" oneShotId="111">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="fluttershyreply_s1a" />
                <condition role="other" character="fluttershy" stage="0-6" sayingMarker="Anatoly_why_bring_Paska_end" />
                <state img="#-conversationalalt.png" marker="fluttershyreply_as1a">She can act so aggressive towards them! When my friend gets too close to me, she nips at her... I've seen her ruin makeup palettes before, too. Isn't it bizarre?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="marireply_s2c" />
                <condition role="other" character="mari" saidMarker="Anatoly_Friends2C" sayingMarker="Anatoly_Friends3C=1" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Ah, no no no! She would have us all sleeping outside if we dare banded together! Karin's word is final, t-that is just how it is...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" oneShotId="71">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="marireply_ms1a" />
                <condition role="other" character="mari" saidMarker="Anatoly_Misunderstanding2" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">&lt;i&gt;Pfft...&lt;/i&gt; Hahahaha! It's fine! Thanks for understanding, okay? Some aren't so kind.&lt;br&gt; {paska}Squeak squeak!{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" oneShotId="115">
                <condition role="other" character="kumatora" sayingMarker="anatoly_greet3" />
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" marker="kumatorareply_as1a">W-What!? Paska! Kumatora, what did she say to you!? T-Tell me!</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" marker="kumatorareply_as1a">P-Paska! What did you say to her!? Kumatora... Tell me what she said, please!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="arueshalae" sayingMarker="Anatoly0c" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png" marker="arueshalae_replyas1">Ah-- I'm sorry! Did I offend you? She's like it to many girls, I swear it isn't personal!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="102" oneShotId="95">
                <condition status="chest_visible" role="self" />
                <condition count="0" status="chest_visible" role="opp" />
                <condition count="1-" gender="female" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I-I'm sorry, a man's chest isn't nearly as exciting as a woman's, huh?</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I-It's nothing special, especially compared to a woman's... So I should not be so embarrassed.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6" id="101" oneShotId="94">
                <condition status="crotch_visible" role="self" />
                <condition count="0" status="crotch_visible" role="opp" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png">S-So... Erm, I'm a bit nervous to be alone in this...</state>
                <state img="#-scared.png">T-The first one to show that... It's a bit of a lame start, isn't it?</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">Oh... W-Won't someone join me? It's embarrassing to be alone!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="mariah" />
                <state img="#-shy.png">She'd laugh and splash me with water, or try and drag me in... I really value that time we shared. I'm happy I know her.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="gregor" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">&lt;i&gt;"I'm gonna chop firewood, and look at the stars!"&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hehehe! When we first met, he was chopping wood outside my house. Not much has changed, it seems!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="womenshirt" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png">W-Wait... My buttons are on the left side. Have I been wearing a woman's shirt this entire time...?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4" id="120">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="boyfriendmaterial" />
                <state img="#-cute.png">S-So, keep that in mind, okay? I promise I won't disappoint you. I am a hard worker, and I really think you would enjoy my cooking. &lt;br&gt; {paska}Squeak squeak!{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">S-So, keep that in mind... I think you would enjoy my cooking, and I-I work really hard! &lt;br&gt;{paska}Squeak squeak!{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-conversational.png">That was a bit boring, huh? You know what isn't boring? Sharing our best vegetarian recipes!</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">(&lt;i&gt;They don't notice the holes in my socks, right? They'd definitely make fun of me if they did...&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="borschtchallenge">Hey, ~player~, if you beat me I'll share my recipe for homemade borscht! It's really good, I promise!</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">H-Hey, ~player~... Height isn't important, right? I'm 25 and only 5'5". So I don't think I'm gonna get any taller...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">W-What is it? You look like you have something you want to say!</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I-I'm sorry. Did I... disappoint anyone?</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">If it's such an issue, t-then you can just look away!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-conversational.png">Want to build muscle? Try hand-whipping whipped cream. You'll be stronger than an ox after that!</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">I never had a swimsuit. Whenever I went swimming, Gregor and I would just go in our underwear! {small}Good times...{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-afterstrip.png">Listen, if my pants fall down now... It isn't my fault, okay?</state>
                <state img="#-knowledge.png">Hmm... I'm definitely doing things wrong. Er-- I mean... This is all part of my super smart plan to lose!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5" id="7">
                <state img="custom:paskaleaves" marker="paskaleaves">Ah-- Paska, where are you going!? You best behave yourself!</state>
                <state img="custom:paskaleaves" marker="paskaleaves">Paska, where are you going!? Don't cause any trouble!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_strip">
            <case stage="0-5" id="240">
                <condition role="self" sayingMarker="dunban_ms1a" />
                <condition role="target" character="dunban" stage="0" sayingMarker="dunban_anatoly_self0a" />
                <state img="#-cute.png">When you, uh, remove your coat. May I examine it? T-The craftmanship is fantastic, and it'd help me in my sewing, you know?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Heheheh... Expect to lose more, ~name~. My knowledge is unmatched!</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">Hey, the chances of at least a pair are just 49.9%, you know. Poker is difficult!</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Winning really &lt;i&gt;does&lt;/i&gt; have its advantages...</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Don't worry! I-It's embarrassing for us as well, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Am I supposed to watch? Am I &lt;i&gt;not&lt;/i&gt; supposed to watch?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">It might not mean much, but I'm rooting for you, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-knowledge.png">You've piqued my curiosity, ~name~. Make it something good!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6 8">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">H-Hey, it's alright, ~name~! </state>
                <state img="#-cute.png">It'll be nice to not be alone...</state>
                <state img="#-cute.png">You aren't alone, ~name~. I-I mean, you know...</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Ahh, ~name~ lost?</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I hope you don't mind me watching...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Heheh... Sorry, ~name~. It's awkward for me too...</state>
                <state img="#-cute.png">I-I don't mean to stare... It's just that... Well, let's just continue.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Curiosity is normal, isn't it?</state>
                <state img="#-mast2.png">How inspiring! Oh, I feel like cooking...</state>
                <state img="#-cute.png">I'm supposed to look, aren't I?</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Does your loss frustrate you? I am okay with you taking that anger out on me, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-nervous.png">{paska}&lt;i&gt;Squeak squeak.&lt;/i&gt;{!reset}&lt;br&gt;Eh!? That's not true! Don't say that when ~name~ is right there, Paska!</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">{paska}&lt;i&gt;Chitter chitter!&lt;/i&gt;{!reset}&lt;br&gt;Oh stop it, Paska! ~Name~ doesn't care, so quit trying to embarrass me!</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Paska... You do not need to stare at ~name~ with such anger.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_strip">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-conversationalalt.png">Come on, ~name~! You can do better than that!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Did you do this on purpose, or were you just unlucky, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Hey! I-I didn't lose!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Aha! I knew it---poker is quite simple with the smarts like mine!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Heheh! Expect to lose even more moving forward, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Unlucky today, are you? Well, it's not a big deal.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6 8">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">T-This is a bit embarrassing, even if ~name~'s the one who has to strip.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Fight hard, never give in! Channel the energy of a Ukrainian boar and give it your all!</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">It's less humiliating to be naked when everyone is focused on ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">European women certainly are beautiful, but none of them really catch my eye.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Huh? Oh, ~name~ lost. </state>
                <state img="#-cute.png">Hey... Um, you aren't mad at me... Right, ~name~?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-mast2.png">(&lt;i&gt;Yes... ~Name~ will keep everyone focused on her, so I don't have to worry about being stared at.&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Ah, s-sorry, ~name~. Hopefully this isn't too awkward for you...</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Heheheh! Another loss for ~name~? It's clear now, I'm the one winning-- {small}Oh, wait a minute...{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-mast2.png">Alone and safe, I can pretend I'm all by myself...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-shocked.png">{paska}&lt;i&gt;Squeeeeeak!&lt;/i&gt;{!reset}&lt;br&gt;Paska! How could you say such a thing about ~name~!?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">{paska}&lt;i&gt;Squeak squeak!&lt;/i&gt;{!reset}&lt;br&gt;Hmmm? Are you jealous of ~name~'s fashion, Paska?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Hm... Any tips for ~name~, Paska? &lt;br&gt;{paska}Chitter chitter.{!reset}&lt;br&gt;Yeah, that should help her out.</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">You win some, you lose some. Isn't that right, Paska? </state>
                <state img="#-petting.png">{uk}ти втомився?{!reset}&lt;br&gt;{paska}Chitter chitter.{!reset}&lt;br&gt;{uk}Ах, спи міцно.{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I hope you are not a woman who gets angry when she loses... That type of person is so awkward to play with!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="tie">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">This is probably a rare occurrence, but I'm currently busy thinking about cabbage.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Aha! A tie! You owe a cola!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0-8" id="26">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-scared.png" marker="bobobo_donpatch">L-Living in that cabin is making me lose my mind! I'm truly beginning to see things!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="245">
                <test expr="~clothing~" value="glasses" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Ah... Were your glasses just for looks? That's not fair! If I took mine off, I'd probably fall over...</state>
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">Ah, so they were not &lt;i&gt;real&lt;/i&gt; glasses, hm? Your eyesight is perfectly fine? Lucky.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-knowledge.png">This is the start of your losing streak, ~name~! You can start as small as you want...</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Hey, did you know? Flax is the earliest known natural textile fabric. It was used in about 5000 BC!</state>
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">{paska}Squeak squeak!{!reset}&lt;br&gt;No, Paska! ~Clothing.toPlural~ are not for chewing!</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="142" marker="annoying">(&lt;i&gt;I don't want to be annoying... ~Name~ is so cute! I really should make a good impression.&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">Ah, your ~clothing~? Not too exciting, but it's no big deal.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I'm no good with smalltalk, and you certainly aren't making it easier for me...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-5">
                <state img="#-conversationalalt.png">~Clothing.a~ ~clothing~? Boring... I can't even think of a fun fact for something like that.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">"Another one eats his dust!" Or... whatever you Americans say!</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Yayyy... ~Clothing.a~ ~clothing~.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Normal, but oh so boring...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6 8">
                <state img="#-cute.png">Y-You don't need to be shy, ~name~. I promise, okay?</state>
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">A-Are you teasing me or something? Playing hard to get? Hmph!</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Ehh!? C-Come on!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">R-Really? Just your ~clothing~...? Oh, I was hoping for more...</state>
                <state img="#-mast1.png">It's a good thing I have a talent for daydreaming.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Ah, c-come on! You're making this difficult for me...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="0-4" id="158" oneShotId="120">
                <condition role="target" character="sly_cooper" stage="2" saidMarker="AnatolyGloves2Reply" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="sly_s2a" />
                <state img="#-petting.png" marker="sly_as2a">Sadly, I am unable to speak squirrel with her. Nor does she truly understand Ukrainian... But it is okay! We understand each other; we do not need words. Isn't that right, Paska?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="44">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-frustrated.png" marker="bobobo_doubleundies">Now you're wasting all that fabric. Not so funny now, hm?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="45">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="bobobo_tripleundies">What is up with this guy...?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="244">
                <test expr="~clothing~" value="glasses" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Ah... Were your glasses just for looks? That's not fair! If I took mine off, I'd probably fall over...</state>
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">Ah, so they were not &lt;i&gt;real&lt;/i&gt; glasses, hm? Your eyesight is perfectly fine? Lucky.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4" oneShotId="8">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="annoying" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="annoying2">Yayyyy! Yippee! Woohoo! Wow, ~name~ that sure was fantastic!!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-cute.png">Gregor taught me how to make friendship bracelets when we were younger... I still have mine, actually.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Isn't it rude to stall with accessories? Or, well, they are in the way...</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">Just your ~clothing~...? That does nothing to distract me from my hunger...</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Let's continue before I fall asleep.</state>
                <state img="#-conversationalalt.png">Hey, Paska, wake up! ~Name~ took off his ~clothing~, and we're moving on!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-5">
                <state img="#-conversational.png">Feeling better now?</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">It's not much of a difference, but progress is progress.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Even lettuce hides itself beneath many leaves... In short, ~name~ is lettuce. {small}Or something.{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">It wasn't much... But still, I find myself breathless!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6 8">
                <state img="#-cute.png">Ah, a-are you making fun of me? Removing your ~clothing~ while I'm like t-this...</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Y-You're embarrassing me!</state>
                <state img="#-conversationalalt.png">You should always remove any accessories in the kitchen. You don't want a ring falling in your porridge, do you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">Hmph. Playing hard to get, are we?</state>
                <state img="#-mast2.png">(&lt;i&gt;Stay patient and waiting. ~Name~'s sure to take something better off soon!&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Staying nude with your ~clothing~ on wouldn't have been a bad look, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-cute.png">Is there something I could do to... "convince" you to take off more? P-Pretty please...?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-calm.png">My mama used to make bracelets for me out of colored thread. I'd wear them until they ripped in half!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Do women still wear corsets, or is that out of style now? I wouldn't know.</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">Is this how everyone dresses where you're from, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">Did you make your ~clothing~ yourself, ~name~? </state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Surely your ~clothing~ ~clothing.ifPlural(are|is)~ handmade, right?</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">Feeling okay, ~name~?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-5">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">How much food could I get if I traded ~clothing.a~ ~clothing~ at a market...? No, I shouldn't resort to that.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Soo... How much ~clothing.ifPlural(are those|is that)~ ~clothing~ worth? Or-- Uh... T-That's rude of me to ask.</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">Removing the layers, slowly but surely... Like peeling an onion! Eh? A good comparison, right?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">My mama once told me that girls who wear lots of makeup and jewelry will burn in the afterlife. I never understood the correlation...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6 8">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Is this some type of high level strategy?</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Gah... I-I shouldn't get frustrated. I'm just so embarrassed!</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">W-Whatever... At this point, I don't really care about ~clothing.a~ ~clothing~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Erm, don't worry about me...</state>
                <state img="#-cute.png">(&lt;i&gt;It's so nice for the spotlight to be on ~name~! Hopefully that isn't rude...&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="0-6" id="153" oneShotId="112">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="mari_s1a" />
                <condition role="target" character="mari_setogaya" stage="1" saidMarker="Anatoly_realSuccubus2" />
                <state img="#-frustrated.png" marker="mari_as1a">You worry the most about your studies, bad girl! Do not distract your fellow students. Education is important! Well, so is eating... But still!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="112">
                <condition role="target" character="ms.fortune" stage="3" sayingMarker="Fortune_Strip_2C" />
                <state img="#-scared.png">...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-conversational.png">{paska}&lt;i&gt;Chitter chitter!&lt;/i&gt;{!reset}&lt;br&gt;Hm? You want ~clothing.a~ ~clothing~, Paska?</state>
                <state img="#-conversationalalt.png">How will you forage efficiently if you're weighed down by accessories? Think about it, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Accessories are definitely a symbol of class, even a nice pair of shoes shows how wealthy you are.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Hahaha! Paska is jealous of your ~clothing~, ~name~. Come on, Paska. What would a squirrel like you do with ~clothing.a~ ~clothing~?</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">~clothing.ifPlural(Have|Has)~ your ~clothing~ been fitting you alright? If you need any alterations, I'm open to do them! {small}Please, I need the extra money.{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-cute.png">Gregor's &lt;i&gt;amazing&lt;/i&gt; at knitting. I still have all the scarves hes made me.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Fashion sure is an interesting thing... It is a shame that the topic itself is considered so feminine.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-5">
                <state img="#-conversational.png">Did you know? Scarves weren't considered fashion accessories until France popularized the idea.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Let's continue on!</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Good to continue, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">You can cover something in seasoning, but it won't change the food it covers.</state>
                <state img="#-conversationalalt.png">You should always keep your fingernails neat and tidy if you're going to cook. Some women like to paint them, but that's not sanitary!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6 8">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Sorry...</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Goodness, ~name~ kicked my butt!</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">J-Just take your time, ~name~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-conversationalalt.png">I'm much too busy to stop and stare at ~clothing.a~ ~clothing~.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">C-Come on, ~name~. Are you trying to drag things out or something?</state>
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">~Name~, you're proof that there are things worse than food poisoning in the world.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Ehh? Are you hungry, or just bored, Paska?</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">{paska}Squeak squeak...{!reset}&lt;br&gt;I'm doing my best here, Paska! I-It can be hard for a shy guy like me...</state>
                <state img="#-knowledge.png">There's no pressure, ~name~... But I &lt;i&gt;am&lt;/i&gt; curious.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">It's just ~clothing.ifPlural(some|~clothing.a~)~ ~clothing~, so why am I so nervous...?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6 8">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Heyyy... D-Don't fluster me, okay?</state>
                <state img="#-cute.png">There can't be too much left, can there?</state>
                <state img="#-cute.png">Y-You've already got my attention, ~name~. Are you sure you will only take off your ~clothing~?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-5">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Should I start paying attention now? No...?</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Well, it's a start!</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">S-Sorry. I'm not bugging you, am I? Oh...</state>
                <state img="#-cute.png">W-Well, I'm still rooting for you, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">You aren't too nervous, are you? I promise you will not disappoint me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-mast2.png">Your ~clothing~ was getting in the way anyways.</state>
                <state img="#-cute.png">E-Excuse me if I end up saying something embarrassing, ~name~. It's hard to think straight...</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">My eyes are still drawn to you, ~name~. Isn't that weird?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_minor">
            <case stage="0-8" id="36">
                <condition role="target" character="ignatz" stage="3" sayingMarker="glassesstart" notSaidMarker="bernadettathrowstart" />
                <condition role="target" character="ignatz" sayingMarker="glassesstart" notSaidMarker="artpunstart" />
                <condition role="target" character="ignatz" sayingMarker="glassesstart" notSaidMarker="igfluttershy_hug" />
                <condition role="target" character="ignatz" sayingMarker="glassesstart" notSaidMarker="artpunstart" />
                <condition role="target" character="ignatz" sayingMarker="glassesstart" notSaidMarker="igpetra_stripglasses2" />
                <test expr="~target.costume~" cmp="!=" value="ignatz_drawn_brawn" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Really? How could you be so careless, Ignatz!?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">{paska}Squeak squeak!{!reset}&lt;br&gt;Well, e-excuse me for trying to be adventurous, Paska! </state>
                <state img="#-conversationalalt.png">Will you go for something more daring next?</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">W-Well, now that ~clothing.ifPlural(those|that)~ ~clothing~ ~clothing.ifPlural(are|is)~ out of the way, the door is open for more!</state>
                <state img="#-conversationalalt.png">No spice and just ~clothing.a~ ~clothing~ makes a dull meal.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-5">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">It's over? A-Already...?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Patience blooms flowers. So take as long as you need, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">The water is simmering, ~name~... How long until it boils?</state>
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">Do not feel like you have captured my heart already, ~name~. I just... haven't been out much.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Just how sexy can ~clothing.toPlural~ be?</state>
                <state img="#-mast1.png">Ah, i-it's okay ~name~. I'll just use my imagination, I guess...</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">You make my soul blue, ~name~...</state>
                <state img="#-cute.png">It is no bother to me... To see you strip makes my heart beat faster, no matter the item.</state>
                <state img="#-mast2.png">I still liked watching, even if it was just your ~clothing~. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6 8">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Ah... I-Is that all...? I see...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">A hungry wolf is stronger than a satisfied dog.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Augh, I need a drink.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">You will need to do more than lose ~clothing.a~ ~clothing~ to satisfy my hunger, ~name~. </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="nagatoro_ms1a" />
                <condition role="target" character="nagatoro" stage="0" sayingMarker="anatoly2" />
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Rghh!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">Karin leaves her dirty clothes around the room all the time! I keep telling her to pick up her dirty laundry, b-but she doesn't listen!</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">There will always be a classic beauty to a woman's ~clothing~.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Good, good! You can do it, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Hehehe! Paska, don't stare at ~name~ so aggressively! What, are you jealous?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-5">
                <state img="#-conversational.png">When it rains, it floods. Be careful next round, o-okay?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Make sure you get your ~clothing~ from a reliable place, ~name~! I don't like what all these modern "companies" are up to...</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I hope you're enjoying yourself, with or without your ~clothing~.</state>
                <state img="#-conversationalalt.png">I've no right to judge you, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6 8">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">(&lt;i&gt;I'm craving cabbage rolls again...&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-conversationalalt.png">Learning to travel light is really important! ~clothing.ifPlural(Are those|Is that)~ really essential?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Uh, I'm r-rooting for you! {small}That probably doesn't mean much...{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-mast1.png">Uh... S-Sorry.</state>
                <state img="#-mast1.png">A-Ah...</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Heheheh! Men really are dogs at a pretty woman's feet, aren't they?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_minor">
            <case stage="0-6" id="152" oneShotId="114">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="mari_s2a" />
                <condition role="target" character="mari_setogaya" stage="2" saidMarker="Anatoly_notUnlucky2" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="mari_as2a">Folklore does not frame you kindly, Mari. Succubi are always displayed as malicious and devilish creatures... But now, here I am having a completely normal conversation with one!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-conversational.png">Paska, what's got you so restless? Are you hungry? Well, I'll find you some lettuce in a bit.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Looking at your ~clothing~... I want to sew! Maybe when I get back home, I'll start a new project.</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">Mariah and Karin don't know anything about tailoring. It's Gregor and I who are talented in knitting and sewing!</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Don't dig your paws into my shoulder, Paska. You'll leave holes in my shirt!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-5">
                <state img="#-conversationalalt.png">A woman’s beauty cannot warm a winter’s night.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I know fashion is important and all that, but you need to be light on your feet!</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">I-I taught myself to sew, actually. So if you need anything, you can let me know!</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">You know what sounds really fun? Reading a good book!</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">When I was a boy, I was mainly bullied by groups of girls. I... don't know why they'd always push me around.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-mast2.png">I-I'm a bit busy, you see...</state>
                <state img="#-mast1.png">Huh? ~Name~'s ~clothing~? That's nice, I guess...</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">~Clothing.a~ ~clothing~? O-Okay...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6 8">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">I've thought of a new dish. S-Stir-fried ~clothing~! Care to try some, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Ahh... Seriously?</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Er... D-Did you know that &lt;i&gt;gossypium&lt;/i&gt; uh... also known as cotton... uh... &lt;br&gt;I-I forgot what I was going to say.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_major">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Oh, come on! Why are my allergies acting up &lt;i&gt;now&lt;/i&gt;?</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">R-Really? Your ~clothing~...? How sweet of you...</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">I-I'm sorry, I promise not to stare too much, ~name~...</state>
                <state img="#-cute.png">M-My heart is beating so fast...</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">I-I'm sorry if I glance at you, ~name~...</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">O-Of course you'd remove your ~clothing~ next! It's all part of the game, n-nothing more!</state>
                <state img="#-knowledge.png">I-It's just part of the game, isn't it? It makes sense for me to stare.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-mast2.png">Gently removing ~clothing.a~ ~clothing~... Slipping it off so intimately b-before... &lt;i&gt;Ah...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-heavy3.png">W-Would a man ever remove my ~clothing~...? Slowly undressing me, then kissing hungrily as a reward... Oh my...</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Um... I... I shouldn't really say what I'm thinking, should I?</state>
                <state img="#-cute.png">Oh, my heart can't handle that!</state>
                <state img="#-heavy1.png">I cannot stop these crass thoughts... Not when you remove your ~clothing~ like that, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6 8">
                <state img="#-cute.png">W-Watching ~name~ remove his ~clothing~, while I'm like this...?</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">Ah, y-your ~clothing~...? Oh my...</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">I'm... I'm embarrassed. But it's worth it to see ~name~ as sweet as this...</state>
                <state img="#-cute.png">E-Excuse me and my silly words, ~name~. I don't want to make things awkward for you...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_major">
            <case stage="0-8" id="226">
                <condition role="target" character="steve" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Oh, it is just too much! I-I can't stare at your body any longer!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Ouch! Oh, I-I think I forgot to blink...</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Flustered? Me? Never... Why would I ever stare at that &lt;i&gt;handsome, charming man... slowly taking off his ~clothing~ while--&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">Gregor was right, I do blush easily... Can you really blame me, though?</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">A fire is sure to start if sparks are there.</state>
                <state img="#-cute.png">That cabin is so cold, but down here... I-I think I'm overheating.</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">Ah, shall we move on? What do you think, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">Do you understand how you make me feel, ~name~? W-What... I want you to do to me?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6 8">
                <state img="#-cute.png">W-Well, if we keep going on like this... Oh my...</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">Ah, are you sure you're okay without your ~clothing~?</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">He's only removed his ~clothing~ and I've already become a blushing mess... </state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">M-My hands are getting sweaty. Oh! That's gross, I'm sorry!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-cute.png">I hear men will do anything for a pretty woman. B-But, I'd do anything for a guy like you, ~name~...</state>
                <state img="#-mast2.png">To remove your ~clothing~ while I'm like this... D-Did you do it on purpose, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-mast1.png">J-Just ~clothing.a~ ~clothing~... But in this context, it's so much more.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_major">
            <case stage="0-6" id="79">
                <condition role="target" character="emi" stage="7" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png">You're dedicated, but this is just for fun, you know... Is losing that bad?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Y-You're sure of this, right, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">This is so strange for me... But really, it must be stranger for ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Eek! A-Are you really sure?</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Male and female clothing is all so different!</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Ah-- Well, d-don't get mad at me, okay?</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I-I won, yay! This is so awkward...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-mast1.png">Uh, sorry, ~name~. I hope I don't offend you... but I've got no interest in women, really.</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Oh no! You've lost? Come on, ~name~! Y-You can do it!</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Removing your ~clothing~ is certainly less embarrassing than this!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6 8">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I hope I don't offend you if I look somewhere else.</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Ah, what a bold move!</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">There's so many proverbs about women and beauty, it's difficult to choose just one.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I-I'm happy I won that round, but I feel sort of bad now...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_major">
            <case stage="0-6" id="151" oneShotId="113">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="mari_s3a" />
                <condition role="target" character="mari_setogaya" stage="3" saidMarker="Anatoly_LackOfNutrition_cont" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="mari_as3a">I think I am beginning to understand... Just like regular food, you have your tastes and prefaces. When it is framed like that... Huh.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="23">
                <condition role="target" character="mari_setogaya" stage="4" sayingMarker="Mari_wings_reveal" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png">&lt;i&gt;EEEEEEK!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">W-Well, best of luck in the coming rounds, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I don't see many women, you know. S-So... yeah.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">W-Well, I hope I haven't offended you... You're pretty, but...</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">It's only natural to appreciate the human body, no matter the gender.</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Ah... Is it dusty in here? I think my allergies are acting up again...</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">N-Next time you cook, be sure to put an apron on, ~name~. You don't want to stain your ~clothing~, r-right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6 8">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">T-There's only so much left... Oh goodness!</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Be careful, ~name~. You don't want someone to plant a pig on you, right?</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">W-Well, you've certainly gotten the attention of the others, ~name~. That must be exciting!</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">Uh, I like your underwear, ~name~. It... It looks nice, and stuff.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I was always taught to be extra nice to women, no matter how they treat me - but that feels patronizing.</state>
                <state img="#-mast1.png">Well, things will get better soon...</state>
                <state img="#-conversationalalt.png">Male clothing, female clothing... It's just clothing! Wear what you want.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-8" id="24" oneShotId="30">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png">EEEEEK!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="dwight" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">America must be backwards. Why are you so sad? Fat means you are eating well, that's a fantastic thing!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-shy.png" oneShotId="312">R-Really...? Oh, I'm looking forward to this, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-cute.png" oneShotId="313">Not enough people appreciate the chest of a man. It's so comforting to rest your head upon...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png" oneShotId="314">Rules are rules, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png" oneShotId="315">The moment of truth...</state>
                <state img="#-cute.png" oneShotId="316">A man without his shirt is completely normal, but it still is so wonderful...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="310">{paska}Squeeaakkk...{!reset}&lt;br&gt;Paska, quiet! T-This is what I've truly been waiting for...!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6 8">
                <state img="#-horny.png" oneShotId="327">This will certainly be a welcome sight...</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png" oneShotId="328">Ah, my cheeks are burning!</state>
                <state img="#-cute.png" oneShotId="329">A big strong man... With his... b-big strong &lt;i&gt;chest&lt;/i&gt;...</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png" oneShotId="330">I have been looking forward to this, y-you know. I hope that does not make you nervous...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-cute.png" oneShotId="337">E-Excuse my staring, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-mast2.png" oneShotId="335">Such a beautiful part of the body...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy3.png" oneShotId="336">To finish this, then rest my hand and nap on ~name~'s chest...</state>
                <state img="#-cute.png" oneShotId="338">I am sure it is just as handsome as the rest of you, ~name~. I-I am admittedly excited.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8" id="218" oneShotId="151">
                <condition role="target" character="dunban" sayingMarker="scar_explain3" />
                <state img="#-sad.png" marker="dunban_chestreveal">Poor man... I thank you for sharing with us. Is there nobody who dotes on you? Someone so brave deserves that, at the very least.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="46" oneShotId="29">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" />
                <state img="#-scared.png" marker="bobobo_chestrevealed">I-I didn't sign up for a night of insanity! I just wanted to see some handsome guys!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="183" oneShotId="125">
                <condition role="target" character="yuno_uno" />
                <state img="#-horny.png">You are just too cute, Yuno... There is no need to be shy, I really enjoy this.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="225">
                <condition role="target" character="steve" />
                <state img="#-horny.png">A man who understands! Chest hair is truly appealing, isn't it? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="dwight" />
                <state img="#-smug.png">Oh, Dwight... There is nothing wrong with chubbiness! Not only is it natural, but it is attractive! Stand proud, you stallion!!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6 8" id="114">
                <condition filter="chubby" role="target" />
                <state img="#-shy.png">Larger men make better lovers. T-That is what I've always believed...</state>
                <state img="#-cute.png">Ukraine can get so cold. If we snuggled up together, we'd both be warm in no time!</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">So very soft... &lt;br&gt;(&lt;i&gt;I want to rest my head on him... Maybe he wouldn't object?&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6 8" id="116">
                <condition filter="muscular" role="target" />
                <state img="#-cute.png" oneShotId="249">Mm... Well, diet is important to keeping such a physique. Won't you let me cook for you sometime?</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png" oneShotId="250">Ah... An arrow has hit right at my heart! Oh, ~name~... You have my attention.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-shy.png" oneShotId="343">There's a reason summer is my favorite season.</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png" oneShotId="344">Did you know? {small}I think you're really handsome...{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" oneShotId="345">W-Would you ever want to go swimming with me, ~name~!? T-There's no need to worry, we can be shirtless at the lake!</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" oneShotId="346">N-No chest hair...?</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png" oneShotId="347">My favorite part of a man. What a beautiful body you have, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6 8">
                <state img="#-horny.png" oneShotId="353">I'd give anything just to run my hands up and down that chest of yours...</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png" oneShotId="354">A-Ah... You look so wonderful. How sweet of you to share such a sight with all of us, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-cute.png" oneShotId="355">O-Oh goodness... My face is heating up again!</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png" oneShotId="356">Y-You're stunning, ~name~... N-Not that this is anything special, or something!</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png" oneShotId="922">I am sorry, ~name~... It's hard to look away, and back into your eyes.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-mast1.png" oneShotId="361">Resting my head on that wide chest... It feels like heaven.</state>
                <state img="#-heavy3.png" oneShotId="362">Playing with his chest hair, kissing against his skin...</state>
                <state img="#-mast2.png" oneShotId="363">Things are so scary, but I can always count on men to stay handsome...</state>
                <state img="#-mast2.png" oneShotId="364">W-When he spends all day chopping wood in the sun, shirtless and sweaty... I can't handle a sight like that!</state>
                <state img="#-heavy1.png" oneShotId="953">I can show you just how sensitive your chest can be, ~name~. I can do so much, just for you.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-8" oneShotId="152">
                <condition role="target" character="dunban" />
                <state img="#-shy.png" marker="dunban_ms7">Every part of you is beautiful... {small}But I did wonder what you looked like under your briefs.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-shocked.png" oneShotId="369">Ah, i-it's really going to happen?</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png" oneShotId="370">W-Well, I'm supposed to look, aren't I?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="371">I-I've always been a curious guy! Surely you understand, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="372">(&lt;i&gt;Gregor... I need to thank you for those poker tips! Winning has so many benefits!&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-frustrated.png" oneShotId="373">I hope you are not expecting some type of food comparison. Bananas, eggplant, cucumbers... N-None of that, okay?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6 8">
                <state img="#-shy.png" oneShotId="381">W-Well, it's not my fault if I stare.</state>
                <state img="#-cute.png" oneShotId="382">It's simply natural to look, isn't it?</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png" oneShotId="379">W-Well thank you so much, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png" oneShotId="380">H-How kind of you, ~name~... I hope you do not mind if I glance.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="389">A-Are you trying to impress me, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-mast2.png" oneShotId="388">Ah, i-it's okay for me to look, right? That's the point, isn't it?</state>
                <state img="#-cute.png" oneShotId="387">I'm already doing this for you, ~name~. The sight will be appreciated...</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png" oneShotId="390">Y-You are quite the helpful man, ~name~. I can show my thanks to you later on...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png" oneShotId="992">I've been waiting for this as soon as I saw you, ~name~... Maybe that's gross, b-but I just can't help myself.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_small_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-awkward.png" oneShotId="397">Huh... Not really my type of guy, then...</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" oneShotId="398">Maybe ~name~'s just... cold?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="399">Be proud of your body, ~name~. Being small has its own perks!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="400">A bit on the small size, hm? Nothing wrong with that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6 8">
                <state img="#-awkward.png" oneShotId="405">O-Oh, it's a bit small, isn't it...? Well, you aren't alone, at least.</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png" oneShotId="406">I-If it means anything, I still think you're cute, ~name~. Though... you aren't really my type.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png" oneShotId="407">Ah, well... You aren't alone, ~name~. D-Does that make you feel any better...?</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" oneShotId="408">It is certainly smaller than average... Erm... At least you aren't alone? Uh, does that help?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-awkward.png" oneShotId="413">Oh... Huh.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" oneShotId="414">That's... a little disappointing.</state>
                <state img="#-mast1.png" oneShotId="415">All that matters is how you use it, right? </state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png" oneShotId="416">I-I'm sure someone out there would prefer that size... Uh... {small}Y-Yeah, I'm sorry...{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-frustrated.png" oneShotId="395">{paska}Chitter chitter...{!reset}&lt;br&gt;Don't. You. Dare. </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_medium_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-cute.png" oneShotId="421">O-Oh! Wow, ~name~... Um, s-sorry, I'm a bit flustered...!</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png" oneShotId="422">T-Thank you, ~name~. For, uh, showing us... and stuff.</state>
                <state img="custom:standinghere" oneShotId="423">I, uh... It looks, tasty-- Gah! Not tasty! Why did I say that!?</state>
                <state img="#-cute.png" oneShotId="424">H-Have you ever been with a man, ~name~? Um, I'm just curious, is all...</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png" oneShotId="1011">Please, stand proud. I want to see you, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-shy.png" oneShotId="435">Ah, well aren't you helpful, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-mast2.png" oneShotId="436">Y-Yes, just the type of thing I wanted to see... Y-You're so handsome, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-heavy3.png" oneShotId="437">Oh, you're sweet as pound cake... What a handsome thing you are, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-mast2.png" oneShotId="438">Even then, compared to me and my small figure... &lt;i&gt;Ah...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-mast2.png" oneShotId="916">Of course I am talented with my mouth, I am a chef after all. Oh, and it seems I am already on the floor beneath you...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6 8">
                <state img="#-shy.png" oneShotId="429">Heheh, excuse me if I'm blushing...</state>
                <state img="#-cute.png" oneShotId="430">Oh, it's just too much!</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png" oneShotId="431">(&lt;i&gt;~Name~'s just too cute... But does he have any interest in men...?&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-cute.png" oneShotId="663">Ah, m-may I have a glass of water? My face is burning up!</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png" oneShotId="1026">(&lt;i&gt;God, ~name~ is too handsome. I just want to eat him up!&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_large_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="huge_penis" role="target" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png" oneShotId="1069">{uk}Боже, помилуй!{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-scared.png" oneShotId="1070">N-Nope! That is too much. S-Sorry, ~name~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6" oneShotId="67">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="peptalk" />
                <state img="#-analtoly.png" oneShotId="451">Ah, I-I think there's something behind me... Allow me to just... turn around for a second!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-horny.png" oneShotId="443">This type of hunger... It is different from the usual.</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png" oneShotId="444">A-Ah... Showing me such a sight... ~Name~, don't embarrass me like this!</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png" oneShotId="445">Mm... Yes, that's exactly what I've come here to see.</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png" oneShotId="446">I-I know that I'm small, and you're so big... But, uh... things will work out if you just give it a try. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6 8">
                <state img="#-shy.png" oneShotId="453">With something like that, g-girls will instantly be interested! Or... would you want the boys to run to you too...?</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png" oneShotId="454">{uk}Господи, візьми мене зараз!{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png" oneShotId="455">Oh, w-wow! I hope I did not bite off more than I can swallow...</state>
                <state img="#-cute.png" oneShotId="456">M-My heart is about to leap from my chest! ~Name~... Goodness!</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png" oneShotId="596">W-Well look at you, ~name~! Aren't you a manly man? Yes, stand proud!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-horny.png" oneShotId="461">This is a hunger only &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; can satisfy, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-heavy1.png" oneShotId="462">Well, y-you've gotten my attention. What now?</state>
                <state img="#-heavy3.png" oneShotId="463">Mm... Just the &lt;i&gt;thought&lt;/i&gt; of playing with such a thing...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy3.png" oneShotId="464">You won't have to worry about me, ~name~. I can take it.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png" oneShotId="465">Aren't you proud, ~name~? Mm... I can only imagine how amazing that would feel.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-6" id="159" oneShotId="119">
                <condition role="target" character="sly_cooper" saidMarker="AnatolyPants2Reply" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="sly_s1a" />
                <state img="#-cute.png" marker="sly_as1a">You have stolen more than just the show with such a move, Sly. I-- Um... Y-Yes, {small}the view is quite nice.{!reset} </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6 8" oneShotId="153">
                <condition role="target" character="dunban" />
                <state img="#-bashful.png" marker="dunban_crotch">Oh, it's even better than I had imagined. Or-- uh! Not that I was... just thinking about-- Oh, I'll shut up now!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7" oneShotId="154">
                <condition role="target" character="dunban" />
                <state img="#-horny.png" marker="dunban_crotchmast">The things running through my head right now... Oh, Dunban!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="471">I always thought it was strange that men can go about shirtless, but women can't.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" oneShotId="472">Err-- I guess if you're certain you'd like to...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="473">(&lt;i&gt;Trees average up to 200,000 leaves. How interesting!&lt;/i&gt;)&lt;br&gt;Oh, right. ~Name~.</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png" oneShotId="474">Wait, what's going on? I think I blanked out for a moment.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6 8">
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="479">Whenever Mariah went swimming with me, she'd go in just her bra. It's not that embarrassing, is it?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="480">Did you know? There are seven types of breasts among women, all varying in shapes and sizes.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="481">Surely I've read about breasts at some point... How many fun facts do I know about them?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="482">N-No hard feelings, right, ~name~?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="487">Stay strong, ~name~! This doesn't mark your defeat!</state>
                <state img="#-mast2.png" oneShotId="489">(&lt;i&gt;I just adore when a man's chest is especially soft... Laying down against it is heavenly!&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-mast1.png" oneShotId="488">Oh, ~name~ is going to show her...? I-I see.</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png" oneShotId="490">I-It is alright, ~name~! Maybe with others distracted, you will do better with your cards...?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_small_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="495">S-Some refer to flat chests as "swimmer chests", you know. I'm not really sure if it actually helps you swim faster.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="496">Small or not, male or female... I-I think all bodies hold a unique beauty!</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="498" font-size="small">Your nipples look small, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png" oneShotId="497">If it means anything, y-you're a really cute girl, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6 8">
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="503">I've altered enough feminine clothing to realize it... Why do dresses need to rely so badly on chest size?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="504">Eating things like nuts and seeds will increase the size of your boobs! E-Er, if you were curious, I mean!</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" oneShotId="505">I-I have a question, but you can't laugh at me for asking! Does touching a girl's breasts make them bigger? It does, right?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="506">I am sure many boys prefer a smaller chest! Keep your head up high, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-bashful.png" oneShotId="511">If you drew a curve above your stomach, i-it would make a smiley face! Cool, huh?</state>
                <state img="#-mast1.png" oneShotId="512">Whenever it gets hot outside, men will walk around shirtless through town. I feel bad for the women who have to overheat...</state>
                <state img="#-conversationalalt.png" oneShotId="513">Why do girls worry so bad about the size of their chest? That size seems most convenient.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png" oneShotId="528">It is certainly flattering that you are comfortable enough to share such a thing with everyone.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_medium_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-6" id="78" oneShotId="78">
                <condition role="target" character="mari_setogaya" saidMarker="Cat_transformation" sayingMarker="Cat_transformed" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png" marker="maricat">{paska}Hissssss! Hisssssss!!{!reset}&lt;br&gt;P-Paska, calm down!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-conversationalalt.png" oneShotId="533">Breasts or butt... Men have argued about this for years!</state>
                <state img="#-scared.png" oneShotId="534">I was reading a horror novel, and a woman had three breasts in it! Isn't that terrifying?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="535">Isn't it weird that it's called "chicken breast" when it's just rib meat? This is why I'm vegetarian.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="536">Breasts are for sucking on, nothing more. Ah-- Wait! That isn't what I meant!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6 8">
                <state img="#-awkward.png" oneShotId="541">Is this what they normally look like?</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png" oneShotId="542">There are four types of nipple! Normal, small, large, and... uh... undetermined.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="543">Have you ever heard of those books by male authors, where they have a weird fixation on the female character's breasts? So weird...</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png" oneShotId="544">There will always be a classic beauty to a woman's body... Even if it isn't something that appeals to me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-shy.png" oneShotId="573">I-I'm flattered you trust everyone enough to show such a thing, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="574">Hey, ~name~. I-If you ever need a wingman, I'm open to help you out!</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png" oneShotId="575">A big reason men are so attracted to breasts is because of the intimacy nipple stimulation creates. There's been studies about it, actually!</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png" oneShotId="576">S-So... Um... This weather, it's been scary, right?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_large_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-awkward.png" oneShotId="549">Sharing a room with Karin... I-I've walked in on her changing by accident. She threw a clock at my head as soon as she noticed me.</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png" oneShotId="550">You know, breast milk is vegan! So leave cow milk for the baby cows, okay?</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png" oneShotId="551">A-Apparently, breasts that large can weigh up to a pound!</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" oneShotId="552">I'm worried for your back, ~name~...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6 8">
                <state img="#-scared.png" oneShotId="586">I heard a rumor that with enough stimulation, m-men can breastfeed.</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png" oneShotId="585">Oh, wow! W-With something like that, girls and guys will both be eager to please you!</state>
                <state img="#-conversationalalt.png" oneShotId="587">It's natural for one breast to be bigger than the other, in fact... It's usually the left one. W-Why do I know such a thing...? {small}I get bored, okay?{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" oneShotId="606">Those are... R-Really big. Um, sorry... There is really no other way to say it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-awkward.png" oneShotId="612">B-Be careful if you go out jogging. You don't want to hurt your chest if you lack proper support!</state>
                <state img="#-frustrated.png" oneShotId="613">The men in my town are all so perverted. "Your boobs look heavy, can I carry them?" That will get you a quick smack to the head!</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png" oneShotId="614">I can't see large breasts without thinking of motherhood... Maybe that's strange.</state>
                <state img="#-mast1.png" oneShotId="611">I'm not sure I understand the attraction... But I'm sure the same thing can be said about a man's chest.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-8" id="27" oneShotId="31">
                <condition role="target" character="sannytess" sayingMarker="COCK" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Y-You two... you have...?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-bashful.png" oneShotId="619">The window to a woman's soul... Her crotch.</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png" oneShotId="620">A-Are you trying to impress anyone in specific, ~name~? Do you want me to "hype you up"?</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="621">Eep! I-I'm sorry! I hope you aren't mad at me...</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="622">Er-- Things may look bleak, but they'll get better! Work hard, fight hard! You'll win in beauty, ~name~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6 8">
                <state img="#-conversational.png" oneShotId="628">Beauty is not food you can cut on a plate.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png" oneShotId="629">What a bold girl! I'm sure you're popular back home.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" oneShotId="627">I'm running out of sayings to share... I mean, there's a lot about women, but still.</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png" oneShotId="825">They say that a woman is the soul of the household, and I truly agree.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-mast1.png" oneShotId="634">He came for a husband and returned with a pumpkin. </state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="635">Everyone's looking, ~name~. B-But there's no need to be nervous! Beauty will always attract attention.</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png" oneShotId="636">I'll do my best for you, okay? I'm a trustworthy wingman!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="633">A-Are you looking for anyone in specific, ~name~? Flatter them! That is a quick way to anyone's heart.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8" id="28" oneShotId="32">
                <condition role="target" character="sannytess" />
                <state img="#-scared.png">What's happened to your testicles!? You poor girl!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="154">
                <condition role="target" character="aimee" />
                <state img="#-scared.png">...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="641">What's the point of all those "ussy" words you English speakers use? It's just a vagina.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="642">What's with all this arguing about pubic hair? It's up to the owner to decide how to groom.</state>
                <state img="#-conversationalalt.png" oneShotId="643">V-Vaginas are acidic, actually.&lt;br&gt; Uh, isn't that an interesting fact...? I don't have more to say beyond that.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="644">E-Every body is really so beautiful. It's nice to see such a thing, even if it isn't for me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-conversational.png" oneShotId="655">I can't recommend being nude in nature enough! It's so calming. It truly cleans the soul.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="656">Have you ever gone swimming in your nudity? It's not as weird as people act. Really, I've swam with Mariah when we were both naked...</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="657">Ah... S-Sorry, I'm not trying to stare.</state>
                <state img="#-conversationalalt.png" oneShotId="658">The association between women and flowers... I guess it relates to anatomy? I should study it more.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6 8">
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="649">A woman can outsmart anyone-- Even the devil.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="650">Everyone always tells me a woman's body defeats all, even war-- But that was a bit anticlimactic.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" oneShotId="651">I-If Karin knew I was here right now, looking at ~name~... She'd rip my arm off!</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" oneShotId="1145">They do vary from woman to woman, like everything does. Even then, this feels intimidating.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_lost">
            <case stage="0-6" id="39" oneShotId="28">
                <condition count="0" role="target" character="human" />
                <condition role="other" character="takatoshi" stage="0-2" sayingMarker="YakisobaPan1" />
                <test expr="~takatoshi.costume~" value="default" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png" marker="takatoshi_yakisobapan">Ehh? You could bring food? Oh, it smells heavenly... I'm so hungry!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="30" oneShotId="15">
                <condition role="target" character="ignatz" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="ignatz_ms1a">I usually don't meet men shorter than me... Are you eating enough, Ignatz?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="32" oneShotId="17">
                <condition role="target" character="jim" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-shy.png" marker="jim_ms1a">O-Oh, wow! Er, excuse me... You're, uh, really muscular, Jim.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="31" oneShotId="16">
                <condition role="target" character="ignatz" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-conversational.png" marker="ignatz_ms2a">You've talked about this Raphael boy... and he seems strikingly similar to &lt;i&gt;my&lt;/i&gt; best friend, Gregor.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="33" oneShotId="18">
                <condition role="target" character="jim" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-conversational.png" marker="jim_ms2a">You must have a fantastic diet to stay so fit! W-Would you care to share it with me...?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="34" oneShotId="19">
                <condition role="target" character="takatoshi" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="takatoshi_ms1a">Yakisoba pan...? I've never heard of such a thing.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="43" oneShotId="27">
                <condition role="target" character="stocking" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="stocking_ms1a">A fan of sweets, hm? Have you ever thought about adding fresh mint leaves on top of your parfait?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="47" oneShotId="33">
                <condition role="target" character="pit" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-bashful.png" marker="pit_ms1a">I never expected to run into someone else unable to read... Er-- I mean, I totally can! But, uh, you know...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="51" oneShotId="36">
                <condition role="target" character="mari_setogaya" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="mari_ms1a">You're not &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; a succubus, are you? Those are fictional, a-and stuff...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="52" oneShotId="37">
                <condition role="target" character="mari_setogaya" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" marker="mari_ms2a">My, you must feel unlucky, then. Getting stuck with a guy like me, when you're a succubus with hunger?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="53" oneShotId="38">
                <condition role="target" character="mari_setogaya" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-conversational.png" marker="mari_ms3a">Uh, well... Have you tried eating normal foods like cabbage or peas? Maybe you're just lacking good nutrition!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="54" oneShotId="39">
                <condition role="target" character="meia" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="meia_ms1a">A land populated by only women... I kind of wonder if the opposite exists somewhere!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="55" oneShotId="40">
                <condition role="target" character="twisted_fate" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-shy.png" marker="fate_ms1a">S-Sorry, Fate. You seem sly, though. You'll kick our butts in the next round, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="56" oneShotId="41">
                <condition role="target" character="twisted_fate" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="fate_ms2a">Oh, your outfit is so amazing! It looks so expensive, but it's really so fashionable!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="57" oneShotId="43">
                <condition role="target" character="aqua_grunt" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-conversational.png" marker="aquagrunt_ms1a">I can tell, Aqua Grunt, you care about animals, don't you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="58" oneShotId="44">
                <condition role="target" character="aqua_grunt" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="aquagrunt_ms3a">A woman who understands! All animals deserve to live naturally and freely, fish, bugs, mammals...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="59" oneShotId="45">
                <condition role="target" character="yuna" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="yuna_ms2a">Ghosts who teach girls about love? Oh, wow! You guys are just like cupid!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="61" oneShotId="47">
                <condition role="target" character="yuna" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-scared.png" marker="yuna_ms1a">Y-Yuna, be careful... Either I've gotten cabin fever, or something is lurking around you!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="62" oneShotId="48">
                <condition role="target" character="yuno_uno" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png" marker="yuno_ms1a">A-A master of cards? Are you really, Yuno? Uh...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="63" oneShotId="49">
                <condition role="target" character="yuno_uno" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-cute.png" marker="yuno_ms2a">Um... W-Would you ever teach me? I never got to play those types of games... Uno, blackjack, anything is fine!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="72" oneShotId="59">
                <condition role="target" character="mari" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="mari_ms1a">You're in college aren't you, Mari? A-Are you enjoying the studies? Are you missing your home? How about your old friends...? I'm so curious!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="73" oneShotId="60">
                <condition role="target" character="mari" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-conversational.png" marker="mari_ms2a">You sound like a wonderful big sister, Mari. I'm sure little Sunny misses you very much! I don't think I'd blame him.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="141" oneShotId="65">
                <condition role="target" character="sly_cooper" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="sly_ms1a">O-Oh my goodness, you're a raccoon? You're so cute... Who's a good boy? Who's a good boy!?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4" id="144" oneShotId="66">
                <condition role="target" character="sly_cooper" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-petting.png" marker="sly_ms2a">Paska, are you jealous of him? You two are barely similar! Why are you comparing yourself to Sly?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="138" oneShotId="76">
                <condition role="target" character="kumatora" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-bashful.png" marker="kuma_ms1a">{paska}Squeak squeak squeak!{!reset}&lt;br&gt;Oh, wow! Paska... You're not usually so social.&lt;br&gt;{paska}Squeak!{!reset}&lt;br&gt;Hm? What about Kumatora?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="134">
                <condition role="target" character="gloria" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="gloria_ms1a">C-Can you speak a little slower? I'm struggling to hear you correctly... English is difficult, but accents make it even harder.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4" id="130" oneShotId="101">
                <condition role="target" character="fluttershy" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-conversational.png" marker="fluttershy_ms1a">{paska}Nice or not, I won't let my guard down. She'll pick on him, I can feel it!{!reset} &lt;br&gt;What is bothering you, Paska? You stare quite intensely at Fluttershy...</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png" marker="fluttershy_ms1a">{paska}I don't care how nice this girl acts, I won't slack off and let her bully him!{!reset}&lt;br&gt;Paska? Do not stare so harshly at Fluttershy. You will make her nervous!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4" id="122" oneShotId="98">
                <condition role="target" character="ahri" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-scared.png" marker="ahri_ms1a">{paska}Hisssss! Hissss!!{!reset}&lt;br&gt;P-Paska? Calm down! It is simply Ahri, my girl... She will not hurt us!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="124" oneShotId="100">
                <condition role="target" character="ahri" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" marker="ahri_ms2a">You... You can see people's desires? Is there no way to stop you from doing that?  Uh, I am just curious... that is all.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="148">
                <condition role="target" character="barbara" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="barbara_ms1a">Barbara, your voice is simply amazing! Just listening to you sing reminds me of home... You have a true talent.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="184" oneShotId="123">
                <condition role="target" character="takatoshi" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="takatoshi_ms4a">Takatoshi, may I ask you something? It might sound personal...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="198" oneShotId="143">
                <condition role="target" character="nagatoro" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-frustrated.png" marker="nagatoro_ms1a">Your "hard to get" act is pathetic, Nagatoro. You really understand nothing. Have you ever been in a relationship? I doubt it!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="199" oneShotId="144">
                <condition role="target" character="nagatoro" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="nagatoro_ms2a">Can't you go one round without yapping like a dog? If all you have to share are insults, then do everyone a favor and &lt;i&gt;stop speaking&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="nagatoro_ms2a">Won't you go one round without yapping like an angry dog? If all you share are insults, then do everyone a favor and &lt;i&gt;shut up&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="211" oneShotId="147">
                <condition role="target" character="natsuki" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-bashful.png" marker="natsuki_ms1a">What a fiery little chef... But, I can tell you have no interest in spicy dishes, huh?</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png" marker="natsuki_ms1a">Aren't you a fiery chef? Though, I can tell... You have no interest in spicy dishes, hm?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="214">
                <condition role="target" character="trifle" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-conversational.png" oneShotId="1112" marker="trifle_ms1a">A pastry chef? That is impressive! Baking and pastries take a lot of talent!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="215">
                <condition role="target" character="trifle" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="1117" marker="trifle_ms2a">You certainly have a unique look, Trifle. Or... I didn't mean that in a mean way, sorry...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5" id="219" oneShotId="158">
                <condition role="target" character="dunban" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="dunban_ms1a">Oh, wow! Your style is fantastic, Dunban. Well groomed facial hair, long hair, wonderful clothing... You're truly stylish!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5" id="220">
                <condition role="target" character="dunban" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-bashful.png" marker="dunban_ms6a">Ah... Hahaha... I-Is it getting hotter in here?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="221" oneShotId="160">
                <condition role="target" character="dunban" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-shy.png" marker="dunban_ms3a">Your boots are quite sturdy, hm? They'd be perfect for a day in the woods. {small}I-If you... would ever... w-want to join me?{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6" id="222" oneShotId="163">
                <condition role="target" character="dunban" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" marker="dunban_ms6b">(&lt;i&gt;Look away from the beautiful man, Anatoly! Otherwise you'll be hard as a rock in front of everyone!&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png" marker="dunban_ms6b">(&lt;i&gt;Resist his charms, Anatoly! Look away before you're hard in front of everyone!&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="224" oneShotId="162">
                <condition role="target" character="dunban" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-bashful.png" marker="dunban_ms4a">Um... If it's okay to ask you, Dunban. Are you... uh... {small}single?{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" oneShotId="167">
                <condition role="target" character="eichi" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-sad.png" marker="eichi_ms2a">Poor boy! Were you sick a lot? That's terrible... When I was young, I was sick too. How are you feeling now? Can I do anything for you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" oneShotId="166">
                <condition role="target" character="eichi" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-conversationalalt.png" marker="eichi_ms1a">There are plenty of herbs and natural remedies I can gather for you. I know how expensive medicine can be.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="237" oneShotId="175">
                <condition role="target" character="okino" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-bashful.png" marker="okino_ms4a">Hm... You and I have quite a bit in common. Maybe we can meet over tea? I'll bake you something too! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="239" oneShotId="177">
                <condition role="target" character="dwight" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-conversational.png" marker="dwight_ms1">An American, hm? I've always wondered what it's like there! Is it "hella sauce"?</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png" marker="dwight_ms1">You are from America, yes? I've aways wonder what it's like there! Is it truly "the shits"?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6 8" id="250">
                <condition role="target" character="aloy" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-conversational.png" marker="aloy_ms1a">You hunt, yes? So you are a woman who knows her way around the forest?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4" id="251" oneShotId="180">
                <condition role="target" character="aloy" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-petting.png" marker="aloy_ms1b">Ah... Paska, you do not need to be scared of Aloy... Yes, yes. I know she is a hunter...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6 8" id="252">
                <condition role="target" character="aloy" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="aloy_ms2a">Your clothing... Did you make it yourself? It is so unique, and the stitching looks to be done by hand.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="212">
                <condition role="target" character="gay_spaghetti_chef" />
                <state img="#-frustrated.png" oneShotId="1105">Are you kidding me? &lt;i&gt;Gay spaghetti chef&lt;/i&gt;?</state>
                <state img="#-frustrated.png" oneShotId="1104">What's so funny about being gay and making spaghetti? Nobody is laughing when I do it!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="1134">Well, I guess &lt;i&gt;two&lt;/i&gt; gay chefs are here tonight...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="113" oneShotId="96">
                <condition filter="straight" gender="male" role="target" />
                <condition count="2" gender="male" />
                <state img="#-sad.png">A table with just one man... And he is straight! Can I not catch a break?</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">H-Hold me, Paska... It appears I will not find my man tonight. I really am unlucky!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="209">
                <condition filter="chef" role="target" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="1083">Come on, chef ~name~. You lost fair and square!</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png" oneShotId="1084">Oh, oh! I'm so excited to be with another chef! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" id="210">
                <condition filter="chef" role="target" />
                <state img="#-petting.png" oneShotId="1085">Hm? What's that, Paska? Ah, you can tell ~name~ is a chef, can you?</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png" oneShotId="1089">Excuse Paska... She always assumes anyone who cooks is willing to make her a special dish. Isn't that rude?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="108">
                <condition gender="female" status="lost_all" role="target" />
                <condition count="0" status="not_alive" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Your luck is tough, ~name~... You worked and fought, but the ending is bitter!</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">I had rooted for you, ~name~... It is a shame to see you lose.</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">Forward with grace and happiness... You will enjoy yourself. N-No worrying, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="109">
                <condition gender="male" status="lost_all" role="target" />
                <condition count="0" status="not_alive" />
                <state img="#-smug.png">B-Be a good boy, ~name~... The ending is bitter, but we will enjoy it.</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">A cute boy like you, losing first...? The world is so very cruel. </state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">Luck flies through the air... It missed you, and now you lost first! Understand?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="13">
                <condition role="target" consecutiveLosses="3" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Ehh? Come on, ~name~... What is distracting you?</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I knew it! Bad luck won't stop with just one loss... It keeps going, and going!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="98" totalRounds="0">
                <state img="#-conversationalalt.png">&lt;i&gt;Tsk tsk tsk...&lt;/i&gt; Luck is tough, ~name~. Do better in the next round, hm?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Do not feel too bad, ~name~. The first round means nothing, honest!</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">It is nothing too big, ~name~. Just work hard, and make up for the first loss.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Do not be deterred! From now on, Paska and I will root for you! &lt;br&gt; {paska}Squeak squeak!{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="48" priority="0">
                <condition filter="shy" role="target" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="213">Um... It'll all be okay, ~name~. Please, you don't need to worry so much!</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" oneShotId="214">W-Would you want me to look away? I don't want to make you uncomfortable.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="118" priority="0">
                <condition filter="skinny" role="target" />
                <state img="#-conversationalalt.png" oneShotId="308">You poor thing... Why are you so skinny? Are you eating okay?</state>
                <state img="#-conversationalalt.png" oneShotId="309">Such a skinny ~target.ifMale(boy|girl)~... Are you eating okay? I can bring you some borscht, if need be!</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png" oneShotId="1060">Oh... I wish I had the food to share. You are so skinny, ~name~. I'm worried!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_stripping">
            <case stage="0-8" oneShotId="174">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="nagatoro_ms2a" />
                <condition role="target" character="nagatoro" stage="1" saidMarker="anatoly0" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png" marker="nagatoro_s2a">Eep! T-That really was mean, wasn't it? Oh, I-I don't know why I said that...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="fate_ms2a" />
                <condition role="target" character="twisted_fate" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-shy.png">You don't have to do that for me! I don't think I'd look very good in that style, anyways. Maybe it's only suited for &lt;i&gt;your&lt;/i&gt; rugged handsomeness, hm?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="142" oneShotId="89">
                <condition role="target" character="sly_cooper" stage="0" saidMarker="AnatolyPants1Reply" />
                <state img="#-shy.png" marker="sly_s1a">Oh, wow... Aren't you bold? Sly as a fox, handsome as a raccoon.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="143" oneShotId="90">
                <condition role="target" character="sly_cooper" stage="1" saidMarker="AnatolyGloves1Reply" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="sly_s2a">Hear him, Paska? He just wants to be friends. You'd be the coolest squirrel around with a raccoon for a companion. &lt;br&gt;{paska}Chitter...{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="80" oneShotId="70">
                <condition role="target" character="mari" stage="0" saidMarker="Anatoly_College1A=1" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="mari_s1a">A girl who's close to her hometown... There's nothing more admirable. You must work to impress everyone back home, right? They're rooting for you!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="81" oneShotId="69">
                <condition role="target" character="mari" stage="0" saidMarker="Anatoly_College1B=1" />
                <state img="#-sad.png" marker="mari_s1b">Being away from your friends like that... I can't imagine it. And you seem so close! I'm sure they miss your music.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="82" oneShotId="68">
                <condition role="target" character="mari" stage="1" saidMarker="Anatoly_Sunny1=1" />
                <state img="#-sad.png" marker="mari_s2a">Poor boy... I can relate, I suppose. But, well, Gregor is &lt;i&gt;still&lt;/i&gt; by my side. Has he been surviving without you, Mari? Send him mail often! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="84" oneShotId="88">
                <condition role="target" character="mari_setogaya" stage="2" saidMarker="Anatoly_LackOfNutrition_reply" />
                <state img="#-sad.png" marker="mari_s3a">Poor girl! Living off of blood, sweat, and semen? It's all so... salty and metallic. Well, at least it's vegetarian...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="85" oneShotId="87">
                <condition role="target" character="mari_setogaya" stage="1" saidMarker="Anatoly_notUnlucky" />
                <state img="#-bashful.png" marker="mari_s2a">Ah, t-that's a relief! Sorry, it was bugging my mind... I wouldn't expect a hungry succubus to be so kind and understanding!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="86" oneShotId="86">
                <condition role="target" character="mari_setogaya" stage="0" saidMarker="Anatoly_realSuccubus" />
                <state img="#-scared.png" marker="mari_s1a">With pointy ears like that, I was expecting something like an elf! Besides, what kind of vampire succubus goes to school in the morning?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="136">
                <condition role="target" character="jim" stage="0" saidMarker="Anatoly_resp0a" />
                <state img="#-cute.png" marker="jim_s1a">Heheh, yeah... J-Just, sorry if I stare. Uh, you know? Yeah... Y-Yeah... {small}Heheheh...{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="135" oneShotId="83">
                <condition role="target" character="jim" stage="1" saidMarker="Anatoly_resp1a" />
                <state img="#-cute.png" marker="jim_s2a">A scrapper! How cool... I can't help but be in awe, it's like I'm speaking with a celebrity! B-But, um, for your consideration... {small}S-Sometimes vegan athletes perform better.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="227" oneShotId="161">
                <condition role="target" character="dunban" stage="3" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="dunban_ms4a" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" marker="dunban_s4a">Oh, I'm so sorry! That was much too forward wasn't it? Oh, I always screw these things up...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" oneShotId="172">
                <condition role="target" character="eichi" stage="1" saidMarker="anatoly_plants1" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="eichi_s2a">Ah, it's not a big deal... Sometimes you need to get creative. Or, I guess not as often {small}uh, if you have the money to spend...{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" oneShotId="173">
                <condition role="target" character="eichi" stage="0" saidMarker="anatoly_sick1" />
                <state img="#-cute.png" marker="eichi_s1a">Hmm? R-Really? Well I'm glad to hear that. Someone as cute as you deserves to feel fresh as spring dasies.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4" id="123" oneShotId="99">
                <condition role="target" character="ahri" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-frustrated.png" marker="ahri_s1a">Allow me to apologize for Paska, Ahri. She has no excuse to be so rude!&lt;br&gt;{paska}...{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7" id="180" oneShotId="126">
                <condition role="target" character="takatoshi" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-heavy1.png" marker="takatoshi_fantasyboxers">(&lt;i&gt;Maybe if I asked nicely, Takatoshi would let me remove his briefs for him... I could even use my teeth.&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="90" oneShotId="79">
                <condition role="target" character="aqua_grunt" saidMarker="Anatoly_ms1a" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="aquagrunt_s1a">Well, now you're contradicting yourself... Would a lover of animals really play favorites? D-Do you even like bugs?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_stripped">
            <case stage="0-8" id="236" oneShotId="176">
                <condition role="target" character="okino" stage="1" sayingMarker="okino_reveal" />
                <state img="#-conversationalalt.png">To be honest, I already could tell.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7" id="181" oneShotId="124">
                <condition role="target" character="takatoshi" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-heavy3.png" marker="takatoshi_noshirtfantasy">&lt;i&gt;So&lt;/i&gt; much better than my imagination... Just look at your beautiful muscles!</state>
                <state img="#-heavy1.png" marker="takatoshi_noshirtfantasy">Ah, goodness, Takatoshi... Are you sweating? {small}What I would give to lick your abs clean...{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="29" oneShotId="14">
                <condition status="exposed" role="target" />
                <condition count="1" status="exposed" />
                <test expr="~target.biggestlead~" cmp="&gt;=" value="3" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png">What's happened, ~name~? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="246">
                <test expr="~clothing.generic~" value="underwear" />
                <test expr="~target.wearing(underwear)~" cmp="!=" value="~blank~" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Why on earth are you wearing multiple pairs of underwear? Do you think someone will kick your groin?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8" id="111">
                <condition role="target" character="chihiro" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">That was what all this fuss was for? My my, Chihiro... Guy or girl, you are pleasant to be around. Please, smile!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8" id="205" oneShotId="146">
                <condition role="target" character="nagatoro" />
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">{small}{uk}Тупа сука. Мені набридло, що чоловіки впадають на такі безглузді вчинки.{!reset}</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-shy.png">Er, you can just... P-Pretend we aren't here. Um, sorry, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">T-This is about ~name~, so don't stare at me!</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">There's nothing sweeter than victory...!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">T-Thank you for those tips, Gregor... I really do adore the reward of winning!</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">I hope you do not mind my hungry eyes, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6 8">
                <state img="#-shy.png">Er-- Uh, heheheh... I-I can't even think of what to say.</state>
                <state img="#-cute.png">Ah, ~name~. Y-You'll rile me up again!</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">M-My eyes move on their own, you see... If you really wished, I could remove my glasses.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I-I'll observe, but it's in the name of research, okay!?</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">I cannot control how my body will respond, o-okay?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-cute.png">T-The two of us... Oh, wow...</state>
                <state img="#-mast2.png">Ah, d-don't mind me, ~name~...</state>
                <state img="#-cute.png">Well, it's just natural for my eyes to wander to you, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Won't you join me, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-mast2.png">Please, ~name~... Do not hold back.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-4" id="230" oneShotId="155">
                <condition role="target" character="dunban" />
                <state img="#-bashful.png" marker="dunban_startmasta">O-Oh... I won't look at you, I swear.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6 8" id="231" oneShotId="156">
                <condition role="target" character="dunban" />
                <state img="#-shy.png" marker="dunban_startmastb">I've um... Been looking forward to this. I hope you don't mind if I... {small}look?{!reset} My eyes are just so drawn to you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7" id="232" oneShotId="157">
                <condition role="target" character="dunban" />
                <state img="#-mast2.png" marker="dunban_startmastc">Ah, I-I have to pace myself... I'm just so excited with you nearby...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-cute.png">Well, don't let us get in the way, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">I-I'm getting hungry again... Though, I suppose it's a different type of hunger.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Mm... I-I never doubted myself for a second! A-And I'm totally confident in, uh, watching ~name~ now!</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">(&lt;i&gt;He won't think less of me for staring, will he? But looking away is probably offensive... I don't know!&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6 8">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">C-Come on, ~name~. You're teasing me!</state>
                <state img="#-cute.png">Ah, d-don't look at me like that!</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I'm overdoing it, a-aren't I? ~Name~... you're just... </state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">I have been good for you... Now let me enjoy this treat, okay?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-heavy3.png">O-Oh, yes... I'm thankful for this, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-mast2.png">It's really quite nice, ~name~... Indulge for a second!</state>
                <state img="#-cute.png">T-The beginning is always a favorite of mine, you know...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">I-If you're nervous, allow me to take your mind off of it, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-heavy2.png">Aren't you sweet, ~name~. Shall I reward you and spread my legs? Hah...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_masturbating">
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-heavy3.png">Oh, ~name~... Those noises you're making...! I'd give so much to feel you pant against my ear...</state>
                <state img="#-mast2.png">We're separated now... But I'm an open guy, y-you know? </state>
                <state img="#-mast2.png">(&lt;i&gt;Laying on my back as ~name~ grinds against me... He won't put it in, no matter how much I beg...&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-heavy3.png">A-Am I a good boy? P-Please, I hope I am...!</state>
                <state img="#-heavy2.png">(&lt;i&gt;I wish to touch ~name~... But I shouldn't. M-Maybe he'd punish me for doing so...?&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-mast2.png">(&lt;i&gt;It's wrong to think about ~name~ like I am... We've only just met! But that makes it even more exciting...!&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-mast2.png">Mutually masturbating is nice... But it's even better when you're kissing.</state>
                <state img="#-heavy3.png">If only I could join you... Wouldn't that be nice, ~name~? </state>
                <state img="#-heavy3.png">If you w-were nervous, I would not mind riding you... Oh, you could sit there as I take it over and over, ~name~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-shy.png">Y-Yes, you're... Um. You're doing well!</state>
                <state img="#-cute.png">You sound like you're enjoying yourself. T-That's all that matters, right?</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Ah, d-don't gaze at me!</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">M-My cheeks are burning up, heheh...</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">I... I won't admit if I've seen something like this before. But either way... It's certainly a nice sight.</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">I hope you're enjoying yourself...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Y-Yes, ~name~. Just like that.</state>
                <state img="#-cute.png">So handsome... You're just too handsome, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">Oh, wow... When you make noises like that, it's hard to look away.</state>
                <state img="#-cute.png">Ah... I feel like I'm melting. &lt;br&gt;(&lt;i&gt;God, he's a stranger... But I want him so much.&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6 8">
                <state img="#-shy.png">W-Would you want me to do anything for you, ~name~? </state>
                <state img="#-cute.png">I'm always happy to help out. Um, i-if you're interested, I mean.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">P-Please let me know if I overstep, okay? I'm... Not very good at talking to people.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Gah! Those noises... They're too much for me! Oh, should I just cover my ears?</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">My heartbeat... It's so loud, I wonder if you can hear me.</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">I-I know I'm not the best to look at, but if you glance... I-I won't shy away.</state>
                <state img="#-cute.png">I'm a puddle at your feet, ~name~...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">I cannot stop all these hungry thoughts... </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_heavy_masturbating">
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-shy.png" oneShotId="302">Aren't you passionate? What a good boy!</state>
                <state img="#-heavy2.png" oneShotId="303">Harder, faster... Yes, ~name~...!</state>
                <state img="#-mast2.png" oneShotId="304">Mm... Heheheh! Y-Yes, ~name~. </state>
                <state img="#-heavy3.png" oneShotId="971">I am a man with experience, ~name~. P-Please, I know I could make you feel good...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy1.png" oneShotId="972">You know exactly what to do to keep me craving for more, ~name~. W-Won't you let me indulge, if just for a bit? </state>
                <state img="#-heavy2.png" oneShotId="982">Allow me to satisfy your desire... For you to satisfy mine... P-Please, ~name~. I need something inside me.</state>
                <state img="#-heavy3.png" oneShotId="983">Oh, ~name~! T-That face you're making... Please, I can't... &lt;i&gt;Ohh...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-shy.png" oneShotId="298">You're almost there, ~name~. Just a little longer!</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png" oneShotId="299">Don't you look beautiful? Just a little longer.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png" oneShotId="991">Come on, ~name~. L-Let me see you cum...</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">(&lt;i&gt;T-They're all going to notice. I'm so hard, just watching ~name~. God, I'm pathetic...&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">All good, ~name~...?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">J-Just so you know, cum is vegan. So... Do with that what you will!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">W-What an exciting sight! Heheheh, you did so well, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Gah! Oh, that... It scared me!</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">If it had happened to hit me, I would have no issues doing some extra laundry. J-Just so you can remember for next time!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6 8">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Ah-- Oh goodness, I-I need a second!</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Ah-- Now where were you aiming that thing!?</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">All good, ~name~...?</state>
                <state img="#-cute.png">W-What a show! I want an encore...</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">I-It's not too much of a pain to clean off my glasses. I have a cloth on hand, s-so you know...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-shocked.png">O-Oh, ~name~! Wow...!</state>
                <state img="#-heavy3.png">I'm already on the floor beneath you... Practice your aim to be better next time, okay?</state>
                <state img="#-cute.png">Well, I'll be there soon, won't I?</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Have you ever tasted such a thing...? You should satisfy your curiosity.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0-6" oneShotId="145">
                <condition role="target" character="nagatoro" />
                <state img="#-frustrated.png" marker="nagatoro_mustforfeit">Hmph!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Y-You worked hard, but it seems luck was against you... Sorry, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Oh, b-be careful! If you're unlucky, it won't stop at just a poker game. Maybe you'll run into a wall later today!</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">If the devil is powerless, send him a woman!</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">If you want me to turn away, I-I promise I will. It's your choice, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6 8">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">It's a strange ending to our friendly competition.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">E-Enjoy yourself, ~name~. That's the point, right? No need to hold back.</state>
                <state img="#-conversationalalt.png">There's all these misconceptions about women and their habits... But in the end, why does it matter? It's none of our business.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">The body is really the most important thing to study, you know!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Ah... Uh, I'm really sorry.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">L-Let's have fun, okay? You don't need to shy away, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Heheheh, it's kinda funny isn't it? What a weird way to make friends...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I'm a bit curious... I'm just eager to learn, that's all!</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Uh, you won't tell anyone about this... will you?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Er-- Of course I've read all about things like this, but, uh... It's still quite new to me.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">It's a bit strange that we'll just continue on like nothing's happening, but oh well...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6 8">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">E-Everyone does this, it's natural! {small}Oh, I guess that would include Mariah and Karin... That's weird to think about.{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-cute.png">Ah, s-so that's how a woman begins...?</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Y-You don't need to hesitate, I promise!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Ah, how bizarre...</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">Er... I hope this won't make you think negatively about me, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I-It feels nice to relax like this. Hopefully you'll enjoy yourself, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">So that's how it's done...?</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Gah! That looks like it'd hurt!</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">(&lt;i&gt;Was this why Karin took so long in the bathroom the other day...? Eek! I shouldn't think about that!&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">It's done so differently... I guess that's a given, but still.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I've gone and seen those books at the market that are made for women. All these weird stories about meeting shirtless lumberjacks...</state>
                <state img="#-conversationalalt.png">See! Keeping your nails short and clean is helpful for many things, but it &lt;i&gt;is&lt;/i&gt; important for the kitchen too.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I doubt ~name~ can even hear me... At that point, you are off in your own world.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6 8">
                <state img="#-nervous.png">You're okay, right? Er-- I've got to stop bombarding you with these questions!</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">It's hard to look away.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I'll just leave you be, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I feel dirty...</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">It's only natural.</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">Nudity in nature is rumored to heal one's soul. It is stated to be cleansing, and very comfortable.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" font-size="small">Geez... That looks like it would hurt.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">There is a song stuck in my head... I can just focus on that instead, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-conversationalalt.png">I just hope you're comfortable, ~name~. </state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">Er-- Just... Well, I hope you're having fun!</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">I just hope you've enjoyed yourself.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">W-What a bizarre way to make friends... I am not weird for this, am I?</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">D-Do not look at me right now!</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">~Name~ looks a bit overwhelmed... A-And I'm sure my commentary is not helping!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Uh... Be sure to wash your hands, and stuff...</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">O-Oh! I didn't realize it was so... explosive?</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Eek!</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">&lt;i&gt;{big}Achoo!!{!reset}&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br&gt;Gah! W-Wait, what did I miss?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6 8">
                <state img="#-shocked.png">W-Woah! I didn't realize it looked like that...!</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I've still got so much to learn, huh?</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">What's the English saying? "Another one eats dust"? Well, ~name~ is out.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">A-All done, ~name~...?</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Oh! It was... It was hard to look away...!</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">W-Well, I hope you can relax in the afterglow...</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Woman down!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate_first">
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-nervous.png">T-The first one? Really...? You're going to make me even more nervous...</state>
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">H-How did I mess up this bad? Those stupid cards... {small}It's not my fault nobody taught me!{!reset}</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate">
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Gah! D-Don't look at me like that! I know, okay? Just give me a second!</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Eep! O-Oh, just give me a second, okay? I'm nervous!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="start_masturbating">
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">Yes, I'm fine... Just need to give some deep breaths.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">Ah, y-you're staring! Come on, I'm trying to calm myself...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="masturbating">
            <case stage="7" id="175">
                <condition role="other" character="takatoshi" stage="6-7" />
                <state img="#-heavy2.png" oneShotId="868" marker="takatoshi_fantasyCOCK">Augh... G-God, Takatoshi. Y-You are so big, and so hard too...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7" id="176">
                <condition role="other" character="twisted_fate" />
                <state img="#-heavy3.png" oneShotId="886" marker="twistedfate_fantasy">With a build like that, Fate could lift me so easily... M-Maybe even {small}while he fucks me...{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-heavy2.png" oneShotId="887" marker="twistedfate_fantasy">Mmm... His facial hair feel like heaven scratching against my thighs...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7" id="177">
                <condition role="other" character="yuno_uno" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png" oneShotId="870" marker="yuno_fantasy">(&lt;i&gt;Yuno is so funny with all of his American slang... I wonder what it is he would say as I rode him over and--&lt;/i&gt;) &lt;br&gt;Gah! T-Too far! </state>
                <state img="#-heavy3.png" oneShotId="871" marker="yuno_fantasy">How do you American boys make love? Please, Yuno, teach me...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7" id="182">
                <condition role="other" character="takatoshi" />
                <state img="#-horny.png" oneShotId="877" marker="takatoshi_fantasy">For such a strong guy, y-you are still so cute, Takatoshi. Have you not noticed my glances at you...?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7" id="195" oneShotId="140">
                <condition role="self" timeInStage="0" saidMarker="fantasyenable" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" marker="fantasystart">(&lt;i&gt;Nobody here can really appeal to me... Maybe I can just daydream instead? Yes, that should work...&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png" marker="fantasystart">(&lt;i&gt;I'm not... very interested in the people around me. Maybe I can rely on my imagination instead?&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7" id="196" priority="5">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="fantasystart" />
                <state img="#-mast1.png" oneShotId="1027">(&lt;i&gt;When life was carefree, I could sneak outside and simply find a guy at a bar to spend the night with. I felt so dirty, but it was all so exciting.&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-heavy3.png" oneShotId="1028">(&lt;i&gt;Gregor... Ever since we were young, I just...&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-cute.png" oneShotId="1029">(&lt;i&gt;Why can't you notice me when I want you to?&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-heavy2.png" oneShotId="1030">(&lt;i&gt;You are much too dense. Do I have to grab at your shirt and pull your lips to mine to finally show you how I feel?&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-heavy3.png" oneShotId="1031">(&lt;i&gt;Those other men... We aren't even together, but I had still felt so guilty. I really can't think of anyone else but you...&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-mast2.png" oneShotId="1032">(&lt;i&gt;When we walk outside together, why do you let those women ogle your muscles? Gregor, I just get so jealous of them...&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png" oneShotId="1033">(&lt;i&gt;I've known you so long. It makes sense I'd feel this way eventually, doesn't it?&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-frustrated.png" oneShotId="1034">(&lt;i&gt;Be aware of your good lucks, damn you! You're so handsome, it's unfair!&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png" oneShotId="1035">(&lt;i&gt;He could get anyone he wants, so why should I ever expect him to fall for a loser like me?&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-heavy2.png" oneShotId="1036">(&lt;i&gt;You can't just walk around shirtless after you finish chopping wood... I-I can't handle that.&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">How long has it been...? It's hard to get privacy in that shared cabin.</state>
                <state img="#-mast1.png">There's n-no need for me to hide myself... People want to see, don't they?</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Uh, what is it that you want me to say? I'm a bit busy, you see...</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">D-Did you know? Just over 60% of homosexual men have anal sex on a regular basis.</state>
                <state img="#-mast2.png">Did you know that...? Uh... {small}Ah...{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">What? A-Are you expecting me to say something embarrassing?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I wonder if we have any bread left at home.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Mm... The taste of pound cake...</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">What's with that look, ~player~? Don't expect me to say some weird fantasy aloud!</state>
                <state img="#-mast2.png">A big strong man... Who allows me to hand-feed him my latest recipes.</state>
                <state img="#-mast2.png">(&lt;i&gt;If I was too shy... he could grab my thighs and open my legs... Then I'd be unable to hide away from his overwhelming strength.&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-mast1.png">I-I did my best... But it just wasn't enough. There's no use in getting mad over it now...</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">Finally, I can just relax for a bit...</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">That cabin can be so suffocating... Just sharing a room is tough. I've no time to do anything like this.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Y-You're really watching me, hm...?</state>
                <state img="#-mast1.png">Ah... I-I had heard it's bad to hold back, but I'm not fully sure...</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">I just want to have some time to myself...</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Mm... Maybe I should have brought that magazine with me...? N-No, it's too embarrassing...</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">W-What's with that look? I can fantasize, can't I!?</state>
                <state img="#-heavy2.png">Hah... Oh, I feel so tingly.</state>
                <state img="#-mast2.png">There is no use in continuing to be shy... R-Really, now everyone knows how filthy my mind is.</state>
                <state img="#-mast2.png">(&lt;i&gt;Would Gregor be jealous in knowing I was here? Knowing what I'm doing in front of everyone?&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">(&lt;i&gt;Would anyone notice if I added a finger...? No, that's much too embarrassing...&lt;/i&gt;) </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7" id="9" priority="0">
                <condition gender="male" character="human" />
                <condition count="0" filter="straight" character="human" />
                <state img="#-cute.png">Some find aprons to be sexy... What if I were to wear nothing but that...? Would it make you happy, ~player~?</state>
                <state img="#-mast2.png">W-What a hungry gaze you have, ~player~...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">D-Do you like when I spread my legs like this, ~player~?</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">A-Aren't you sweet, ~player~? Inviting me here...</state>
                <state img="#-mast2.png">Y-Yes... It feels nice to be watched by someone so handsome...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">I am a man with experience, ~player~... I am sure I would be able to please you, heheh.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="heavy_masturbating">
            <case stage="7" id="197">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="fantasystart" />
                <state img="#-heavy2.png" oneShotId="1051" font-size="small">Harder, faster... Y-Yes, just like that...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy3.png" oneShotId="1050" font-size="small">Come on, I'm o-ordering you to be rougher with me...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy1.png" oneShotId="1049">(&lt;i&gt;Please, won't you kiss me while you fuck me?&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-heavy3.png" oneShotId="1048">(&lt;i&gt;I do not care if the others hear us, I just need you.&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-heavy2.png" oneShotId="1047" font-size="small">Mmph... Don't pull out, do it inside...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-heavy2.png">Ah... I've begun to drool...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy2.png">I-It's... Ah... It's hard to commentate right now...!</state>
                <state img="#-heavy1.png">A b-big guy, and a little guy... like me...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy1.png">&lt;i&gt;I-In my mouth...?&lt;/i&gt; Oh, I've always loved that taste...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy3.png">You don't have to be gentle with me... I promise I can handle it...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy3.png">Mm... The things I'd let you do to me...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy1.png">Hah... M-My glasses are fogging...!</state>
                <state img="#-heavy2.png">Mmm... M-My hips are moving on their own...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy2.png">I-It's normal to blush when he speaks to me like that...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy3.png">A-Ah... I'm close, I'm close...!</state>
                <state img="#-heavy3.png">T-The counter in the kitchen... So perfect to be bent over...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy3.png">&lt;i&gt;Ohh...&lt;/i&gt; Yes, I do not care anymore! {small}D-Do it inside...{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-heavy2.png">That look he had in his eyes... I know what he wanted, and I wish I could have given it to him...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7" id="8" priority="0">
                <condition count="0" filter="straight" character="human" />
                <condition gender="male" character="human" />
                <state img="#-heavy3.png" oneShotId="9">I'm pretty small, aren't I? T-The perfect size for you to throw me around, ~player~...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy1.png" oneShotId="11">Y-You're &lt;i&gt;starving&lt;/i&gt;, aren't you? What can I do to help, ~player~?</state>
                <state img="#-heavy3.png" oneShotId="229" marker="cursing">It has been so long since I've been properly &lt;i&gt;f-fucked...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-heavy2.png">O-Oh! I want... I want you, ~player~! Mm... please...!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7" id="12">
                <state img="#-heavy3.png" oneShotId="70">{uk}Грегор... Ви'такі великі...!{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-heavy2.png" oneShotId="71">{uk}Він відчуває себе так добре...{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-heavy1.png" oneShotId="72">{uk}Якби ж... Я хочу, щоб ти був всередині мене...{!reset}</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finishing_masturbating">
            <case stage="7" id="11">
                <state img="#-finishing.png">{uk}О, так! Чорт забирай!{!reset}</state>
                <state img="#-finishing.png">A-Ah! Yes...!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-finished.png">Ah... S-Sorry... I just... Wow.</state>
                <state img="#-finished.png">O-Oh... I'm sorry... Whew, l-let me catch my breath for a second...</state>
                <state img="#-finished.png">M-My mind... is fuzzy. English is... How do I say what I need to...? {uk}вау це було чудово...{!reset}</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="after_masturbating">
            <case stage="8" oneShotId="13">
                <condition filter="uses_camera" role="other" />
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Don't you &lt;i&gt;dare&lt;/i&gt; take a photo of me! What kind of person brings a camera to this game without asking!?</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">You... Don't you even try taking a photograph of me! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="18" oneShotId="9">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="marriage1" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="marriage2">Spending all day handling the cleaning and cooking while my husband is out chopping wood...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="19" oneShotId="10">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="marriage2" />
                <state img="#-shy.png" marker="marriage3">I could kiss him when he was returned inside, and we could relax and eat together. I-I am 25 now, it's fitting to think about marriage, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="20" oneShotId="12">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="marriage3" />
                <state img="#-sad.png">Ah, but it's silly to dream about such a thing, R-Really, I should be more realistic.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" oneShotId="56">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="butt" />
                <state img="#-sad.png">Yes, if you were thinking of it earlier... I know I have a small butt. But it's something that's out of my control!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" oneShotId="97">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="cursing" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png">W-When I was touching myself... I swore! I am so sorry, I did not even think about that! Oh, I really have messed things up...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="15" oneShotId="6">
                <state img="#-reading.png" marker="illiterate">What a great book. It's so... i-interesting. Lots of, uh, great words...</state>
                <state img="#-reading.png" marker="illiterate">W-Wow! What an unexpected twist! I love books, a-and I sure love to read.</state>
                <state img="#-reading.png" marker="illiterate">Hmmm... What fantastic writing. I'm s-so thankful to be able to read...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">I don't want to talk about it!</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Hey, is anyone else sweating? Oh, that's kind of a gross question, actually... Never mind!</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">Have you ever made homemade jam? It's to die for! And so simple, too!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Last time I did that, my glasses fell off. Nothing ruined my mood like going blind.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">T-That was really embarrassing, honestly... But it felt nice!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Being smart isn't all glitter and glam... I was bullied really bad. M-My mama said it's because they were jealous, though!</state>
                <state img="#-conversationalalt.png">I've always been the white crow in my family. My papa was barely shocked when I came out to him.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="180">Why do they call it oven when you of in the cold food of out hot eat the food? The use of an oven is to of in the cold food only to of out the hot.</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">I-I'll still appreciate Gregor. He spent all that time to teach me about poker, isn't that sweet?</state>
                <state img="#-finished.png">Ah, my heart refuses to calm down...!</state>
                <state img="#-conversational.png">Your diet will have an effect on the taste of your cum, you know! </state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Broccoli and cauliflower are certainly delicious, but ugh! They really make semen taste disgusting!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Hmm... I'll need to budget my time better now. I can't get lazy when it comes to foraging.</state>
                <state img="#-conversationalalt.png">It would really do you good to recognize what food you can and can't eat in the wild. I've seen people try and eat poison ivy before.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Ah! I've spotted a little ant! How adorable...</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Sexy, or cute? Which is it that a man truly prefers?</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">U-Usually I'll use my fingers too... But, um, that's kind of humiliating to be watched doing.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I am no stranger to such a thing. K-Karin once, um, discovered a magazine I had... She ripped it up and screamed at me over it!</state>
                <state img="#-scared.png">What kind of things did I say aloud? I'm so embarrassed!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="17" oneShotId="11">
                <state img="#-cute.png" marker="marriage1">It's a bit silly, but I've been daydreaming a lot recently. A-About being a good husband, actually.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_victory">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-smug.png">I expected nothing less!</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Those poker tips Gregor told me... Were they magic!?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-4">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">S-So what now...? I have my own problems now, even if I won...</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">W-Well, what now? I've got my own issue to resolve!</state>
                <state img="#-knowledge.png">Well... I really should run off to somewhere private... Erm, to read, of course!</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Um... Are you all alright? I-I hope you had fun!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Aha! I knew I'd win in the end!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">My knowledge will always prevail!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Eek! That was close... Too close! I'm so embarrassed...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_defeat">
            <case stage="8">
                <condition filter="chef" role="target" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">My compliments to the chef.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-conversationalalt.png">Congratulations and all, but I've got to go find Paska! I don't want her to continue stirring up trouble.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Urgh... Now I'm all tired... Oh, but I've got to go get Paska. I'm sure she's starting all types of trouble.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" hidden="1">
                <state img="#-reading.png" collectible="book">Unlocks collectible.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="global">
            <case stage="0-8" id="37">
                <condition role="other" character="ignatz" stage="3-4" saidMarker="glasseslocated" sayingMarker="glassesfound" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">Phew! I think I was more worried than you were! I know what it feels like to lose your glasses...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" hidden="1">
                <condition count="4-" gender="female" />
                <state marker="fantasyenable">Enables Anatoly's fantasizing forfeit.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" hidden="1">
                <condition count="3-" gender="female" />
                <condition filter="straight" gender="male" />
                <state marker="fantasyenable">Enables Anatoly's fantasizing forfeit.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

    </behaviour>
</opponent>
