<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<metadata>
    <owner>nayru</owner>
    <noteworthy>
        <case name="Possession" min="4" max="4">
            <description>Must-target; Nayru is visibly lifted into the air by a dark spirit</description>
            <trigger tag="must_strip_normal" notSaidMarker="null_possess" priority="40">
                <state img="losthand.png">I've felt this... no! I-I can...!</state>
                <state img="losthand.png">Ngh! B-be gentle!</state>
                <state img="losthand.png">Wh-what? V-Veran?! No!</state>
            </trigger>
        </case>
    </noteworthy>
    <hidden />
    <responses />
    <notes />
    <nextId>0</nextId>
    <markers>
        <marker scope="Public" name="" />
        <marker scope="Public" name="9s_goron">Veran has attempted to goad 9S by likening him to a "stunted goron".</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="9s_upgrade">Veran comments on being an upgrade to Nayru</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="armorlose">Nayru asks an armored opponent to discard the armor. No need for everyone to be asked this individually.</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="assessment">Nayru assesses the table and makes a comment about the sort gathered. She often has no reason to do so repeatedly.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="badhand">Nayru inquires about just what a bad hand is. Thus, she doesn't need to repeat herself.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="confused">The player just lost with a great hand. Done to set up "surprise", and prevent spam.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="despair">"Suffer defeat! Know despair!"</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="dire">Nayru senses an evil like nothing she's felt before.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="drinks_response">At Sei's inquiry, Nayru typically refuses a drink. Late enough into the game, however, she may go along with it...</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="fakeout">Joey's fakeout just caught her. Used as a failsafe, since Joey's code strips 2 bras.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="femaleplayer">Marker to remember player gender choice</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="filter_bluehair">Nayru comments on someone besides her having blue hair.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="firsthand">The first hand of the game. Used as a failsafe.</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="flor_fled">Florina has fled during her first strip round.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="forgiveness">Veran offers forgiveness during a minor round; this keeps her from getting too angry.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="fut_chihaya" />
        <marker scope="Public" name="fut_fortune" />
        <marker scope="Public" name="fut_fortune2" />
        <marker scope="Public" name="harped">Nayru had commented on her harp. Used to prevent spam.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="harpedtoo">Nayru recalled that Link once used the harp to save her, her childhood friend Ralph, and the whole land of Labrynna; from Veran, incidentally</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="jura_future_fail">Nayru hasn't managed to glimpse Jura's future at all.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="jura_future_fair">Nayru's given a hopeful report to Jura</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="jura_future_good">Nayru's given an optimistic report to Jura</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="jura_future_poor">Nayru's refused to give a poor report to Jura</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="jura_strumming">Nayru comments on playing a lullaby, but decides against doing so immediately</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="justfinished">Her first line upon finishing; used to ensure the "standing up" pose occurs only once.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="justnow">Nayru expresses disappointment at how poorly she's doing. (removed minor, male; rounds 5-7</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="kyu_intro">Nayru mistakes Kyu for a Great Fairy during the hand-quality phase</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="lessdire">Nayru ignores dire evil, because she's been wrong before.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="mahiru_cam_call">"Invisible" marker (doesn't change dialogue) to set up the Mahiru snapshot chain. Marker 0 of snapshot chain. Given on the must strip stage.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="mahiru_intro">Intro for Mahiru</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="mahiru_keep">Marker 3 of snapshot chain. Given as Nayru asks Mahiru to keep the picture safe. Hand quality phase.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="mahiru_keepsake">Marker 4 of snapshot chain. Given as Nayru comments on her unfamiliarity with keepsakes in general. Hand quality phase.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="mahiru_keese">Marker 2 of snapshot chain. Given as Nayru says "Keese!"; stripped stage.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="mahiru_snap">Marker 1 of snapshot chain. Given as Nayru asks for a picture; stripping stage.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="maleplayer">Marker to remember player gender choice</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="marin_akuma">Keeps Nayru from asking about the Akuma twice.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="marin_behest">Veran claims to be present at Nayru's behest; given during a hand-quality phase</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="marin_darkness">Veran claims that Nayru is needed to bring about eternal darkness; given during a hand-quality phase</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="marin_finished">Nayru gives a line after having finished; used to prevent repetition</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="marin_intro">Nayru introduces herself to Marinette</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="marin_magic">Veran asks what sort of magic Marinette has to prevent her; given during a hand-quality phase</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="marin_pantydrop">Veran gives a line about what this reminds Marinette of, specifically; during her panty strip, of course</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="marin_weight">Nayru replies that a weight has been lifted; used to prevent spam</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="meia_din" />
        <marker scope="Public" name="meia_doubt">Nayru tells Meia that her doubt is understandable; hand quality during Meia's second layer</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="meia_elegy" />
        <marker scope="Public" name="meia_farore" />
        <marker scope="Public" name="meia_friend1">Nayru suggests that Jura has a surprise for Meia, but refuses to elaborate</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="meia_funny1">Nayru sees something funny, probably at Meia's expense</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="meia_intro">Nayru introduces herself to Meia</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="meia_scary1">Nayru sees something that scares her, though it could be just daily life for Meia</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="meia_strip1">Marker used to ensure that Nayru finishes the Meia chain if she starts it</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="meia_veranhand">Veran's first real line to Meia</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="meiaprep">Prepares for the Meia song chain. Can be given different string values depending on the song chosen (storms, din, farore, nayru)</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="mj_intro">Nayru introduces herself to Meia and Jura both (and immediately takes Jura's side)</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="MP_earlydong">If Nayru sees the human player strip their important lower before something else, she remembers</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="MP_finaldong">Set when Nayru sees a male player preparing to remove their final lower item. If not set when male player crotch is revealed, earlydong is set instead</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="mulan_intro">Nayru introduces herself to Ping</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="n_forfeit">Backup marker, set after must-masturbate, for when Nayru dismisses Veran for her forfeit. May ease targeting to an extent.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="nat_adorb">Failsafe to ensure that Nayru doesn't call Natsuki "adorable" more than once; here in case I make more lines using this marker in the future</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="nat_adorb_setup">Setup to make target responses simpler; next line Nayru gives will call Natsuki "adorable"</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="nat_adorb_setup_p">Alternative setup for nat_adorb which only activates while Veran is present</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="nat_intro">Nayru introduces herself to Natsuki</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="navi_hero">Nayru asks whether Navi knows the spirit of the hero (that is, any incarnation of Link)</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="navi_intro">Nayru introduces herself to Navi</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="nines">Nayru introduces herself to 9s</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="null_possess">Nayru is beginning to feel more comfortable, as well as more skilled at the game. If not met, Veran will take over out of shame for Nayru's pitiful display thus far.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="palutena_intro">Intro for Palutena, sans Pit</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="pit_intro">Intro for Pit, sans Palutena</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="pit_pal" />
        <marker scope="Public" name="poss_draw">The first instance of drawing/swapping after the possession. Veran's first real line.</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="poss_hand">The first hand while possessed. Prevents spam.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="possess">prevents most null-possess markers down the road; set upon possession to allow for future case work</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="pretense">Nayru makes a comment during an early must_masturbate phase about how oracles are above such debasement.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="rain" />
        <marker scope="Public" name="rainstart" />
        <marker scope="Public" name="rainstop" />
        <marker scope="Public" name="revysight">Prepares for the Revy futuresight chain. Stores different values based on Nayru's slightly different reactions.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="shima_intro">Nayru introduces herself to Shimakaze</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="shima_panty">(Invisible) Marker set to telegraph a line for Shimakaze</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="song_epona">Nayru alludes to Epona's Song, claiming it causes animals of all sorts to come running (female removing accessory, 0-2)</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="song_eponatoo">If an MLP girl is present, Nayru will follow-up her Epona's Song line</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="song_fairy">Reference to the Great Fairy Fountain theme, a non-magical song (female removing accessory, 3-4)</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="song_fairytoo">If a fairy is present, Nayru will ask if the song sounds familiar</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="song_hero">During her first four strips, Nayru has a small chance of referencing one of the heroes of legend</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="song_hero_full" />
        <marker scope="Public" name="song_hero_half" />
        <marker scope="Public" name="song_hero_link" />
        <marker scope="Public" name="song_hero_stop" />
        <marker scope="Public" name="song_herotoo">If Nayru references a hero of legend, she'll claim that the song is changing even as she sings it</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="song_zelda">Nayru references Zelda's Lullabye</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="song_zeldatoo">If Zelda is present, she follows up to ask if the song sounds familiar</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="start_forfeit">Round 1 of the forfeit; currently only used by Veran</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="storyend">It's not a very good story. (Veran, 5-7, female losing minor)</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="storytime">Veran tells a story!</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="surprise">Upon seeing the player's excellent hand, Nayru realizes that the player actually lost with it.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="urav_intro">Introduction to Uravity</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="urav_strip1">Sets off the dialogue chain to Uravity during Nayru's first strip</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="v_forfeit">(Invisible) Marker set to enable Veran's forfeit. Determined by level of nudity at the table.</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="Veran1">Nayru begins to explain why she lets Veran control her; they've come to an agreement.</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="Veran2">Veran's limited in some way by something at the Inventory, so Nayru's always in some amount of control.</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="Veran3">But Veran has certain useful skills; like poker.</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="Veran4">Technically, if Nayru is possessed, it's not Veran who's playing the game, so...</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="Veran5">Maybe Veran has too much fun, but in the end, Nayru always knew what the game entailed.</marker>
    </markers>
</metadata>
