<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<markers>
    <marker scope="Public" name="9s_goron">Veran has attempted to goad 9S by likening him to a "stunted goron".</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="armorlose">Nayru asks an armored opponent to discard the armor. No need for everyone to be asked this individually.</marker>
    <marker scope="Private" name="assessment">Nayru assesses the table and makes a comment about the sort gathered. She often has no reason to do so repeatedly.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="badhand">Nayru inquires about just what a bad hand is. Thus, she doesn't need to repeat herself.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="confused">The player just lost with a great hand. Done to set up "surprise", and prevent spam.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="dire">Nayru senses an evil like nothing she's felt before.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="drinks_response">At Sei's inquiry, Nayru typically refuses a drink. Late enough into the game, however, she may go along with it...</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="fakeout">Joey's fakeout just caught her. Used as a failsafe, since Joey's code strips 2 bras.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="femaleplayer">Because the player has stripped once, Nayru now knows their gender for the remainder of the game.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="filter-bluehair">Nayru comments on someone besides her having blue hair.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="firsthand">The first hand of the game. Used as a failsafe.</marker>
    <marker scope="Private" name="flor_fled">Florina has fled during her first strip round.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="harped">Nayru had commented on her harp. Used to prevent spam.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="justfinished">Her first line upon finishing; used to ensure the "standing up" pose occurs only once.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="justnow">Nayru expresses disappointment at how poorly she's doing. (removed minor, male; rounds 5-7</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="kyu_intro">Nayru mistakes Kyu for a Great Fairy during the hand-quality phase</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="lessdire">Nayru ignores dire evil, because she's been wrong before.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="maleplayer">Because the player has stripped once, Nayru now permanently remembers the player's gender.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="nines">Nayru introduces herself to 9s</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="null-possess">Nayru is beginning to feel more comfortable, as well as more skilled at the game. If not met, Veran will take over out of shame for Nayru's pitiful display thus far.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="poss_draw">The first instance of drawing/swapping after the possession. Veran's first real line.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="poss_hand">The first hand while possessed. Prevents spam.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="pretense">Nayru makes a comment during an early must_masturbate phase about how oracles are above such debasement.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="storyend">It's not a very good story. (Veran, 5-7, female losing minor)</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="storytime">Veran tells a story!</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="surprise">Upon seeing the player's excellent hand, Nayru realizes that the player actually lost with it.</marker>
    <marker scope="Private" name="Veran1">Nayru begins to explain why she lets Veran control her; they've come to an agreement.</marker>
    <marker scope="Private" name="Veran2">Veran's limited in some way by something at the Inventory, so Nayru's always in some amount of control.</marker>
    <marker scope="Private" name="Veran3">But Veran has certain useful skills; like poker.</marker>
    <marker scope="Private" name="Veran4">Technically, if Nayru is possessed, it's not Veran who's playing the game, so...</marker>
    <marker scope="Private" name="Veran5">Maybe Veran has too much fun, but in the end, Nayru always knew what the game entailed.</marker>
</markers>
