<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>

<!--This file was machine generated using the Character Editor v6.7.4 at 6:51:49 PM on February 04, 2022. Do not edit this file directly unless you know what you're doing.-->
<opponent>
    <version>v6.7.4</version>
    <first>Reimu</first>
    <last>Hakurei</last>
    <label>Reimu</label>
    <gender>female</gender>
    <size>small</size>
    <timer>20</timer>
    <intelligence>bad</intelligence>

    <intelligence stage="3">average</intelligence>

    <intelligence stage="5">good</intelligence>

    <nicknames>
        <nickname for="critical_darling">Critical</nickname>
        <nickname for="remilia">Remi</nickname>
    </nicknames>


    <wardrobe>
        <clothing name="bloomers" generic="underwear" position="lower" type="important" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="sarashi" generic="bra" position="upper" type="important" />
        <clothing name="sleeves" position="arms" type="minor" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="skirt" generic="skirt" position="lower" type="major" />
        <clothing name="shirt" generic="shirt" position="upper" type="major" />
        <clothing name="socks" generic="socks" position="feet" type="minor" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="shoes" generic="shoes" position="feet" type="extra" plural="true" />
    </wardrobe>


    <behaviour>
        <trigger id="selected">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="mari" sayingMarker="OppSelected_Reimu" />
                <state img="#-select.png" marker="MariSelected_resp">Thank you Mari! The red stands for… something I think, but it’s an important part of the shrine maiden uniform! And I don’t mind if it catches &lt;i&gt;someone’s&lt;/i&gt; attention.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-select.png">You know, it was a pain to find this place. Oh, I’m Reimu Hakurei, the Shrine Maiden of Paradise. I’m sure at least some of you will be worth getting to know!</state>
                <state img="#-select.png">I’m Hakurei Reimu, Gensokyo’s freewheeling shrine maiden. I need a break after all the hard work I’m always put through, so the rest of you had better be nice to me!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_selected">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="jura" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png" marker="JuraSelected">&lt;i&gt;Urk!&lt;/i&gt; Hold on ~player~, I dunno if we want to invite this lady to the table. Look at her legs, her hair. Her boobs! She blows me out of the water, pick someone I compare favorably to.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="miko" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" marker="MikoSelected">&lt;i&gt;Urk!&lt;/i&gt; Why is— ~Player~, find someone else, quick, before &lt;i&gt;she&lt;/i&gt; opens her mouth!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" oneShotId="91">
                <condition role="target" character="remilia" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png" marker="RemiliaOpponentSelected">Oh, where did &lt;i&gt;she&lt;/i&gt; come from? Say, ~player~, do you want to try moving to another table? This one is bad now.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_start">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="miko" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="MikoSelected" />
                <state img="#-blunt.png" marker="MikoGameStart">The game’s starting? Wait, I— &lt;i&gt;Ugh&lt;/i&gt;, why are &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; here, Miko? I’m trying to meet someone that &lt;i&gt;isn’t&lt;/i&gt; already married, you philanderer.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="miko" saidMarker="ReimuSelected" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png" marker="MikoGameStart_resp">I’m Reimu Hakurei, the Shrine Maaaa&lt;i&gt;aaaah!&lt;/i&gt; No, don’t start now—&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;Ugh&lt;/i&gt;, hello Miko. Go away. I’m trying to meet people who are both &lt;i&gt;single&lt;/i&gt; and &lt;i&gt;not you&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~day.number~" value="3" />
                <test expr="~month.number~" value="2" />
                <state img="#-cheerful.png">I can’t stay too long, I’ll need to get back to the shrine. It’s Setsubun, and I can charge people to throw beans at Suika.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="remilia" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" marker="RemiliaGameStart">&lt;i&gt;Sigh…&lt;/i&gt; Hey Sakuya, if you’re going to stay here, could you at least fetch me some tea or something?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="fischl" />
                <state img="#-select.png">I’m a Shinto shrine maiden for the Hakurei Shrine, Fischl. My job is to communicate with the gods and exterminate youkai. It’s a lot of work, you know.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~background~" value="hot spring" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">Taking off all my clothes at an onsen kind of removes the allure of the game. Like, I do that often enough anyway.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="3" priority="5">
                <condition count="3" status="alive" />
                <state img="#-smug.png">Easy mode? Disgusting.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-select.png">Don’t worry, I know what I’m getting into. I have to protect my reputation in Gensokyo, but there’s no need to care what any of &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; think— unless you’re particularly eligible ~human.ifMale(bachelors|bachelorettes)~!</state>
                <state img="#-select.png">It’s just one thing after another when you’re Gensokyo’s number one incident resolver! I’m here to relax and hopefully meet someone special, so try not to get on my nerves.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="swap_cards">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <test expr="~cards~" value="5" />
                <state img="#-angry.png">All of them! I don’t care, anything’s better than this!</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">This hand is awful!</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Ughhhh. To hell with the whole lot.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <test expr="~cards~" value="0" />
                <state img="#-cheerful.png">Nope, nothing for me!</state>
                <state img="#-cheerful.png">I’m good! I’m gonna win for sure!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-cheerful.png">I know ~cards.text~ ~cards.ifplural(cards|card)~ will do the trick!</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Hmmm… ~cards.text~? Does that feel like it will work?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">~Cards.text~ will work! I’m sure of it!</state>
                <state img="#-blunt.png">Do I look like I have a clue here?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Dealer, ~cards.text~ new ~cards.ifplural(cards|card)~— for a cute girl!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">~Cards.text~ ~cards.ifplural(cards|card)~. Exactly ~cards.text~.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I think if I read it, my poker book would say to swap ~cards.text~ ~cards.ifplural(cards|card)~.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">~Cards.text~. &lt;i&gt;Please.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">Give me something better than these ~cards.text~!</state>
                <state img="#-pleasant.png">Hmm, hmm… ~cards.text~ ~cards.ifplural(cards|card)~.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">Don’t care!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">It’s the luck of the draw anyway, right? Well, give me ~cards.text~  ~cards.ifplural(cards|card)~.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Can I have ~cards.text~ ~cards.ifplural(cards|card)~?&lt;br&gt;{small}Is that a lot?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="good_hand">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-happy.png">The plum trees by the Hakurei Shrine are blooming really nice this year! I’ll have a lot of plums to make plum wine with!</state>
                <state img="#-cheerful.png" oneShotId="5" marker="SakeTalk" weight="3">Does anyone here like sake? I can’t get enough of the stuff! Ask me anything about sake!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">If I wanted to, I could communicate with the god of these cards. I wouldn’t though, I don’t need such parlor tricks to secure a win.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I wish I snuck some sake from home here. Not for &lt;i&gt;now&lt;/i&gt; of course, but for after the game.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">Do you think any of the other shrines or temples could pull off a miracle like this hand? Not on your life!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Winning is more fun than losing, even if it’s all meaningless in a game like this! Though, I’d probably be saying something different if my cards were lousy.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-smug.png">I’m pretty well feared by all the local fairies. That’s why they always come over to the shrine to play. They want to curry favor with me because I’m so terrifying.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">It makes my job easier if the youkai already know to fear me. That’s why I’m always rude when solving incidents, and sometimes don’t offer them the first cup of sake at parties.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I knew bullying Tewi the lucky rabbit wouldn’t have any negative consequences!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">When I get back, maybe I should treat the three fairies behind the shrine to some dango. They &lt;i&gt;have&lt;/i&gt; been somewhat well-behaved recently.</state>
                <state img="#-pleasant.png">Victory is what builds faith. People are wishy-washy, though, so I always have to succeed to keep them believing in me. Not that it matters in this sort of game.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">There’s no one in Heaven or Hell who can stop me! At least that I’ve fought. And I’ve fought plenty.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-cheerful.png">Playing strip poker to find a spouse seems &lt;i&gt;way&lt;/i&gt; easier than dating. Man, I’m a genius or something.</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">I didn’t think about what cards to swap that time, but it worked!</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">The universe shall provide… which is good, since I have no idea what I’m doing.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Trying to figure out this game is too much effort after all. I’m glad I didn’t bother!</state>
                <state img="#-bluffing.png">Even my mentor Kasen couldn’t lecture me with cards like these! Don’t tell her I’m here.</state>
                <state img="#-cheerful.png">I wouldn’t mind a mid-match tea break. I deserve a chance to relax!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-cheerful.png">What sort of meal would be good for our wedding dinner? I’d prefer something Japanese over Western, but I definitely want to eat meat!</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">I admit I like to get myself off as a way to de-stress after a hard day’s work. And I may just be motivated to work &lt;i&gt;even harder&lt;/i&gt; if I had someone waiting for me!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I’ll swap… wait, I already swapped. Nevermind.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I’d wonder who I should invite to my wedding when the time comes… but the usual lot will show up regardless, so who cares?</state>
                <state img="#-cheerful.png">It probably won’t happen, but in case anyone &lt;i&gt;does&lt;/i&gt; want to throw themselves at me after the game, I’ll bring you back to the shrine and cook you a warm and filling meal!</state>
                <state img="#-pleasant.png">I like having time to relax in this game. It lets me just sort of &lt;i&gt;feel&lt;/i&gt; the people here. I’m not sure how to explain it better.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" priority="0">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="SakeTalk" />
                <state img="#-cheerful.png" oneShotId="16" marker="SakeTalk">Plum wine isn’t actually the same as Western “wine” where you ferment the grapes. Rather, plums are steeped in sake. It makes a tasty drink that’s sweet and full of alcohol— just like me!</state>
                <state img="#-cheerful.png" oneShotId="17" marker="SakeTalk">Some people call &lt;i&gt;nigori&lt;/i&gt; “unfiltered sake”, but it’s actually just less filtered than standard sake. It’s a sweet drink served chilled, perfect for the summer months!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="18" marker="SakeTalk">There are plenty of Shinto gods who love alcohol! That’s why it’s a religious experience to offer sake. After all, getting drunk is a mystical experience, exceedingly close to the divine!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="181" marker="SakeTalk">Most of the oni and tengu I know like to drink sake out of wooden boxes called &lt;i&gt;masu&lt;/i&gt;. Some of them have masu &lt;i&gt;ten times&lt;/i&gt; normal size! I can still drink them all under, though.</state>
                <state img="#-cheerful.png" oneShotId="182" marker="SakeTalk">During ceremonies, like weddings, sake is drunk out of saucers called &lt;i&gt;sakazuki&lt;/i&gt;. The oni Yuugi even has a magic sakazuki that transforms any sake poured into it into the highest grade!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7" id="89" oneShotId="50" priority="0">
                <condition count="0" status="not_lost_some" />
                <state img="#-interested.png" marker="Reimu_SpouseQualities" weight="0.5">Oh! I can’t believe we’ve gotten this far in the game without me asking the important question! Obviously everyone here would want to marry me. Why would &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; make a good spouse?</state>
                <state img="#-cheerful.png" marker="Reimu_SpouseQualities" weight="0.5">We’ve been here a while, but I’m still not sure who here’d be the best to marry. So, I’ll ask it straight: what would make you a good spouse?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="okay_hand">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Hakurei Shrine should be alright while I’m gone, I left Aunn in charge. She’s my komainu. It’s like a dog, except… it’s a dog.</state>
                <state img="#-cheerful.png">Hey, you should come stop by Hakurei Shrine’s plum wine festival! Contrary to what you may hear in the newspaper, I did &lt;i&gt;not&lt;/i&gt; drink our entire stock this year.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Why are buildings all so big in the outside world? Is it because everyone’s super rich?</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">I can’t read minds like some youkai. Gimme a hint on how good your hands are.</state>
                <state img="#-dismissive.png">Poker is a Western card game, so it’s not something I’m well versed in. I’m lucky some books on it fell in from the outside world.</state>
                <state img="#-greedy.png">Do any of you think you’ve been cursed by some youkai? I can exterminate them for you… for a donation to the Hakurei Shrine, of course!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="2">My most important job is keeping the balance of power in Gensokyo. It’d be dangerous if any single youkai faction got undue influence over the land. Therefore I beat everyone up, impartially.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="712">I deal with “incidents” in Gensokyo, which are mysterious happenings extending over the land. I solve them by wandering around beating up the youkai I meet, until I find the mastermind and beat them up too.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">The gatekeeper at the Scarlet Devil Mansion no longer tries to stop me from coming in. Not sure if it’s due to fear, negligence, or the mistress’s orders.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">The Prismriver Trio sure have gotten popular recently. I listened to them when their music was unknown… and their tickets were cheap.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">The new book by my favorite mystery author is coming out soon, but I’m worried some youkai is going to start an incident before I can finish reading it. Maybe I should go around fighting everybody ahead of time.</state>
                <state img="#-blunt.png">Kappa tech is supposedly &lt;i&gt;soooo&lt;/i&gt; great… well, I wouldn’t know. You’d think those misers could at least offer me a discount, seeing as they’d never be able to peddle their wares without my shrine’s festivals.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-serious.png">By the way, this stick with tassels here? It’s called a &lt;i&gt;gohei&lt;/i&gt;. It’s used for Shinto purification ceremonies, and smacking youkai in the face.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Animals are dumb. All you need to do is give them a little bit of food and attention and take them for walks and set up a nice place for them to sleep and they just glom onto you. What’s up with that?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Do I have enough green onions at home for miso soup? It’d be bad if I couldn’t properly prepare tomorrow’s breakfast.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">I wonder if I can spin playing this game into a tale to impress the villagers… “I exterminated the evil cloth wrapped around them… um, donate to the Hakurei Shrine.”</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">Good thing no one in Gensokyo’s human village knows about this place. They already think I’m flakey, despite always trying my hardest when it matters.</state>
                <state img="#-greedy.png">I have an arrangement with Clownpiece, the fairy who lives under my shrine. As long as she doesn’t make it too hot in the summer, I won’t exterminate her.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-pleasant.png">Getting married isn’t &lt;i&gt;just&lt;/i&gt; about the lovemaking, you know. I want someone who I can chat with as we sit outside, sipping sake.</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">Playing this game, I’m starting to understand what’s accurate and what’s not in those &lt;i&gt;shunga&lt;/i&gt; erotic art books I— I &lt;i&gt;found&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-cheerful.png">Everyone else here is so good looking… but I can’t &lt;i&gt;just&lt;/i&gt; marry for looks. I want someone who can properly take care of me.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Gensokyo’s been sealed off from the outside world for a long time now… I wonder how people’s attitudes towards marriage have changed. Maybe they don’t even wait until the wedding night to “do it”!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I should make sure to stock up, there’ll be a party soon at the Hakurei Shrine. I don’t know when, or why. But we all love excuses to party.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">If I bring anyone home to be my spouse, I’m sure Yukari will be her usual nosy self. Don’t let her intimidate you though, that gap hag’s just bitter since she’s an old maid.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">I wonder if I could entice some people to play this game at our next party. Not until the fairies go to bed, of course, but I want to see how some of those more modern girls &lt;i&gt;style&lt;/i&gt; themselves.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" oneShotId="20" priority="0">
                <test expr="~background.location~" value="indoors" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" weight="0.25">Wow, the lights on the wall and ceiling sure are bright. They don’t even flicker. People in the Outside World have gotten really good at candle-making.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" priority="0">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="SakeTalk" />
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" oneShotId="12" marker="SakeTalk">Only very expensive sake is sold chilled, by the way! I’ve, uh, never had any expensive sake myself, though. But I can brew my own for you! It’ll have lots of love, and also a high alcohol content.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="13" marker="SakeTalk">In Japanese, &lt;i&gt;sake&lt;/i&gt; actually refers to any alcoholic beverage. What Westerners think of as sake is called &lt;i&gt;nihonshu&lt;/i&gt;, or “Japanese wine”.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" oneShotId="22" marker="SakeTalk">Nothing warms you up better on cold winter nights than hot sake! It also brings out the flavors, making even the cheapest sake taste wonderful!&lt;br&gt;{small}I drink a lot of the cheap stuff…</state>
                <state img="#-pleasant.png" oneShotId="23" marker="SakeTalk">While sake has existed since the birth of Japan, most of what’s brewed outside Gensokyo uses methods developed in the last 50 years. Plenty of modern bottles fall into my shrine.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" oneShotId="188" marker="SakeTalk">A lot of Westerners living in Gensokyo like drinking sake out of wine glasses, but I prefer &lt;i&gt;ochoko&lt;/i&gt;, traditional small ceramic cups.&lt;br&gt;{small}Though, if I’m drunk enough, I drink straight out of the bottle… Ehehe…</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="bad_hand">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">I think I need to exorcise these cards.</state>
                <state img="#-bluffing.png">So… who else here has won hundreds of games of poker in their life before? Ehehee…</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png" oneShotId="1" weight="0.2">This hand is due to magic, Eirin’s shady new drug, Yukari fooling around again, or a Moriya shrine con— Oops, I forgot templates like that were forbidden.</state>
                <state img="#-bluffing.png">I-it’s never too late to pray to the gods for good fortune! But be sure to pray to the god of the Hakurei Shrine— as soon as I figure out what it is.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I wonder, could I use my ability to communicate with the gods to make money somehow? Like giving blessings or telling fortunes? …Wait, that’s just being a shrine maiden.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">I hope Aunn properly guards the shrine while I’m gone. The tanuki have been putting leaves in the donation box again.</state>
                <state img="#-blunt.png">I’d order some sake from the bar, but I don’t know what sort of money they use here… and I don’t have any of any kind.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="727">I sure hope Sumireko is okay. I overheard her telling someone she had an Outside World disease called &lt;i&gt;“Ligma”&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Does anyone here have this outside world doodad, I think it’s called a “phone”? Sumireko says she can use hers to look up anything. I want to ask it how to properly play this game.</state>
                <state img="#-bluffing.png">If I wanted to, I could exterminate every youkai in Gensokyo. Any time I wanted. As soon as I had the chance. If I wanted to.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-angry.png" oneShotId="180">You must be ever-vigilant against the evil youkai! They can blend in with humanity using such tactics as “taking off their hat,” or “wearing a slightly different hat.” </state>
                <state img="#-greedy.png">I don’t know of any youkai who affect people’s cards… but if you are cursed by one, come to Hakurei shrine! We’ll exterminate any youkai.&lt;br&gt;{small}Be sure to leave a donation!</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Did you see what Aya put in her rag of a paper this week? Well, no, of course you wouldn’t. Good. It was all lies anyway.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" dialogue-layer="over">The Moriya Shrine goddess Kanako is a shrewd businesswoman, and she and the other goddess Suwako are always fussing over their shrine maiden, Sanae. I wish I had a god who fussed over me… or whose name I knew.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">I hate dealing with the pharmacy at Eientei. They make themselves &lt;i&gt;so&lt;/i&gt; hard to find, and Eirin acts so smug just because she’s a genius doctor. Also their hangover medicine is too expensive.</state>
                <state img="#-blunt.png">Celestials need to learn some manners and stop exiling idiots to Gensokyo. If you don’t want Tenshi, what makes you think &lt;i&gt;we&lt;/i&gt; do?</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">If that damn youkai punk rock duo wakes me up one more time, I’m going to give them a &lt;i&gt;real&lt;/i&gt; reason to scream when I silence them!</state>
                <state img="#-dismissive.png">I hope Hell doesn’t drag me into any more of their imbecilic schemes. That goddess of Hell Hecatia Lapislazuli may have three bodies, but she’s got zero brains.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Is there a god of poker I can commune with? I suppose I should know all the gods, but… I don’t.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="735" marker="ReimuDoggo">Say, does anyone know what a “doggo” is? Sumireko used it to describe Aunn, and when I asked her what it meant she said “a smol pupper.”</state>
                <state img="#-bluffing.png">Hardly any people come to the Hakurei Shrine, so it’s a bit shabby. But we have the best shrine maiden around!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I hope there isn’t any sudden change in weather while I’m out. I’m not sure if Aunn knows how to set the storm shutters.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">You’re lucky I’m not showing off my skills in a Spell Card duel. This game is &lt;i&gt;abouuuut&lt;/i&gt; even for everyone.</state>
                <state img="#-blunt.png">I hope no one notices I’m gone! …Who am I kidding, no one comes to Hakurei Shrine except youkai.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">&lt;i&gt;Ugh&lt;/i&gt;, I just know my mentor Kasen is going to stop by tomorrow and lecture me for hours about every little thing she thinks I’m doing wrong… I hope she brings some sweets again.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">The Buddhist temple is holding another event soon. Don’t people realize that it’s just a ploy to proselytize them? Not like the festivals for &lt;i&gt;my&lt;/i&gt; religion.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">No one here would try to card shark in a game like this, right? That would be super lame.</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">&lt;i&gt;Hmmmmm…&lt;/i&gt; I was worried, but I feel as if I won’t have any trouble doing it if I lose. This game’s been exhilarating!</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Before, I was nervous about everyone watching me play with myself. Now the thought excites me a bit… but still makes me nervous.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">…Maybe I should spruce up the shrine a little bit. No one’s going to marry me if I have a shabby shrine.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I’ve been naked in public plenty of times in my dreams, so this is kinda familiar.&lt;br&gt;{small}I sure hope that dream world youkai hasn’t been spying on those ones.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">If I can’t get a spouse from this go-around, when should I come back? I don’t want to seem desperate, but I also want to be done with the hassle of finding my soul mate.</state>
                <state img="#-dismissive.png">When it comes to finding a spouse, this beats trying to make small talk with the village boys. I swear, they’re crazier than some &lt;i&gt;youkai&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-blunt.png">I still wonder if there was maybe a better way than this to find a spouse. Hmm, but every idea I can think of is even &lt;i&gt;more&lt;/i&gt; work.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="1" oneShotId="1">
                <state img="#-greedy.png" marker="Reimu_GetRichQuick" weight="0.5">Hmmm… I feel like I haven’t had any good ideas lately, so maybe it’d be best to ask one of you. I’m always trying to think up schemes to bring in the dough— what’s one you’d fall for?</state>
                <state img="#-greedy.png" marker="Reimu_GetRichQuick" weight="0.5">Lately, I haven’t been getting the kind of draw to my shrine I need. Usually I’d come up with some get rich quick scheme, but I’m stumped! So, I’ll ask: what kind of scams would work on &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt;?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7" oneShotId="94" priority="0">
                <condition status="alive" role="other" character="human" />
                <state img="#-cheerful.png">Hey, ~player~, if you throw this hand, I’ll let you buy me snacks. Don’t you want to buy snacks for a cute girl?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-butt.png" oneShotId="174">Do we have to do it here? Is there anywhere else more comfortable?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="hand">
            <case stage="0-9" oneShotId="49" priority="500">
                <condition role="other" character="miko" stage="1" timeInStage="0-0" sayingMarker="Tojiko_Intro" />
                <state img="#-blunt.png">&lt;i&gt;Ugh…&lt;/i&gt; Did you not notice she had followed you, Miko? I worry you’ve lived so long, you’ve outlasted your own common sense.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="2" priority="151">
                <condition role="other" character="meia" sayingMarker="pilot_recruitment" />
                <state img="#-blunt.png" marker="MeiaPilotRecruit_resp">I already have to do danmaku battles at home in Gensokyo, I can’t help you out on top of that. And no way am I using some giant machine either, I prefer being a &lt;i&gt;smaller&lt;/i&gt; target, thanks.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="29" priority="142">
                <condition role="other" character="ignatz" sayingMarker="hobbiesqna" />
                <state img="#-cheerful.png" marker="IgnatzHobbies_resp">My favorite hobby is sake, Ignatz! Drinking it, brewing it, using it in religious rituals, drinking more of it! I love sake!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="24" priority="116">
                <condition role="other" character="meia" sayingMarker="men_info" />
                <state img="#-angry.png" marker="MeiaMen_resp">Meia, this may be hard for you to believe— but I have no experience with men! Not a shred! So the rest of you tell me too!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="26" priority="116">
                <condition role="other" character="jura" sayingMarker="seduction" />
                <state img="#-bluffing.png" marker="JuraSeduction_resp">O-oh… I’ve seduced s-so many men before, Jura. Bunches of ‘em! I don’t wanna talk all day, though, so let’s let the others chime in for now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="28" priority="116">
                <condition role="other" character="jura" sayingMarker="seduction" />
                <condition count="5" gender="female" />
                <state img="#-bluffing.png" marker="JuraSeductionF_resp">W-well, Jura, I’m &lt;i&gt;well&lt;/i&gt; acquainted with, um, charming ladies. Erm…&lt;br&gt;{small}The local book renter has a crush on me, so…{!reset}&lt;br&gt;Since there’s always more to learn, I want to hear the others’ tales!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="25" priority="111">
                <condition role="other" character="meia" sayingMarker="earth_sightseeing" />
                <state img="#-cheerful.png" marker="MeiaSightseeing_resp">Ooh Meia, you and your crew should come visit the Hakurei Shrine! We’ll even throw a biiiiig festival for the occasion!&lt;br&gt;…You people have Earth money, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="27" priority="111">
                <condition role="other" character="jura" sayingMarker="babies" />
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" marker="JuraBabies_resp">A kid? I-I’m not even married, Jura! And if I did get, um, get pregnant, I wouldn’t be able to safeguard Gensokyo’s balance. Or worse, drink booze!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="138" totalRounds="3-">
                <condition role="other" character="fischl" sayingMarker="fischl_fairytale" />
                <state img="#-blunt.png" marker="FischlFairytail_resp">Gensokyo is full of the sorts of things the people of the Outside World call myths, legends, and fairytales. We even have fairies themselves. I could never pick a &lt;i&gt;favorite&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="30" oneShotId="35">
                <condition role="other" character="ignatz" sayingMarker="igassassin_study" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" marker="IgnatzAssassin_resp">An assassin, Ignatz? That’s dangerous, I don’t want to become a young widow! Stick to something safer and more profitable, like painting.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="31" oneShotId="33">
                <condition role="other" character="ignatz" sayingMarker="paintingoffer" />
                <state img="#-greedy.png" marker="IgnatzPainting_resp">Really, Ignatz? A valuable painting, just for me? Of course I’ll accept! Paint me however you’d like!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="32" oneShotId="34">
                <condition role="other" character="ignatz" sayingMarker="igbullykink" />
                <state img="#-angry.png" marker="IgnatzBully_resp">Ignatz, you fool, no one gets a reputation as a plum picker unless they’ve picked a few plums! So out with it! Did you get a stiffy the last time a girl took your lunch money?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="46">
                <condition role="other" character="yuri" sayingMarker="yuri_book_recommendations" />
                <state img="#-cheerful.png" marker="YuriBook_resp">I once stayed up for three days straight reading Agatha Chris-Q’s mystery novels! She’s my favorite author! Oh, but her stories are only available in Gensokyo.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" oneShotId="58">
                <condition role="other" character="meia" sayingMarker="reimu_recruitment" />
                <state img="#-blunt.png" marker="MeiaPilotRecruit2_resp">Solving incidents in Gensokyo means diving headfirst into the bullets pelted at me by various youkai. Some others are fast enough to weave through the patterns, but my thing is being too scrawny to hit.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="94" oneShotId="56">
                <condition role="other" character="nami" saidMarker="reimu_rich" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="NamiGetRichQuick_resp">Okay, I’ve been thinking about your idea, Nami. It’s pretty sharp, except I don’t have the cash to buy even a bunch of cheap goods. And all the merchants in Gensokyo have better business sense than me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="95" oneShotId="57">
                <condition role="other" character="nami" saidMarker="reimu_spouse" />
                <state img="#-pleasant.png" marker="NamiSpouse_resp">I’ve never thought much about kids, Nami… but I got plenty of fairies to deal with. It would be nice to have someone manage the budget… well, as much as there is to manage.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="96" oneShotId="59">
                <condition role="other" character="fina" saidMarker="FinaReimuGetRichQuick" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="FinaGetRichQuick_resp">I don’t think I’d like to make myself rich through piracy, Fina. We don’t have an ocean, so the closest I could get is robbing the vampire’s mansion. That’s more my friend Marisa’s thing.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="97">
                <condition role="other" character="fina" saidMarker="FinaReimuSpouseQualities" />
                <state img="#-pleasant.png" marker="FinaSpouse_resp">You seem like you’d be a good wife, Fina. You’re caring and attentive. Too bad you already seem to have two suitors. I wouldn’t want to break something like that up.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="98" oneShotId="60">
                <condition role="other" character="nami" sayingMarker="dangerous_places" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="NamiDangerousPlace_resp">The most dangerous place I’ve been? Probably Hell. Though some of the Hells were pretty boring too.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="99" oneShotId="61">
                <condition role="other" character="nami" sayingMarker="dreams" />
                <state img="#-bluffing.png" marker="NamiDreams_resp">M-my dreams, Nami? It’s um… yeah, that’s right! It’s to exterminate all the youkai, and create a human only world!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="100">
                <condition role="other" character="nami" sayingMarker="body_positive" />
                <state img="#-cheerful.png" marker="NamiBodyPositivity_resp">I like how gorgeous I am! I’m every bit the traditional Japanese beauty. I also like how I can eat sweets and never get fat.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="101" oneShotId="62">
                <condition role="other" character="zoe" sayingMarker="ReimuIsFollowedByProblems" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" marker="ZoeFollowedByProblems_resp">Huh? How do you know me? I don’t think I’ve seen you in Gensokyo before. Not that I’m saying you’re right about me being followed by trouble!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="102">
                <condition role="other" character="fina" sayingMarker="FinaPublicMasturbationPrompt" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png" marker="FinaPublicMasturbation_resp">Are you crazy, Fina? I could &lt;i&gt;never&lt;/i&gt; do something like this in public!&lt;br&gt;{small}I’s different here because one or more of you is almost certainly going to marry me. Otherwise I’d be a weirdo.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="103" oneShotId="63">
                <condition role="other" character="fina" sayingMarker="FinaExposurePrompt" />
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" marker="FinaExposure_resp">I’ve been to hot springs with others before, Fina. But that’s different, you’re &lt;i&gt;supposed&lt;/i&gt; to be naked there.&lt;br&gt;{small}Though, I guess you’re supposed to be naked here too.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="104">
                <condition role="other" character="fina" sayingMarker="FinaMoonberryOffer" />
                <state img="#-cheerful.png" marker="FinaMoonberry_resp">I’ve never heard of Moonberries, but I wonder if I could steep them in sake for a tasty drink. I do the same with some of the plums at my shrine.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="105" oneShotId="65">
                <condition role="other" character="fina" sayingMarker="FinaDatingPrompt" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" marker="FinaDating_resp">Oh, um, Fina… what you need to do, is… actually, to be honest I thought someone would have whisked me away from the game to marry me by now. So if this isn’t working I have no clue.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="106" oneShotId="64">
                <condition role="other" character="fina" sayingMarker="FinaHomeworldsPrompt" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="FinaHomeworlds_resp" dialogue-layer="over">I’m from Gensokyo, land of illusion. It’s a place hidden from the modern world, where the mundane is repelled and mysticism can still thrive.&lt;br&gt;{small}My job’s to go around and smack sense into anyone who misbehaves.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="107">
                <condition role="other" character="fina" sayingMarker="FinaCharity==reimu" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" marker="FinaCharity_resp">&lt;i&gt;Urk!&lt;/i&gt; I know I’m always bugging others for donations, but somehow being offered charity here of all places just makes me feel pitiful.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="108" oneShotId="67">
                <condition role="other" character="jim" sayingMarker="Intergalactic_journey" />
                <state img="#-cheerful.png" marker="JimJourney_resp" dialogue-layer="over">Intergalactic…? Do you mean you’re from the Moon, Jim? I had to beg the gap youkai Yukari to take me. She was so smarmy the whole time, but I’ll show her how good an idea finding my Prince Charming at a strip bar is!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="109" oneShotId="66">
                <condition role="other" character="jim" sayingMarker="Matts_mishap" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" marker="JimMattsMishap_resp">I’ve never really won… anything from a game. But I win all my spellcard duels and resolve all the incidents, and that’s what really matters!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="110" oneShotId="68">
                <condition role="other" character="fina" sayingMarker="FinaReimuCharity" />
                <state img="#-blunt.png" marker="FinaReimuCharity_resp">Beautiful girls like me can always marry up, there’s nothing shameful about that. Besides, it’d be nice to have a spouse to take care of me… I’ll still accept your money as a donation, though.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="111" oneShotId="70">
                <condition role="other" character="critical_darling" sayingMarker="NotSuper" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="CriticalDarlingNotSuper_resp">I’ve never heard of anything called a “superhero”, Critical, but it doesn’t seem odd to me. Everyone in Gensokyo has &lt;i&gt;some&lt;/i&gt; kind of power, but I’m the only truly altruistic one.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="112" oneShotId="69">
                <condition role="other" character="critical_darling" sayingMarker="MetalMoods" />
                <state img="#-blunt.png" marker="CriticalDarlingMetalMoods_resp">Here’s a mood I feel often, Critical: I’m hungover, shut up you dumb youkai.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="113" oneShotId="71">
                <condition role="other" character="critical_darling" sayingMarker="Prompt_DevilDuel" />
                <state img="#-blunt.png" marker="CriticalDarlingDevilDuel_resp">Eh, I’ve fought the Goddess of Hell and the Goddess of Makai before. It was a pain, but I still won in the end. Though the only thing I’d like them to give me is my free time back.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="114" oneShotId="72">
                <condition role="other" character="critical_darling" sayingMarker="Prompt_WingWish" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="CriticalDarlingWingWish_resp">I don’t see what’s so good about wings, Critical. Everyone in Gensokyo can fly already, so the wings are just for show. Now the ability to gather fame and fortune… that sure would be nice to have.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" oneShotId="73">
                <condition role="other" character="myriam" sayingMarker="reimu_hand_1" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" marker="MyriamHand1_resp">If more people knew of my heroic deeds, I’m sure they’d be lining up to donate. Unfortunately, the &lt;i&gt;muckraking newspaper reporters&lt;/i&gt; only ever seem to print bad things about me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" oneShotId="74">
                <condition role="other" character="myriam" sayingMarker="reimu_hand_2" />
                <state img="#-extermination.png" marker="MyriamHand2_resp">Youkai are meant to be exterminated or sealed, Myriam. &lt;i&gt;That&lt;/i&gt; is the only justice they deserve, and &lt;i&gt;my&lt;/i&gt; duty.&lt;br&gt;{small}Please write that I said that in your paper and take a picture of me looking cool like this.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="115" oneShotId="75">
                <condition role="other" character="syrenne" saidMarker="reimu_spouse1" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" marker="SyrenneSpouse_resp">Syrenne, when you said “you’ll get what you get”… do you mean all the handsomest rich guys show up on other days? I’m new to all this, but I want the best spouse possible.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="116" oneShotId="76">
                <condition role="other" character="syrenne" saidMarker="reimu_rich1" />
                <state img="#-greedy.png" marker="SyrenneGetRichQuick_resp">Syrenne, you said you knew a good scheme to rake in dough? I’m all ears! Go ahead and take whatever cut you want, we’ll all be rich soon enough!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="117" oneShotId="78">
                <condition role="other" character="syrenne" sayingMarker="prompt_dye" />
                <state img="#-blunt.png" marker="SyrenneDye_resp">Dye that makes clothes &lt;i&gt;invisible&lt;/i&gt;? I’ve never heard of anything of the sort, but wouldn’t that defeat the purpose of clothes? Unless it makes the wearer invisible too.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="118" oneShotId="77">
                <condition role="other" character="syrenne" sayingMarker="prompt_magic" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="SyrenneMagic_resp">My pal Marisa puts a ton of time and effort into studying magic and improving herself. Thankfully, I’m naturally gifted at mysticism, which is great because I hate working hard.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="119" oneShotId="80">
                <condition role="other" character="syrenne" sayingMarker="prompt_mates" />
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" marker="SyrenneMates_resp">Imagine bringing Marisa here… taking off her clothes… touching ourselves together… &lt;i&gt;urk—&lt;/i&gt; I’m not imagining anything!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="120" oneShotId="79">
                <condition role="other" character="syrenne" sayingMarker="prompt_rich" />
                <state img="#-greedy.png" marker="SyrenneRich_resp">Oh, I’m broke all the time, Syrenne! All you have to do is come up with a get rich quick scheme, like the time I turned the shrine into Hakureiland! Wait, that was a disaster.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="121" oneShotId="81">
                <condition role="other" character="syrenne" sayingMarker="prompt_odd_jobs" />
                <state img="#-blunt.png" marker="SyrenneOddJobs_resp">Those sorts of things are usually &lt;i&gt;my jobs&lt;/i&gt; where I’m from, Syrenne… and I don’t even get paid as it is.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="122">
                <condition role="other" character="syrenne" sayingMarker="prompt_tease" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png" marker="SyrenneTease_resp">&lt;i&gt;Fancy me?&lt;/i&gt; With all the people who bug me and tease me— no! Absolutely not! Just being an arse it is!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="123" oneShotId="82">
                <condition role="other" character="syrenne" sayingMarker="prompt_bath" />
                <state img="#-cheerful.png" marker="SyrenneBath_resp">Ahhhh, a bath would be so nice after this game! I’ve been to hot springs with my friends plenty of times. Is that not common where you’re from, Syrenne?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="124" oneShotId="83">
                <condition role="other" character="syrenne" sayingMarker="prompt_story" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="SyrenneStoryYoumu_resp">I got plenty of drinking stories, Syrenne. Like the time we tied a balloon to our scaredy-cat friend Youmu and told her it was a ghost!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="SyrenneStorySanae_resp">I’ve got so many drinking stories, Syrenne. My friend Sanae is infatuated with giant robots, so one time we convinced the fairies at my shrine to dress up like one!</state>
                <state img="#-cheerful.png" marker="SyrenneStoryTenshi_resp">I don’t have an end to drinking stories, Syrenne. Once, we threw this annoying girl, Tenshi, off a waterfall! …It was Tenshi, she was fine.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png" marker="SyrenneStoryOkuu_resp">I got drinking stories for you, Syrenne. Like the time we bet the nuclear hell raven Okuu she couldn’t make a sun bright enough to turn night into day— actually, I don’t want this story to get out.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="125">
                <condition role="other" character="syrenne" sayingMarker="prompt_opener" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" marker="SyrenneOpener_resp">Opener? Like… something I say to her if I want to marry her? Wait, am I supposed to say something specific? I didn’t practice for this!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="126">
                <condition role="other" character="hu_tao" sayingMarker="hu_tao_poems" />
                <state img="#-blunt.png" marker="HuTaoPoem_resp">A poem, Hu Tao? I was hoping someone here would read me a love poem, but I’m guessing that’s not your style.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="127" oneShotId="84">
                <condition role="other" character="hatsune_miku" saidMarker="Reimu_SpouseQualities" />
                <state img="#-angry.png" marker="MikuSpouseQualities_resp">Listen Miku, who asked you about being a wife? I mean, I know I literally did, but I don’t think youkai have much interest in holy matrimony, so just can it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7" oneShotId="85">
                <condition role="other" character="stocking" sayingMarker="ReimuAuction" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="StockingAuction_resp">I have no idea what an “internet” is, but I need these bloomers to wear. If I sold them, that money would have to go to buying new bloomers, so I don’t see the point.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" oneShotId="86">
                <condition role="other" character="stocking" sayingMarker="ReimuMarisa" />
                <state img="#-angry.png" marker="StockingMarisa_resp">Incompetent…? Wait, are you talking about Marisa? She may act easygoing, but she’s one of the hardest working people I know! And she’s not my sidekick, she’s my rival… who I team up with a lot.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" oneShotId="87">
                <condition role="other" character="stocking" sayingMarker="ReimuYoukai" />
                <state img="#-serious.png" marker="StockingYoukai_resp">There’s plenty of youkai in Gensokyo, and it’s no easy feat taking them down if they get serious. Thankfully, full scale incidents are pretty infrequent.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" oneShotId="88">
                <condition role="other" character="nami" sayingMarker="reimu_hell" />
                <state img="#-blunt.png">I been plenty of places that &lt;i&gt;felt&lt;/i&gt; hellish, Nami, but the actual realms of Hell suck. Avici the Infinite Hell is boring, the Lake of Blood is gaudy, and the Hell of Blazing Fires is too hot.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" oneShotId="89">
                <condition role="other" character="nami" sayingMarker="reimu_dream" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Obviously, that’s the dream of every youkai exterminator, Nami. What else would we dream about? It’s not like &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; would know my dreams better than me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" oneShotId="90">
                <condition role="other" character="hu_tao" sayingMarker="reimu_poem" />
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Oh, wow, you wrote an actual lo— an actual poem. I thought you’d think up something rude! Um, sorry, it’s a nice poem.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="128">
                <condition role="other" character="fluttershy" sayingMarker="pets_question" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="FluttershyPets_resp">I don’t have any pets, per se… but I do have Aunn, a mystical lion-dog protector of my shrine known as a &lt;i&gt;komainu&lt;/i&gt;. She’s a cutie.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="129">
                <condition role="other" character="fluttershy" sayingMarker="flowers_in_garden" />
                <state img="#-greedy.png" marker="FluttershyFlowers_resp">I get what you mean, Fluttershy. The shrine does its best business when the cherry trees around it are blooming. Too bad we can’t have that year-round— I’d make a mint!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="130">
                <condition role="other" character="fluttershy" sayingMarker="spider_trivia" />
                <state img="#-blunt.png" marker="FluttershySpider_resp">At least I don’t live in my friend Marisa’s house. That place is full of all sorts of junk and she never cleans. If she’s not careful she’ll turn into a spider youkai herself.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="131">
                <condition role="other" character="fluttershy" sayingMarker="bird_talk" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" marker="FluttershyBird_resp">I’ve tried listening to the birds around Hakurei Shrine, but it’s all “buy my grilled eel” this and “I’ll burn the world in nuclear hellfire” that. Bunch of bird brains.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="132">
                <condition role="other" character="fluttershy" sayingMarker="reason_for_coming_question" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="FluttershyReasonForComing_resp">I’m a girl of marriageable age, Fluttershy. I’d like someone to cuddle with and buy me sake. Is there a better place to find my destined than a seedy club?&lt;br&gt;{small}Wait, it sounds bad when I say it aloud…</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="133" oneShotId="96">
                <condition role="other" character="cynthia" saidMarker="ReimuGetRich1" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" marker="CynthiaGetRich_resp">Why are you lecturing me, Cynthia? I get enough of that at home. I do have a job, by the way, it just doesn’t pay well and is a pain to do.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="134" oneShotId="97">
                <condition role="other" character="cynthia" saidMarker="ReimuSpouseQualities1" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="CynthiaSpouse_resp">I’d like having a responsible, hard working wife. The only thing, Cynthia, is you’d have to promise not to lecture me for being none of those traits.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="137" oneShotId="98">
                <condition role="other" character="heris" sayingMarker="HerisPassion" />
                <state img="#-cheerful.png" marker="HerisPassion_resp">I’m passionate about sake! Brewing it, drinking it, eating some shredded cabbage and chicken karaage then drinking more! It’s a spiritual sensation all its own!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="139">
                <condition role="other" character="lux" sayingMarker="japan_ionia" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="LuxJapanIonia_resp">Ionia? Maybe, I don’t really know how things are organized in the outside world, but according to maps I’ve seen Japan is an archipelago east of mainland Asia.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="143" oneShotId="99">
                <condition role="other" character="kora" sayingMarker="kora_gossip" />
                <state img="#-bluffing.png" marker="KoraGossip_resp">Um, yes, I heard… that Hakurei Shrine &lt;i&gt;isn’t&lt;/i&gt; visited by youkai regularly, and that the shrine maiden there is &lt;i&gt;very&lt;/i&gt; hard working and of marriageable age. Tell your friends!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" priority="0">
                <condition role="other" character="remilia" stage="1-6" />
                <state img="#-angry.png" oneShotId="192" marker="RemiliaTupai">Don’t think I’ve forgiven you for that incident you caused, Remi! Not that Scarlet Mist hogwash, I mean that time your dumb pet chupacabra drank all the good booze at Geidontei.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" oneShotId="190" marker="RemiliaFate">Remi, isn’t your self-proclaimed ability to control fate? That’s pretty romantic when you think about it. You could help people meet their destined soulmates…</state>
                <state img="#-blunt.png" oneShotId="191" marker="RemiliaHeight">Hey, Remi, why are you so short and scrawny? Do you not get enough vitamins by sucking blood? Or did you just not eat your veggies when growing up?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7" priority="0">
                <condition role="other" character="remilia" stage="1-6" />
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" oneShotId="196" marker="RemiliaHymen">Say, Remi, vampires like you can reconstruct themselves no matter how much damage they take, right? Um, so does that mean your, uh, maidenhead reforms after you do the deed?</state>
                <state img="#-cheerful.png" oneShotId="197" marker="RemiliaWalkIn">You’ve got so many people in your mansion, Remi. Tell me, have they ever walked in on you during an &lt;i&gt;“intimate moment”?&lt;/i&gt; I’m talking about masturbation.</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png" oneShotId="198" marker="RemiliaDomOrSub">Remi, when you, uh, &lt;i&gt;do it&lt;/i&gt;… do you prefer being the one in charge? Or would you rather be “served” by the other party? I could see you into either.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" priority="0">
                <condition role="other" character="remilia" stage="1-5" />
                <state img="#-greedy.png" oneShotId="203" marker="RemiliaSakuyaWine">Sakuya, if you’re running back to the mansion to get Remi more wine, can’t you grab me some sake too? I know Remi keeps some in the cellar.</state>
                <state img="#-bluffing.png" oneShotId="204" marker="RemiliaSakuyaStripping">Hey Sakuya, why aren’t you stripping with Remi? Not that I want to see you naked! It just seems against the spirit of the game, is all.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="202" marker="RemiliaSakuyaStories">Hey Sakuya, while we’re all here, you got any lewd stories of your mistress? I wanna hear about the side of her she doesn’t show when pretending to have charisma.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="miko" sayingMarker="ReimuShoes1" />
                <state img="#-bluffing.png" marker="MikoShoes1_resp">&lt;i&gt;E-explorations?&lt;/i&gt; What’s there to explore, Miko? I’m just here to find a rich spouse so I can live on easy street!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="ms.fortune" sayingMarker="Reimu_Maiden_0A" />
                <state img="#-serious.png" marker="FortuneShoes1_resp">A shrine maiden is someone who calls upon the powers of the gods and exterminates youkai. I’m a particularly &lt;i&gt;ruthless&lt;/i&gt; one at that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="ms.fortune" sayingMarker="Reimu_Lover_1A1" />
                <state img="#-angry.png" marker="FortuneSocks1A_resp">Do you think I’m some sort of idiot, Fortune? I didn’t come here to buy a nightstand, I don’t even have a place to put it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="ms.fortune" sayingMarker="Reimu_Lover_1A2" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="FortuneSocks1B_resp">Think about it, Fortune! Normally, I’d have to waste all sorts of time finding my perfect soul mate and slowly wooing them with my charms. Here, we can skip straight to the part where they get seduced.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="meia" sayingMarker="reimu0" />
                <state img="#-angry.png" marker="MeiaShoes1_resp">Youkai are the enemy of humans, Meia. It is my sacred duty to exterminate them. I don’t even invite them over to my shrine, they just show up with sake and snacks!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="meia" sayingMarker="reimu1" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="MeiaSocks1_resp">Men aren’t rare in Gensokyo, what are you… hm, now that I think about it, almost all my friends are women. Guess I never really noticed.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="jura" sayingMarker="reimu0" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="JuraShoes1_resp" dialogue-layer="over">My plan is perfect, Jura. I’m sure this place is filled with lonely souls just waiting to be charmed by my beauty, All I need to do is find one who’s good looking, has a great personality, and gets along with me perfectly.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="revy" sayingMarker="reimu0" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" marker="RevyShoes1_resp">I wasn’t planning to get anything at the bar, Revy. For one, I don’t know what sort of money they use here. For two, I probably don’t have enough of it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="nami" sayingMarker="reimu0" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="NamiShoes1_resp">Don’t worry Nami, I’ve given this plenty of thought! I’m going to make sure my future spouse lets me do whatever I want, in addition to being rich, handsome, and charming.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="fina" sayingMarker="FinaReimuStart1" />
                <state img="#-confident.png" marker="FinaShoes1_resp">Youkai are monsters, the enemy of humanity. My sacred duty is to exterminate them all. I definitely don’t get drunk with them and goof off with them!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="zoe" sayingMarker="ReimuGensokyo" />
                <state img="#-bluffing.png" marker="ZoeShoes1_resp">&lt;i&gt;Urk!&lt;/i&gt; I’m sure Marisa or Sanae can take care of anything that comes up. I’m only going to be gone for a short while anyway. It’s fine, it’s fine!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="critical_darling" sayingMarker="Reimu_Touhou1" />
                <state img="#-confident.png" marker="CriticalDarlingShoes1_resp">Touhou games… what’re you talking about? Wait, do you mean the danmaku battles we have in Gensokyo? Those aren’t games, Critical, those are serious!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="yuri" sayingMarker="reimu_extermination" />
                <state img="#-extermination.png" marker="YuriShoes1_resp">Humans and youkai are eternal enemies, Yuri. Youkai attack humans. Humans fear youkai. Humans exterminate youkai. Those are our sacred duties.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="syrenne" sayingMarker="reimu_0" />
                <state img="#-bluffing.png" marker="SyrenneShoes1_resp">What are you talking about Syrenne, I don’t want to get drunk… tonight… before the game’s over. Why, are you buying?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="hu_tao" sayingMarker="tao01" />
                <state img="#-greedy.png" marker="HuTaoShoes1_resp">&lt;i&gt;Inu-zuna&lt;/i&gt;? Well, I’m a shrine maiden at any rate. I come from Gensokyo, the land of illusion! For a small donation, my mystical powers can erase what troubles you!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="hu_tao" sayingMarker="tao11" />
                <state img="#-cheerful.png" marker="HuTaoSocks1_resp">That’s easy. They need to be rich, good-looking, have a good personality, are caring, attentive, hard-working, good at brewing sake, doesn’t nag me too much, devoted. You know, the basics.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="ignatz" sayingMarker="igreimu_ms1" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="IgnatzShoes1_resp">Wow, you’re quite the romantic, Ignatz. Honestly, I mostly just know about this sort of stuff from the novels I read. The men in those books are all really romantic too.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="hu_tao" sayingMarker="tao21" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="HuTaoShirt1_resp">I was aiming for a human wife, yes. I wasn’t really considering &lt;i&gt;undertaking&lt;/i&gt; specifically as a charm point, but I guess it’s a career that’ll always be needed.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="hu_tao" sayingMarker="tao31" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" marker="HuTaoSkirt1_resp">You’d better, Hu Tao. I’ve had more than enough of humans who are afraid of commitment.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="hu_tao" sayingMarker="tao41" />
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" marker="HuTaoSleeves1_resp">I’m considering, I’m considering! Give me a minute, okay?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="fluttershy" sayingMarker="Reimu_shrine_maiden_question" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" marker="FluttershyShoes1_resp">It’s not all fun and games, Fluttershy, being a shrine maiden is &lt;i&gt;work&lt;/i&gt;! Every morning I sweep up the shrine grounds. Then I take a tea break. Afterwards I wait for donating visitors. Then I take another tea break.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="barbara" sayingMarker="ReimuShoes1" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="BarbaraShoes1_resp">Right, you’re basically the same thing as me, Barbara. Do you have trouble getting donations as well?&lt;br&gt;{small}In no small part due to all the rival religions muscling in.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="opp" character="fina" sayingMarker="FinaReimuStart2" />
                <state img="#-blunt.png" marker="FinaSocks1_resp">What, you think I’m going to pocket everything along the way that’s not nailed down? That’s called being a thief, Fina. Like my friend Marisa, who steals junk on the off-chance it’s important to her study of magic.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="tomoko" sayingMarker="ReimuShoes1" />
                <state img="#-dismissive.png" marker="TomokoShoes1_resp">What are you muttering about, Tomoko? I do live in the mountains, yes, but I also love taking long, relaxing baths!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="cynthia" sayingMarker="ReimuStrip01" />
                <state img="#-dismissive.png" marker="CynthiaShoes1_resp">I don’t see what the big deal is, shrine maidens can look for love same as any other girl. As for the hakama… well, I don’t know what the modern style is, but this is comfortable for me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="heris" sayingMarker="HerisReimuMaiden" />
                <state img="#-greedy.png" marker="HerisShoes1_resp">That’s me, Heris. If you ever feel science is leaving you empty and want to reawaken your spiritual side, Hakurei Shrine is always open for business!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="140">
                <condition role="other" character="lux" sayingMarker="ReimuShoes1" />
                <state img="#-dismissive.png" marker="LuxShoes1_resp">I doubt you’d find Gensokyo on any maps, it was sealed off from the outside world long ago. It’s a place where creatures of myth and legend run around annoying me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="141">
                <condition role="other" character="lux" sayingMarker="ReimuSocks1" />
                <state img="#-blunt.png" marker="LuxSocks1_resp">There’s too many strong idiots in Gensokyo, Lux, so we needed a system where we could battle without causing too much carnage. Mostly it’s an excuse for them to flaunt their pretty bullet patterns.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="142">
                <condition role="other" character="mari" sayingMarker="Reimu_Impressions1" />
                <state img="#-dismissive.png" marker="MariShoes1_resp">You don’t look all that spiritual yourself, Mari. I can communicate with the gods and solve whatever incidents befall Gensokyo. I work as hard as I need to!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="ganyu" sayingMarker="GanyuReimu01" />
                <state img="#-blunt.png" marker="GanyuShoes1_resp">&lt;i&gt;Gensokyo.&lt;/i&gt; I’ve never heard of Inazuma, but if it’s like where I’m from it has rowdy youkai and shrine maidens with the power to silence them.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="noelle" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="NoelleShoes1_resp">Inazuma? I’ve never heard of any place like that. I’m from Gensokyo, in Japan. It’s a mystical land hidden from the modern world.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="jim" />
                <state img="#-cheerful.png" marker="JimShoes1_resp" dialogue-layer="over">There’s no problem being here, Jim. All I’m &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; doing is looking for a husband or wife. I’m just skipping the boring bits and starting with everyone falling for me while in the throes of passion.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="opp" character="jim" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="JimSocks1_resp">I heard about this place the other day from a gap youkai named Yukari, and came up with the plan then and there. If a plan’s good, it comes together without you needing to think about it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="opp" character="jim" />
                <state img="#-cheerful.png" marker="JimShirt1_resp">Well, obviously they need to be able to support me and my lifestyle. They need to be charming, good looking, can hold their sake, able to get along with the local fairies, and enjoy &lt;i&gt;all&lt;/i&gt; of my cooking!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="jason" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="JasonShoes1_resp">I’m a shrine maiden, Jason. That means it’s my duty to exterminate youkai and channel the gods’ blessings to humans.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" totalRounds="0">
                <state img="#-angry.png" marker="ReimuLosing0">Hold on, hold on, how am I the first to go? I read the first third of a poker strategy book and everything!</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png" marker="ReimuLosing0">I can’t be &lt;i&gt;first&lt;/i&gt;! I read through a book on card games {small}and didn’t finish it{!reset} for weeks! The overdue fees for that book weren’t cheap, either.</state>
                <state img="#-dismissive.png" marker="ReimuLosing0">I read almost half of a &lt;i&gt;whooole&lt;/i&gt; book about poker to prepare myself, but I forgot most of it so don’t get cocky.&lt;br&gt;{small}It was pretty boring, what can you do?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <condition count="0" status="crotch_visible" />
                <state img="#-angry.png" marker="ReimuLosing6">You— was this was a ploy to make a pure shrine maiden expose herself? I better see &lt;i&gt;every last bit&lt;/i&gt; of the rest of you— or I’m exterminating everyone associated with this establishment!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_winning">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Don’t let little old me interrupt the rest of you. I’m only going to take off something boring like my shoes anyway.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-pleasant.png">According to ReformCopyright, this line will never play. Well, saves me from having to come up with a line here. Writing is such a pain. &lt;i&gt;Sigh…&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-smug.png">They say it’s better to be lucky than good, and it’s true. Mostly because being lucky is less work.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-smug.png">I look more gorgeous with my ribbons, and I’d feel &lt;i&gt;more&lt;/i&gt; naked without my sleeves. Besides, they’re a quintessential part of my look</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-interested.png">This is getting fun! And also… a l-little… risqué.&lt;br&gt;{small}Hoo Boy…</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-cheerful.png">This is &lt;i&gt;way&lt;/i&gt; more fun than doing boring marriage interviews or dating! The gap youkai Yukari is taking me back to Gensokyo, and I can’t wait to tell her of my conquests.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-interested.png">Well, a promise is a promise. All the ladies in the saucy novels I read can’t wait to bare their breasts, so…</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_normal">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-happy.png">I didn’t come here expecting to win every hand. I mean, winning and losing doesn’t matter so much in a game like this. Unless you’re losing.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-interested.png">Oh. Well, it’s just my holy of holies. Um… well, it’s okay to do this sort of this with your spouse, right? Right. Let’s do this.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-greedy.png">My job is to protect humans, but in a game like this it’s every girl for herself! But if you do need real protection, the Hakurei Shrine is always accepting visitors.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Hm… in a game like this, winning is worth far less than grabbing people’s attention. In that case, let’s forget about the small stuff.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-bluffing.png">I’ve taken off my clothes &lt;i&gt;hundreds&lt;/i&gt; of time by myself at home, so it’s not like this is anything new to me. Just… gotta do it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-happy.png">By the way, if I do choose one of you to wed me you should stay until after the game. I came over with the gap youkai Yukari, and it’d be good to introduce you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Yep. I lost. Nothing to do now, but… to do it. Yes.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_losing">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-dismissive.png" marker="ReimuLosing0">Well, whatever. There’s nothing riding on this game except a little bit of pride. Four of us will be out by the end no matter what.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-angry.png" marker="ReimuLosing6">Well, you know what I’ve got left to show. Don’t make me say it. But remember, if no one’s interested in marrying me I’ll be mad, and when I’m mad, youkai get exterminated!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-blunt.png" marker="ReimuLosing1">Whatever. I didn’t come here to work. I don’t even go to &lt;i&gt;work&lt;/i&gt; to work!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" marker="ReimuLosing2">Well, I’m definitely not going to be taking off my ribbon or hair tubes. I could be &lt;i&gt;anyone&lt;/i&gt; without those!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" marker="ReimuLosing3">We’re all going to be married when this is all said and done, so there’s no shame in taking off our clothes! Wait, that wasn’t how this works.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-nervous.png" marker="ReimuLosing4">Now I’m starting to worry. Not about losing so much as I needed the gap youkai Yukari’s power to traverse the barrier. If no one here wants me, it’ll be an awkward ride back.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-bluffing.png" marker="ReimuLosing5">Oh. Oh, I gotta…&lt;br&gt;{small}It’s for finding a doting partner for me. Still beats working.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripping">
            <case stage="0" id="135">
                <condition role="other" character="fluttershy" stage="0" sayingMarker="Reimu_shrine_maiden_cont" />
                <state img="#-stripping-.png" marker="FluttershyShoes2_resp">What do you mean, is that all? Well, if that’s not enough for you, I’m also Gensokyo’s number one youkai exterminator and incident resolver! That means I’ve defeated countless enemies!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="jason" stage="0-6" sayingMarker="TReimu1" />
                <state img="#-stripping-.png" marker="JasonShoes2_resp">I suppose you could think of youkai like demons. They’re creatures born of the mysterious and unexplained. And &lt;i&gt;very&lt;/i&gt; annoying.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="miko" sayingMarker="ReimuShoes2" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="MikoShoes1_resp" />
                <state img="#-stripping+.png" marker="MikoShoes2_resp">A-ah, well, I’d hate to make you bother with &lt;i&gt;lowly old me&lt;/i&gt;, Miko. After all, you’re so strong. And cool.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="meia" sayingMarker="reimu01" />
                <state img="#-stripping-.png" marker="MeiaShoes2_resp">They look like— well to be honest, they look like cute girls. But don’t be deceived, youkai bring destruction and chaos when left unchecked! Never let your guard down!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="meia" sayingMarker="reimu12" />
                <state img="#-stripping-.png" marker="MeiaSocks2_resp">There’s plenty of both men and women in the human village, but I was raised apart from them at the Hakurei Shrine. And the sages of Gensokyo are all old hags.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="fina" sayingMarker="FinaReimuContinue1" />
                <state img="#-stripping+.png" marker="FinaShoes2_resp">Ah, I guess that wasn’t a very good lie. Still, people generally don’t show up to my parties until after I stop whatever crazy incident they caused. It’s such a pain.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="critical_darling" sayingMarker="Reimu_Touhou2" />
                <state img="#-stripping+.png" marker="CriticalDarlingShoes2_resp">Right, I’m Hakurei Shrine’s shrine maiden. It’s my duty to protect the Great Hakurei Barrier and keep order in Gensokyo!&lt;br&gt;{small}I accept donations of all types.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="hu_tao" sayingMarker="tao02" />
                <state img="#-stripping-.png" marker="HuTaoShoes2_resp">What? No! I meant I’ll exterminate any youkai that are plaguing you! I’m not— I haven’t— Look, I’m here to find a &lt;i&gt;spouse&lt;/i&gt;, Hu Tao, nothing less!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="hu_tao" sayingMarker="tao12" />
                <state img="#-stripping+.png" marker="HuTaoSocks2_resp">Wow, you’re almost a Christmas Cake, Hu Tao! Don’t feel bad though, I know some people that are hundreds of years old and have never married!&lt;br&gt;{small}They’re all youkai, though.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="nami" sayingMarker="reimu01" />
                <state img="#-stripping+.png" marker="NamiShoes2_resp">Obviously, I’m going to treat my future spouse right. I may not look it, but I’m good at cooking. And unlike youkai, I’m going to be loyal to my one-and-only!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="hu_tao" sayingMarker="tao22" />
                <state img="#-stripping+.png" marker="HuTaoShirt2_resp">I don’t have trouble exorcising spirits and the like… but it is nice having someone I can share a drink with and talk youkai extermination… or whatever you do, Hu Tao.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="hu_tao" sayingMarker="tao32" />
                <state img="#-stripping+.png" marker="HuTaoSkirt2_resp">Pranks, huh? I suppose that’ll make you popular with the local fairies. Not that I care what &lt;i&gt;they&lt;/i&gt; think when choosing &lt;i&gt;my&lt;/i&gt; partner!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="hu_tao" sayingMarker="tao42" />
                <state img="#-stripping+.png" marker="HuTaoSleeves2_resp">Of course I want to talk with everyone here, but you &lt;i&gt;are&lt;/i&gt; cute, Hu Tao. Though I’m going to tell our future children we met when I saved you from youkai.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="syrenne" sayingMarker="reimu_01" />
                <state img="#-stripping+.png" marker="SyrenneShoes2_resp">I’m always up for free drinks! Just so long as I don’t have to put any effort into my end. That would defeat the purpose.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="yuri" sayingMarker="reimu_extermination2" />
                <state img="#-stripping-.png" marker="YuriShoes2_resp">You just don’t get it, Yuri! Youkai &lt;i&gt;are&lt;/i&gt; the mysterious, the unknown, the unexplainable! If they were to become forgotten or explained away, they would &lt;i&gt;die out!&lt;/i&gt; Is that what you want?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="ms.fortune" sayingMarker="Reimu_Maiden_0B" />
                <state img="#-stripping-.png" marker="FortuneShoes2_resp">Don’t judge me based on my looks, I’m known to spare youkai no mercy. And you’d &lt;i&gt;better&lt;/i&gt; learn what youkai are, seeing as a bakeneko like you qualifies.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="opp" character="ms.fortune" sayingMarker="Reimu_Lover_1B1" />
                <state img="#-stripping-.png" marker="FortuneSocks2A_resp">You’re totally ruled by your base desires, that’s why I can’t stand you youkai at all. And you’re a particularly crass one at that. Maybe your owner should get you spayed.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="opp" character="ms.fortune" sayingMarker="Reimu_Lover_1B2" />
                <state img="#-stripping+.png" marker="FortuneSocks2B_resp">No one’s going to let a catch like me get away. Not only am I the hard working Shrine Maiden of Genokyo, I’m a great cook and know a bit about brewing sake!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="136">
                <condition role="other" character="barbara" sayingMarker="ReimuShoes2" />
                <state img="#-stripping-.png" marker="BarbaraShoes2_resp">Must be nice to have official funding, I wouldn’t have to work as hard and would still get paid more. My shrine is totally reliant on worshippers’ donations.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="jim" />
                <state img="#-stripping+.png" marker="JimShoes2_resp" dialogue-layer="over">I’ve thought this out pretty well. One, I’m sure most people here are lonely. Two, they’ll be touching themselves while thinking of me, making them sure to fall in love! Three, I’m too beautiful to not want to marry!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="ReimuLosing0" />
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">I’m used to taking off my shoes when I go inside anyway, though Westerners like the Scarlet Devil group don’t seem to care.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="ReimuLosing1" />
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">Winning, losing, it’s all the same to me. I’ve got my own reasons for being here, so I don’t have much of a plan beyond going with the flow.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="ReimuLosing2" />
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">In any case, I just want people to be turned on during this game. Once their blood starts pumping, they’ll fall in love with me without me having to do any boring courtship rituals.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="ReimuLosing3" />
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">Gensokyo’s been sealed off for a long while, so I dunno how in fashion these bloomers are in the outside world. But most traditions never change… right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="ReimuLosing4" />
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">I’ll trust my intuition when it comes time to pick a betrothed. If I don’t think you’re acceptable, I’ll come back later. It’s still fun to do the things I don’t get to do in Gensokyo anyway.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="ReimuLosing5" />
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">Hold your damn horses, I’m getting them out. Ugh, it’s always a pain to wrap my sarashi right. Whoever I marry oughta do it for me too.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="ReimuLosing6" />
                <state img="#-stripping-.png">I don’t know what sort of &lt;i&gt;bizarre&lt;/i&gt; trends the outside world has come up with for… this body part, but I’m just… I’m traditional, got it? All natural, no fuss.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">I’m not like the Westerners that migrated into Gensokyo, I don’t usually wear my shoes indoors. Taking these off is nothing to me!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">Don’t get too carried away now. I can only wed one of you, after all. Maaaaybe two of you, if I like you both enough.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">I’ve got my own reasons for playing a game this racy, but I don’t mind showing off and I sure don’t mind other people showing off.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">With this game heating up, people are going to be swimming in their passions! They won’t be able to help but fall in love with me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">I hope I don’t appear too old fashioned. My undies, I mean. Gensokyo’s been sealed off from the outside world since… um, a good length of time.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">Even if I don’t find a match this go around, I’ve had fun with the, um, sexual aspects. Gensokyo is very traditional, but I have my share of… needs.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-stripping+.png">T-this is a sight only my husband or wife should see! B-but if one of you is destined to become my future companion, I suppose it’s okay…</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripped">
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="MikoShoes2_resp" />
                <condition role="other" character="miko" sayingMarker="ReimuShoes3" />
                <state img="#-stripped+.png" marker="MikoShoes3_resp">&lt;i&gt;Pfft.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="hu_tao" sayingMarker="tao03" />
                <state img="#-stripped-.png" marker="HuTaoShoes3_resp">W-well I wouldn’t know! At least not until after I get married!&lt;br&gt;{small}Are most Chinese girls this libertine? Meiling always seemed approximately normal.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="hu_tao" sayingMarker="tao13" />
                <state img="#-stripped+.png" marker="HuTaoSocks3_resp">I think traditions are good. Without tradition, how would you know how to defeat youkai… or that you need to pay pilgrimage to your local shrine?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="fina" sayingMarker="FinaReimuEnd1" />
                <state img="#-stripped-.png" marker="FinaShoes3_resp">Even if you’re not the same sort of shrine maiden I am, our methods are pretty similar. Except I don’t get bounties for solving incidents. Or paid at all. What gives?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="meia" sayingMarker="reimu1s" />
                <state img="#-stripped-.png" marker="MeiaShoes3_resp">I’m sure there was a good reason you were told to fear men, Meia. Like, maybe they’re magical beings and if humans ever stopped fearing them they’d lose their reason for existing and fade away.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="meia" sayingMarker="reimu2s" />
                <state img="#-stripped-.png" marker="MeiaSocks3_resp">I’m not “kept away” from anyone, we just don’t get a ton of visitors to my shrine of either gender. It means less work I have to do, so it’s not all bad.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="critical_darling" sayingMarker="Reimu_Touhou2" />
                <state img="#-stripped-.png" marker="CriticalDarlingShoes3_resp">Famous? Hmm, I never thought about it, but I guess everyone in Gensokyo does know me. …Yet none of them donate to my shrine.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="hu_tao" sayingMarker="tao23" />
                <state img="#-stripped+.png" marker="HuTaoShirt3_resp">I don’t think the human village would approve all that much of me marrying another woman, Hu Tao, but there are enough rumors swirling around me. Who’d pay attention to one more?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="hu_tao" sayingMarker="tao33" />
                <state img="#-bluffing.png" marker="HuTaoSkirt3_resp">I was hoping for someone rich enough they could hire someone else to resolve incidents… somehow.&lt;br&gt;{small}But being a wife and wife youkai extermination team would be nice.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="other" character="hu_tao" sayingMarker="tao43" />
                <state img="#-stripped+.png" marker="HuTaoSleeves3_resp">Oh, that’s the easy part, I can just get some medicine from Doctor Yagokoro that lets two women have kids together. She owes me big time after I saved the moon from Hell’s invasion.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <condition role="other" character="hu_tao" sayingMarker="reimu63" />
                <state img="#-stripped-.png" marker="HuTaoBloomers3_resp">Shave? What am I supposed to— wait, you mean my hairs? That would be too weird, not to mention too much trouble, so it’s not happening.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="opp" character="nami" sayingMarker="reimu1s" />
                <state img="#-stripped-.png" marker="NamiShoes3_resp">Hmph. I don’t know what you might think of me, Nami, but I’m not going to abandon someone for some bad luck. I’m sure we’ll figure something out.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="jim" />
                <state img="#-stripped+.png" marker="JimShoes3_resp">I’ve got other plans I could put into motion to make some quick yen, Jim, but it’d be nice to have someone to drink sake with.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="ReimuLosing0" />
                <state img="#-stripped-.png">The Inventory will keep a close eye on all our clothing, right? It’d be bad publicity if my shoe got lost and turned into a youkai.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="ReimuLosing1" />
                <state img="#-stripped-.png">Trying to win at this game is too exhausting. Really, trying to do anything is a pain. That’s why I need some nice, good-looking person to take care of me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="ReimuLosing2" />
                <state img="#-stripped-.png">So long as I get a nice suitor to take care of me, and take them home to flaunt to my boring mentor Kasen, I could care less about the rest of this game!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="ReimuLosing3" />
                <state img="#-stripped-.png">It’s drafty…</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="ReimuLosing4" />
                <state img="#-stripped-.png">This dumb game is just an excuse to see nudity, right? As long as the rest of you get worn down too, I don’t care if none of you meet my standards for marriage.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="ReimuLosing5" />
                <state img="#-stripped-.png">Yeah, yeah. Other people have fatter breasts. These are well-shaped, compliment them or move on.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="ReimuLosing6" />
                <state img="#-stripped-.png">Just… Someone please marry me after all this is over. I kinda already bragged about it to Kasen.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">I’m the best incident solver around! I’ve exterminated countless youkai on my own— I don’t care if I’m in my socks or not!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">And to think, all this could be yours if you took me as your wife and pampered me! Please only charming and handsome men and/or smart and beautiful women apply.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">I’m going to put all my effort into winning! But not during this next round. Putting in all my effort at once is too troublesome, that’s why it’d be nice to have someone to take care of me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">I’ll be leaving here with a doting fiancee of my own! And I’ll rub it in my dumb mentor Kasen’s face! She said this was a terrible idea, you know.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">…And that’s how I take off my skirt.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">So all the rest of you, don’t be afraid to flaunt what you’ve got! Even if I don’t get a spouse, I’ll still get a show!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-stripped+.png">S-so here you are. No touching, though~! We &lt;i&gt;definitely&lt;/i&gt; have to be married before you can think of that.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_strip">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="ignatz" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="IgnatzShoes1">Say, Ignatz was it? You mentioned something about being an artist? I read in a magazine from the outside world some paintings go for millions of Yen!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="jim" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-extermination.png" marker="JimGloves1">Jim, huh? You look big and mean. Don’t think you can push me around though— I’ve used my sacred needles on bigger than you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="jim" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="JimBandolier1">Jim, you’re big. That means you eat a lot of meat, right? I wish I could eat big, fancy meals all the time— how do you do it?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-smug.png">This is what happens when you tangle with me, after all. I'm the Hakurei shrine maiden who silences crying children!</state>
                <state img="#-dismissive.png">We’re not playing for money, so there’s no reason to be stingy. The only thing you stand to lose is some pride, and &lt;i&gt;yours&lt;/i&gt; can’t be worth much.</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">To the victor go the spoils! Spoil me, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Don’t mind me, just keeping my eyes peeled. The Tengu tabloids would have a field day if they could snap a picture of me here.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">I hope no incidents occur while I’m gone. I’m sure Sanae can handle anything, being a shrine maiden herself and all, but I don’t like the idea of &lt;i&gt;my&lt;/i&gt; shrine falling further into irrelevancy.</state>
                <state img="#-blunt.png">This week was such a pain. I had to knock some sense into Tenshi, Cirno, Aya, Remilia, Cirno, Clownpiece, Seija, and Cirno again. In other words, make this good, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-dismissive.png">I wish they had nice pillows or something for us to sit on, at least between rounds. I know they want us to show off, but we’re all focused on ~name~ right now anyway.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-nervous.png">If some incident get started while I’m away, someone else is going to have to solve it. I can’t exactly rush over looking like this, huh?</state>
                <state img="#-cheerful.png">Are you nervous getting naked when I’m like this, ~name~? Why not have a cup of sake to relax? And while you’re at the bar, how about getting me some too?</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">Does seeing me like this make you self-conscious, ~name~? Could it be… because I’m the girl of your dreams? Awww, I knew it!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-cheerful.png">You did your best, and I get to see a &lt;i&gt;liiittle&lt;/i&gt; bit more of you. I’d say we both did good this round.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">If we’re going to get married, it’s important to know— do you prefer red miso or white miso in your miso soup?</state>
                <state img="#-blunt.png">“I didn’t play this game for the fun of the cards, hard as it is to believe. I wanna see something good.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">I’ve heard boys can’t wait to show themselves off in front of a beautiful girl… well, I want to see you too, but no funny business before we’re married.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_strip">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="yuna" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-extermination.png" marker="YunaVest1">Yuna, stay calm, but it appears you’re being possessed by two ghosts. Don’t worry. I’ll exterminate them for you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="meia" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="MeiaEyepiece1">Meia? You’re the “dreaded team leader”, right? I’ve never seen armor as sleek as yours.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="jura" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-angry.png" marker="JuraRapier1">Look at you with your long blonde hair and your dolled up face and your plunging neckline and your seductive laugh. I’m gonna send you home crying into your girlfriend’s chest!&lt;br&gt;…I wish I had that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="yuri" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="YuriShoes1">Yuri, was it— I think you were the one talking about books earlier? I’m a big big fan of murder mysteries! Oh, but I read all kinds.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="miko" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-blunt.png" marker="MikoCape1">Did you seriously just stumble upon this place, Miko? Just my luck. I can’t even threaten to tell your followers because that’d implicate &lt;i&gt;me&lt;/i&gt; as well.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="zoe" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="ZoeShoes1">Zoe, was it? Do you work for some seafaring merchants or something? I heard you talking about “shipping” earlier.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="ms.fortune" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-blunt.png" marker="FortuneLegWarmers">A cat, huh? What’re you doing here playing a game for humans? Shouldn’t you be making yourself useful chasing mice somewhere?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="revy" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-cheerful.png" marker="RevyGloves1">I’ve met oni more cheerful than you, Revy. I’m sure if you smiled a bit, even you could snag a husband or wife as easy as I will!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="nami" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-cheerful.png" marker="NamiBelt1">Say, Nami, are you some kind of sailor girl? That sounds like it’d be a fun job! Sailing to new lands, drinking rum all day, relaxing in the sea breeze…</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="fina" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-pleasant.png" marker="FinaBoots1">Are you some sort of shrine maiden or priestess where you’re from, Fina? You have a similar air to me… not to mention similar sleeves.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="noelle" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="NoelleArmor1">Since you’re a maid, Noelle, are you here to find a suitor too? I’m sure your mistress is a layabout who works you to the bone, it’s the same in Gensokyo.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="critical_darling" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-blunt.png" marker="CriticalDarlingGloves1">What kind of music do you play, Critical? It better not be the obnoxious loud noise some of the youkai have been blasting lately.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="myriam" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" marker="MyriamTie1">Ugh, a newspaper reporter. I have to deal with those back home, and the &lt;i&gt;last&lt;/i&gt; thing I need is word of my being here getting out.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="syrenne" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="SyrenneTop1">You seem pretty tough for a human, Syrenne. Are you a sort of Youkai exterminator where you’re from? Protecting humans from evil and all that?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="petra" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-pleasant.png" marker="PetraBoots1">So you’re a princess, Petra? What does a princess of Brigid actually &lt;i&gt;do&lt;/i&gt; in terms of royal duties?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="hu_tao" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-blunt.png" marker="HuTaoShoes1">Hu Tao, was it? You have an air of death around you. I don’t think you’re a ghost or jiang-shi &lt;i&gt;yourself&lt;/i&gt;, but that might be worse.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="meia" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-cheerful.png" marker="MeiaArmor1">Meia, you need to relax, throw some parties, and find yourself a nice girl to drink sake with. Otherwise you’ll find yourself waking up a wrinkly old maid some day.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="hatsune_miku" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-blunt.png" marker="MikuTie1">I don’t think I’ve ever seen a creature like you, Miku. Your outfit’s weird enough, but what’s with your voice? You sound like you’re speaking through a gramophone.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="stocking" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="StockingShoes1">Hey Stocking, you’re an angel who got banished from Heaven, right? I know a delinquent celestial who got kicked out of there, but angels are different sorts of beings.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="samus_aran" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-pleasant.png" marker="SamusPowerSuit1">Are you a youkai exterminator yourself where you come from, Samus? I know an enchanted suit of armor when I see it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="hu_tao" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-blunt.png" marker="HuTaoSocks1">So, Hu Tao, what it is you &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; do? No ordinary undertaker carries around spirits or knows how to use magic.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="remilia" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" marker="RemiliaHat1">Why are you here, Remi? Did Yukari tell you what I was up to?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="remilia" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" marker="RemiliaShoes1">Unlike Vampires, who are content to shut themselves in a coffin all day, humans have certain needs. We need companionship, and… well, you know…</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="remilia" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" marker="RemiliaSkirt1">You youkai only care about your own desires— you’re all shameless. You’ll do &lt;i&gt;whatever&lt;/i&gt; with &lt;i&gt;whoever&lt;/i&gt;.&lt;br&gt;{small}You know it’s all your faults I’ve become open to liking women.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="remilia" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">So tell me, Remi… have you really had sex before? What, um, was it like? I mean— how does a youkai engage in that sort of thing?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="remilia" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" marker="RemiliaBra1">…I’ll be honest, Remi. I know plenty of humans engage in premarital sex. I didn’t want to admit it, because… well, it’s embarrassing.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="remilia" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="RemiliaPanties1">Flan? Oh right! Earlier today Koishi was bothering me, so I gave her a bunch of candy and told her to share it with her friends. I guess she must be on a sugar high right now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="hu_tao" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="HuTaoCoat1">So, Hu Tao, if we’re getting married… it’d be nice to know more about you. How’d you get into the undertaker/youkai exterminator business?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="hu_tao" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" marker="HuTaoShirt1">Hu Tao, what makes you so interested in me? I’m not used to people being so forward and open. It’s nice, but why me?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="hu_tao" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" marker="HuTaoShorts1">Hu Tao, are you… experienced? I don’t care either way, but I’m a virgin. You don’t mind, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="hu_tao" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-blunt.png" marker="HuTaoHat1">Oh, you’re taking off your hat now? We’ve already seen all of you, so what does the top of your head matter?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="fluttershy" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-serious.png" marker="FluttershySleeves1">Fluttershy, you seem awfully jumpy. Are you unwell? Or are you trying to hide something?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="barbara" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png" marker="BarbaraHat1">W-wait, you’re doing a prayer, &lt;i&gt;here&lt;/i&gt;? I can’t let myself fall behind! Let’s also give thanks to the god of the Hakurei Shrine!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="barbara" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="BarbaraShoes1">I didn’t expect to meet another holy woman here. I’m looking to find a fine husband or wife, but why did you come, Barbara?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="fina" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="FinaHeaddress1">It must have been rough leaving the Silver Shrine, Fina. Even if it was lonely there, it was the only world you’ve ever known. I can’t imagine leaving Gensokyo for good…</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="trixie" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" marker="TrixieHat1">Are you one of those hobgoblins? I didn’t even know they made female ones. Shouldn’t you be off cleaning someone’s house?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="fischl" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-blunt.png" marker="FischlRibbon1">Are you a princess, Fischl? Really? Because you remind me of a certain &lt;i&gt;self-styled&lt;/i&gt; vampire princess from back home.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="tomoko" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-extermination.png" marker="TomokoTie1">Tomoko, huh? You look rather gloomy. That’s a youkai’s curse if I’ve ever seen one! All right Tomoko, prepare to get exorcized!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="cynthia" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="CynthiaCoat1">You don’t &lt;i&gt;look&lt;/i&gt; like anything special to me, Cynthia, but from the sounds of things you’re a powerful shikigami user. Is it true you’ve made dragons your servants?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="heris" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-greedy.png" marker="HerisLabcoat1">I’ve seen labcoats like that in books and worn by science types before, Heris. Do you invent stuff and then sell it for big bucks?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="lux" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="LuxBracers1">I didn’t expect to meet a magic wielding human here. We have some Western magicians in Gensokyo. Are you any good, Lux?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="ganyu" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-extermination.png" marker="GanyuDress1">Ganyu, eh? Are you with one of the beast gangs in the Animal Realm? You look a lot like the Toutetsu lady who runs one of the &lt;i&gt;“families”&lt;/i&gt; there.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="kora" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="KoraLightningBolts1">You called yourself a “blade”, Kora. Do you mean literally that you’re a &lt;i&gt;tsukumogami&lt;/i&gt;— a sword that has been around so long it developed a spirit?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="opp" character="mari" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="MariNecktie1">Mari, your outfit reminds me of what Sumireko, a girl I know from the outside world, wears. Some sort of school uniform, I think. What do you study?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Well, of course &lt;i&gt;someone’s&lt;/i&gt; got to lose. It’s not a big deal.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">If this were an incident, and you were a youkai, I’d be whacking you with my gohei right about now! Good thing you just have to take off some clothing, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-cheerful.png">Another win for me! Once my hard work is over, I can’t wait to go home and goof off.</state>
                <state img="#-blunt.png">This would be easier if the rest of you didn’t put up so much of a fight. You know I &lt;i&gt;do&lt;/i&gt; want to see more of you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-blunt.png">Please just strip normally. I’m getting exhausted just &lt;i&gt;imagining&lt;/i&gt; the rigamarole a youkai would go through stripping. They always have to be the center of attention.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Don’t worry, ~name~, I won’t tell anyone anything about this. And you won’t tell anyone from the human village. &lt;i&gt;Right&lt;/i&gt;?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I’m fine with anyone, so long as we get closer to seeing &lt;i&gt;someone&lt;/i&gt; naked!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-9" priority="0">
                <condition count="0" status="not_lost_some" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="31">~Name~? I forget, what did you take off last time? There’s been so much removed, it’s hard to remember who was wearing what at the beginning.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-dismissive.png">There’s no reason to be concerned, even the winner will likely lose most everything. I-I’m just saying that because you’ll harsh the mood if you’re upset!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">It all comes down to luck, doesn’t it? Outside of youkai extermination I’m pretty unlucky, so I can’t feel too bad about you losing.</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">Well, if you didn’t want to strip, you should have played better. I wanna see you in the buff, so I’m trying my best.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-smug.png">I’m sure your body is very beautiful, ~name~. And I’m sure the sight of you pleasuring yourself is also beautiful. Anyway, get going so we can reach that point.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">I guess if we did get married, you’d see me like this a lot, ~name~. You wouldn’t get tired of me, would you?</state>
                <state img="#-bluffing.png">Erm, give me a moment. I need to prepare myself for seeing a more naked version of ~name~.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="tie">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">A &lt;i&gt;draw&lt;/i&gt;? I guess no one &lt;i&gt;has&lt;/i&gt; to lose, but it still feels like I was wasting my time.</state>
                <state img="#-blunt.png">So, nothing happens? That’s a disappointment. I know it doesn’t matter here, but I’d still rather win outright.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-greedy.png">If you’re ever in need of more ~clothing.toPlural~, look no further than Hakurei Shrine! We can figure out how to sell you some, probably!</state>
                <state img="#-dismissive.png">~clothing.ifPlural(~Clothing~ are|A ~clothing~ is)~ too lame to have an opinion about.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">You should be happy you can finally take off ~clothing.ifPlural(those|that)~ ugly looking ~clothing~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I’m keeping a lookout for any youkai afoot. It’d be a problem if they recognized— I mean, &lt;i&gt;attacked&lt;/i&gt; me.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">I need an excuse to hold another festival at Hakurei Shrine soon. I heard the Moriya Shrine is planning one of their own, and I can’t let them hog all the donations.</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">Hurry it up, I would have had enough time here to warm up a flask of sake!&lt;br&gt;{small}I wish I had a flask of sake.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Your ~clothing.ifPlural(~clothing~ are|~clothing~ is)~ just fine for now. After all, you had to take ~clothing.ifPlural(those|it)~ off eventually!</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">I’d rather you took something important off instead. After all, I’m already like this. Don’t you want to be a gentleman?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">…I’m not done yet, you know.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="752" marker="MenDesire1">I don’t have a lot of guy friends, ~name~, so I don’t really know what men want. I-is it true they’re obsessed with sex? I wouldn’t want to just p-put myself out for anyone…</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" marker="OutsideMen1">I very rarely interact with people from the world outside Gensokyo, ~name~, but I’m always amazed how, er, &lt;i&gt;forward&lt;/i&gt; they are. My reputation &lt;i&gt;requires&lt;/i&gt; me to act like the ideal shrine maiden, and all that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-cheerful.png">The Hakurei clan have the innate ability to undo any seal— so watch as I negate the seal on your ~clothing~! Hehe, just kidding~!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">What a boring choice. Maybe I’ll take a quick break, rest up a bit.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">I’m glad ~name~ hasn’t made any odd comments about my armpits! Though wait… are people actually into that? Um, if you want to marry me and… uh, nevermind!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="4-7" oneShotId="39">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="MenDesire1" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png" marker="MenDesire2">It seems odd to me that men want their wives to be virgins, but can’t wait to get their own rocks off… unless… could it be men are all having sex with &lt;i&gt;each other?&lt;/i&gt; I knew it!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7" oneShotId="40">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="OutsideMen1" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="OutsideMen2">Even if I didn’t have to maintain my standing, I’m not interested in a relationship with one of the village men. It’s just… I feel like my world is too different from theirs.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-happy.png">I wish I had some tea to warm me up. I prefer green tea, but this place might only have black tea.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I wonder… if I sold ~clothing.toPlural~ like that at the shrine, would anyone buy?</state>
                <state img="#-dismissive.png">You’re not gonna impress me with small stuff like your ~clothing~, after all I’ve been on fantastical adventures since the outside world year of 1996! No don’t ask me how I’m still 20, I don’t care.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">What’s the point of teasing me at this stage? Just take the damn ~clothing.ifPlural(things|thing)~ off!</state>
                <state img="#-blunt.png">Next person who loses, &lt;i&gt;please&lt;/i&gt; give me something better.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I’d rather have everyone’s attention anyway. Thanks for being boring, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-dismissive.png">Kind of an uninspired choice, ~name~. I was hoping to find a proper suitor here, but you’re not really doing it for me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-blunt.png">Great, great. I make nothing exterminating youkai, and I was hoping I could at least have some cheap entertainment doing this. Guess that was too much to ask.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I’m sure those fairies are preparing all sorts of pranks for me when I get back. What stupid, annoying creatures! …I wonder how those tykes are doing anyway.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Do I have cat hair on me? A feline youkai named Orin was lounging around the shrine earlier. She likes the sun there.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-confused.png">That’s… good? Yeah, I suppose that’s good. You took off something, so let’s keep on playing.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">How much did you pay for ~clothing.ifPlural(those|that)~ ~clothing~, ~name~? I wonder if the Hakurei Shrine could start selling clothes… nah.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">The people from the outside world all have these strange doodads. I thought they were for fashion or ceremonial, but apparently you can use them to see pictures of cute girls.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Hey ~name~, have you ever heard of “electricity”? People in the outside world use it a lot.  It’s like harnessing the power of lightning, apparently.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Does your ~clothing~ serve a purpose? Like the &lt;i&gt;ofuda&lt;/i&gt; paper amulets or needles that I use to battle youkai.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">I wish I had the money for a fresh cup of sake, so I could go to the bar during the lull in the game.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">~clothing.ifPlural(~Clothing~|A ~clothing~)~? Yeah, sure, whatever.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-cheerful.png">Taking off your ~clothing~? Well, that’s fine. Just don’t get mad when I do the same next loss!</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">Never fear, ~name~, if any youkai attack you while you’re taking off your ~clothing~, I’ll exterminate them! Without mercy! Because that’s what I, the shrine maiden of Gensokyo, do!</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">My shrine’s not super popular, so I can go a while without seeing another human being. Well, there’s always fairies and youkai hanging about. And my best friend Marisa, but she &lt;i&gt;barely&lt;/i&gt; counts.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">You’re taking off your ~clothing~ just as ~clothing.ifPlural(their|its)~ own thing? …Well, I don’t care if I win or lose, but I &lt;i&gt;do&lt;/i&gt; care if you’re smug about it, so don’t rub it in.</state>
                <state img="#-dismissive.png">Go ahead and take off whatever you want. I’ll just be over here relaxing.</state>
                <state img="#-greedy.png">~Name~, if you ever no longer want your ~clothing~, come see me. I’ll give ~clothing.ifPlural(them|it)~ a proper burial so ~clothing.ifPlural(they don’t|it doesn’t)~ come back as a tsukumogami… for a low, low price.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" oneShotId="746" marker="YoukaiDesire1">I’ll just watch you for now, ~name~. I’m not like youkai, craven beings of pure desire. I got &lt;i&gt;standards&lt;/i&gt;, so I’ll use this time to see if you’re a keeper!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="747" marker="GenokyoDating1">I came here because dating within Gensokyo’s human village seems almost impossible, given how different I am from most humans. But I could never date a youkai either!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-interested.png">~Name~, does seeing me like this excite you? I’m of marriageable age, you know. In case you wanted to marry me.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Eh, whatever. I have to deal with so much stuff normally, I don’t care what you take off in this game.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">That’s not going to excite me much at this stage… but I’m used to using my fantasies.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="4-7" oneShotId="41">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="YoukaiDesire1" />
                <state img="#-angry.png" marker="YoukaiDesire2">Youkai are all self-centered and capricious, so they’re willing to have meaningless sex with anyone. Humans aren’t like that at all! I wouldn’t do that, even if I’m drunk.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7" oneShotId="42">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="GenokyoDating1" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" marker="GenokyoDating2">Youkai can’t commit, I could never enjoy a relationship with one. And wishy-washy youkai-like humans are the worst! We’ve known each other for years, but you can’t settle down!&lt;br&gt;{small}I know so many girls like her, but still…</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Oh, I just got an idea of how I can get rich quick selling knockoff ~clothing.toPlural~! Hmmm, but where would I get the materials?</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">~Clothing.toPlural~? &lt;i&gt;~Clothing.toPlural~?&lt;/i&gt; Ah, well, whatever.</state>
                <state img="#-blunt.png">Do you wear ~clothing.ifPlural(~clothing~|a ~clothing~)~ most days, ~name~? Or did you just grab that to be annoying in strip poker?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-confused.png">I haven’t gotten any visitors to the shrine in a while. Well, besides fairies, but they don’t donate. Unless you count the time Cirno put a frog in the offering box.</state>
                <state img="#-greedy.png">If you don’t want your ~clothing~ anymore, how about donating ~clothing.ifPlural(them|it)~ to the Hakurei Shrine? No? You can also donate money.</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">I’ve exterminated youkai for far less than boring me in games, you know.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I hope my guard komainu Aunn is keeping a close eye on the shrine, I’m sure Marisa would love to steal whatever she could find. …What do I have worth stealing, anyway?</state>
                <state img="#-blunt.png">Could be worse. I could be like this watching you take off ~clothing.ifPlural(some|a)~ ~clothing~, &lt;i&gt;and&lt;/i&gt; my mentor Kasen could be lecturing me on how bad I’m doing.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Well, I tried my best. I didn’t try that &lt;i&gt;hard&lt;/i&gt;, since who cares about a game like this, but despite not trying my hardest I tried my best.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-cheerful.png">By the way, don’t worry about buying me lots of candies and other delicacies once we get married, ~name~. My ability is to eat sweets and never get fat!</state>
                <state img="#-greedy.png">It feels like you’re stalling, ~name~… but all will be forgiven with a healthy donation to the Hakurei Shrine. We accept money and sake.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I sure did lose this game. Maybe ~name~ and I could have a private rematch. I bet I could win with a little extra practice.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">If I smacked you with my gohei, would that cause you to take off something bigger? When I’m battling, the harder hits do the most damage, right?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I’ve studied your ~clothing~, and I can assure you I’ve felt no youkai aura from ~clothing.ifPlural(them|it)~. Well, that’s as much as I want to work today. Please leave a donation at the Hakurei Shrine.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Hmm… I wonder if there are any rituals to protect people while they’re stripping? And if not, could I invent one? Might bring in some donations.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-blunt.png">Better than having to go to the moon, yet again. Honestly, the Lunarians consider themselves &lt;i&gt;soooo&lt;/i&gt; superior, yet we’re always drawn into their problems.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">People are always quick to believe rumors. Like how they call my place “The Youkai Shrine” without so much as a &lt;i&gt;shred&lt;/i&gt; of evidence.</state>
                <state img="#-blunt.png">You know what’s a pain? Going to Hell. So much tedium just to get in, and once you’re there you’re bored out of your mind.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Will you buy me clothes as expensive as ~clothing.ifPlural(those|that)~ ~clothing~ if we get married? I… don’t know if it’s expensive really, but it seems nicer than I’m used to.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">If I courted someone from the human village, what would they say when they found out my shrine really &lt;i&gt;is&lt;/i&gt; infested with youkai? Coming here was definitely a better idea.</state>
                <state img="#-cheerful.png">Let’s take it easy while ~name~ strips. I won’t be able to keep up with everyone unless we take breaks.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-cheerful.png">I’m reliant on festivals for most of the Hakurei Shrine’s income. I’m not playing the strip version in public any time soon, but maybe a &lt;i&gt;regular&lt;/i&gt; poker tournament? I bet I’d be great at bluffing!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I hope you keep losing lots more, ~name~! I may be out, but hopefully we can get everyone naked before the night’s over.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">I shouldn’t have gotten my hopes up for anything good. Not like I care what &lt;i&gt;~name~&lt;/i&gt; takes off.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_minor">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-pleasant.png">The land of Gensokyo was sealed off over 100 years ago, so your ~clothing~ probably ~clothing.ifPlural(aren’t|isn’t)~ like anything I’ve seen.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I’ve exterminated your ~clothing~ just like I exterminate troublesome youkai.</state>
                <state img="#-cheerful.png">Right, I’ve given ~name~ the attention he deserves. Now, let’s get back to me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-dismissive.png">Hmm, there’s so much about the outside world I still don’t understand… Oh, this isn’t about your ~clothing~, ~name~. I don’t care about ~clothing.ifPlural(those|that)~.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I like you well enough ~name~, so if you ever wind up in Gensokyo I’ll try my best to make sure you don’t get eaten by a youkai.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Let’s move on. If I’m away for too long, some rowdy youkai might start a party at my shrine without me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Things are heating up a bit, huh? I want to get to the next round fast… but not so fast that it feels like work.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I hope you’re not trying to impress me with your stripping, ~name~. I couldn’t blame you if you were, but it’ll take more than that!</state>
                <state img="#-cheerful.png">Watching you strip ~clothing.ifPlural(those|that)~ gives me the same feeling as when I finally catch the trail of whoever’s responsible for the latest incident. I haven’t fought the mastermind yet, but I have beaten someone who can show me the way.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Even when taking off something boring, make a big show of it. Tease us a little to build up anticipation for the good stuff.</state>
                <state img="#-cheerful.png">We’ll see plenty more of you soon, ~name~. Better get comfortable!</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">I’ll be angry if I never get to see more of you, ~name~! You’re not so cruel a man as to disappoint me, are you?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Do people in the outside world wear ~clothing.ifPlural(those kind of|that kind of)~ ~clothing~, ~name~? Or are you just strange?</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">Normally my victories are celebrated with a full flask of sake, but this’ll do too!</state>
                <state img="#-greedy.png">People in Gensokyo’s Human Village probably have never seen ~clothing.ifPlural(~clothing~|a ~clothing~)~ like that. I oughta make my own and sell them!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Most of the village girls wouldn’t even take off something as minor as  ~clothing.ifPlural(~clothing~|a ~clothing~)~ in public. People in Gensokyo are pretty old fashioned.</state>
                <state img="#-blunt.png">~clothing.ifPlural(They’re|It’s)~ a boring choice. Oh, don’t get me wrong, &lt;i&gt;”boring”&lt;/i&gt; is relaxing, I like it. My &lt;i&gt;“thrilling”&lt;/i&gt; events involve stuff like a nuclear chicken tossing suns at me.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Do the rest of you always have people &lt;i&gt;lecturing&lt;/i&gt; you all the time? Like who do those sages think they are, my mothers?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-happy.png">In Gensokyo we settle everything with a battle of magic bullets, known as &lt;i&gt;danmaku&lt;/i&gt;. Losers usually end up with clothing damage. So really, this isn’t much different than that.</state>
                <state img="#-cheerful.png">You can take off whatever you want this round, because eventually I’ll find my goal. Just like when I solve incidents!</state>
                <state img="#-cheerful.png">We should add another rule on top of the stripping part. Like: “losers have to buy the others a cup of sake!”&lt;br&gt;{small}I don’t have enough money to buy sake for anyone else, though.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Sometimes, when it’s warm at night, I lounge inside naked with a cup of chilled sake. Like I’m doing now, but without the sake.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">My friend Marisa once joked that I didn’t need a sarashi because my breasts were so small. Except you can totally see my chest through the side of my shirt! Unless… that’s what she wanted?</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">Take off whatever you want, ~name~, but remember that &lt;i&gt;I&lt;/i&gt; wanna see what my potential future wife has to offer as well.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_minor">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-confident.png">To have a filling meal, you need &lt;i&gt;rice!&lt;/i&gt; Your ~clothing~ ~clothing.ifPlural(are|is)~ just the sprinkles of salt and seaweed you put on top!</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">I wouldn’t even be able to get any new congregants with this victory. What a waste.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Do you want to pray to the God of the Hakurei Shrine for your ~clothing.ifPlural(~clothing~’ protection while they’re|~clothing~’s protection while it’s)~ gone?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-angry.png">Youkai are weak to mental and psychological attacks. &lt;i&gt;You disgusting sow.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;…Okay, just checking.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Where do you even get ~clothing.toPlural~ in the Outside World anyway? I’ve seen big, shiny buildings there, are there people in those that make them?</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">I wonder how the Tengu papers would spin ~name~ taking off her ~clothing~ to make it sound exciting? Ugh, they’d just pile on a ton of self-important, self-serving hogwash. Like always.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-happy.png">~clothing.ifPlural(Are ~clothing~ like those|Is ~clothing~ like that)~ traditional where you’re from, ~name~? I modified my shrine maiden outfit to be easier to move around in.</state>
                <state img="#-cheerful.png">Just like when I’m flying about resolving incidents, I tend to space out when there’s a lull in the action. As well as during the action itself.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">If you’re only going to take off your ~clothing~, could you at least brew me a cup of tea too? I’ve been working so hard lately, I need a pick-me-up.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">~Name~, even if you make me your pampered wife, don’t expect me to be able to do many chores. I can’t figure out any of those outside world machines.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">There’s no need to fight with me, you know. It’ll be fine by me if you just want to strip bare and show everything off. I promise to savor it.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">You’re not just taking that off to tease me, are you? If I come home after a hard, hard day’s work, I wouldn’t want to be teased. My wife should take care of me.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_major">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-interested.png">I feel like I should have a drink before watching this.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Wonderful choice! I wish youkai were as amenable as ~name~ is. Would make my job a lot easier.</state>
                <state img="#-cheerful.png">I didn’t really come here with a plan, but I guess it all worked out. Now to enjoy this!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Heh heh, maybe I’m a little too good for my &lt;i&gt;own good&lt;/i&gt;, huh?</state>
                <state img="#-bluffing.png">Gensokyo doesn’t have many ~clothing.toPlural~ like that. So if I stare, it’s just because I’m curious about it! Also, I want to check out your body.</state>
                <state img="#-bluffing.png">Oh, we’ve gotten to taking off people’s ~clothing.toPlural~ already? Doesn’t matter much to me, of course, I prepared myself for what I was going to see here.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5" oneShotId="9" priority="0">
                <condition count="0" status="exposed" />
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Ah, we’re really gonna get naked, huh? it’s only now starting to sink in.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-bluffing.png">&lt;i&gt;Yaaaay&lt;/i&gt; I was hoping it’d be your— I mean… &lt;i&gt;ahem&lt;/i&gt;, that’s good, but feel free to take off whatever you want, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">I’m doing great if I’m getting ~name~ out of his ~clothing~ now! …Oh, sorry, I don’t mean to make you feel bad.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">How do girls generally react to men taking off ~clothing.toPlural~? I don’t want to be &lt;i&gt;weird&lt;/i&gt; about it, but I do want to imagine ~name~ spilling his seed.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-interested.png">Oooh, this is exciting! A man taking off his ~clothing~, while I lie here naked. Just like in those thin books I’ve read.</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">Take that damn thing off sensually, ~name~! Do a proper strip! Erm, if you want, I mean.</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">I want a husband who’ll be able to excite me, even when we’re old. Oh, I don’t mean that husband had to be &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; specifically, ~name~. If you didn’t want it to be.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_major">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Soon you’ll get naked, but don’t expect me to be fazed by that. You won’t &lt;i&gt;believe&lt;/i&gt; the diagrams I’ve seen in books.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">~Name~, you can continue to play bad if it’ll give the rest of us a chance to see you revealing yourself!</state>
                <state img="#-cheerful.png">Not only is this game fun, but it doesn’t seem too hard for me. I’ll for sure play more often if I can see guys like ~name~ show off without much work.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-interested.png">Oh man, I didn’t think about how erotic it’d be with us both half naked. Um, nevermind, don’t listen to me.</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">If this view were sake, I’d be guzzling it.</state>
                <state img="#-bluffing.png">There was a scene like this in a &lt;i&gt;shunga&lt;/i&gt; book! Oh, shunga is erotic Japanese art. I, uh, found a book or three of it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">This is just like in my erotic novels! Not that I read that sort of thing!</state>
                <state img="#-greedy.png">I’m excited for the next round, but only if ~name~ loses again!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Even if I don’t walk out of here with a husband tonight, I’m still enjoying the show. Would be nicer with something to drink, though.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-interested.png">~Name~, if we were to get married, how often would you want to do it? Sorry, maybe a strange time to ask.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I know some men prefer women experienced in sexual matters, but think of it this way: if you’re bad at sex I’ll literally never know and have nothing to compare to.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Some people talk about being “good” or ”bad” at sex, but all you’re doing is putting your penis in my vagina. How could you be &lt;i&gt;bad&lt;/i&gt; at that?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_major">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Wow, you’re already taking off your ~clothing~? I must be doing better than I thought. And I thought I was doing pretty good!</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">You &lt;i&gt;finally&lt;/i&gt; took off your ~clothing~. I was waiting forever for you to pony up! …Sorry, I shouldn’t be so pushy.</state>
                <state img="#-blunt.png">Urgh, Outside World women are supposed to be really forward, right? What even am I supposed to say? “Hey, I really hope to see your br—“ nope, can’t do it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-interested.png">Now’s the time when we switch from drinking tea to the stronger stuff.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">H-hey, ~name~… would you be willing to take it off… slowly? Nevermind actually, that’s boring. Just rip it all off.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">W-why am I feeling so flushed? Did I have too much to drink last night?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-cheerful.png">We both know what we were getting into when we signed up for this, ~name~. You would show off your body, and I’d get to see your body.</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">This is further than I’ve ever gotten with a girl before! …Unless you count the dozens of times I’ve gotten naked with groups at the hot springs.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I’m always so stressed out from dealing with youkai and gathering worshippers, I needed a pick-me-up like this. Thanks for thinking of me, ~name~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Winning and losing doesn’t matter. So long as I can get a nice treat like this, I’m happy. Though if I could watch ~name~ &lt;i&gt;and&lt;/i&gt; had a cup of sake, I’d be even happier.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">~Name~, if we were to, say, get married, would you still strip for me sensually? Even after many years?</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">I’m saving myself for my one true love, of course… but there’s no reason I can’t &lt;i&gt;fantasize&lt;/i&gt; before marriage.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_major">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-confused.png">I like your skin, ~name~! D-does that sound creepy? Erm… your skin sure is beautiful? Do you take care of your skin? Can I see &lt;i&gt;more&lt;/i&gt; skin?</state>
                <state img="#-cheerful.png">I thought you were annoying earlier, ~name~, but I’m glad you’re willing to show off. I guess you’re still annoying, but you’re less dressed now.</state>
                <state img="#-bluffing.png">I’ve seen girls in Gensokyo take off as much as &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; during some of our drunken gatherings. You’re going to have to do more to impress me.&lt;br&gt;{small}Though, I’d like to be impressed.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-smug.png">There’s no way I’d be intimidated by a game like this! I’ve read so many steamy novels, I’m basically a sex expert!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I could charge money for this view! Should I charge money for this view? Nah…</state>
                <state img="#-greedy.png">This view’s as good as gold! Pity I can’t actually buy anything with it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Gensokyo’s pretty old-fashioned, so this is already more skin than I’m used to.</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">We’re already both showing off a lot, ~name~. And soon, we’re going to get naked. The thought’s, um, pretty steamy.</state>
                <state img="#-cheerful.png">Ah, now this is a lovely sight! I &lt;i&gt;knew&lt;/i&gt; this was a great way to find an enchanting partner with barely any work on my end!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">In a game like this, would it be disrespectful if I &lt;i&gt;didn’t&lt;/i&gt; ogle ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">Just like I was imagining it in my head when I was fantasizing last night.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I don’t think I could easily get tired of a view like this. Does that make ~name~ good marriage material?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-bluffing.png" oneShotId="217">Seeing a guy’s chest doesn’t mean anything, you know. I’ll just be looking over here and stealing glances at you out of the corner of my eye for unrelated reasons.</state>
                <state img="#-bluffing.png" oneShotId="218">Guys like showing off their chest. I guess because it’s not something you normally see, while still acceptable to reveal in the right circumstances. I’m not impressed, but I’ll watch ~name~, of course.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" oneShotId="219">Oh, was I staring? It’s just… if you do decide to make me your bride, I want to make sure you’re healthy and eating properly. That’s all.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="220">Men’s chests aren’t &lt;i&gt;super&lt;/i&gt; exciting, since they aren’t exactly taboo, you know? I’m going to be checking out ~name~ regardless, but I’ll be disappointed if we don’t see more.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-forfeit-A.png" oneShotId="225">I’m going to rub it to your chest, ~name~. Hope you don’t mind.</state>
                <state img="#-forfeit-B.png" oneShotId="226">Even I’ve seen guy’s chests before. I suppose I’ll still have to use my fantasies… unless you wanted to take off something more?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" oneShotId="213">It’s not embarrassing for guys to show off their chests, unlike girls. How unfair… Um, it’s not like I &lt;i&gt;want&lt;/i&gt; to show off my chest, though!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="214">Are you wearing anything under ~clothing.ifPlural(those|that)~ ~clothing~? So we’re going to be seeing some skin from ~name~… but it’s not exactly &lt;i&gt;nudity&lt;/i&gt;, you know?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="209">Stand up straight, ~name~, when you’ve taken off your ~clothing~. I want to see if my maybe potential future hubby is taking proper care of himself.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" oneShotId="210">I’ve seen guys without shirts before, but never when I’m as underdressed as I am now. It, uh, feels a lot different watching you like this.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" oneShotId="229">I wouldn’t mind if my future husband did work around the shrine without his shirt… but I’d want him to put it back on if any other women came around. Otherwise I might get jealous!</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="230">You’ve already seen more of me than any man before, ~name~, so don’t say a word if I want to take a good long look at you!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-3" id="47">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-blunt.png" oneShotId="97">Well, it’s not a remarkable chest, but presumably it holds your ribcage together, so hooray?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5" id="48">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-cheerful.png">Well, you look decent enough, ~name~. I’m sure there’s someone out there who will like you. Just gotta keep at it!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7" id="50">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-interested.png" oneShotId="99">Heeey, nice chest, ~name~! You’ll make whatever cute girl who marries you very happy one day!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="49">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-interested.png">I’m sure your future wife would love to stroke your chest… as she feels herself… intimately.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9" id="51">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-cheerful.png">You’re looking good, ~player~. And I’m finished being horny, so you know I’m telling the unvarnished truth!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" priority="0">
                <condition filter="chubby" role="target" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="237">You’re a bit chubby, ~name~… but that just means you’re well fed, right? And you’ll make sure &lt;i&gt;I’m&lt;/i&gt; well fed once we get married, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" priority="0">
                <condition filter="muscular" role="target" />
                <state img="#-cheerful.png" oneShotId="239">Woah… you take &lt;i&gt;good&lt;/i&gt; care of your body, ~name~. That must mean you’re a hard worker— all the better to take care of your delicate wife.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" oneShotId="243">I’ve seen guys’ chests before, of course. But things are &lt;i&gt;steamier&lt;/i&gt; here…</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png" oneShotId="252">It’s a nice chest. It’s not the most tantalizing of male body parts, but I like checking it out.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" priority="0">
                <condition filter="skinny" role="target" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="241">You’re kinda scrawny, ~name~. Could it be you don’t know how to properly prepare meals for yourself? Just leave it to me, I know my way around a kitchen!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="233">All right, we’ve all appreciated it. Let’s hurry up and move on.&lt;br&gt;{small}~Name~ needs to lose some more for me.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="234">You look good, ~name~, be proud. But seeing your chest makes me want to peek at more. A lot more. Get busy losing.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-interested.png" oneShotId="246">I-it’s nice that I don’t have to hide my desire in a game like this. We’re all, uh, “horny on the main street”.</state>
                <state img="#-cheerful.png" oneShotId="247">You look great, ~name~! Or maybe that’s just the hormones talking. It’s possible you look bad, but I’m too turned on by the game to notice.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-bluffing.png" oneShotId="259">&lt;i&gt;Mmmmm!&lt;/i&gt; Oh! that wasn’t a satisfied moan. That, was, um… a hiccup! Yeah!</state>
                <state img="#-forfeit-A.png" oneShotId="260">I know beggars can’t be choosers… but do you mind showing off a bit? Juuuuust a chest by itself won’t really— &lt;i&gt;ah—&lt;/i&gt; push the needle for me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="255">Better late than never, but would’ve made by job a bit easier if I had seen that when I was &lt;i&gt;“busy”&lt;/i&gt; earlier.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="256">I would complain about not seeing it earlier, but it’s not so spectacular a chest that I’d &lt;i&gt;need&lt;/i&gt; it for… inspiration. I’m just staring at it now to get my money’s worth, is all.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-9" oneShotId="4" priority="0">
                <condition count="0" gender="male" status="crotch_visible" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="ReimuBookPenis">I’ve seen plenty of these in books, nothing you’ve got’s gonna phase me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" oneShotId="267">Oh… he’s removing &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt;. I guess we’re going to see his piece then. His manhood. His rod. Twig and berries? Pork sword?&lt;br&gt;{small}Erm, I’m getting silly.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="268">I’ve seen that sort of art of men, you know. But I’m sure it always exaggerates the sizes of things. That’s why I’m preparing myself for disappointment.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png" oneShotId="269">You better properly show us your penis. No hiding it behind your hands!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="273">Because I need my pure shrine maiden reputation, I could never see a village man like this. Youkai don’t care about that sort of thing, but getting with one of them is even worse.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="274">Hurry up and get out your rod, ~name~, I wanna see it! Oh, I mean, I don’t want to pressure you for it or anything.&lt;br&gt;{small}I still want to see it, though.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-interested.png" oneShotId="277">You’re not wearing anything under your ~clothing~. So we’ll see it… Oh, sorry, ~name~. I’m just getting a little excited.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="278">I don’t expect it to be all rotted and mangled, or anything like that. Still, doesn’t hurt to make sure everything works down there. If you wanted to become my future husband, that is.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-interested.png" oneShotId="286">&lt;i&gt;Ah—&lt;/i&gt; …I should slow down. Okay, ~name~, you can reveal it &lt;i&gt;slowly.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="287">Make sure it’s a good one. &lt;i&gt;For me.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="393">Oh, are we gonna see— I’m not gonna ogle, but I will stare appreciatively.</state>
                <state img="#-cheerful.png" oneShotId="394">I was fantasizing about it earlier, so I’m curious how the real thing compares. Hope it’s not terrible.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_small_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="378">I think it looks pretty, ~name~. I know the way people are drawn in those &lt;i&gt;shunga&lt;/i&gt; sex art books isn’t realistic to real life.</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png" oneShotId="379">That’s not scary at all! I won’t need to worry about it hurting if it’s just that size.</state>
                <state img="#-pleasant.png" oneShotId="380">I think yours looks nice, ~name~! I was worried after seeing pictures of gigantic ones, but I think yours will do the job just fine!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="290">That’s fine! It doesn’t matter how big you are, if you’re able to take care of me. Just buy me plenty of nice gifts and learn how to please me in… other ways!</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png" oneShotId="291">I really don’t know if that’s good or bad. I don’t have much to compare it to. Though, I have a hard time imagining something like that could be &lt;i&gt;bad&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-cheerful.png" oneShotId="302">It’s kinda… cute. Not as intimidating as I was expecting, but I don’t mind at all. I think it’ll do just fine!</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png" oneShotId="303">I think yours will do just fine, ~name~. And when you get married, you can practice how to use it best.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="298">Everything looks pretty good to me right now… Show it off more, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="299">A shoddy carpenter blames their tools. You could do plenty with that tool. You just gotta… practice.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="294">Not how I was imagining it a moment ago, but I think it still looks nice in its own way. I’d like to see it in action too.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="295">I like how it looks, ~name~. I’d be happy with a husband who looks like that!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_medium_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" oneShotId="312">I saw pictures in a book, but the real thing is a lot more… three dimensional.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="313">Ehe, the real thing is a &lt;i&gt;biiiiit&lt;/i&gt; different from the books… but yours looks nice, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-cheerful.png" oneShotId="314">I haven’t exactly seen many in my life, but my instincts tell me you’ve got a nice looking one, ~name~.&lt;br&gt;{small}Now lose more so I can see it in action.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-bluffing.png" oneShotId="308">It’s fine… I guess. What? I don’t see any reason to be blown away by a bit of flesh. I’ll keep an eye on ~name~ though, to make sure he doesn’t get up to any funny business!</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png" oneShotId="309">&lt;i&gt;Hahaha!&lt;/i&gt; Oh, sorry ~name~. It’s just, um, I was worried it’d be this great, hulking thing. It actually looks… normal. But I guess it’d feel good to… use.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-bluffing.png" oneShotId="320">Oh, it’s… it’s nothing that would phase me at all… Anyway, um, ~name~… you do know how to be gentle during love making… right?</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" oneShotId="332">Huh, it’s not a big scary thing. It actually looks kinda… nice. I wouldn’t mind it. Um, g-going inside of me, I mean.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-interested.png" oneShotId="328">So if you pushed that… into me… we’d both feel really good. I can’t way to try that with my future husband.</state>
                <state img="#-forfeit-A.png" oneShotId="329">So that thing… can give you the greatest pleasure. How would it feel… to enter me?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-cheerful.png" oneShotId="338">I’m a little spent now, but it sure is a good, um, &lt;i&gt;“piece”&lt;/i&gt;. I’ll file it away in my mind for next time.</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png" oneShotId="339">Pity you didn’t show that off earlier, ~name~. I’m a &lt;i&gt;little&lt;/i&gt; turned on again, but I’m too tired to go twice tonight.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_large_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-9" id="53" oneShotId="6">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" weight="0.2">Yeah, I’m so sure.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="52">
                <state img="#-bluffing.png" oneShotId="353">Th-that’s nothing at all.</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png" oneShotId="354">Woah, that’s big! Wait, &lt;i&gt;~name~&lt;/i&gt; had a big one? Never would have guessed.</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png" oneShotId="355">I figured most of those art books I found were exaggerating how big men were, but I guess not. Still, it’s not so intimidating for someone like me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-bluffing.png" oneShotId="348">W-would that even fit…? I mean, obviously I’d want to be intimate with my husband, but if his was that size… of course it stretches…&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;Urk!&lt;/i&gt; I’m not fantasizing!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="347">That’s sizable. Would it take effort to get it into me when it’s all hard? I don’t want to put effort into lovemaking, so smaller might be better for me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" oneShotId="374">The books I read talk about large ones, but seeing it in real life… you’d be gentle, right ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png" oneShotId="375">I’d want to do it with my husband, but would I be able to handle one that big? If not, would I be a bad wife?&lt;br&gt;…Eh, I’m sure I’ll be fine. I’ve beaten worse challenges than that!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-interested.png" oneShotId="364">It’s not about the tool, it’s how you use it. &lt;i&gt;If&lt;/i&gt; you got married… would you be sure to give your wife the &lt;i&gt;best pleasure&lt;/i&gt;?</state>
                <state img="#-forfeit-B.png" oneShotId="365">I’m so wet… even though that’s so big… I think it’d be able to slide in easily. &lt;i&gt;Umf!&lt;/i&gt; I wonder how deep it’d go?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-bluffing.png" oneShotId="368">&lt;i&gt;Mmmmm…&lt;/i&gt; It’s tempting, but I’m too spent to try going again.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" oneShotId="369">Hmph. You were keeping that hidden away from me, even though I could’ve used it when I was going earlier? My future husband would never be so cruel.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-4" id="77">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="173">Ugh, already? You didn’t have to play this game if you just wanted to show it off to me, you could’ve just walked up to the shrine.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5" id="76">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">Well, I’m sure you like playing with it a lot, right? That’s… good. I’m glad you can enjoy it… or whatever…</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7" id="78">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-bluffing.png">Um… I think it looks good… and I’m sure the rest here do too! W-well, don’t think about it! You’re still in this game, so it’d suck to falter now!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="75">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-interested.png">Do you mind if I… do it… while thinking of your stuff?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9" id="74">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-confident.png">Bah, coulda used that earlier. Well, too late now. Anyway, ~name~, you better win, or I’ll look like an idiot for siding with you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" oneShotId="5">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="ReimuBookPenis" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Ahhh! This is nothing like in the books!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-bluffing.png" oneShotId="400">I’ve seen how different everyone’s breasts can be when we’re in the hot springs. Don’t get me wrong, I’m not a perv! It’s just something I notice.</state>
                <state img="#-cheerful.png" oneShotId="401">Boys seem to make a lot of fuss over big boobs, or small boobs, or whatever. I think as long as it’s part of a cute girl, any size looks great!</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png" oneShotId="402">Now we’ll see &lt;i&gt;juuuust&lt;/i&gt; how into the game ~name~ is. Or if it’s cold in here. Either one.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="414">Don’t cover up right away, ~name~! I want to get a good look at ‘em!</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png" oneShotId="415">Please and thank you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="396">I wonder if ~name~ pads her chest.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" oneShotId="397">Gensokyo girls would never show off their breasts like this! Well, there was Sanae that one time, but she was pretty hammered.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-cheerful.png" oneShotId="410">Breasts all look pretty different… but I think they all look nice. Can we get a look at yours, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png" oneShotId="411">You don’t have to be afraid of showing yourself off to me. I’m a pure shrine maiden, after all.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="406">It was embarrassing to show mine at first, but after everything &lt;i&gt;I’ve&lt;/i&gt; shown off, you’ve got no reason to hold back. Also I want to see them.</state>
                <state img="#-bluffing.png" oneShotId="407">I wouldn’t touch ~name~’s chest before we were married, no matter how supple her breasts looked. I will sneak a few peeks, though.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_small_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-cheerful.png" oneShotId="430">The perfect size for a true Japanese lady.</state>
                <state img="#-pleasant.png" oneShotId="431">You’re about the same size as me. I like myself just fine, so you should feel good about yourself too.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="432">A modest chest. But it fits you, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="426">You look good, ~name~. Who needs fat, saggy mom boobs, right?</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" oneShotId="427">My sarashi doesn’t compress my chest that much… I’m about that size is what I’m trying to say. Well, I think I’m nice looking too.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-cheerful.png" oneShotId="422">Small breasts look great, and I bet those are super sensitive!</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png" oneShotId="423">Those are more than enough for any wife of mine!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-forfeit-A.png" oneShotId="418">Can you squeeze them for me, ~name~? I just want to watch…</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" oneShotId="419">Beautiful. You could get right up close to me, and…</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="436">I read in a book small breasts are more sensitive. Though, I’ve never had anyone else play with mine. Have you?</state>
                <state img="#-cheerful.png" oneShotId="437">Even if it’s not much, I’m still glad we got to see ~name~’s petite chest before the game was over!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_medium_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" oneShotId="458">Your breasts look nice, ~name~. That’s not too forward, is it? Or is it better to be forward, in this situation?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="459">Am I a “breast lady” if I think all sizes are good? Well, whatever. I like &lt;i&gt;yours&lt;/i&gt;, ~name~. That’s what matters.</state>
                <state img="#-cheerful.png" oneShotId="460">I don’t really get it, but I feel those are the perfect size for “~name~ breasts”.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="454">This is so exciting! What? It’s not like you outside world people would have a magic box that shows you an unlimited number of these! …Right?</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png" oneShotId="455">Breasts are fine and all, but what I really look for in a woman is her heart. Those breasts are great, though.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" oneShotId="450">W-wow… those would fill both my hands. I wonder how it’d feel?</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png" oneShotId="451">I could imagine being married to a lady with a chest that beautiful. I can imagine a lot of things about that chest.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-forfeit-B.png" oneShotId="444">Cup them for me, ~name~…</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png" oneShotId="445">So beautiful. What would those nipples feel like against my lips?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-bluffing.png" oneShotId="440">I don’t have a &lt;i&gt;fetish&lt;/i&gt; for it or anything, but it &lt;i&gt;is&lt;/i&gt; interesting to see how different everyone’s look. They’re all so lovely.</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png" oneShotId="441">There’s no comparison between the real thing and my fantasies after all. If I wasn’t so exhausted I’d go again.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_large_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-confident.png" oneShotId="476">Don’t get cocky, ~name~! I bet if we felt each other up, I’d be &lt;i&gt;way&lt;/i&gt; more sensitive!</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" oneShotId="477">C-can I feel those? No, nevermind, that’d be way too embarrassing! B-but, I am curious…&lt;br&gt;{small}and maybe a &lt;i&gt;teensy&lt;/i&gt; bit aroused.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="478">They look so big! And malleable. I’d need two hands.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="472">Sure is nice being able to sleep on my stomach.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="473">I dunno if I want a wife with large breasts. What would people say about me? Probably all the things I say about those women in Gensokyo with big tits wives.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" oneShotId="468">W-wow, they’re really big! Okay, if we ever have a kid together, you have to breastfeed.</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png" oneShotId="469">If we got married, I’d need to develop a fetish for manhandling large breasts! Well, can’t let that stop true love.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-forfeit-A.png" oneShotId="464">So big. So good. Just let me feel one. Half of one even.</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png" oneShotId="465">Ahhhhh… gorgeous. Don’t mind… my fingers…</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-interested.png" oneShotId="482">Those are bigger than mine, meaning they got more fat on ‘em. I bet they’re super soft to feel.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="483">Those would be lovely to rest my head on after a long hard day at work. You pass, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-3" id="54">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="103">They look… fine? I’m honestly not a breasts woman, so I can’t give better feedback than that. Do you even want feedback?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5" id="55">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-cheerful.png">They look good, ~player~. Like, good enough to feed a baby? I dunno if that’s what you want, but that’s what they’re there for.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7" id="57">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-interested.png" oneShotId="106">Keep your chin up, ~player~! With boobs that nice looking, you’ll have no problem finding someone who will want you!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="56">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-interested.png">N-nice… those will be nice for your future wife… to fondle… as you bring each other to finish, ~player~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9" id="58">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-cheerful.png">Ahhhh, I’m spent. I’m rooting for you, but I wouldn’t have minded seeing those earlier.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-interested.png" oneShotId="498">It’s nothing I haven’t seen before… just nothing I’ve seen before in a super sexual context.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" oneShotId="499">Oh, are you showing off your— I mean of course you are, it’s this sort of game. I’ll just… ogle.</state>
                <state img="#-bluffing.png" oneShotId="500">Everyone’s looks different, right? Not that I’ve been sneaking glances, it just stands to reason.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="494">I want you to know I’m fairly hairy myself, so don’t worry about what yours looks like! Er, I don’t know why I thought that’d be encouraging.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" oneShotId="495">Youkai don’t mind, um, sleeping around, but for me this is a little embarrassing. The others would probably make fun of me for blushing like this.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-cheerful.png" oneShotId="486">I don’t know what I’ve been doing to get this far, but we’re all going to see ~name~ lose her bloomers!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="487">All my hard work has finally led me to ~name~’s holy of holies. I deserve a treat!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-shocked.png" oneShotId="504">Oh! ~Name~’s about to show her— oh!</state>
                <state img="#-forfeit-A.png" oneShotId="505">Let me see it properly… please.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-cheerful.png" oneShotId="490">~Name~ is cute, so I’m sure &lt;i&gt;all&lt;/i&gt; parts of her are cute too!</state>
                <state img="#-bluffing.png" oneShotId="491">I didn’t get a chance to, uh, peek at ~name~’s when I was busy earlier… but I’m glad I still got to see it in the end.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-3" id="83">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-blunt.png">Couldn’t wait to show it off, huh, ~name~? It’s not like I’ve never seen one of those.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5" id="81">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-cheerful.png">Yours looks great, ~name~! Hmm, is that not good enough wing-womaning? &lt;i&gt;Ahem…&lt;/i&gt; I’d love to rub your glistening womanhood, ~name~!&lt;br&gt;{small}Nailed it!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7" id="80">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-bluffing.png">Well, you kinda suck if you’re showing it off already, but… it looks nice. I’m glad I, uh, saw it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="79">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-interested.png">I hope… that feels as good to touch… as mine does.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9" id="82">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-angry.png">Don’t lose now, ~name~! I got beaten, and can’t rub myself to your parts now, you there’s no reason for you to do anything but &lt;i&gt;win&lt;/i&gt;!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" oneShotId="31">
                <condition filter="hairy" role="target" />
                <alternative>
                    <condition filter="shaved" status="crotch_visible" role="other" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <condition filter="trimmed" status="crotch_visible" role="other" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-pleasant.png">Oh, it’s just like mine! Ehehe, sorry if that sounded weird, ~name~. I was worried for a bit that mine was no good. But it’s everyone else who’s strange!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition filter="hairy" role="target" />
                <state img="#-bluffing.png" oneShotId="528">It’s just like I imagined it… not that I was imagining anything! Okay, yeah I was.</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png" oneShotId="529">It looks very mature. Like those I see in &lt;i&gt;shunga&lt;/i&gt; erotic art books. I wonder what else is like those books…</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="530">Hehe, I was nervous at first, but yours looks like one should, ~name~. Like how I imagine my wife would look.</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png" oneShotId="531">I-if my wife looked like that, I wouldn’t mind running my fingers through her hair. When we were getting intimate, that is.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-smug.png">You’re glistening, ~name~. Does that mean you’re turned on too? I’m excited to see what else you can show off.</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">…Nice womanhood, girl? I-is that an acceptable way to complement a lady?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" priority="0">
                <condition filter="shaved" role="target" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="536">Are you not able to grow any? S-sorry, maybe it’s not something you like to talk about. It’s just, I’ve had hair for a while now, so…</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" oneShotId="537">Did you shave it or something? Wh-why, it’s not like anyone’s gonna see it… wait, we’re seeing it now! Was I expected to cut mine off!?</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="538">Oh, uh, I don’t mean to stare, it’s just… before this game, I hadn’t seen very many without, um… hair.</state>
                <state img="#-dismissive.png" oneShotId="539">Seems like a lot of effort just for your private parts… how often do you show that off to other people?</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="540">Did you shave off all your hair down there? That sounds like effort. I sure hope my future spouse doesn’t expect me to put in that amount of work in for just my privates.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" oneShotId="93" priority="0">
                <condition filter="shaved" role="target" />
                <condition count="1" filter="shaved" status="crotch_visible" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png">There’s no hair— I read in books that’s how p-prostitutes do it. I mean, I guess should have expected that sort of clientele here, but it’s still a shock!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-blunt.png" oneShotId="520">So that’s your coochie, huh? Your love muffin? …There’s no way to make it sound sexy, huh, so why even try?</state>
                <state img="#-bluffing.png" oneShotId="521">N-now that ~name~ is exposed, I don’t have to care a whit when it’s my turn to get naked.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-interested.png" oneShotId="516">I’ve never looked &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; close at another girl’s— at another girl. Yours is very pretty, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" oneShotId="517">It’s embarrassing to say aloud but… yours is very nice looking, ~name~. Th-thanks for showing it off…</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-interested.png" oneShotId="512">&lt;i&gt;Ooooooooh…&lt;/i&gt; it’s beautiful.</state>
                <state img="#-forfeit-A.png" oneShotId="513">Your… your clitoris. How would something so hard feel against my tongue?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-bluffing.png" oneShotId="508">It looks pretty, ~name~. I hope to see how you pleasure yourself later! Er, only because it’s good to know if we ever get married.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="509">Don’t bother hiding it, we all know how turned on you must be from me fiddling with myself earlier.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" priority="0">
                <condition filter="trimmed" role="target" />
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" oneShotId="546">Looks fine, I suppose. But does it matter if it’s not as hairy as mi— some other people’s?</state>
                <state img="#-dismissive.png" oneShotId="547">Did you trim your hairs? Feels like a lot of work for something that’ll just grow back.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="548">Do I want to marry a woman who trims like that? I hope she wouldn’t expect me to put out the same level of effort into my appearance.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_lost">
            <case stage="0-9" id="63" oneShotId="45" priority="502">
                <condition filter="gay" gender="male" role="target" character="human" />
                <condition role="self" notSaidMarker="ReimuPlayer1" />
                <state img="#-blunt.png" marker="ReimuPlayer1" dialogue-layer="over">~Player~, you’re totally gay, right? And I’m a girl, right? Look, obviously you wouldn’t be interested in me, so you’d better help wingman me with one of the others here. It’s the least you could do after stealing a spot from an eligible bachelor!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="61" oneShotId="46" priority="502">
                <condition filter="straight" gender="female" role="target" character="human" />
                <condition role="self" notSaidMarker="ReimuPlayer1" />
                <state img="#-blunt.png" marker="ReimuPlayer1" dialogue-layer="over">Hey, ~player~, you’re, uh, &lt;i&gt;straight&lt;/i&gt;, right? Not that there’s anything wrong with that, but why didja pick me for your table? I’m trying to find people who are into me, so can you at least help me out with that?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="62" oneShotId="44" priority="501">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <condition role="self" notSaidMarker="ReimuPlayer1" />
                <state img="#-blunt.png" marker="ReimuPlayer1">What’s with you, ~player~? You don’t look rich, or powerful, or even like you own your own sake brewery!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" id="86">
                <condition status="lost_all" role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Already? Do you just suck, or… Well, have fun.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5" id="87">
                <condition status="lost_all" role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">Aw, I was hoping we could tag team a bit more. I guess in the end, you couldn’t find your destined partner tonight.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7" id="85">
                <condition status="lost_all" role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">W-well, you did your best. I had hoped you’d be able to find your spouse, like I surely will, but… well, I’ll enjoy watching you… at least?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="84">
                <condition status="lost_all" role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-bluffing.png">Oh, too bad… not that I care. But, I’ll enjoy having fun with you, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9" id="88">
                <condition status="lost_all" role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">Awww… that’s disappointing.&lt;br&gt;{small}Why am I disappointed?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="65" oneShotId="48">
                <condition role="target" character="human" consecutiveLosses="3-" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">Wow, uh, you don’t actually know how to play this game, do you ~player~? I kinda feel sorry for you. Look, I won’t blame you if you just want to give up and leave.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" id="67">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="44">Who’s up this round? Oh, ~player~? Well, better you than me.</state>
                <state img="#-blunt.png" oneShotId="42">~Player~’s going? Well, get a move on. There’s a bunch of people here and I want to see them all naked.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="43" weight="3">~Player~, since you’re obviously not fantastically wealthy or powerful yourself, are you out to score a ~human.ifMale(groom|bride)~ of your own? Maybe we can tag team or something.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5" id="64">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-cheerful.png" oneShotId="54">Ehe~! Come on, ~player~, you can do better than that! Remember, we just need the other poor sods to lose.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png" oneShotId="55" weight="2">Give me a break, ~player~! We’re fellow poor, lonely hearts. You have to put up a good showing, the honor of both of us is at stake!</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" oneShotId="56">You lost, ~player~! What, were you too preoccupied thinking about what was under my sarashi and bloomers? Perv.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7" id="60">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="48">Ehh, what are you doing, losing this late in the game? Come on, ~player~, aren’t you here to find your destined loved one too?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="49">You’ll never impress your beloved if you give up now, ~player~! We’re both poor and lonely, so you need to impress me too!</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png" oneShotId="50">Fine, ~player~, strip off something good, and show off a little. But now’s not the time to relax! You’ve almost got me beat, you better not fold now!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="59">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="60">Come on… Now’s not the time for collapse! Anyway, feel free to take off something big.</state>
                <state img="#-forfeit-A.png" oneShotId="61">Was I distracting you… well, too bad. I’ve got to enjoy myself, to hopefully catch the eye of my future paramour. You should do the same.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9" id="66">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-confident.png" oneShotId="64">I’m too spent to care… Just &lt;i&gt;win&lt;/i&gt;, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png" oneShotId="65">You beat me long ago, already. I won’t forgive you if you fall &lt;i&gt;now&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="34" oneShotId="2" priority="0">
                <condition filter="chef" status="decent" role="target" />
                <state img="#-pleasant.png" weight="3">Are you a chef, ~name~? My buddy Marisa is a terrible cook, always grills everything to a crisp. It’s the best way to burn the poison out of the mushrooms she subsists on.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="39" oneShotId="3" priority="0">
                <condition filter="enf" status="decent" role="target" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" weight="3">You up for stripping, ~name~? I won’t force you. I learned from Sanae that’s called “beer pressure” and it’s bad.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="40" oneShotId="10" priority="0">
                <condition filter="drunk" status="decent" role="target" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" weight="3">You remind me of Suika, ~name~, she’s drunk out of her gourd all the time too. Literally, she’s an oni, she’s always drunk, and she drinks out of a magic sake gourd.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="35" oneShotId="11" priority="0">
                <condition filter="drill_hair" status="decent" role="target" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" weight="3">I know a little fairy girl with drill hair. Not that a place like this would be appropriate for a fairy.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="44" oneShotId="12" priority="0">
                <condition filter="heterochromia" status="decent" role="target" />
                <condition count="0" character="yukari" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" weight="3">You remind me of that cheery forgotten umbrella youkai, Kogasa. She has eyes like yours, ~name~. I should put in an order with her for more needles.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="43" oneShotId="13" priority="0">
                <condition filter="muscular" gender="female" status="decent" role="target" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" weight="3">You’re pretty beefy, ~name~. Reminds me of that oni of the underground, Yuugi. If being strong enough to bench press a mountain wasn’t enough, she’s always drunk, too.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="33" oneShotId="14" priority="0">
                <condition filter="alien" status="decent" role="target" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" weight="3">You’re not a human, huh ~name~? You remind me of that annoying Nue. Sent a bunch of Undefined Fantastic Objects at us one time.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="36" oneShotId="15" priority="0">
                <condition filter="elf" status="decent" role="target" />
                <state img="#-blunt.png" weight="3">I can tell from your aura you’re not a human, ~name~. I’m not sure what species of youkai you are, but I’m only interested in marrying a human, thanks. Well, for the most part.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="37" oneShotId="16" priority="0">
                <condition filter="fairy" status="decent" role="target" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" weight="3">W-wait, are you a &lt;i&gt;fairy&lt;/i&gt;, ~name~? I’ve never seen a fairy who looked so… adult before. Kinda weirds me out, to be honest.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="42" oneShotId="17" priority="0">
                <condition filter="glasses" status="decent" role="target" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" weight="3">Do you need glasses because you stayed up too late reading books, ~name~? I hope I won’t need glasses myself some day.</state>
                <state img="#-blunt.png" weight="3">You wear glasses, ~name~? So does the Tanuki Boss, Mamizou. But she’s an old biddy.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="38" oneShotId="18" priority="0">
                <condition filter="clown" status="decent" role="target" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" weight="3">…I’ve had bad times with a clown before, ~name~. Her name was Clownpiece, she was a fairy of Hell who threw the moon at me. At least you’re not dressed in the stars and stripes.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="41" oneShotId="19" priority="0">
                <condition filter="prince" status="decent" role="target" />
                <condition count="0" role="target" character="miko" />
                <state img="#-cheerful.png" weight="3">You’re a prince, right ~name~? That means you can take me as your bride and pay off my pub tab for me!&lt;br&gt;{small}Glad you’re not like the last prince I met…</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" priority="0">
                <condition role="self" hasHand="High Card" />
                <state img="#-dismissive.png" oneShotId="4" weight="0.5">Whoa, I thought I was gonna lose for sure! Is ~name~ trying to court me by losing on purpose?</state>
                <state img="#-pleasant.png" oneShotId="3" weight="0.5">Oh good. ~Name~ is even worse at this dumb game than me. Or more unlucky, whatever.</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png" oneShotId="208" weight="0.5">I didn’t lose, ~name~ did? I’d already accepted defeat. ~Name~, is playing this bad your way of flirting?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="45" oneShotId="36" priority="0">
                <condition filter="demon" status="decent" role="target" />
                <state img="#-serious.png">Do you think you’re tough, ~name~, being a demon and all? I’ve put the God of Makai in her place, and I won’t hesitate to do the same to you if you cause trouble.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" oneShotId="43" priority="0">
                <condition status="not_decent" role="target" />
                <state img="#-angry.png">My future ~target.ifMale(husband|wife)~ can’t be playing this badly! That’s it, I want a divorce!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="90" oneShotId="52" priority="0">
                <condition filter="bisexual" status="decent" role="target" />
                <state img="#-pleasant.png">Unlike Gensokyo’s humans, people in the outside world seem comfortable, um, swinging both ways. Maybe I’m too used to youkai, they don’t seem to care much about gender.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">You seem pretty comfortable, uh, romancing both men and women, ~name~. I am too! Most other humans in Gensokyo are pretty old fashioned, though.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="91" oneShotId="53" priority="0">
                <condition filter="bald" gender="male" status="decent" role="target" />
                <state img="#-blunt.png">Are you a monk, ~name~? Did you shave your head as part of your ascetic training? …Or are you just bald?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="92" oneShotId="54" priority="0">
                <condition filter="bald" gender="female" status="decent" role="target" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">You must be a monk of some sort, ~name~. I’ve never seen a woman with a shaven head except in pictures of buddhist trainees. Even the nuns in Gensokyo keep their hair.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="93" oneShotId="55" priority="0">
                <condition filter="animal_ears" status="decent" role="target" />
                <state img="#-blunt.png">…~Name~’s ears are twitching. I’ve met enough beast youkai in Gensokyo to tell what ~target.ifMale(he|she)~ is thinking most of the time.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_stripping">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="jura" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" marker="JuraRapier2">O-okay, Jura. Let’s say I happened to want a girlfriend of my own. How would I go about getting one?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="miko" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="MikoCape2">Oh! You’re that thunder spirit! Miko’s consort from the Soga clan or whatever.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="meia" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="MeiaEyepiece2">We’re the same age, but you’re in charge of your own squad. Plus you have such an air of maturity. You must be a real hard worker!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="zoe" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="ZoeShoes2">Fandom? I have some fans at home, but it hasn’t been hot enough to use them recently.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="fina" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="FinaBoots2">Was there anyone else at at the Great Silver Shrine? Gensokyo is separated from the outside world, but at least people from within still visit my shrine… sometimes.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="jim" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-extermination.png" marker="JimGloves2">I don’t sense that you’re cursed, but you’ve got a mean looking face! You have to be planning to eat me bones and all with an appearance like that!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="yuri" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="YuriShoes2">I try to figure out who did it, but I’m not very good at it. Usually I end up fingering everyone at some point, and in the end I still wasn’t right.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="hu_tao" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-serious.png" marker="HuTaoShoes2">I guess carrying around ghosts would explain it. Though I haven’t met an undertaker so enthusiastic about their work before.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="ignatz" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png" marker="IgnatzShoes2">Wait, your family has a trading company? I mean— I love art! What do you like to paint? Landscapes? Still lifes? &lt;i&gt;Pretty girls?&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="critical_darling" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="CriticalDarlingGloves2">“Alternative metal”? Plenty of instruments are made out of metal, but I don’t know of a good alternative to the material. Why can’t you just play regular instruments?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="noelle" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="NoelleArmor2">So there’s no one person you serve, you’re the maid for a whole country? All the maids and servants I know are slavishly devoted to some mistress.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="nami" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="NamiBelt2">I suppose there are youkai of the sea as well. But it can’t be &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; scary, since I’ve seen some cute sea creatures too. So, anyway, what does your crew do?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="remilia" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-extermination.png" marker="RemiliaHat2">Whatever, could you just leave? That is, I want you to leave this world. I don’t need you getting in my way tonight.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="remilia" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" marker="RemiliaShoes2">Maybe Patchy never told you how the birds and the bees work Remi, but humans need to do this thing called “sex” to make babies. And it feels good to do it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="remilia" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-angry.png" marker="RemiliaSkirt2">But what really makes youkai gross is how promiscuous you all are! You’ll sleep with someone one night and a different person the next! Like animals!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="remilia" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-bluffing.png" marker="RemiliaShirt2">What sort of things feel good? Not like I would ever do something like that with the likes of you, but it might be useful knowledge for my future spouse. I need to know how to be a good wife.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="remilia" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="RemiliaBra2">You know how I need to put myself up on a pedestal so the human village gives me their faith. But I’m not all that close to them. The idea of engaging romantically with any of them is just awkward.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="remilia" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="RemiliaPanties2">Well, it doesn’t matter. The Scarlet Devil Mansion gets blown up often enough anyway. You can just rebuild.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="hu_tao" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="HuTaoSocks2">From the sound of it, you’re something like a youkai exterminator? Just, one that focuses on restless spirits specifically.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="hu_tao" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="HuTaoCoat2">I can understand carrying on the family business. Youkai extermination is the trade of the Hakurei clan for as long as there have been gods in the land.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="hu_tao" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-cheerful.png" marker="HuTaoShirt2">Ehehe, that makes me happy to hear. I’m glad you think so highly of me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="hu_tao" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-bluffing.png" marker="HuTaoShorts2">You’ll have to take the lead on… things. It’ll be fine so long as you’re gentle, but don’t judge me if I’m bad at it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="hu_tao" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" marker="HuTaoHat2">I’m not disappointed you’re not… out yet, it just seemed odd, is all! Not that I &lt;i&gt;don’t&lt;/i&gt; want to see you, it’s just— &lt;i&gt;ugh!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="hatsune_miku" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" marker="MikuTie2">So you’re like a shikigami? A familiar of some powerful sorcerer? This “computer” artifact sounds fearsome indeed if it can let people control you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="syrenne" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" marker="SyrenneTop2">For the coin, huh? Sadly, it’s the &lt;i&gt;duty&lt;/i&gt; of the Hakurei Shrine maiden to exterminate youkai… meaning I’m always short on coin. Despite all I do, people never show appreciation and donate to the shrine.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="fluttershy" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-extermination.png" marker="FluttershySleeves2">Something about you reminds me of an &lt;i&gt;umatsuki&lt;/i&gt;, a horse youkai I once exterminated. I don’t show mercy to youkai who try to trick me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="barbara" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" marker="BarbaraHat2">Oh great god of the Hakurei Shrine… I don’t know your name… or what blessings you bestow. But I’m sure they’re very good!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="samus_aran" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-dismissive.png" marker="SamusPowerArmor2">Youkai are youkai. Annoying creatures who act only on selfish desire. They’re the enemy of humans, so I exterminate them whenever they cause trouble.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="ms.fortune" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" marker="FortuneLegWarmers2">What, are you saying somebody actually owns a mangy bakeneko like you? You look like a stray! The kitties that hang out at my shrine are much prettier.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="tomoko" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="TomokoTie2">Hold on… on closer inspection, I don’t detect any Youkai aura from you. Are you just a sad sack instead?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="barbara" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="BarbaraShoes2">I’ve always thought religionists have to be something of performers to be successful, but you really go above and beyond. Does being a singing, dancing nun actually bring in worshippers?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="fina" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-pleasant.png" marker="FinaHeaddress2">So you gave up the shrine maiden life for good? Nice as it must feel to be free, people still gotta eat. What do you do now to make ends meet?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8" oneShotId="8" priority="0">
                <condition status="not_finished" role="target" />
                <condition count="2-" status="exposed" />
                <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="extra" />
                <state img="#-blunt.png" weight="0.2">I’m too horny for this.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_stripped">
            <case stage="0-9" id="73" oneShotId="47" priority="501">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="ReimuPlayer1" notSaidMarker="ReimuPlayer2" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" marker="ReimuPlayer2">I’m looking for a ~human.ifMale(handsome husband|beautiful wife)~ who can take care of me, so try not to get in my way, okay?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="miko" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png" marker="MikoCape3">Wait! Tojiko! Don’t tell anyone I was here! But take your stupid prince with you!!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="meia" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" marker="MeiaEyepiece3">Say, Meia… with all your work and responsibilities, do you have any time to, you know, get to know other girls?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="hu_tao" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" marker="HuTaoShoes3">I don’t think I’ll be visiting. In fact, I’ve had to put in a lot of effort in the past to &lt;i&gt;not&lt;/i&gt; have to use services like yours myself, thank you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="fina" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" marker="FinaBoots3">That actually sounds pretty rough, Fina. I may not get many visitors, but at least I see Marisa plenty. She’s another human my age. It’s… well, it’s more lively with her around.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="jim" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-blunt.png" marker="JimGloves3">Now you’re just making fun of me. I’ve had to deal with plenty of big, ugly onis before, you know. Still, I guess I can forgive you for looking like that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="remilia" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-angry.png" marker="RemiliaHat3">Why are youkai all so meddlesome? What I’m trying to do here is a deeply &lt;i&gt;human&lt;/i&gt; thing. You wouldn’t understand at all, Remi.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="remilia" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-bluffing.png" marker="RemiliaShoes3">I admit I don’t have any experience with anyone’s touch but my own… but I’m not ashamed of that. Unlike youkai, humans &lt;i&gt;only&lt;/i&gt; ever have sex with their husband or wife.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="remilia" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" marker="RemiliaSkirt3">You act like the high and mighty mistress of the Scarlet Devil Mansion, but you’re no different in that regard, I bet. I’m sure you’ve had your way with plenty of men and women!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="remilia" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-bluffing.png" marker="RemiliaShirt3">I’ll be thinking of that later, when I’m— um, when I’m getting angry over the evil deeds of youkai.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="remilia" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" marker="RemiliaBra3" dialogue-layer="over">That’s the real reason I came here to find a spouse. If it’s someone I can get to know and fall in love with, I think it wouldn’t be so scary for me to get with them… physically.&lt;br&gt;{small}But I’m for sure not moving to the SDM.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="remilia" stage="6" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" marker="RemiliaPanties3">More importantly, Remi… where are your hairs? Is that the style in Europe? In the outside world? It just looks off to me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="hu_tao" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="HuTaoSocks3">I don’t particularly mind that, Hu Tao. After all, I can balance you out by being extra lazy!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="hu_tao" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-serious.png" marker="HuTaoCoat3">The shrine maiden of paradise must exterminate youkai. That was my mother’s duty, and it’ll be my daughter’s. Well, if that’s how it is there’s no sense worrying over it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="hu_tao" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" marker="HuTaoShirt3">Being the Hakurei Shrine Maiden… it feels like I have to hold people at arms’ length. It’s my duty to be impartial and cold… I hope you can warm me up a bit, Hu Tao.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="hu_tao" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png" marker="HuTaoShorts3">Did you cut off your hairs? Is that the style in China these days? D-don’t expect me to go around like that… at least not right away.&lt;br&gt;{small}What would they say if they saw me in the hot springs with all my hair gone?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="hu_tao" stage="6" />
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" marker="HuTaoHat3">You sure like to tease people, Hu Tao. I’m not so good at that sort of thing. Though, I don’t mind… so long as you make it up to me later.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="critical_darling" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="CriticalDarlingGloves3">I guess beer keg percussion wouldn’t be the oddest music I’ve heard. Though I’d rather evacuate the beer out first, if you get my meaning.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="barbara" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-cheerful.png" marker="BarbaraHat3">Let us all donate to the Hakurei shrine, so that it may continue to guide us and protect us. Remember, cherry blossom viewings are held every weekend in Spring!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="nami" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-interested.png" marker="NamiBelt3">A navigator, huh? That sounds important! And on such a big merchant ship to boot! You must get lonely out on the high seas, with all that money and no one to spend it on!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="yuri" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="YuriShoes3">Fingering? It means accusing. You know, like when there’s an incident and I beat up every youkai in my way until I find the culprit. What did you think I meant?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="fluttershy" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" marker="FluttershySleeves3">Well… honestly, you look pretty easy to exterminate if I need to, so I might as well let things be for now. I’ll be keeping an eye on you… um, unless it’s too embarrassing.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="samus_aran" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="SamusPowerSuit3">You look tough, even without your suit of armor. What sort of youkai do you battle? I’ve never had trouble fighting in this outfit or blasting them with my sacred ofuda.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" id="70">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="68" dialogue-layer="over" weight="3">~Player~, why’d you even come here? Lonely? Lovestruck? Tired that your best friend and rival refuses to commit and desperately want to move on from her? That’s lame, but I guess I can commiserate.</state>
                <state img="#-blunt.png" oneShotId="69">Right, let’s deal.</state>
                <state img="#-cheerful.png" oneShotId="70">Say, if ~player~ rage quits, does someone rotate in to replace ~human.ifMale(him|her)~? Ooh, will that person come in half-naked?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5" id="71">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="74">Right, ~player~, head in the game. I’ll be pissed if you wipe out this early!</state>
                <state img="#-cheerful.png" oneShotId="75">Time to deal. And don’t worry, ~player~. I’ll keep my eye out for anyone who seems your type. Um, what was your type…?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="76">You’ll get ‘em next time, ~player~. Or maybe you won’t. Hell if I know.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7" id="69">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="80">You’re not beat yet, ~player~, and neither am I! We can still join forces to find our destined beloveds!</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png" oneShotId="81">What are you doing, screwing around like this? Listen, you’ve already gotten me like this. I wouldn’t like it if you collapsed now.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png" oneShotId="82">Aren’t you out to nab a spouse of your own, same as I am? Then focus! Look at me, I’m totally exposed! Imagine I’m your ideal girl, and use that as motivation to pull this one out.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="68">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" oneShotId="90">Don’t… give up now, ~name~. I’m already like this… I’m sure your dearly beloved… wouldn’t want to see you fail now.</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png" oneShotId="91">You’re almost to the finish, ~name~… just like me. Well, I’m headed to a different kind of finish. Go ahead and… watch.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9" id="72">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-interested.png" oneShotId="86">Listen, ~name~, you got… you got someone out there for you. A soulmate or whatever… I’m sure she’d hate it if you made an ass of yourself.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" oneShotId="87">I couldn’t keep up my end of the bargain. We were both looking for someone to take care of us… well, it doesn’t matter. Keep up the good fight, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-interested.png" oneShotId="561">You’ve got nothing left to take off, right? That means… That means…</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" oneShotId="562">W-well, part of the draw of this game is that you’re going to see three others “take care of” themselves, so I’d be lying if I said I wasn’t looking forward to this.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-dismissive.png" oneShotId="557">Honestly, you could’ve done a lot of things different to win this one, ~name~. Well, it is what it is. At least the rest of us can enjoy the view.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" oneShotId="558">I’m not… I haven’t gotten into this game enough to really… &lt;i&gt;enjoy&lt;/i&gt; this. But I’m curious enough to watch.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-shocked.png" oneShotId="553">~Name~’s up this turn. W-wait, he’s out of clothes, he’s gotta—! W-well, I might as well watch, if everyone else is going to.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" oneShotId="554">I’ve read stories and seen pictures of men stroking themselves, but I’ve always had to imagine the details of it. I hope the real thing compares favorably.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="549">Yes… ~name~, your sacrifice won’t be in vain!</state>
                <state img="#-cheerful.png" oneShotId="550">Did I distract you, ~name~? I’ll let you return the favor, then.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-interested.png" oneShotId="565">~Name~ lost. That means he has to grip his thick member, and stroke it…</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" oneShotId="566">~Name~’s out. Too bad you didn’t lose earlier. Us going at the same time would be pretty close to sex. Of course, if we get married we can do the real thing.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-cheerful.png" oneShotId="585">If &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; have a good time, &lt;i&gt;I&lt;/i&gt; get a good show! Everyone wins with this loss!</state>
                <state img="#-bluffing.png" oneShotId="586">Remember! I’m not a perv for looking! This is just me enjoying my victory!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" oneShotId="581">When you uh, c-cum, ~name~, does the um, the cum itself splash everywhere? I’ve only ever read descriptions in books, but you know how those are.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" oneShotId="582">Let me know when you’re about to explode, ~name~! I wanna get a good look, but avoid anything getting on me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="577">So guys just like, grab it and stroke it up and down, right? They seem pretty easy to please. That’s good.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" oneShotId="578">I’m just curious… what a real man’s &lt;i&gt;“load”&lt;/i&gt; looks like. That’s all.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-forfeit-B.png" oneShotId="573">Feel free to use me as you like… in your mind’s eye.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="574">Use this view as you wish, ~name~. It’s only fair… I’m going to be watching you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="569">Will you be using your memories of me servicing myself earlier? Or will you use the view of me as I am now?</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png" oneShotId="570">Too bad I’m all tired and sweaty now, ~name~, I would’ve been great &lt;i&gt;“material”&lt;/i&gt; earlier. Or, perhaps you like that sort of thing?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-interested.png">Your rod, ~name~… it looks warm. If I reached out and touched it, how hot would it be?</state>
                <state img="#-cheerful.png">F-feel free to stroke it to me, ~name~. I’m very pretty, and doing so will of course make you fall completely in love with me.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Does it feel good to be rough on your rod, or is gentle better?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I don’t know what a boy’s looks like when they’re having a good time… but ~name~ seems pretty engrossed in the act, at least.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">I should t-take careful note of how ~name~ does it. I’ll need to make sure my husband feels good too, like that. Think of it like a cheat sheet!</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">If ~name~’s hand were me then… would I feel good too? It seems so violent, but I guess that’s the way it goes in the stories too…</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">The way ~name~’s stroking it is almost hypnotic. That’s the only reason I’m transfixed on it.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">The books did &lt;i&gt;not&lt;/i&gt; prepare me for seeing a man really doing this in front of me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">A guy doing it is a lot like danmaku battles. You have to… There’s a… Well, it’s not really like danmaku battles.</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">Make sure you don’t get any of your seed on me, ~name~! That’d be gross, and if any drops got in my vagina I might get pregnant!</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Looking at one in real life… it doesn’t seem that impressive. What can it do my fingers can’t?&lt;br&gt;{small}But there’s got to be a reason my erotic stories always talk about how good it feels…</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Does your arm get tired doing that so much, ~name~? Us girls mostly just move our fingers.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-interested.png">W-wow… the descriptions in books hardly do it justice…</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">You look like you’re having fun, but… a hand couldn’t possibly feel as nice as… as a girl. Another reason you might consider getting married, then.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">It looks w-warm, ~name~. Having something so warm… inside you… it might be nice.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">How does it feel, ~name~? To do that in front of a beautiful and pure shrine maiden?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-interested.png">Just something as simple as letting me stroke it… while you rub me between the legs… that’d bring us closer, wouldn’t it ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-forfeit-A.png">If we were h-having sex, ~name~, instead of your hand wrapped around your penis… it’d be my womanhood.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">It almost feels like… ~name~ and I are getting lost in each other.</state>
                <state img="#-forfeit-B.png">I can almost… feel ~name~ from here. His warmth… it’s a good feeling. What would it be like if we got closer?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-butt.png" oneShotId="176">~Name~, w-were you looking at me while you stroked it? That’s a bit too embarrassing to deal with! I’ll just turn away so you have nothing to look at.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Men don’t want to finish too quickly, right? I’ll need to make sure I pace myself if I marry a man.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">When you’re pleasuring yourself, all you care about is yourself. But when you’re doing it with another person, you want &lt;i&gt;them&lt;/i&gt; to feel good. I hope it’s not too much effort to pull that off.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Normally in the books, the man and the woman finish together. It’s a bit awkward waiting for ~name~ while I’m all unwound.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Remember ~name~, if we get married you wouldn’t have to do this all by your lonesome. In fact, we could do &lt;i&gt;all&lt;/i&gt; sorts of things.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" oneShotId="606">S-so that’s a man’s seed. It’s… well, it’s gooey.</state>
                <state img="#-bluffing.png" oneShotId="607">That’s a lot of— that’s a lot. is that how much you enjoyed yourself?</state>
                <state img="#-cheerful.png" oneShotId="608">If boys are this easy to please, maybe I’ll get myself two husbands!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="602">There’s so much… who cleans it up? Who’s in charge of keeping track of it all?</state>
                <state img="#-blunt.png" oneShotId="603">If I was more, uh, turned on, I’d probably find that incredibly hot. But as it is, it just looks strange and goopy.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" oneShotId="598">Wow, he really c-came! So I guess if we were to do it… all that seed would… would be inside me…</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png" oneShotId="599">I enjoyed watching ~name~… and clearly, he liked it too. If we got married, could I even pleasure him as well as he can himself?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="594">I hope my future husband is better at outlasting me… or is it &lt;i&gt;because&lt;/i&gt; I’m like this now?</state>
                <state img="#-pleasant.png" oneShotId="595">Done already? I wanted to cum together.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-cheerful.png" oneShotId="590">So much pleasure from such a simple action. Taking care of my future husband will be a breeze!</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png" oneShotId="591">When you climaxed, ~name~, who were you thinking of? What sort of things were you doing with her?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="remilia" />
                <state img="#-blunt.png" marker="RemiliaMustMasturbate">Hey, Remi, are you drunk? You’ve knocked back more than a couple of those glasses, and I think Sakuya stopped time once or twice to sweeten your glass.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="hu_tao" />
                <state img="#-bluffing.png">It’s this sort of game, so there’s nothing wrong with me watching you. Respectfully, of course.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7" priority="0">
                <condition count="0" status="not_alive" />
                <state img="#-butt.png" oneShotId="178" marker="Buttpose01" weight="3">~Name~ has to be the first one to do it? I-it was awkward enough just being naked with her! No way I can watch this!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="629">So ~name~ has to spread her legs for everyone? I’d complain about how perverted a rule that is, but I’m super turned on and want to watch myself.</state>
                <state img="#-pleasant.png" oneShotId="630">So with nothing left… Well, we’ve all done this sort of thing in private before, right ~name~? Just tune the rest of us out and have fun.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-interested.png" oneShotId="625">~Name~ has to “do it” now, right? It’s fine if I watch, though, since she might end up becoming my wife when all is said and done.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="626">~Name~ lost &lt;i&gt;already&lt;/i&gt;? It’s too soon. Can she wait to go until I’m more turned on?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-interested.png" oneShotId="621">I hope you have a great time, ~name~. Really, I mean it!</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png" oneShotId="622">~Name~’s out! I suppose it’s fine if I watch this next part, seeing as she could maybe one day become my wife. I need to know &lt;i&gt;all&lt;/i&gt; about her.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="617">Losing… losing yourself… it’s not so bad, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-cheerful.png" oneShotId="618">I’m sorry… but I’m glad you lost. Us both going together… the idea feels exhilarating!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-pleasant.png" oneShotId="613">Losing’s not that bad, ~name~. In fact, it’s kinda fun.</state>
                <state img="#-cheerful.png" oneShotId="614">I don’t know if I ought to feel sorry for ~name~… or happy for her. Hope she has a good time though.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="remilia" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" marker="RemiliaStartMasturbating">She’s gone into her own little world of fantasy. This is why I can’t stand youkai…</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="hu_tao" />
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">I’m not going to offer up any dirty talk, I hope you don’t mind. Even if I knew how to, it’d be too embarrassing to vocalize my thoughts.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7" oneShotId="51">
                <condition count="1" status="masturbating" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Buttpose01" notSaidMarker="Buttpose02" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="Buttpose02">Sorry, I realized I’m too horny to be able to not watch you. I won’t make any lewd comments at least.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="649">I didn’t realize how embarrassing it’d be to have a girl touch herself while I stare. Oh well, I’ll just blame her loss on everyone else.</state>
                <state img="#-bluffing.png" oneShotId="650">W-wow, I can’t believe all the rest of you can’t wait to see ~name~ stroking her loins! I bet you’re all super turned on right now, and are imagining &lt;i&gt;your&lt;/i&gt; fingers on her mound! F-for shame, guys.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="651">Do you have to put in a lot of effort to get yourself off, ~name~?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" priority="0">
                <condition count="0" status="not_alive" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">So, is it normal for us to comment on other people’s, um, proceedings? Well, I’ll just follow the lead of everyone else.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" oneShotId="645">Do— do you want any suggestions, ~name~? I, uh, do this often enough at the shrine, I’m willing to help… if needed…</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="646">You don’t mind, right ~name~? If I check you out and take any ideas for myself. Oh, but I guess if I get married, I won’t need to masturbate any more, huh?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" oneShotId="637">When I was imagining this scenario in my mind, it was a lot &lt;i&gt;hotter&lt;/i&gt;. Right now, I just feel jealous.</state>
                <state img="#-dismissive.png" oneShotId="638">I’m not taking off any more clothes than I need to. You’re just going to have to use your imagination, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-heavy-B.png" oneShotId="641">I’ve never played with myself… while another girl did the same. It feels like— &lt;i&gt;Aah-ha!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-forfeit-B.png" oneShotId="642">We can feed off each other’s pleasure… ~name~…</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-interested.png" oneShotId="633">If going again wasn’t too much work for me to want to bother with, you’d totally make me want to go again, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="634">I’m exhausted so I won’t be going again, but if seeing me lazing about all sweaty and flushed turns you on, feel free to look.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-bluffing.png">If it were me doing that, I’d be more gentle with you, ~name~. Um, would that make me a bad lover?</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">It doesn’t look like ~name~’s being gentle with herself… Do I look that aggressive when I do it, too?</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Watching ~name~… The idea of stroking her to finish myself is… really tempting.&lt;br&gt;{small}But actually doing it? &lt;i&gt;Nooooooo.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">~Name~’s face looks so happy. It’s as appealing as… as looking at her nethers.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">The point of a party is to have a good time. I’m glad ~name~ isn’t holding back!</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">I wonder how ~name~’s feels different than my own… w-wait, what am I saying?&lt;br&gt;{small}I am a little curious, though…</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">It’s pretty relaxing, watching someone else have a good time.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">I want you to know, I’m not only interested in getting married for the hanky-panky bits. But the hanky-panky bits &lt;i&gt;do&lt;/i&gt; look like fun.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-interested.png">I can feel your body heat from here, ~name~. It’s not a bad feeling…</state>
                <state img="#-bluffing.png">I’m not imagining ~name~ stroking me like that, as her other hand cups my breasts and her lips meet mine, at all.</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">She’s just completely absorbed in her… in herself. Sh-she must really be feeling good.</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">I read stories in which two girls, um, do it. I always wondered if the things they described actually feel good. Seeing ~name~ makes me think… anything we’d do together would feel so good…</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" oneShotId="7" priority="0">
                <condition filter="uses_toy" role="target" />
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">R-remember, every tool contains a spirit inside, so be sure to treat your tools with respect, or else they’re turn into tsukumogami.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-forfeit-A.png">You know, ~name~… since two girls can’t have sex the usual way… would this be pretty close to the way we’d do it? Just touch each other? I could reach over, and…</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">It looks so… warm in there, ~name~. I wonder what it’s like to touch…</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">You look so pretty, ~name~… especially so… wrapped up in pleasure.</state>
                <state img="#-forfeit-A.png">That place… that place that gives you so much pleasure… yours looks beautiful, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-bluffing.png">How does it feel, ~name~, to, um, poke your pea pod? Ugh, what sort of dirty talk did they use in that thin book?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">~Name~’s doing things differently than I do… but I guess most people do most things different. Hmm… well, if it feels good to me I’m doing just fine, so who cares?</state>
                <state img="#-blunt.png">You look like you’re having the time of your life, ~name~. To be honest, I’m jealous.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">You’re so vigorous, ~name~. You’re not going to damage it or anything, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-bluffing.png">I wonder what ~name~’s thinking about as she does that? A l-lover? A crush? Or o-one of us…</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">I wonder if I look like that when I do it… it’d be too embarrassing if someone saw me like that… or made me look like that.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">You clearly have a way you like to pleasure yourself, ~name~. Though if we did get married, would you be open to trying something different? The Hourai Pharmacy has some &lt;i&gt;“marital aids”&lt;/i&gt; we could try.</state>
                <state img="#-cheerful.png">Let me know if there’s anything I can do to help you enjoy yourself, ~name~. As long as it’s not too much effort.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-9" oneShotId="92">
                <condition role="target" character="remilia" />
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" marker="RemiliaFinished">For a youkai, Remi’s face when she, er, finishes is kind of cute…</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-cheerful.png" oneShotId="670">Your orgasm looked great, ~name~!&lt;br&gt;{small}No? Is that not a normal thing to say?</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png" oneShotId="671">Oh! I guess I got a little engrossed in watching you. You were mesmerizing, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-heavy-B.png" oneShotId="666">Ah, w-watching ~name~… go over the edge… It’s making me want to join her… &lt;i&gt;umf!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-heavy-A.png" oneShotId="667">&lt;i&gt;Oooooh!&lt;/i&gt; I’m gonna be joining you soon!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-bluffing.png" oneShotId="674">W-woah, I didn’t expect seeing someone finish right in front of me would— nothing! Nevermind!</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" oneShotId="675">Watching someone c-come, when I’m not yet turned on myself is kind of… strange. Do I look that goofy when I…? Maybe I shouldn’t get married. I wouldn’t want anyone to see me look so… compromised.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-interested.png" oneShotId="678">If ~name~ made herself feel that good, imagine what she could do to me as my wife…</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="679">Hehe, ~name~ is cute when she finishes. If she was my wife, I’d have fun with her every day, just so I could see that face.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-cheerful.png" oneShotId="662">You look nice and satisfied. Isn’t it fun?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="663">So that’s how ~name~ gets herself off? I could do that for her, no problem.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate_first">
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">I gotta go first? I’ve never done this in front of other people before. I mean, there was this one time— but I’m pretty sure Marisa was asleep— you know what, nevermind.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate">
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Oh… that’s me. At least I know how to do this part well enough. It can get lonely at the shrine sometimes.</state>
                <state img="#-cheerful.png">Okay… so, um, everyone who would like to marry me is free to watch. But if you &lt;i&gt;don’t&lt;/i&gt; want me as your bride, I’ll exterminate you if you so much as peep!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="start_masturbating">
            <case stage="7" id="5" priority="500">
                <condition count="1" status="alive" />
                <condition status="alive" role="other" character="human" />
                <state img="#-starting.png" marker="PlayerFantasy">You know, being the last one to have to go makes it a lot easier. Maybe I’ll talk out my favorite fantasy. It’s not like I’d be interrupting any important poker.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <condition role="other" character="hu_tao" />
                <state img="#-starting.png">L-lewd talk, Hu-Tao? I like reading stories like that, but I’ve never heard people say those sorts of things out loud.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7" priority="0">
                <condition count="2-" status="exposed" />
                <state img="#-starting.png">At this point, I’m… I’m happy to do this. Ehehe…</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-starting.png">I do have a vagina under all this hair… just in case you were wondering.</state>
                <state img="#-starting.png">I h-hope this helps you imagine all the things we could do if I was your wife… ehehe…</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="masturbating">
            <case stage="8" id="4" oneShotId="21" priority="500">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="PlayerFantasy" />
                <condition gender="male" role="other" character="human" />
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" marker="MPlayerFantasy1">Hmm.. I’ll imagine my darling husband, coming home from his work after a long day. He embraces me as soon as he gets through the door, scooping me off my feet.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="6" oneShotId="22" priority="500">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="MPlayerFantasy1" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="MPlayerFantasy2">My husband slides a hand under my shirt, ripping off my sarashi. One breast he kneads in his hand, the other he teases by flicking his tongue on my nipple.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="8" oneShotId="24" priority="500">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="MPlayerFantasy2" />
                <state img="#-interested.png" marker="MPlayerFantasy3">My skirt on the ground, he thrusts a hand down my bloomers, fingers running through my pubic hair. My husband’s fingers stop at my clit, and he begins to tease it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="9" oneShotId="23" priority="500">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="MPlayerFantasy3" />
                <state img="#-forfeit-A.png" marker="MPlayerFantasy4">I’m sopping wet now, and neither my husband nor I can control out animalistic lust. My bloomers fall to the ground as he rips off his own garments. I’m pushed onto the futon. I look up at him. I feel him against my entrance.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="10" oneShotId="25" priority="500">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="MPlayerFantasy4" />
                <state img="#-forfeit-B.png" marker="MPlayerFantasy5">My husband pushes into me, and his whole girth slides in. He takes it slow as I catch my breath. He speeds up, and I match him. Soon he is moving wildly. I am in bliss.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="11" priority="500">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="MPlayerFantasy5" notSaidMarker="MPlayerFantasy6" />
                <state img="#-forfeit-A.png" marker="MPlayerFantasy6">
                    <text>It’s wonderful. Small moans escape my lips. I feel every movement, every twitch, of my husband inside of me. I want him deeper, I don’t care about anything else.</text>
                    <markers>
                        <marker name="MPlayerFantasy7" op="=" value="0" />
                    </markers>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="12" priority="500">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="MPlayerFantasy6" notSaidMarker="MPlayerFantasy7" />
                <state img="#-forfeit-B.png" marker="MPlayerFantasy7">
                    <text>I feel the heat generated by the two of us, sweat drips down my husband’s chest but all that matters is he keep filling me, and I keep taking him in. My deepest parts ache in ecstasy.</text>
                    <markers>
                        <marker name="MPlayerFantasy6" op="=" value="0" />
                    </markers>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="15" oneShotId="26" priority="500">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="PlayerFantasy" />
                <condition gender="female" role="other" character="human" />
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png" marker="FPlayerFantasy1">Umm… let’s imagine my beautiful wife, returning home after a long day. She lays her hand on my cheek and gives me a peck on the lips. Then another… and one more, longer this time.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="16" oneShotId="27" priority="500">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FPlayerFantasy1" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="FPlayerFantasy2">As my wife’s lips again touch mine, I feel her hand drift up my back, under my shirt. She expertly undoes my sarashi. Her hands tease my breasts and tweak my nipples. Soon I’m breathing too hard to keep my lips against hers.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="17" oneShotId="28" priority="500">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FPlayerFantasy2" />
                <state img="#-interested.png" marker="FPlayerFantasy3">My wife slides her hand down my bloomers, slooowly running through my pubic hair, until it reaches the top of my slit. She expertly rubs up and down its length, and soon I’m sopping wet. She teases me, first putting in one finger, then two.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="18" oneShotId="29" priority="500">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FPlayerFantasy3" />
                <state img="#-forfeit-A.png" marker="FPlayerFantasy4">Neither of us control ourselves now, as we collapse onto the futon, clothes discarded with abandon. I look into her eyes, as this time I place my own fingers at her entrance. She’s already drenched. I enter.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="19" oneShotId="30" priority="500">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FPlayerFantasy4" />
                <state img="#-forfeit-B.png" marker="FPlayerFantasy5">I begin speeding up, teasing my wife’s clit with my thumb. My free hand finds her breast, and begins to play with it. She’s caught off guard as moans escape her lips. But not to be outdone, she matches my finger-work with her own, giving me another wave of pleasure.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="20" priority="500">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FPlayerFantasy5" notSaidMarker="FPlayerFantasy6" />
                <state img="#-forfeit-A.png" marker="FPlayerFantasy6">
                    <text>One hand rubs the inside of my wife, exploring every ridge. The other grabs every bit of her luscious flesh. She does the same to me. Though she was so bold a moment ago, her eyes begin to glaze. We’re as deeply connected as two people can be, body and soul.</text>
                    <markers>
                        <marker name="FPlayerFantasy7" op="=" value="0" />
                    </markers>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="21" priority="500">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FPlayerFantasy6" notSaidMarker="FPlayerFantasy7" />
                <state img="#-forfeit-B.png" marker="FPlayerFantasy7">
                    <text>We’re both deep inside one another, eyes locked even though it seems impossible to focus. I once again kiss my wife’s lips, tasting the sweat now on them. She responds by rubbing even more vigorously, but my aching sex needs that now.</text>
                    <markers>
                        <marker name="FPlayerFantasy6" op="=" value="0" />
                    </markers>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" oneShotId="95">
                <condition role="other" character="hu_tao" />
                <state img="#-forfeit-B.png">Hu Tao, that’s… how do I respond? I don’t dislike you saying these sorts of things, though. I’ll just… let you speak… and I’ll just enjoy myself.&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;Mmmph!&lt;/i&gt; T-thank you, Hu Tao.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Sometimes at the shrine, I can tell no one’s coming… so I stay inside, and um… do this.</state>
                <state img="#-forfeit-A.png">It’s shameful doing this with all you watching… but somehow, the shame makes it more exciting.</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">It feels good, to rub it here. Promise me, if any of you marry me… you’ll take good care of me this way too.</state>
                <state img="#-forfeit-B.png">&lt;i&gt;Hmmph!&lt;/i&gt; S-sorry, I don’t want to “go” too quickly.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Don’t you wish you could do this to me?</state>
                <state img="#-forfeit-B.png">I like the books with the lurid details. Sometimes I’ll rub myself to climax while reading them.</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Is this something a proper wife should do? I don’t know anymore.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Someone marry me… Then I won’t have to use my hands all the time.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Toys… I think Sanae has some… but my fingers are cheaper. Work well, too.</state>
                <state img="#-forfeit-B.png">&lt;i&gt;Mmph…&lt;/i&gt; Marisa, stop playing around... come settle down with me. Just the two of us.</state>
                <state img="#-forfeit-A.png">I’m more experienced with this than I wanna admit. But it makes it easier to do for a crowd.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">I’m the Shrine Maiden of Hakurei… I need to remain pure… but this is nice too.</state>
                <state img="#-cheerful.png">I know what a wife’s duty is. Her spouse has that same duty. Let’s make each other feel good, okay?</state>
                <state img="#-embarrassed.png">Sometimes, I imagine it with someone else’s fingers. Or tongue.</state>
                <state img="#-pleasant.png">I do this a lot at home. G-gotta relieve stress somehow…</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I have to keep it down when I do this at home because others live with me. It’s nice I can let myself be seen here.</state>
                <state img="#-forfeit-B.png">What would it be like if I gave myself to someone else to pleasure me? I… really want to feel that.</state>
                <state img="#-forfeit-A.png">My body’s… pretty sensitive. If you were to run your hands up and down me, I might finish right then and there.</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">I start by focusing on th-the clitoris. As I rev up, I touch more and more of myself.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="heavy_masturbating">
            <case stage="8" id="13" priority="500">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="MPlayerFantasy5" notSaidMarker="MPlayerFantasy8" />
                <state img="#-heavy-A.png" marker="MPlayerFantasy8">
                    <text>We’re going faster now. Our whole bodies alight in passion. I know nothing in the world except for the hammering of my husband’s hot cock. I try to match his fucking. I need this!</text>
                    <markers>
                        <marker name="MPlayerFantasy9" op="=" value="0" />
                    </markers>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="14" priority="500">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="MPlayerFantasy8" notSaidMarker="MPlayerFantasy9" />
                <state img="#-heavy-B.png" marker="MPlayerFantasy9">
                    <text>I feel my husband tense up. I feel the wave about to crest. My pussy clamps down. I need his hot seed in me! I yell his name!</text>
                    <markers>
                        <marker name="MPlayerFantasy8" op="=" value="0" />
                    </markers>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="22" priority="500">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FPlayerFantasy7" notSaidMarker="FPlayerFantasy8" />
                <state img="#-heavy-A.png" marker="FPlayerFantasy8">
                    <text>We’re going faster now. We’re burning in our passion. My pussy feels so good. I know my wife’s does do. Ragged breathing. I press my lips to hers. Make me cum!</text>
                    <markers>
                        <marker name="FPlayerFantasy9" op="=" value="0" />
                    </markers>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="23" priority="500">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FPlayerFantasy8" notSaidMarker="FPlayerFantasy9" />
                <state img="#-heavy-B.png" marker="FPlayerFantasy9">
                    <text>I feel our pleasure peak. I feel my wife’s pussy clamp down on my fingers. Mine too. One last wave! We cum together! I yell her name!</text>
                    <markers>
                        <marker name="FPlayerFantasy8" op="=" value="0" />
                    </markers>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-heavy-A.png">I wanna… I wanna… &lt;i&gt;fffffffuck!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-heavy-B.png">M-my— my— pussy! Feels so good.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finishing_masturbating">
            <case stage="8" priority="500">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="MPlayerFantasy5" />
                <state img="#-finishing.png" marker="MPlayerFantasyFinish">~PLAYER~!!!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" priority="500">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FPlayerFantasy5" />
                <state img="#-finishing.png" marker="FPlayerFantasyFinish">~PLAYER~!!!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-finishing.png">OH! OH! &lt;i&gt;OHHHHHHhhhhhhhhh!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-finishing.png">Ah! &lt;i&gt;A-ahhh!&lt;/i&gt; I’m— &lt;i&gt;Hhhhk!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="9" oneShotId="32" priority="500">
                <alternative>
                    <condition role="self" saidMarker="FPlayerFantasyFinish" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <condition role="self" saidMarker="MPlayerFantasyFinish" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-bluffing.png">Oof, got a little too engrossed in that. Huh, what are you all looking at me like that for? Did I say something strange?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-bluffing.png">W-woah, I didn’t expect to— to cum that hard. Let me know how much the rest of you liked that.</state>
                <state img="#-cheerful.png">I— I didn’t expect to cum that hard! Was it because you all were watching? I-if you want to make me cum hard some more, I’m taking marriage applications at Hakurei Shrine!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="after_masturbating">
            <case stage="9" oneShotId="37">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="YoukaiExplanation==1" />
                <state img="#-serious.png" marker="YoukaiExplanation=2">Youkai die out when they become forgotten or replaced by rational explanations. That’s why the Great Hakurei Barrier exists— to keep out the modern world.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9" oneShotId="38">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="YoukaiExplanation==2" />
                <state img="#-serious.png">Youkai attack humans, and humans fear youkai. Even if it’s just an act, that’s a youkai’s duty. Without that, the youkai would vanish from this world… and I’d be out of a job.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-serious.png" oneShotId="29" marker="YoukaiExplanation">I see some of you side-eye me when I mention my commitment to exterminating youkai. Well, too bad. That’s my duty as Gensokyo’s shrine maiden—  protect the barrier, exterminate youkai.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">All of you are free to come over to the parties at the shrine— if you bring something, of course. No one really gets invited to the parties at my place anyway, they just show up.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">The human village is &lt;i&gt;strictly&lt;/i&gt; off-limits to youkai! Unless they disguise themselves. And I’m too lazy to stop them. Which is always.</state>
                <state img="#-blunt.png">Some people say I’m too brutally honest. I don’t care. Lying is too much effort, so I just tell the truth all the time.</state>
                <state img="#-cheerful.png">I’m kind of hungry after my… ordeal. Does anyone want to buy me something from the bar? I’ll exterminate a youkai for you for free!</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">Wine’s okay and all, but when it’s a Gensokyo get together you have to have sake! With proper Japanese side dishes!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">You know, I may not look it, but I’m good at making Japanese staple dishes. You save a lot of money by cooking for yourself!</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">I wish people would stop making weird comments about my armpits and shoulders. I wear those sleeves because they’re comfortable, not to show off.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I wonder what would have happened if I had a little sake to relax myself before hand? I’d probably win the whole shebang.</state>
                <state img="#-pleasant.png">It’d be nice to swing by the onsen before going to bed to wash off the sweat. Plus, I deserve to relax after my hard work here today.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">It’s tradition in Gensokyo to throw a party and drink the night away whenever an incident is resolved. This could have been an incident, so we should throw a party!</state>
                <state img="#-interested.png">I’ve heard some of the kappa sell “toys” you can use… but why spend money when my fingers are free?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9" priority="0">
                <condition count="1" status="alive" var="winner" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="40">So, is ~winner~ going to invite us all over for a tea party after ~winner.ifMale(his|her)~ win? I mean, that’s what I do to all the youkai I beat up.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_victory">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-cheerful.png">Now that my hard work is over, I can’t wait to go home and goof off.</state>
                <state img="#-blunt.png">Um, even though I won… someone among you wants to wed me and take care of me, right? For my, uh… poker skills? &lt;i&gt;Ugh, this was a terrible idea.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-bluffing.png">That’s right, I’m &lt;i&gt;champion&lt;/i&gt; wife material! So, uh, if anyone here wants to propose to me, you can stop by Hakurei Shrine anytime! Um… you know where that is, right?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_defeat">
            <case stage="9">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-cheerful.png">~Name~, you seemed hopelessly uncool, but could the reason you won be— you got lucky? Ugh, I was hoping some ~human.ifMale(handsome prince|gorgeous princess)~ would take my hand, but stuff like that only happens in fairy tales, huh?&lt;br&gt;{small}Between you and me, the others here are total weirdoes.{!reset}&lt;br&gt;Well, at least I had fun. Thanks, ~name~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-confused.png">Uh… so someone is going to marry me and share their finances with me.. or something… right? Oh, who am I kidding? Kasen was right, this was a terrible idea.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">So, anyone want to come by the Hakurei Shrine and propose to me? Anyone? W-what about you, ~name~? You haven’t experienced any “Post Come Clarity”, right? that means you should &lt;i&gt;definitely&lt;/i&gt; throw yourself at me!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9" hidden="1">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" collectible="yin-yang_orb">u got da orb</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

    </behaviour>
</opponent>
