<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>

<!--This file was machine generated using the Character Editor v6.7.3 at 6:22:05 PM on November 18, 2021. Do not edit this file directly unless you know what you're doing.-->
<opponent>
    <version>v6.7.3</version>
    <first>Charlie</first>
    <last>Magne</last>
    <label>Charlie</label>
    <gender>female</gender>
    <size>medium</size>
    <timer>21</timer>
    <intelligence>average</intelligence>

    <nicknames>
        <nickname for="wikipe-tan">Ms. Wiki</nickname>
    </nicknames>


    <wardrobe>
        <clothing name="panties" generic="underwear" position="lower" type="important" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="bra" generic="bra" position="upper" type="important" />
        <clothing name="pants" generic="pants" position="lower" type="major" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="shirt" generic="shirt" position="upper" type="major" />
        <clothing name="bowtie" generic="tie" position="upper" type="extra" />
        <clothing name="jacket" generic="jacket" position="upper" type="minor" />
    </wardrobe>

    <poses>
        <pose id="get-piggy">
            <sprite id="charlie" src="8-pig.png" x="0" y="0" />
            <sprite id="FatNuggets" src="FatNuggets/FatNuggets.png" x="-800" y="1050" scalex="-0.65" scaley="0.65" alpha="0" />
            <directive type="animation" id="FatNuggets" ease="linear" interpolation="linear">
                <keyframe time="0" x="-800" />
                <keyframe time="1.65" x="-325" />
                <keyframe time="1.75" x="-300" />
            </directive>
            <directive type="animation" id="FatNuggets" loop="true" ease="linear" interpolation="spline" clamp="wrap" iterations="3">
                <keyframe time="0" y="1050" />
                <keyframe time="0.1" y="950" />
                <keyframe time="0.25" y="925" />
                <keyframe time="0.45" y="950" />
                <keyframe time="0.55" y="1050" />
            </directive>
            <directive type="animation" id="FatNuggets" loop="true" ease="smooth" interpolation="spline" clamp="wrap" iterations="3">
                <keyframe time="0" scalex="-0.65" scaley="0.65" />
                <keyframe time="0.05" scalex="-0.6" scaley="0.7" />
                <keyframe time="0.5" scalex="-0.6" scaley="0.7" />
                <keyframe time="0.55" scalex="-0.65" scaley="0.65" />
            </directive>
            <directive type="animation" id="FatNuggets" ease="ease-in-cubic" interpolation="spline">
                <keyframe time="0" alpha="0" />
                <keyframe time="0.25" alpha="100" />
            </directive>
        </pose>
    </poses>

    <behaviour>
        <trigger id="selected">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Hello, everyone! My name's Charlie! I'm the princess of Hell.  It's &lt;i&gt;super&lt;/i&gt; nice to meet you!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Hello! My name's Charlie! Demon Princess of Hell! It's a pleasure to meet you.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Pleasure to make your acquaintance! My name's Charlie. Princess of Hell. You don't have to say the whole thing. </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_selected">
            <case stage="0" id="138">
                <condition role="target" character="wikipe-tan" saying="Vivienne &quot;VivziePop&quot; Medrano." />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="WikiSelect1">Um... hello, Miss...? How do you know my name? A web series? What are you talking about?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="demon" role="target" />
                <state img="#-cheeky.png">Oh, hello! I didn't know another one of my kind would be playing, too!</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Wow, another demon? Um... say, when this is over, I won't tell anyone back home that you're here if you don't tell anyone I'm here, alright?</state>
                <state img="#-content.png">Always nice to see another one like me at the table!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="criminal" role="target" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">Hmmm... I get the sense that there are criminals at this table. I'm starting to have second thoughts about this.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Hmmm... There are criminals at this table... Maybe I can try to reform them?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="angel" role="target" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Wow... an angel playing strip poker along with the Princess of Hell. This isn't too awkward, is it? Should I leave?</state>
                <state img="#-delighted.png">Wow, an actual angel is playing strip poker with me! You know, our hotel has a patron named Angel! He really &lt;i&gt;isn't&lt;/i&gt; an angel, though.</state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png">Wow, an angel is playing strip poker with me? Care to get a bit devilish?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_start">
            <case stage="0" id="59">
                <condition filter="non-human" role="opp" />
                <condition role="other" character="chell_wheatley" sayingMarker="nonHumanQuestion" />
                <state img="#-giggle.png" marker="ChellBasketball">I'm a demon, little guy! The princess of Hell, in fact. And what are you? You look like a basketball!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="51" priority="102">
                <condition role="other" character="twisted_fate" saidMarker="Hat_Start" sayingMarker="Hat_Deal" />
                <state img="#-flirt.png">In my family, we know &lt;i&gt;all&lt;/i&gt; about deals, and you have made a good one! But let's see what comes of this, shall we?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="130">
                <condition role="other" character="wikipe-tan" sayingMarker="CharlieSelect" />
                <state img="#-consider.png">Mmm, well, I hope they are at least known for good reasons...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="139">
                <condition role="other" character="mari" saidMarker="OppSelected_Charlie" />
                <state img="#-consider.png" marker="MariStart">Erm, yes, that's what I said. I know how this sounds, but Hell isn't as bad as you probably think it is, trust me!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="3">
                <condition count="0" gender="male" role="opp" />
                <test expr="~background.time~" cmp="!=" value="day" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">This'll be the best ladies night since the time Vaggie and I finished our scrapbook!</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">This bunch of gals is about to have one Helluva night!</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">What better way to spend your evening than with a deck of cards and a couple of your favorite ladies? Maybe a little deviance on the side, who knows?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="4">
                <condition count="0" gender="male" role="opp" />
                <state img="#-flirt.png">Nothing but us ladies, a deck of cards, and some deviant desires. What could possibly go wrong?</state>
                <state img="#-giggle.png">Just us ladies? Sweet! If this turns into a pillow fight slumber party, I wouldn't complain!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I'm not used to the living world, so please forgive my unfamiliarity with everything up here.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I hope I don't step on any toes or anything. I'm not used to the living world, so I'm... probably going to stand out a little.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">So... the living world... I'm &lt;i&gt;not&lt;/i&gt; familiar with it. Like, at all. I hope I don't freak anybody out!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="swap_cards">
            <case stage="2" id="80" oneShotId="21" priority="666">
                <state img="#-shoefull.png">These cards are fine. I'll keep them.</state>
                <state img="#-shoefull.png">I'll exchange ~cards.text~ ~cards.ifplural(cards|card)~, please!</state>
                <state img="#-shoefull.png">May I have ~cards.text~, dealer?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <test expr="~cards~" value="0" />
                <state img="#-consider.png">I'm actually going to stay with the hand I've got. That's cool, right?</state>
                <state img="#-consider.png">I think I'll stick with what I have. That's allowed, right?</state>
                <state img="#-content.png">I'm not switching any of these. That's how you know I've got a great hand, right? Big dicked move.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Uhh, I think I'm holding. Like, not exchanging any cards.</state>
                <state img="#-smile.png">These are perfect! I don't need to switch any out this time.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~cards~" value="69" />
                <state img="#-sarcastic.png">Bro, you seriously need to find something better to do than to snoop through my lines in the character editor. Go on a walk. Read a book. Hug your dad. I don't care. Anything's better than reading this.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">I think I'll exchange ~cards.text~ ~cards.ifplural(cards|card)~.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I'll have ~cards.text~, please!</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">May I have ~cards.text~, please?</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">I would like ~cards.text~ this time, please.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Oh, shoot. I'm not sure. I think I'll take... ~cards.text~. Thanks!</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Oh, umm... I think I'll go with... ~cards.text~? ~Cards.text~ sounds nice.</state>
                <state img="#-content.png">&lt;i&gt;Every&lt;/i&gt; card deserves a chance to show its true potential! Just kidding. ~Cards.text~ of these cards suck, so please have ~cards.ifplural(them|it)~~ back.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I don't think ~cards.ifplural(these|this)~ ~cards.text~ ~cards.ifplural(are|is)~ going to do me much good, so I'll switch ~cards.ifplural(them|it)~ out.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">May I have three cards? Wait, no. Make it two. Actually, uhh, yeah. Make it ~cards.text~. Final answer. Thank you!</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I think I'll go with... ~cards.text~. ~Cards.text~ sounds good.</state>
                <state img="#-smile.png">I'll have ~cards.text~. Please and thank you!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="good_hand">
            <case stage="0-6" id="33">
                <test expr="~background~" value="bedroom" />
                <state img="#-giggle.png" oneShotId="394">This is the second most fun I've had in a bedroom! Besides, y'know, sleeping.</state>
                <state img="#-content.png" oneShotId="405">Being alone in this bedroom with all of you makes it feel... more intimate.</state>
                <state img="#-delighted.png" oneShotId="406" marker="HandSnacks">This feels like a sleepover! I think we should get some snacks to make it even more accurate!</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="407" marker="HandPajamas">I wish I'd known we'd be in a bedroom. I would have brought my pajamas! I have some really cute ones!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="65">
                <test expr="~background~" value="paris rooftop" />
                <state img="#-giggle.png" oneShotId="408">I've always wanted to go to Paris! Sinners have told me all about it.</state>
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="409" marker="HandParis">♫ &lt;i&gt;When the Moon hits your eye like a big pizza pie...&lt;/i&gt; ♫ ...wait, that's Italy, isn't it?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="67">
                <test expr="~background~" value="purple room" />
                <state img="#-cheeky.png" oneShotId="410" marker="HandPurpleRoom">I love the color of these walls! Purple is such a pretty color!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" oneShotId="18">
                <test expr="~background.surface~" value="sand" />
                <state img="#-giggle.png" oneShotId="1152">I love the feeling of sand under my bare feet!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-smile.png">I would &lt;i&gt;love&lt;/i&gt; to have a date on a beautiful ocean pier. We could share a cheap pizza and talk about our feelings!</state>
                <state img="#-giggle.png">I love it when puppies go &lt;i&gt;full zoomy mode!&lt;/i&gt; When they're so full of excitement that they can't help but run around aimlessly with their little arfs! They're so precious!</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Is there an ice cream flavor that combines white chocolate with joyberries and seahorse dreams? If not, I'll make it happen!</state>
                <state img="#-delighted.png" marker="HandPrizes">One of our patrons has a cute little pet pig. He likes to bring me "prizes." This morning, I got a rolled up gum wrapper. &lt;i&gt;I love him so much!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">The best pranks are the ones that make your friends giggle and laugh!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I can get along with &lt;i&gt;anyone&lt;/i&gt; who shares their kindness with others!</state>
                <state img="#-smile.png" marker="HandCottonCandy">Has anyone ever dreamed of sleeping in a bed of cotton candy? Or is it just me?</state>
                <state img="#-sing.png">Few things make me happier than when I can express myself through song!</state>
                <state img="#-cheeky.png">I &lt;i&gt;adore&lt;/i&gt; humans! They’re full of happiness, hopes, and dreams! I only ever get to know them after their lives have ended.</state>
                <state img="#-content.png" marker="HandDateIdeas">Do any of you keep a journal of cute date ideas for your friends? I'd love to have someone to swap notes with...</state>
                <state img="#-cheeky.png">It's so nice getting to know all of you! It feels like we're a nice big group of friends!</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" marker="HandBath">Is there anything better than sharing a hot bath with someone you love?</state>
                <state img="#-giggle.png">I don't think I'll ever get tired of those little novelty blankets that make puppies look like they're wrapped in a burrito.</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png" marker="HandPranks">I love the little pranks our hotel staff plays on each other. I found a skeleton in my shoe this morning! </state>
                <state img="#-giggle.png">Niffty talks to herself when she thinks nobody is around. She's a cute little housekeeper. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="1" priority="0">
                <test expr="~background.location~" value="outdoors" />
                <test expr="~background.time~" value="day" />
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="411">It's a &lt;i&gt;beautiful&lt;/i&gt; day. The sun is shining, the birds are chirping, and there are no violent turf wars in sight!</state>
                <state img="#-delighted.png" oneShotId="412">I'm not used to seeing the sun! It's more beautiful than I'd ever imagined!</state>
                <state img="#-cheeky.png" oneShotId="413">The sunshine out here feels so warm and snugly! It makes me want to smile until my cheeks are sore!</state>
                <state img="#-giggle.png" oneShotId="414">I should have brought sunglasses. I don't think my eyes have adjusted to the wonderful sunshine!</state>
                <state img="#-smile.png" oneShotId="415" marker="HandWeather">Is this magnificent weather typical of Earth? Maybe I should visit more often!</state>
                <state img="#-giggle.png" oneShotId="416" marker="HandTan">As you may be able to tell, we don't get a lot of sunlight back in Hell. I don't exactly have a tan here!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="6" priority="0">
                <test expr="~background.dark~" value="true" />
                <state img="#-smile.png" oneShotId="417">Playing in the dark is great! You can imagine &lt;i&gt;anything&lt;/i&gt; is in the shadows! Like a purple puppy! That sure would be a cool find, wouldn't it?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="418">I love the dark! Well, I mean, I'm kind of used to it. Hell is always dark.</state>
                <state img="#-giggle.png" oneShotId="419">You can't make shadow puppets or light shows without being in the dark!</state>
                <state img="#-smile.png" oneShotId="420" marker="HandRave">Would a rave be any fun if it happened in broad daylight? I don't think so! Darkness is an opportunity for something special.</state>
                <state img="#-content.png" oneShotId="421">My fireworks look a lot better when it's dark out. That's... not very surprising. I'm sure you know how fireworks work.</state>
                <state img="#-delighted.png" oneShotId="422" marker="HandStars">Oh wow, the stars here are so cool! I bet it would be so relaxing to lie under the stars and just... look at them.</state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png" oneShotId="423">They say crazy things happen after dark... I guess we'll find out if that's true!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="7" priority="0">
                <test expr="~background.surface~" value="sand" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="424">What feels more relaxing than fresh sand on your bare feet? Seriously, please tell me. I'd love to feel even &lt;i&gt;more&lt;/i&gt; comfortable!</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="425">Maybe when we're finished, we can build a sand castle! With flags, and a tower, and &lt;i&gt;oooh!&lt;/i&gt; We &lt;i&gt;definitely&lt;/i&gt; need a moat!</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" oneShotId="426" marker="HandSandball">Sand is kinda like snow, right? Maybe we could have a sandball fight?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="427" marker="HandBury">Winner gets to bury me in the sand!</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="428" weight="2">Would it be okay if I took a seashell home with me? Or two? Or twenty?</state>
                <state img="#-smile.png" oneShotId="429">My favorite popsicles are the rocket pops. Not just because they're shaped like rockets. They taste nice, too!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="9" priority="0">
                <test expr="~background.bathing~" value="true" />
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="430" marker="HandTowelTag">Shall we play a game of towel tag? My sorority sisters and I used to love that game, but they didn't like how fierce I was with it!</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="431" marker="HandBathBombs">Did anyone bring any bath bombs? The fruitier the scent, the better!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="432">The steam in here is great for the lungs! I'm used to breathing dirty, basalty air.</state>
                <state img="#-delighted.png" oneShotId="433">There's nothing more relaxing than a nice hot shower after a long, exhausting day!</state>
                <state img="#-smile.png" oneShotId="434">I have a collection of loofahs with cute little animals in the middle. My favorite one has a yellow flamingo, I call him Samson! ...Is that weird? </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="okay_hand">
            <case stage="3-6">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="strip_al" />
                <state img="#-giggle.png" oneShotId="881">Whatever dad jokes you may have heard, I doubt they're as groan-worthy as Alastor's. They're so bad, they wrap back around to being funny!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-shrug.png">There aren't really any rules in Hell, so you have to learn to make do on your own. </state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">I hope I didn't forget to wish our bartender a good morning today!</state>
                <state img="#-content.png" marker="HandYears">I've lived in Hell for two hundred years. I can handle anything this game throws at me. </state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png" marker="HandHell">Hell really isn't &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; bad... I mean, yes, it's filled with suffering, drug users, sexual deviants, and anarchy, but I &lt;i&gt;know&lt;/i&gt; there's a beautiful, shining spirit in every sinner!</state>
                <state img="#-content.png" marker="HandCook">I've been thinking, who would make a good cook at the Hotel? I sure would love to have Vaggie's Salvadorian cuisine around!</state>
                <state img="#-consider.png" oneShotId="859" weight="0.5">~Player~, are you thinking what I'm thinking? </state>
                <state img="#-smile.png">What would make good background music for the lobby at the Happy Hotel? I'm looking for something relaxing that puts you in a good mood, but doesn't stick out too much.</state>
                <state img="#-smile.png" marker="HandSpider">I found the biggest spider I've ever seen under my bed last night. No, it wasn't Angel Dust. I carefully took it outside. It wasn't hurting anything. </state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">A smile and a wave goes a long way towards making a good impression!</state>
                <state img="#-content.png">An ussie is always better than a selfie. I prefer to share my moments with a friend!</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="HandHumanDisguise">Perhaps I should have worn a human disguise so that I wouldn't stand out so much. </state>
                <state img="#-content.png">Some demons are sinners who get sent down to Hell, but I was born and raised there. Just a fun piece of trivia for you.</state>
                <state img="#-giggle.png" marker="HandAngelDust">Our first patron is such a flirt. His confidence is certainly through the roof!</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">What brightens your day quite like a bundle of colorful balloons?</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" marker="HandSmile">Has something made you smile today?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">A smile in the morning is as important as butter on toast!</state>
                <state img="#-giggle.png">Have you ever heard a puppy make an angry little "arf?" It's the cutest thing!</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">It's so fascinating meeting new people. Everyone has their own little quirks that make them special and unique.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="bad_hand">
            <case stage="0-6" id="66">
                <test expr="~background~" value="bedroom" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" oneShotId="435" marker="HandWhoseBedroom">So... whose bedroom is this, anyway? We aren't invading anyone's property by being here, are we?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-bruh.png">There's nothing that yanks my noodle harder than someone who's given up on being happy. </state>
                <state img="#-sarcastic.png" marker="HandPessimists">Sometimes I wonder if people &lt;i&gt;want&lt;/i&gt; to be unhappy. If you aren't willing to try, you can't expect anything to change. </state>
                <state img="#-bruh.png">This is when I would like to say, "At least I have my Dad's support!" But that wouldn't be true. </state>
                <state img="#-sarcastic.png" marker="HandDad">Oh, don't worry, Lucifer. Just raise a beautiful child in Hell and crush all her dreams. After all, it's &lt;i&gt;her&lt;/i&gt; fault she's a failure! </state>
                <state img="#-bruh.png" marker="HandTV">Despite what you may assume, being Princess of Hell doesn't have many perks or privileges. I can't even appear on TV without being laughed at!</state>
                <state img="#-bruh.png" marker="HandPessimists2">I don't get people who think it's foolish to be optimistic. What's wrong with wanting to see the best in people?</state>
                <state img="#-sarcastic.png">If I had a dime for every demon who laughed at my dreams, I could topple the anarchic economy of Hell. </state>
                <state img="#-plead.png" marker="HandExtermination">It breaks my heart to see thousands of souls be exterminated each year in my kingdom. Guilty or not, nobody deserves that!</state>
                <state img="#-bruh.png" marker="HandCharlie">The audacity of some demons. They can't even get my name right! It's not "Charlotte," "Charlene," or "Charlize"; it's Charlie! How hard is that to remember?</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Some people say my goals are impossible, and that people can't change. But I think most people aren't even given the opportunity to change!</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="HandFistfight">Pro tip: If you ever get into a fistfight with a reporter on live TV... well... pray nobody was watching that channel.</state>
                <state img="#-pout.png" marker="HandMusical">Vaggie says that life's not a musical and not every problem in the world can be solved by singing, but wouldn't it be so much easier if it &lt;i&gt;were&lt;/i&gt; a musical?</state>
                <state img="#-point.png" marker="HandApathy">Apathy is easy. It's a cowardly attitude and I hate it. If you don't care, you don't have to face your conscience. How convenient!</state>
                <state img="#-consider.png" oneShotId="870">Sometimes... I wish I could just be struck by lightning and not have to face being a failure. But if that happened, I wouldn't get to help anyone! </state>
                <state img="#-plead.png" oneShotId="871">Sometimes I feel like there's nobody left for me to trust in the world. Like even my best friends may turn on me any second if I make a mistake.</state>
                <state img="#-bruh.png" marker="HandSongStuck">Do you ever hear a song so good, it gets stuck in your head and you can't remember what it is? It's like it's always just out of reach!</state>
                <state img="#-plead.png">There are so many things in the world that we may never understand. About why people are they way they are. But we can always try.</state>
                <state img="#-bruh.png">There are so many places in the Seven Rings that I wish I could take Vaggie. Damn rules...</state>
                <state img="#-uncertain.png" marker="HandLetters">After I got into a fight on nine-circle TV, I started getting... interesting fan letters. I'm flattered, but, did they have to go into so much detail?</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" marker="HandThrone">Hell will be a much nicer place when I take the throne. No more fire, screams, or commercials that are louder than the program!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="2" priority="0">
                <condition count="0" gender="male" role="opp" />
                <state img="#-bruh.png" oneShotId="1297" marker="HandSmileMore">Don't you hate it when men tell you to smile, but don't even &lt;i&gt;try&lt;/i&gt; to give you any reason to? Like, back the fuck off.</state>
                <state img="#-content.png" oneShotId="1298">At least we can comfortably be ourselves with just us ladies.</state>
                <state img="#-consider.png" oneShotId="1299">It's nice not to have any men around who think we're only here to "impress them."</state>
                <state img="#-content.png" oneShotId="1300" marker="HandCatcalling">Catcalling is a regular thing in Hell. Demons think it's funny to pick on the pretty princess of Hell, but they stop laughing when they're on fire. </state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="1301">I dream of a world where I can be more than "just a pretty lady." Where my ideas aren't ridiculed and my speaking isn't interrupted at the first chance.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="8" priority="0">
                <test expr="~background.surface~" value="sand" />
                <state img="#-shrug.png" oneShotId="436">Every time I go to the beach, I end up with sand in every crevice of my body. I guess that doesn't change on Earth!</state>
                <state img="#-bruh.png" oneShotId="437" marker="HandSandShoes">I think I'll be picking the sand out of my shoes forever. Maybe I'll just get a new pair.</state>
                <state img="#-point.png" oneShotId="438" marker="HandSeagull">If a seagull shits on me, I'm wiping it on the dealer. He should be rewarding my wicked smile with better cards!</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="439">I hope I don't get sunburned. We don't get much sunlight in Hell!</state>
                <state img="#-uncertain.png" oneShotId="440">I see spots everywhere. Is it from staring at the sun too much? It's so beautiful, I can't help it!</state>
                <state img="#-bruh.png" oneShotId="681">On a particularly hot day in Hell, the sand always feels too hot on my feet. But then the water is always too cold! What's up with that?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="hand">
            <case stage="2" id="72" oneShotId="20" priority="666">
                <condition role="self" />
                <state img="#-shoeless.png" marker="charlie_shoes">You know what would make today better? Freeing my feet from these damn heels. I think I'll do that right now, actually!</state>
                <state img="#-shoeless.png" marker="charlie_shoes">Very little feels better than throwing your heels off after a long day. And you know what? Now's a good time. Why wait until I lose another hand? </state>
                <state img="#-shoeless.png" marker="charlie_shoes">You know what feels fantastic? Freeing your feet after wearing heels all day. No time like the present, now that I think about it!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="79" oneShotId="19" priority="666">
                <state img="#-giggle.png" marker="HandBra">Do you like my new look? I'm partial to the polka dot design, myself. I think it looks cute!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6 8" id="37" priority="383">
                <condition role="other" character="chell_wheatley" stage="3-4" saidMarker="fiveAces!=2" sayingMarker="fiveAces=1" />
                <alternative>
                    <condition role="other" character="chell_wheatley" stage="3-4" saidMarker="fiveAces!=4" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="441">You know, lying is a sin... though would that send you to hell? Can robots even &lt;i&gt;go&lt;/i&gt; to hell? That's a good question...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="52" totalRounds="0">
                <condition role="other" character="meia" stage="0" sayingMarker="birthday" />
                <test expr="~month.number~" value="6" />
                <test expr="~day.number~" value="10" />
                <state img="#-delighted.png" oneShotId="442">Oh! Happy birthday, Miss Gisborn! I hope the day has been going well for you!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="133">
                <condition status="finished" role="other" character="polly" sayingMarker="Polly_Wikipetan_PoltergeistArticle2" />
                <condition role="other" character="wikipe-tan" sayingMarker="PoltergeistArticle3" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">Ms. Wiki, please calm down! I'm sure Polly didn't mean it!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6 8" id="40" totalRounds="2-">
                <condition role="other" character="jessie" stage="0-2" sayingMarker="JessieQA_DarkSecrets" />
                <state img="#-point.png" oneShotId="443" marker="JessieSecrets">I have secrets, yes. But they wouldn't be secrets anymore if I told you about them, now would they?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6 8" id="41" totalRounds="2-">
                <condition role="other" character="jessie" stage="0-2" sayingMarker="JessieQA_LittleLies" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" oneShotId="444" marker="JessieLittleLies">Little lies? U-um, I guess they're okay? I will need some more context as to what &lt;i&gt;kind&lt;/i&gt; of lies, though...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="42" totalRounds="2-">
                <condition role="other" character="jessie" stage="0-2" sayingMarker="JessieQA_Smokers" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" oneShotId="445" marker="JessieSmoking">I don't condone smoking... not that I hate the smell of smoke or anything. I mean, I grew up in Hell and all.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="43" totalRounds="2-">
                <condition role="other" character="jessie" stage="0-2" sayingMarker="JessieQA_Family" />
                <state img="#-plead.png" oneShotId="446" marker="JessieFamily">...I... have a complicated relationship with my family. I'd rather not talk about it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6 8" id="44" totalRounds="2-">
                <condition role="other" character="jessie" stage="0-2" sayingMarker="JessieQA_StupidMistakes" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" oneShotId="447" marker="JessieStupidMistakes">Um... well, &lt;i&gt;I&lt;/i&gt; personally wouldn't, if they have moved on and truly regret it, but it's really not &lt;i&gt;my&lt;/i&gt; place to say why people get sent down here.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6 8" id="132">
                <condition role="other" character="aoba" stage="0-8" saidMarker="MentionsHajime" sayingMarker="QnA_Hajime" />
                <state img="#-uncertain.png" marker="AobaHappy">Oops... Does it count if I think I &lt;i&gt;am&lt;/i&gt; that person?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="46" totalRounds="10-">
                <condition role="other" character="twisted_fate" sayingMarker="Lady_Luck" />
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="448">♫ &lt;i&gt;Lady Luck never smiles, so lend your love to me awhile!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6 8" id="60" oneShotId="2" totalRounds="2">
                <condition role="other" character="jim" sayingMarker="Intergalactic_journey" />
                <state img="#-delighted.png" marker="JimInventory">Arriving in the human world was simply a matter of finding someone with a &lt;i&gt;grimoire&lt;/i&gt; I could use to come to the surface!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="100" totalRounds="14-">
                <condition role="other" character="neptune" sayingMarker="state_goddess" />
                <state img="#-amused.png" marker="NeptuneGoddess">So you're a goddess and I'm a demon, and we're playing poker together. Isn't that ironic?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="45" priority="102">
                <condition role="other" character="aoba" saidMarker="MentionsYun" sayingMarker="QnA_Yun" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" oneShotId="449" marker="AobaMonsters1">...Do demons count as monsters? I suppose in some worlds, they might, but I do not &lt;i&gt;think&lt;/i&gt; I am a monster.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" oneShotId="450" marker="AobaMonsters2">We have hell-hounds and succubi down here, but I don't really know if they count.</state>
                <state img="#-bruh.png" oneShotId="451" marker="AobaMonsters3">The biggest &lt;i&gt;monsters&lt;/i&gt; we have down here are those who refuse to better themselves!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="99" priority="102">
                <condition role="other" character="futaba" saidMarker="futaba_jukebox" sayingMarker="futaba_juke_ask" />
                <state img="#-delighted.png" marker="FutabaMusic">I like any music that I can sing along to... ooh! I could sing something right now if you want!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="47">
                <condition role="other" character="twisted_fate" sayingMarker="Stories" />
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="452">Oh, I have &lt;i&gt;plenty&lt;/i&gt; of stories! I certainly have a lot to tell since I opened the Hotel!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="54">
                <condition role="other" character="marceline" sayingMarker="AskMusic" />
                <state img="#-excited.png" marker="MarcelineSongs">Oh! Oh! I like so many songs! I have some of my own! You and I should sing together sometime, Marceline!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="55">
                <condition role="other" character="marceline" sayingMarker="AskPets" />
                <state img="#-delighted.png" marker="MarcelinePets">I don't have any pets, but our client Angel Dust has a pig, Fat Nuggets. He's so adorable!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-6" id="71">
                <test expr="~background~" value="beach" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" oneShotId="607" marker="HandSunburn">Am I going to get sunburn out here? We don't have a sun in Hell, so I've never needed to worry about it. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <condition role="self" timeInStage="0" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" oneShotId="877" marker="HandMonopoly">Strip poker is a relatively harmless game, all things considered. I've seen some rounds of Monopoly that have ended much, &lt;i&gt;much&lt;/i&gt; worse.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4" id="22" oneShotId="1">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="shirt_strip_gluttony2" />
                <state img="#-sarcastic.png">If overindulging on happiness is a bad thing, then maybe I don't always want to be right. Fudge cake tastes too good to stress about it. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4" id="31" oneShotId="10">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="shirt_strip_wrath2" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png">My dad is prone to his fits of rage, and... as much as I hate to admit it, the apple doesn't fall far from the tree.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">They say that rage only leads to a shorter life, but... demons are immortal, so that doesn't always apply. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-delighted.png" marker="HandAfterlife">I think &lt;i&gt;every&lt;/i&gt; sinner deserves the chance to turn their life, or, u-umm, their &lt;i&gt;afterlife&lt;/i&gt; around. Does that make sense? </state>
                <state img="#-consider.png" oneShotId="937" marker="HandFires">It's weird not seeing any fires blazing outside. Or hearing terrorized screams in the distance. Earth is so... quiet!</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">I might win this hand. Or... maybe I won't. I'll leave you in suspense!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">If I can help just &lt;i&gt;one&lt;/i&gt; person avoid ending up in Hell, I've made a difference, and this game will have been worth it!</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I think my partner would enjoy this game if she could get over the public nudity thing. </state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Our patron, Angel Dust, would probably enjoy this game a little too much. I mean, he &lt;i&gt;is&lt;/i&gt; a porn star. Remind me never to invite him!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6">
                <state img="#-consider.png" oneShotId="1314" marker="HandHypocrisy">Look, I &lt;i&gt;know&lt;/i&gt; it probably sounds weird for me to preach a life without sin while I stand here naked before you, but... just trust me, okay?</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" marker="HandHeaven">There are plenty of beautiful, fun, &lt;i&gt;crazy&lt;/i&gt; things in Hell. But I bet you'd be even happier in Heaven!</state>
                <state img="#-bruh.png" marker="HandToilet">Our client told me this morning that he "forgot" to put the toilet seat down. How could he forget? &lt;i&gt;It's such a simple thing!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-4" id="85" priority="0">
                <condition count="0" gender="male" role="opp" />
                <state img="#-consider.png" oneShotId="828" marker="HandAllGirlBand" weight="2">Which sounds better? Demon Disciples? Or Charlie's Angels? For the all-girl band we're starting once we're finished, of course.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip">
            <case stage="0" id="126">
                <condition role="other" character="jim" stage="0-8" sayingMarker="Charlie0a" />
                <state img="#-smile.png" marker="Jim_Hotel_1" dialogue-layer="over">That's right! Hell is... kind of a capital for hedonism, as you can imagine, so the Happy Hotel is meant to rehabilitate sinners and send them on a one-way trip to Heaven!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="91">
                <condition role="other" character="chara_dreemurr" sayingMarker="ResponseCharaCharlieMustStrip1" />
                <state img="#-uncertain.png" marker="chara_deal_tricky">Well, Chara, making deals with a demon is tricky business. I wouldn't recommend it! </state>
                <state img="#-uncertain.png" marker="chara_deal_trust">Funny you should ask, Chara. I tend to avoid making deals with other demons. I find trust and friendliness to be more effective!</state>
                <state img="#-uncertain.png" marker="chara_deal_tell">Is this your way of telling me you want to make a deal, Chara? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="94">
                <condition role="other" character="wikipe-tan" sayingMarker="Charlie1" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="WikiInquiry">You have, have you? What &lt;i&gt;kind&lt;/i&gt; of things do you know? Good things? Bad things? Should I be concerned?</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="WikiInquiry">People on the surface &lt;i&gt;know&lt;/i&gt; about me? That's... a little strange. What sorts of things are people saying?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="98">
                <condition role="other" character="fina" sayingMarker="FinaCharlieStart1" />
                <state img="#-uncertain.png" marker="FinaAfterlife1">That's right, Fina! I'm the Princess of Hell. My... erm, &lt;i&gt;dad&lt;/i&gt; is Lucifer. I'm surprised you haven't heard of him before.</state>
                <state img="#-uncertain.png" marker="FinaAfterlife2">Yup! Most people end up in Hell because they lived a sinful life, but Hell is the only life I've ever known!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="105" oneShotId="40">
                <condition character="miko" sayingMarker="CharlieJacket1" />
                <state img="#-uncertain.png" marker="miko_one_hell">The feeling is mutual, Miss Toyo...sato...errr—you can call me Charlie. There's only one Hell, at least as far as I know. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="109" oneShotId="43">
                <condition character="saki_zls" sayingMarker="CharlieJacket1" />
                <state img="#-delighted.png" marker="saki_cuddle">Oh, Saki, you're so kind! I hope we can be friends, I wouldn't ever want to hurt you. </state>
                <state img="#-giggle.png" marker="saki_cuddle">Cuddling is my middle name, Saki! I hope one day that cuddling won't be an unusual thing where I come from. </state>
                <state img="#-giggle.png" marker="saki_cuddle">Is it that obvious that I love to cuddle? I really wear my heart on my sleeve, huh?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="117">
                <condition role="other" character="wikipe-tan" sayingMarker="Charlie_Hell_1" />
                <state img="#-consider.png" marker="Wiki_Hell_1">Well, yes, Hell is a dangerous place, full of fire, murder, violence, and other assorted crime. Not an ideal place to conduct my mission, I'll admit.</state>
                <state img="#-consider.png" marker="Wiki_Hell_1">Hell is my home, I was born and raised there, but... it's basically how you've heard it. You're likely to be killed the first day you arrive there!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="125">
                <condition role="other" character="cynthia" sayingMarker="CharlieIntro1" />
                <state img="#-consider.png" marker="Cynthia_Intro1">Well, Princess of Hell is something you have to be &lt;i&gt;born&lt;/i&gt; into, my dad being Lucifer and all. I know I don't &lt;i&gt;look&lt;/i&gt; like a Princess, but I figure this outfit makes sense for running my Hotel!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="129">
                <condition role="other" character="perona" sayingMarker="charlie1" />
                <state img="#-uncertain.png" marker="PeronaHell1">...You, erm, might want to hold off on that vacation, Perona. Hell has actually had an overpopulation problem for several years now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="128">
                <condition role="other" character="perona" sayingMarker="charlie0A" />
                <state img="#-giggle.png" marker="PeronaCute1a">Oh wow, thank you so much! I never get compliments very often, but thank you! And I love the color of your hair!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="134">
                <condition role="other" character="fluttershy" sayingMarker="Charlie_strip_singing_voice" />
                <state img="#-smile.png" marker="FluttershySing1">Oh yes! Singing is one of my greatest passions in life. If you can't get enjoyment from a good song, then what joy can you take from anything?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="135">
                <condition role="other" character="fluttershy" sayingMarker="Charlie_age_question" />
                <state img="#-pleased.png" marker="FluttershyAge1">I suppose by your standards, maybe. Humans only live to 150, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="141">
                <condition role="other" character="petra" sayingMarker="petra_charlie_strip0a" />
                <state img="#-uncertain.png" marker="PetraSubjects1">Well, 200 is actually pretty young for my family. I don't really have a lot of power over here, but I suppose I could call the Hotel my royal duty?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-5">
                <condition role="self" consecutiveLosses="2" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png" oneShotId="610">Wha—again? I lost twice in a row? That shouldn't be possible with my unshakable optimism!</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="609">Twice in a row?! Maybe I'm not being positive enough...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-5">
                <condition role="self" consecutiveLosses="5" />
                <state img="#-bruh.png" oneShotId="622">Okay, now you &lt;i&gt;have&lt;/i&gt; to be kidding me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-5">
                <condition role="self" consecutiveLosses="3" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="613">Wow. That's three in a row! I need to stop thinking about puppy kisses and start focusing!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-5">
                <condition role="self" consecutiveLosses="4" />
                <state img="#-uncertain.png" oneShotId="615">I'm beginning to think the dealer &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; wants to see me naked. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" totalRounds="0">
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="First">O-oh. I'm first? That doesn't happen very often. Two hundred years of playing poker doesn't give you much of an advantage, does it?</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="First">Oh! I'm first? I mean, it's no big deal. I wouldn't have shown up if I was afraid to lose!</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png" marker="First">Huh? I'm first? But what about my beaming smile and positive thinking? I thought that would give me good luck!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4" totalRounds="5-20">
                <state img="#-consider.png">Is it time to let the girls out already?</state>
                <state img="#-pout.png">Damn, this was sooner than I expected. I should practice up on my poker skills...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-5">
                <state img="#-cheeky.png">I &lt;i&gt;may&lt;/i&gt; have had the worst hand that round, but I think I still have the biggest smile! </state>
                <state img="#-consider.png">Oops! I probably should have held onto one of those. I had high hopes that I was going to luck out. </state>
                <state img="#-pout.png">Well, that was a stinker. Next round will be better! </state>
                <state img="#-pout.png">Why do I always think luck will grace me with a flush?</state>
                <state img="#-content.png">This isn't too bad. I've still got my positive attitude!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-uncertain.png">Here's the skinny: Hell has an overpopulation problem, and no one has found a non-violent way to solve it, yet. </state>
                <state img="#-uncertain.png">So here's the deal: Hell has become overrun with sinners these days, and I'm hoping to solve that problem non-violently. </state>
                <state img="#-uncertain.png">As I'm sure you can imagine, there's an ever growing population of sinners in Hell. It's getting to be too much.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-happy.png">The Happy Hotel is full of wonderful people with fascinating stories!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I'm lucky to have such a wonderful hotel staff! Each and every one of them has something special to bring to the table. </state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">My team at the Happy Hotel are more than just staff—they're my friends! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-amused.png">What a great time to get started!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Perfect! Now it's time to get more comfortable. </state>
                <state img="#-smile.png">It's always nice to feel included!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_winning">
            <case stage="0" totalRounds="7-">
                <state img="#-content.png">Hmmm. I was wondering when it would be my turn.</state>
                <state img="#-content.png">I didn't think I was ever going to lose!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripping">
            <case stage="0" id="140">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Jim_Hotel_1" />
                <condition role="other" character="jim" stage="0-8" sayingMarker="Charlie0b" />
                <state img="#-zstripping.png" marker="Jim_Hotel_2" dialogue-layer="over">Well, I've been thinking about it for a long time now, but I kind of figure people would &lt;i&gt;want&lt;/i&gt; to reform? After all, Hell has been overpopulated for some time now...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="97">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="WikiInquiry" />
                <condition role="other" character="wikipe-tan" sayingMarker="Charlie2" />
                <state img="#-zstripping.png" marker="WikiInquiry2">Well, I don't know what A24 is, but you should know that I maintain &lt;i&gt;soul ownership&lt;/i&gt; of this establishment!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="118">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Wiki_Hell_1" />
                <condition role="other" character="wikipe-tan" sayingMarker="Charlie_Hell_2" />
                <state img="#-zstripping.png" marker="Wiki_Hell_2">I... wouldn't know what those places are, but yes, it's heavily overpopulated! That's why I've created the Happy Hotel, in the hopes to rehabilitate sinners!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="119">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Wiki_Hell_1" />
                <condition role="other" character="wikipe-tan" sayingMarker="Charlie_Hell_3" />
                <state img="#-zstripping.png" marker="Wiki_Hell_3">Haha, no, my dad's &lt;i&gt;way&lt;/i&gt; too busy to spend time doing that. He spends more of his time claiming souls on the surface and... being disappointed in me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="127">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Cynthia_Intro1" />
                <condition role="other" character="cynthia" sayingMarker="CharlieIntro2" />
                <state img="#-zstripping.png" marker="Cynthia_Intro2">It's called the Happy Hotel! It's... um... in Hell. I don't know if there's any way to &lt;i&gt;visit&lt;/i&gt; it, unless you come down here, of course, but I wouldn't really advise that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="142">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="PeronaHell1" />
                <condition role="other" character="perona" sayingMarker="charlie12" />
                <state img="#-zstripping.png" marker="PeronaHell2">Oh? What's your castle like? I don't know if it could accommodate even &lt;i&gt;half&lt;/i&gt; of our population, but that's still a very generous offer!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="144">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="PeronaCute1a" />
                <condition role="other" character="perona" sayingMarker="charlie01A" />
                <state img="#-zstripping.png" marker="Perona_Pink">I'd like to think that Hell will turn pink when, hah, you know... after more of my people learn the joys of redemption...</state>
                <state img="#-zstripping.png" marker="Perona_Pajamas">I have great taste in a lot of things! Like, uhh... desserts... and pajamas! Oh, and table manners. So the desserts don't get on my pajamas.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="102" oneShotId="37">
                <condition character="chara_dreemurr" sayingMarker="ResponseCharaCharlieStripping1Tell" />
                <state img="#-zstripping.png" marker="chara_deal_hug">Don't you think you could use a warm hug, Chara? Or a friendly letter? Or a bright smile in the morning?</state>
                <state img="#-zstripping.png" marker="chara_deal_scrapbook">You're looking at the best scrapbooker in the underworld, Chara. You could have a well-organized keepsake, including every memory of our friendship!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="103" oneShotId="38">
                <condition character="chara_dreemurr" sayingMarker="ResponseCharaCharlieStripping1Tricky" />
                <state img="#-zstripping.png" marker="chara_deal_backrub">Oh? Did ~player~ offer you a back rub? A spa treatment? A hand holding session?</state>
                <state img="#-zstripping.png" marker="chara_deal_scrapbook">~Player~ must have offered you something really good! Does it involve acts of service, or physical affection? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="104" oneShotId="39">
                <condition character="chara_dreemurr" sayingMarker="ResponseCharaCharlieStripping1Trust" />
                <state img="#-zstripping.png" marker="chara_deal_throw">Well, Chara,  they say you can't trust a demon as far as you can throw them, but I'm a better thrower than people expect!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="107" oneShotId="41">
                <condition character="miko" sayingMarker="CharlieJacket2" />
                <state img="#-zstripping.png" marker="miko_names_makeup">Whoa, Miko, that's a lot of names. Are you making those up on the fly?</state>
                <state img="#-zstripping.png" marker="miko_names_hug">Well, Miko, I &lt;i&gt;would&lt;/i&gt; tell you, but then I would have to hug you, and I might not let go!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="110" oneShotId="44">
                <condition character="saki_zls" sayingMarker="CharlieJacket2" />
                <state img="#-zstripping.png" marker="saki_u_lie">I'm sure you're one tough cookie, Saki, but nobody's ever left Hell like that before!</state>
                <state img="#-zstripping.png" marker="saki_u_lie">I don't think many demons would want to run into you if you ever &lt;i&gt;did&lt;/i&gt; end up in Hell, Saki. </state>
                <state img="#-zstripping.png" marker="saki_u_lie">Oh, Saki, I'm sure you're much too sweet and kind to ever end up in Hell!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="137">
                <condition role="other" character="magma_grunt" saidMarker="mg_charlie_strip1a" />
                <state img="#-zstripping.png">That's what I'm trying to do, actually! That's why I established the Hazbin Hotel, a place where sinners can be rehabilitated and sent to Heaven!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <test expr="~background.exhibition~" value="true" />
                <state img="#-zstripping.png">I must admit, I've been through a lot but I never thought I'd be out here getting naked in public. That's, like, something Angel would do.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~background~" value="beach" />
                <state img="#-zstripping.png">Do you have a sunburn, or are you always this hot? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~background~" value="roof" />
                <state img="#-zstripping.png">Boy, things are starting to get steamy! You know, they say that all the best things happen on the roof!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-zstripping.png" marker="charlie_strip_sonder">Have you ever wondered how many people have thought about you romantically?</state>
                <state img="#-zstripping.png" marker="charlie_strip_opia">Have you ever looked deeply into someone's eyes, and really &lt;i&gt;"listened"&lt;/i&gt; to what you saw? </state>
                <state img="#-zstripping.png" marker="charlie_strip_enouement">Do you ever wish you could tell your past self not to say that stupid thing to your partner?</state>
                <state img="#-zstripping.png" marker="charlie_strip_ellipsism">Have you ever wondered what happens to the rest of the world when you're not around, parading your fancy? </state>
                <state img="#-zstripping.png" marker="charlie_strip_exulansis">Sinners act like it's &lt;i&gt;crazy&lt;/i&gt; to help others feel good. Hell, I guess I'm crazy, then. </state>
                <state img="#-zstripping.png" marker="charlie_strip_liberosis">Bringing smiles to other people isn't just fun; it's &lt;i&gt;imperative&lt;/i&gt; for a fulfilling night life.</state>
                <state img="#-zstripping.png" marker="charlie_strip_occhiolism">I've been around for a long time, but it hasn't &lt;i&gt;felt&lt;/i&gt; very long to me. Hell, I don't even know ~player~'s story, yet. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-zstripping.png" marker="strip_angel">Our first patron at the Happy Hotel is a flamboyant spider demon named Angel Dust. He's... a porn star. He's very protective of his image. </state>
                <state img="#-zstripping.png" marker="strip_husk">Our bartender is a charming fellow! He's a cat demon named Husk. His short temper is alleviated by his adorable little hat. </state>
                <state img="#-zstripping.png" marker="strip_al">Alastor, the Radio Demon, is serving as the hotel's concierge. He's sketchy as fuck and &lt;i&gt;menacingly&lt;/i&gt; evil. </state>
                <state img="#-zstripping.png" marker="strip_niffty">Our housekeeper is a little one-eyed chatter box named Niffty. But don't let her size fool you...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-zstripping.png" marker="shirt_strip_envy">Have you ever seen something good happen to someone you care about, but you can't help but wish it had happened to you instead?</state>
                <state img="#-zstripping.png" marker="shirt_strip_sloth">There are times when I've woken up and not been in the mood to get out of bed, or to do &lt;i&gt;anything,&lt;/i&gt; really. So I just stayed in. </state>
                <state img="#-zstripping.png" marker="shirt_strip_wrath">Do you ever get &lt;i&gt;so mad&lt;/i&gt; that you want to just incinerate the evil of this world and laugh at its screams as it succumbs to the literal inferno of your rage?</state>
                <state img="#-zstripping.png" marker="shirt_strip_lust">Love is a mighty emotion that comes with a price. It lives with an awesome responsibility. </state>
                <state img="#-zstripping.png" marker="shirt_strip_gluttony">I have a confession to make... sometimes, I can't help but over indulge myself on life's joys. I'm like a pig! </state>
                <state img="#-zstripping.png" marker="shirt_strip_pride">My mission at the hotel is really important to me. Nothing would make me happier than to see it succeed. </state>
                <state img="#-zstripping.png" marker="shirt_strip_greed">At first glace, Hell looks like a terrible place. Everyone for themselves, trust no one, stab everyone in the back. My people aren't given a chance to love.  </state>
                <state img="#-zstripping.png" marker="bra_failure">I've been called a failure. I feel their doubts. I hear their laughter. But it shouldn't bother me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-zstripping.png">I have to admit, playing this game with all of you feels a little bit naughty...</state>
                <state img="#-zstripping.png">I know what you're thinking. "Why is Charlie playing strip poker? Doesn't she want to &lt;i&gt;discourage&lt;/i&gt; sin?"</state>
                <state img="#-zstripping.png">It might sound a little &lt;i&gt;weird&lt;/i&gt; to hear me preach about sin... during a game of strip poker. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-zstripping.png">Is it getting hot as &lt;i&gt;hell&lt;/i&gt; in here, or is it just me?</state>
                <state img="#-zstripping.png">Boy, it sure is &lt;i&gt;heating up&lt;/i&gt; in the Inventory, isn't it?</state>
                <state img="#-zstripping.png">Want to grab me by the horns? It would be one &lt;i&gt;hell&lt;/i&gt; of a ride!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="89">
                <state img="#-zstripping.png">I run the Happy Hotel. We take in sinners from Hell, and redeem them so they can happily ascend to heaven!</state>
                <state img="#-zstripping.png">I've founded a place where sinners can turn a new leaf, and ascend to Heaven. I call it the Happy Hotel! </state>
                <state img="#-zstripping.png">I dream of a Hell &lt;i&gt;without&lt;/i&gt; sin! At the Happy Hotel, we're helping sinners become good citizens. I'll make my dream a reality, one sinner at a time!</state>
                <state img="#-zstripping.png">My mission at the Happy Hotel is to rehabilitate sinners! I hope to solve Hell's overpopulation with ascension. </state>
                <state img="#-zstripping.png">I believe everyone deserves a second chance, whether they're a serial killer, cannibal, or a jerk who talks in the theatre. That's why I've opened the Happy Hotel!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripped">
            <case stage="2" id="120" priority="103">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Wiki_Hell_2" />
                <condition role="other" character="wikipe-tan" saidMarker="Charlie_Hell_2" sayingMarker="Charlie_Hell_4" />
                <state img="#-aastripped.png" marker="Wiki_Hell_4">You don't have to tell me. I'm reminded every day that people don't believe in my mission. But I believe everyone deserves a shot at redemption!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="121" priority="103">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Wiki_Hell_2" />
                <condition role="other" character="wikipe-tan" saidMarker="Charlie_Hell_2" sayingMarker="Charlie_Hell_5" />
                <state img="#-aastripped.png" marker="Wiki_Hell_5">You... could say that. But yes, in many ways, Hell is punishment enough for the sinners who live here. Dad doesn't even need to intervene.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="96">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="WikiInquiry2" />
                <condition role="other" character="wikipe-tan" saidMarker="Charlie2" />
                <state img="#-aastripped.png" marker="WikiInquiry3">...Get it? &lt;i&gt;Soul&lt;/i&gt; ownership? Like... all the souls we'll be sending up to heaven?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="143">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Cynthia_Intro2" />
                <condition role="other" character="cynthia" sayingMarker="CharlieIntro3" />
                <state img="#-aastripped.png" marker="Cynthia_Intro3">Um... I don't know what you mean. My city &lt;i&gt;is&lt;/i&gt; Hell... In fact, people on the surface are technically not even supposed to know it exists.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="113">
                <condition role="other" character="fluttershy" saidMarker="Charlie_happyhotel_inspiration" />
                <state img="#-aastripped.png" marker="Fluttershy_Inspiration">Not really any &lt;i&gt;one&lt;/i&gt; single person, Fluttershy. But it just breaks my heart to see so many souls be purged every year with no hope of a second chance.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="122">
                <condition role="other" character="colress" sayingMarker="faceturn3" />
                <state img="#-aastripped.png" marker="Colress_Face_Turn_3">That's what I want to know, Colress. I believe that everyone has a good heart deep within, even if they have done bad things. But some people don't believe.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="123">
                <alternative>
                    <condition role="other" character="colress" saidMarker="faceturn" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <condition role="other" character="colress" saidMarker="faceturn2" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <condition role="other" character="colress" saidMarker="faceturn4" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-aastripped.png" marker="Colress_Face_Turn_1">I believe that the first step to redeeming yourself is acknowledging that you have made mistakes. You're already on your way, Colress.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="136">
                <condition role="other" character="hatsune_miku" />
                <state img="#-aastripped.png" marker="MikuAscension" dialogue-layer="over">I've never thought about that, but I don't think so? I was &lt;i&gt;born&lt;/i&gt; in Hell, after all. But I don't &lt;i&gt;need&lt;/i&gt; to go to Heaven; helping other people is its own reward!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <test expr="~background.exhibition~" value="true" />
                <state img="#-aastripped.png">I should have worn a human disguise... If other demons found out I was getting naked on the surface, I'd be in trouble.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="26">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="strip_angel" />
                <state img="#-aastripped.png">But I know that Angel cares about others. It won't be easy, but we'll find a way to reach him. </state>
                <state img="#-aastripped.png">I can tell he's making significant progress! He just needs a few months to get accustomed to the Hotel, and he'll be heaven-bound, like the &lt;i&gt;Angel&lt;/i&gt; he is!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="27">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="strip_husk" />
                <state img="#-aastripped.png">He isn't very friendly, but I'm sure that after a few days with the rest of us, he will come around to enjoy it!</state>
                <state img="#-aastripped.png">My partner, Vaggie, doesn't like the idea of a bar in our hotel, but I think it'll be a way to help us all wind down.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="25">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="strip_al" />
                <state img="#-aastripped.png">I think I can lead him to righteousness, though. Anyone with a smile as big as his &lt;i&gt;has&lt;/i&gt; to have some good in them!</state>
                <state img="#-aastripped.png">But I learned one thing from my dad: &lt;i&gt;"Ya don't take shit from other demons!"&lt;/i&gt; So I won't fall for his... trickster... voodoo magic!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4" id="10">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="charlie_strip_sonder" />
                <state img="#-aastripped.png">To think, with &lt;i&gt;billions&lt;/i&gt; of people out there, imagine how many people would enjoy you if they got to meet you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4" id="11">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="charlie_strip_opia" />
                <state img="#-aastripped.png">It can feel almost... invasive. And vulnerable. Isn't it beautiful? Seeing someone for all their gifts, and flaws? I find it very intimate! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4" id="12">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="charlie_strip_enouement" />
                <state img="#-aastripped.png">How enviable it would be to tell your past self that everything will be okay. As long as you don't eat your bbf's leftover pupusas!</state>
                <state img="#-aastripped.png">What is done cannot be undone, and realizing that is a part of personal growth. But sometimes, I still wish I had a time machine. I've made some silly mistakes!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4" id="13">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="charlie_strip_ellipsism" />
                <condition role="opp" var="random" />
                <state img="#-aastripped.png">Can you &lt;i&gt;imagine&lt;/i&gt; what would we do without ~random~ brightening up our day?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4" id="14">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="charlie_strip_exulansis" />
                <state img="#-aastripped.png">I want to believe people are just afraid to get hurt again, that the hope is still there. But I don't know. My brain tells me to give up, but my heart tells me I can't!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4" id="15">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="charlie_strip_liberosis" />
                <state img="#-aastripped.png">Caring about others will bring both ups &lt;i&gt;and&lt;/i&gt; downs to your life. It's like a rollercoaster! A rollercoaster I love to ride. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4" id="16">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="charlie_strip_occhiolism" />
                <state img="#-aastripped.png">My point of view is so small in the grand scheme of things. I want to know more—I cherish every single life story that's shared with me!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5" id="17">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="shirt_strip_envy" />
                <state img="#-aastripped.png">If you love yourself enough, you'll find joy in the happiness of others. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5" id="18">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="shirt_strip_sloth" />
                <state img="#-aastripped.png">I'm talking sweat pants, a cute girlfriend, and some terrible television. Doing nothing can be &lt;i&gt;decadent.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5" id="19">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="shirt_strip_wrath" />
                <state img="#-aastripped.png" marker="shirt_strip_wrath2">Rage is just a symptom of being passionate about something. That's why I'm no stranger to anger. </state>
                <state img="#-aastripped.png" marker="shirt_strip_wrath2b">Maybe that was a little too specific. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5" id="20">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="shirt_strip_lust" />
                <state img="#-aastripped.png">I think love is power. If you routinely relate your intimate feelings to someone who cares about you, you'll make someone very happy. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5" id="21">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="shirt_strip_gluttony" />
                <state img="#-aastripped.png" marker="shirt_strip_gluttony2">Two hundred years just &lt;i&gt;isn't long enough&lt;/i&gt; to enjoy every hot fudge cake, every refreshing bubble bath, or every hug from your fuck buddy!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5" id="23">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="shirt_strip_pride" />
                <state img="#-aastripped.png">But it isn't just &lt;i&gt;my&lt;/i&gt; mission anymore. Love must be shared. I know I can count on all of you to do that!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5" id="24">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="shirt_strip_greed" />
                <state img="#-aastripped.png">I will show them how rewarding it can be to help someone else. When you help one person, you've helped everybody!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5" id="63">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="bra_failure" />
                <state img="#-aastripped.png">They'll know soon enough. My people will feel the freedom of righteousness!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="78">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="strip_niffty" />
                <state img="#-aastripped.png">Niffty has the heart of a giant. I don't think anything could deter her!</state>
                <state img="#-aastripped.png">Niffty has big ambitions, and her fashion-sense is second to &lt;i&gt;none!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-aastripped.png">Most people laugh when I tell them that. </state>
                <state img="#-aastripped.png">It hasn't been easy to find people who believe in my cause, though.</state>
                <state img="#-aastripped.png">Our first patron hasn't fully bought-in to the mission, yet. But I'm sure he'll come around.</state>
                <state img="#-aastripped.png">Our mission hasn't gained much traction in Hell, yet. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-uncertain.png">Please bug report this line if it plays!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-uncertain.png">Please bug report this line if it plays!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-aastripped.png">Here's the thing: &lt;i&gt;little&lt;/i&gt; sins make life worth living. "Peccadillos," as some call them. </state>
                <state img="#-aastripped.png">But is it &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; a sin to celebrate the beauty that the Heavens have bestowed upon you?</state>
                <state img="#-aastripped.png">Consider this; our little game isn't hurting anybody, is it?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-aastripped.png">Please laugh at my terrible jokes. </state>
                <state img="#-aastripped.png">...I can only get people to laugh when I tell them about my dreams.</state>
                <state img="#-aastripped.png">Maybe that would have sounded better in song. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-uncertain.png">Please bug report this line if it plays!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_strip">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" stage="0-2" />
                <state img="#-smile.png">Don't fret, ~name~! I'm sure you'll do better next time!</state>
                <state img="#-consider.png">I'm proud of you for sticking with that hand, ~name~. My Dad always cheats when his luck is that bad. Anything's game when souls are on the line!</state>
                <state img="#-delighted.png">I love your outfit, ~name~! It suits you well.</state>
                <state img="#-consider.png">Bad luck? I know the feeling, trust me. Well, might as well make the best of this!</state>
                <state img="#-smile.png">So many items of clothing to choose from! Which will you go with first?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" stage="3-4" />
                <state img="#-content.png" marker="OpponentStripDarkSide">Every one of us has a secret, ~name~, a dark side to ourselves, whether it is a kink we're ashamed of or some past skeletons in our closet. What's yours?</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Every item of clothing you remove is like opening up a bit of your soul, revealing a little more about yourself. Isn't it refreshing, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png">Just remember, ~name~, that the most important thing is that you are having fun. If there's any way that I can help, just let me know.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" stage="5-8" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">Am I enjoying this game a bit &lt;i&gt;too&lt;/i&gt; much? I can't help it, I just can't wait to see what ~name~ does next...</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">We're arriving at the good stuff. What'll it be, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png">The longer we play this game, the more exciting it gets!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" oneShotId="26">
                <condition role="self" hasHand="High Card" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="454">Wow, I &lt;i&gt;didn't&lt;/i&gt; lose that hand? That's... surprising. Um, n-not that yours was the &lt;i&gt;worst&lt;/i&gt; hand in the world, ~name~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <state img="#-flirt.png" oneShotId="931">I hope seeing me like this provides you with some extra motivation, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-uncertain.png">Please bug report this line if it plays!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_strip">
            <case stage="0-6 8" id="101">
                <condition role="target" character="magma_grunt" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-smile.png" marker="MagmaGrunt1Animals1">Miss... Magma Grunt, was it? You seem to know about animals. I was curious, do you work with animals for a living?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6 8" id="115">
                <condition role="target" character="fluttershy" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-pleased.png" marker="Fluttershy_Kind">Fluttershy, was it? It's a nice change of pace meeting you. You seem like someone who cares a lot about helping others, just like me!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6 8" id="131">
                <condition role="target" character="wikipe-tan" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-consider.png" marker="Wiki_Surface_1">Miss... Wikipe-tan, was it? I've always been curious, what is life like up on the surface?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="princess" role="target" />
                <state img="#-smile.png" oneShotId="455">Oh! Another princess has decided to join us? Well, it's good to know I'm in good company!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="75">
                <condition role="target" stage="0-2" />
                <state img="#-smile.png">Aw, don't feel so down, ~name~. Always look on the bright side!</state>
                <state img="#-smile.png">Don't fret, ~name~. I'm sure you'll have a better hand next time!</state>
                <state img="#-giggle.png">If it makes it any easier, ~name~, close your eyes and imagine you're in a room filled with cuddly kittens! Does that help?</state>
                <state img="#-giggle.png">Go on, ~name~, don't be shy!</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">How lucky for us that ~name~ screwed the pooch!</state>
                <state img="#-smile.png">I'm excited to see what you choose, ~name~! </state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">I think this is a sign that you're wearing too much, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-consider.png">Oooh, tough luck, ~name~. Maybe a bigger smile will give you better odds next time!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="76">
                <condition role="target" stage="3-4" />
                <state img="#-amused.png" marker="OpponentStripDarkSide">I wonder what ~name~ might be hiding. </state>
                <state img="#-content.png" marker="OpponentStripDarkSide">Everyone has a dark side to them, something they don't want others seeing. What about you, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png">They say that what you wear says a lot about you, ~name~. But when you're &lt;i&gt;not&lt;/i&gt; wearing anything, it says even more.</state>
                <state img="#-consider.png" marker="OpponentStripDarkSide">Do you think that ~name~ might be hiding any juicy secrets? </state>
                <state img="#-uncertain.png">Something tells me there is more to ~name~ than what meets the eye. </state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I hope you're having a good time, ~name~! If there is anything I can do for you, please don't hesitate to ask.</state>
                <state img="#-smile.png">~Name~, as long as you're happy, then I'm happy too. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" stage="5-8" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">What a wonderful opportunity to learn more about ~name~! </state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png">Go on, ~name~. Give us something good!</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">The longer we play this game, the more exciting it gets!</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">I hope she goes with something good!</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Don't worry, ~name~, you can take your time!</state>
                <state img="#-consider.png">You're already looking pretty exposed, ~name~. I hope that doesn't crush your spirit!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <state img="#-flirt.png" oneShotId="633">You know, ~name~, I'm already this far. I hope you take off something good for me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-uncertain.png">Please bug report this line if it plays!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="tie">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Wait... hold on. Nobody lost? What happens? Nothing?</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Seriously? That's an odd coincidence. You have to have like, the exact same hands to tie, right?</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Whoa. Is that a tie? So I guess we just... move on? Weird.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">A... tie? Does this happen very often? So do we just move on to the next round?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="shy" role="target" />
                <state img="#-uncertain.png" oneShotId="635">No need to be nervous, ~name~! We're all friends here... I think.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="smart" role="target" />
                <state img="#-flirt.png" oneShotId="637">You seem pretty smart, ~name~, but I hope you're &lt;i&gt;wise&lt;/i&gt; enough to avoid the depths of Hell.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition status="exposed" role="target" />
                <state img="#-shrug.png">Why do you still have your ~clothing~ on in the first place?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-shrug.png">Whenever you're feeling down, ~name~, remember that an angel grows wings every time you make someone smile. </state>
                <state img="#-smile.png">The seven rings haven't fallen, and evil tentacles haven't sucked you into oblivion. You'll be okay.</state>
                <state img="#-content.png">Ah, building the suspense? I see you're something of a showman, ~name~. I can respect that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-consider.png">There's nothing wrong with taking it slow at the beginning, ~name~. We're all here to have fun!</state>
                <state img="#-content.png">I hope you have people who care about you back home, ~name~. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6">
                <state img="#-consider.png" oneShotId="639">Anyone else think it's a little unfair that some of us are naked and he's only removing his ~clothing~, or is it just me?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-bruh.png">Well, now you're just teasing me.</state>
                <state img="#-pout.png">Come on, ~name~! We're this far along already, you don't need to keep messing around!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="995" marker="+Sing">♫ &lt;i&gt;~Name~ thought he might win, but he had no chance. I wonder what's hiding underneath his pants?&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="996" marker="+Sing">♫ &lt;i&gt;~Name~ was chasing a rainbow, looking for gold. I hope you have more luck in the next cards you hold!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="990" marker="+Sing">♫ &lt;i&gt;You've lost this round, but don't lose your glee--the future's full of possibility!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="991" marker="+Sing">♫ &lt;i&gt;You win some, you lose some, that's just how it goes. It's a familiar story that everyone knows!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="992" marker="+Sing">♫ &lt;i&gt;'Twas a swing and a miss, but don't fret as I sing: have patience and see what the future will bring!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="993" marker="+Sing">♫ &lt;i&gt;Our story is told, how ever so slow. I can't wait to see just how far ~name~ will go!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="994" marker="+Sing">♫ &lt;i&gt;~Name~ tries to stall, but the conclusion is foregone. In the words of the masters, the show must go on!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0-8" id="49" priority="381">
                <condition role="target" character="akko" stage="0" saidMarker="necronomicon" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">This looks like something the Radio Demon would do...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" totalRounds="5-">
                <condition filter="mean" role="target" />
                <state img="#-point.png" oneShotId="643">I think your ego should be taken down a few notches, ~name~. You're in this as much as we are.</state>
                <state img="#-sarcastic.png" oneShotId="644">You can't ever expect to go to Heaven with behavior like that, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="shy" role="target" />
                <state img="#-uncertain.png" oneShotId="648">Nervous? I understand. This game can be exhilarating if you haven't done it before.</state>
                <state img="#-uncertain.png" oneShotId="647">I hope this isn't too uncomfortable for you, ~name~. The goal of strip poker is to have fun! ...Well, at least that's &lt;i&gt;one&lt;/i&gt; of the goals.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition status="exposed" role="target" />
                <state img="#-shrug.png">Why do you still have your ~clothing~ on in the first place?</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">Don't you think it's a little late to be taking your ~clothing~ off?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-delighted.png">Whenever I'm in a bad place, I always find it cheers me up when I sing. Do you like to sing, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-content.png">As the saying goes, it's not about the destination, it's about the &lt;i&gt;journey.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-content.png">The game is still young, and so am I! ...Well, relatively speaking. Humans only live to, like, 150, right?</state>
                <state img="#-content.png">Mmm, I suppose I would do the same in your position.</state>
                <state img="#-content.png">It's understandable that you'd start with your ~clothing~, ~name~. No need to rush into things.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-bruh.png">Well, now you're just taunting me.</state>
                <state img="#-bruh.png">Well, that's just unfair.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="shy" role="target" />
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="456" marker="+Sing">♫ &lt;i&gt;Gentle miss ~name~, coming out of her shell. So tense and skittish, you'd think she's in Hell!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="457" marker="+Sing">♫ &lt;i&gt;Little miss ~name~, voice soft as a kitten. She went with her ~clothing~, 'cause she forgot her mittens!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="458" marker="+Sing">♫ &lt;i&gt;~Name~ saw no escape, she wanted to hide. Please stay here with me, I'll make you my bride!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="459" marker="+Sing">♫ &lt;i&gt;~Name~ reached towards the light, searching deep for her nerve. Don't worry my dear, for my love you deserve!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="460" marker="+Sing">♫ &lt;i&gt;She may seem shy, or even timid. But I see right through, her heart is so vivid!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="mean" role="target" />
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="461" marker="+Sing">♫ &lt;i&gt;She may seem quite harsh, or even malicious. But I know deep down, her spite is fictitious!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="462" marker="+Sing">♫ &lt;i&gt;So full of contempt, her heart is mistaken. When I'm done with ~name~, her soul shall awaken!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="463" marker="+Sing">♫ &lt;i&gt;~Name~'s words can bite, so nasty, so vicious! She thinks life is vile, I think it's delicious!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="464" marker="+Sing">♫ &lt;i&gt;So quick to sulk, so eager to abuse. Follow my lead, ~name~, I will be your muse!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="465" marker="+Sing">♫ &lt;i&gt;She thinks she is clever, but I think she's rude. ~Name~ won't be so keen when she's in the nude!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="tsundere" role="target" />
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="466" marker="+Sing">♫ &lt;i&gt;She might seem cold, she might sound crass, but I know deep down, ~name~'s not really an ass!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="467" marker="+Sing">♫ &lt;i&gt;Tough on the outside, but sweet in the center. Be true to yourself, ~name~, let me be your mentor!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="468" marker="+Sing">♫ &lt;i&gt;~Name~ hides her true feelings, as if they're secret. When she opens her heart, she'll live free from regret!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="469" marker="+Sing">♫ &lt;i&gt;She'll tease you with warmth, won't confess her admiration. If only ~name~ knew the power of true love's revelation!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="470" marker="+Sing">♫ &lt;i&gt;~Name~ masks her affection, too afraid of humiliation. If she stays on this path, she'll only find devastation!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="smart" role="target" />
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="471" marker="+Sing">♫ &lt;i&gt;~Name~'s very special, she's sharp as a whip. I see you staring at her, ~player~, now get a grip!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="472" marker="+Sing">♫ &lt;i&gt;~Name~ is so smart, her knowledge so vast. I can't help but feel that I'm being outclassed!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="473" marker="+Sing">♫ &lt;i&gt;I admire her acuity, ~name~'s mind is so bright. What a pleasure it is to witness her might!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="474" marker="+Sing">♫ &lt;i&gt;You may be a genius, this I concede. Please grant with your talents the gift of a good deed!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="475" marker="+Sing">♫ &lt;i&gt;So easy things come, how strong her mentality. What I'd like to learn is ~name~'s strength of morality!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="ditzy" role="target" />
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="476" marker="+Sing">♫ &lt;i&gt;A strange one for sure, I can't say she's brilliant. To make it this far, ~name~ must be resilient!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="quiet" role="target" />
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="477" marker="+Sing">♫ &lt;i&gt;She may be silent, but ~name~'s body is rockin'. So don't be surprised when Charlie comes knockin'!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="478" marker="+Sing">♫ &lt;i&gt;Quiet miss ~target~ is lacking in words. Soon she will be just as nude as the birds!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="angel" role="target" />
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="479" marker="+Sing">♫ &lt;i&gt;Though ~name~ is an angel, she's taken a fall. By playing this game, she's not so above it all!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="musician" role="target" />
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="787" marker="+Sing">♫ &lt;i&gt;Like me, ~name~ is musically-inclined. I think she's making me lose my mind!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="788" marker="+Sing">♫ &lt;i&gt;So calming she is, ~name~'s voice is a treat. If we sang a duet, we couldn't be beat!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="kind" role="target" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="687">~Name~, you have a good heart. Your kindness will serve you well, in and after life! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition status="naked" role="target" />
                <state img="#-shrug.png" oneShotId="680">I'm almost tempted to call that cheating, but if you held onto that for the whole game, it must mean something.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="1051" marker="+Sing">♫ &lt;i&gt;Her hand was weak, she's not doing well. Her ~clothing~ ~clothing.ifPlural(are|is)~ no more, but no one could tell!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="1052" marker="+Sing">♫ &lt;i&gt;Don't worry, my ~name~, I will cheer you up. Kiss me like a puppy, and I'll melt like a buttercup!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="1053" marker="+Sing">♫ &lt;i&gt;So she took off her ~clothing~ and tossed ~clothing.ifPlural(them|it)~ aside. She's lost one more turn, but she still has her pride!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="1054" marker="+Sing">♫ &lt;i&gt;Stay with me, and then you'll see: our joy, love, and laughter, you'll wake up with glee!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="1055" marker="+Sing">♫ &lt;i&gt;Look deep inside and find your love, work towards the day you rise to the heavens above!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="1056" marker="+Sing">♫ &lt;i&gt;She takes off her ~clothing~, for it is the law. We long for the moment she unhooks her bra!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="1057" marker="+Sing">♫ &lt;i&gt;She swapped the wrong cards, ~name~ dropped the ball. We shall not wait long for her panties to fall!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="1058" marker="+Sing">♫ &lt;i&gt;~Name~ tossed her ~clothing~ aside, at our game's demand. May fate grant her peril upon her next hand!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="1059" marker="+Sing">♫ &lt;i&gt;I see the way ~name~'s stalling, trying to maintain her pride. But when the chips are falling, it may be too hard to hide!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-uncertain.png" oneShotId="498" marker="MinorHotel">If you ever find yourself in Hell, ~name~, you know where to find me!</state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png">Better be careful, ~name~. You don't want to end up in Hell with me, do you?</state>
                <state img="#-smile.png">Don't sweat it, ~name~. I'm rooting for you to have a good time, most of all. </state>
                <state img="#-smile.png" oneShotId="499" marker="MinorFunMale">If you ever find yourself in Hell, there's a wealth of fun things to do there!</state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png">Are you feeling sinful today, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-uncertain.png" oneShotId="886" marker="MinorPositiveSpin">Aw, don't let it get to you, ~name~. With the right attitude, you can put a positive spin on your losses!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_minor">
            <case stage="0-8" oneShotId="12">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="MinorHotel" />
                <state img="#-pleased.png">But you're such a good person, that you'll never end up there. Right, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">I bet you're far too good to ever end up in Hell, though!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" oneShotId="11">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="MinorFunMale" />
                <state img="#-delighted.png">A swim at Crowley Beach, or an excursion to Lulu Land... it's not &lt;i&gt;all&lt;/i&gt; fire and brimstone! Just mostly.</state>
                <state img="#-uncertain.png">We even have a theme park in the Greed Ring! I haven't been there since I was a little demon. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" oneShotId="32">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="MinorPositiveSpin" />
                <state img="#-pleased.png">For example, you may have lost, but you no longer have your bulky ~clothing~ weighing you down! ...That makes sense, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-uncertain.png" oneShotId="1072" marker="+Sing">♫ &lt;i&gt;It's a little bit funny, this feeling inside...&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="1073" marker="+Sing">♫ &lt;i&gt;Open up your mind and let me step inside~ Rest your weary head and let your heart decide!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="1074" marker="+Sing">♫ &lt;i&gt;If you're feeling down and your mood is low, just forget all your worries and let yourself go!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="1075" marker="+Sing">♫ &lt;i&gt;Love doesn't discriminate between the sinners and the saints...&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Often times it's the small things in life that make it worth living. </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0-8" totalRounds="0-5">
                <state img="#-flirt.png">Going for the smaller items, I see. Makes sense. The game is just beginning, and you want to build anticipation.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="504" marker="MinorSong">Do you ever have a thought that's hard to explain in words, ~name~? Sometimes it's easier to get out through song!</state>
                <state img="#-content.png">It looks like ~name~ is going for her ~clothing~. Not bad, not bad.</state>
                <state img="#-smile.png" oneShotId="505" marker="MinorFun">Hell's really not as bad as some might think it is. Despite the violence and chaos, you can have a lot of fun there!</state>
                <state img="#-delighted.png" oneShotId="564" marker="MinorSlumberParty">Don't worry, ~name~. I've seen more during the slumber parties I had when I was younger. Oh! Great idea, we should have a slumber party after this!</state>
                <state img="#-content.png">Every gambler knows that to lose is what you're &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; here for.</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">What does a loss matter as long as you're having fun?</state>
                <state img="#-uncertain.png" oneShotId="912" marker="MinorPositiveSpin2">Think of it this way, ~name~: you may have lost that round and your ~clothing~, but there are still more rounds left to go!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_minor">
            <case stage="0-8" oneShotId="14">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="MinorSong" />
                <state img="#-sing.png">♫ &lt;i&gt;Inside of every demon is a rainbow! Inside every sinner is a smiiiiile!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">Although singing isn't for everyone, I'm admittedly biased. Music kind of runs in the family, you know?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" oneShotId="13">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="MinorFun" />
                <state img="#-delighted.png">I sometimes like to go for a swim at Crowley Beach! I have a bunch of cute swimsuits for the occasion!</state>
                <state img="#-bruh.png">The only downside is, many of these places are exclusive to us Hell-born demons and are locked off to sinners, which means I can't take all of my friends there.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" oneShotId="15">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="MinorSlumberParty" />
                <state img="#-consider.png">...We &lt;i&gt;are&lt;/i&gt; going to remain friends after this game, right? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" oneShotId="33">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="MinorPositiveSpin2" />
                <state img="#-delighted.png">Taking negative things that happen to you and flipping them to be neutral or positive can help you live a happier, healthier life.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-delighted.png">Those are some nice threads, ~name~! You'll have to tell me who your designer is! I might get to meet them someday.</state>
                <state img="#-content.png">Others may be impatient, but I don't mind stretching the game out. </state>
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="1086" marker="+Sing">♫ &lt;i&gt;So you've lost your ~clothing~. But things could be worse! You might just meet me after your ride in the hearse!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
                <state img="#-consider.png">I wonder if ~name~ is aware of how much sunshine is waiting in her heart. </state>
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="874" marker="+Sing">♫ &lt;i&gt;The more rounds we play, the more that we see, the more that you make me wanna screeeeeeam!&lt;/i&gt; ♫ </state>
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="1087" marker="+Sing">♫ &lt;i&gt;~Name~'s lost her ~clothing~, and now this is war. A few more rounds should even the score!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_major">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">A gentleman always treats his partner's happiness with the utmost importance.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">I like a man who enjoys the afterglow more than the main event. </state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">A man who has great strength but chooses not to use it is so... &lt;i&gt;enchanting.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">I find it so soothing when a guy knows how to help others smile.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">A man's heart is his most important endowment. </state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">I find it attractive when a man knows how to take it slow, and treats his lady to a &lt;i&gt;show&lt;/i&gt; without speeding things up too much.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_major">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-smile.png">Are you a good listener, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">The best part about having a boyfriend is stealing their ~clothing~ to wear on rainy days. </state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">We had to get you out of your ~clothing~ eventually. What did you think we came here for? </state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">It's much easier to focus on your shining smile without your ~clothing~ drawing the eye! </state>
                <state img="#-smile.png">What ~clothing.ifplural(are|is)~ your ~clothing~ made out of? ~clothing.ifplural(They look|It looks)~ very comfortable!</state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png">Feeling daring, are we? I can respect that.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_major">
            <case stage="0-8" id="53" oneShotId="25">
                <condition role="target" character="neptune" stage="2" sayingMarker="forget_shoes" />
                <state img="#-excited.png">Way to go, Neptune! Leaving the shoes for later, I like it!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="69">
                <condition role="target" character="akko" stage="4" sayingMarker="akko_succubus" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">Goodness, that was actually pretty convincing. I've met several succubi, and you've got the look down. Mostly.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-consider.png">I have to admit... I'm getting a little hot and bothered by this. That wasn't supposed to happen.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="868">I feel like I'm at Lewdy Lu's or something right now. It's a little strange.</state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png">Not too fast... I like a woman who knows how to keep a girl hanging on.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">One thing I find most important in a person is whether they can make me smile. And might I just say, you're certainly doing a good job.</state>
                <state img="#-smile.png">While good looks can get you far, strength of character goes a long way, too. I can tell you have a powerful will.</state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png">I see you're building the suspense. Like waiting for the encore at a show. Should I cheer for you, ~name~?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_major">
            <case stage="0-8" id="57">
                <condition role="target" character="bernadetta" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-content.png">Well, I may be showing my bias, but I personally believe the red looks simply exquisite on you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <test expr="~background.time~" value="day" />
                <test expr="~background.location~" value="outdoors" />
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="1092" marker="+Sing">♫ &lt;i&gt;~Name~ shines so brightly, here under the sun. The more she takes off, the more we have fun!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-flirt.png">You can still be a good person without your ~clothing~.</state>
                <state img="#-smile.png">Excellent!</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">We had to get you out of your ~clothing~ eventually. What did you think we came here for? </state>
                <state img="#-smile.png">It's much easier to focus on your shining smile without your ~clothing~ drawing the eye! </state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png">Ah, I see you're feeling &lt;i&gt;extra&lt;/i&gt; sinful today.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-content.png">You're finally getting to the good part, ~name~. Bravo. </state>
                <state img="#-content.png">This is great. We're getting closer and closer to your heart. </state>
                <state img="#-content.png">Not too quickly, ~name~. Let us savor the moment. </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="athletic" role="target" />
                <state img="#-flirt.png" oneShotId="480">You keep yourself in good shape, ~name~. I bet you have a helluva workout routine.</state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png" oneShotId="481">Don't bother bragging about your resting heart rate. When we're together, you'll never reach it. </state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png" oneShotId="482">I hope you've been keeping up with your cardio, because your heart's going to be racing in a minute. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="muscular" role="target" />
                <state img="#-flirt.png" oneShotId="483">Next time you lift weights, why don't you lift me instead? </state>
                <state img="#-consider.png" oneShotId="484">You better put your ~clothing~ back on before your muscles give me sinful thoughts. </state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png" oneShotId="485">Think you're stronger than a demon princess, ~name~? Maybe we should find out...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-flirt.png">Don't worry if you start to get chilly, ~name~. I can keep you warm. </state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">That looks like a nice resting place. </state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png">You've finally freed the nipple, kind sir. Maybe you can free me of my temptations, later. </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-consider.png">Oh boy, this is it, isn't it? </state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Is it time for the good part?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-flirt.png">Trying to give me some encouragement, I see? Well, go on.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-consider.png">Well, better early than never, I suppose.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-flirt.png">It's about time, ~name~. Let's see what you're made of.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_small_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-flirt.png">It's looking a little... cold. Maybe I should warm it up for you...</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Don't worry, ~name~, I'm sure when you're not so nervous...</state>
                <state img="#-giggle.png">Aww, what a lil' cutie!</state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png">Y'know, if you're feeling chilly, I've got ways I can help...</state>
                <state img="#-consider.png">I bet it'll look a little different under the right circumstances...</state>
                <state img="#-delighted.png">Nothing to be ashamed of, ~name~! If it were any bigger, it would distract from your big heart!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_medium_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-flirt.png">If I hold your hand, will it grow? </state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png">Let's say... we make a deal. </state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png">Y'know... I'm passionate in many ways, ~name~. </state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png">You didn't tell me you were hiding your &lt;i&gt;own&lt;/i&gt; little demon, ~name~. </state>
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="486" marker="+Sing">♫ &lt;i&gt;With nothing to cover him but his hands, ~name~ can no longer hide when his member expands!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="487" marker="+Sing">♫ &lt;i&gt;~Name~ knew he was finished, no matter what he'd select. Now with nowhere to turn, he stands tall and erect!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_large_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="smart" role="target" />
                <state img="#-flirt.png">Mmm, I see your brain isn't the &lt;i&gt;only&lt;/i&gt; thing that's big.</state>
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="1102" marker="+Sing">♫ &lt;i&gt;~Name~'s pants have been removed, and his size is through the roof. They say that smart is sexy, and now we have our proof!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-shocked.png">It's so... umm... wow. That looks... punishing. </state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png">You know what to do with that, right? Don't tell me you rely on your endowment alone...</state>
                <state img="#-consider.png">Whoa. I'm not even sure that would... y'know, &lt;i&gt;fit....&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-consider.png">Oh. This, I wasn't expecting. Though I can't say I'm disappointed...</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">It... it never ends!</state>
                <state img="#-sing.png" marker="+Sing">♫ &lt;i&gt;Though missing his ~clothing~ but not lacking in size, ~name~ can't help but be easy on the eyes!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-flirt.png">I think &lt;i&gt;all&lt;/i&gt; of us are sweating with anticipation!</state>
                <state img="#-consider.png">There's nothing wrong with having a little fun along the way, right?</state>
                <state img="#-consider.png">Would you feel better or worse if I stared a little too long? </state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">How sinful, ~name~!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_small_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="athletic" role="target" />
                <state img="#-pleased.png">You're aerodynamic! It suits you well.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">I can imagine it would be hard to work out if they were &lt;i&gt;too&lt;/i&gt; big.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">I like them, ~name~! They feel familiar, in a comforting way! Spiritually, I mean. I obviously haven't  felt them, &lt;i&gt;yet&lt;/i&gt;...</state>
                <state img="#-uncertain.png" weight="0.5">Quality over quantity right? Wait, no, that doesn't make much sense. That sounds like I'm hating on women with three boobs.</state>
                <state img="#-smile.png">They're so cute! Just like you. Very fitting!</state>
                <state img="#-delighted.png">I love them! They're like little bundles of joy.</state>
                <state img="#-delighted.png">How delightful. They're small, but they pack a big punch!</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">They might get in the way when they're &lt;i&gt;too&lt;/i&gt; big. I'd like to get as close as possible to your heart.</state>
                <state img="#-delighted.png">Fabulous! They suit you very well, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-content.png">If they were any bigger, they might distract from your charming smile.</state>
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="1104" marker="+Sing">♫ &lt;i&gt;Though not big in size, they're certainly pleasing. ~Name~'s fans would still love to give them a squeezing!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_medium_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">There's nothing like a beautiful bosom to ease your mind after a long, stressful day.</state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png">You haven't lived until you've rubbed your bosom against a woman you love. </state>
                <state img="#-content.png">You can play with mine if I can play with yours. It can't be sinful if we both enjoy it, right?</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">I must have ascended, because I'm in heaven right now!</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">~Name~, those are so perfect that I &lt;i&gt;refuse&lt;/i&gt; to believe you're not an angel!</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I feel like I shouldn't look, but the temptation is irresistible!</state>
                <state img="#-uncertain.png">I think this sight is &lt;i&gt;almost&lt;/i&gt; worth sinning for!</state>
                <state img="#-uncertain.png">I have many dreams, but one of them just came true!</state>
                <state img="#-smile.png">Those are almost as beautiful as your smile, ~name~!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_large_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8" oneShotId="24">
                <condition filter="huge_breasts" role="target" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png">In the name of the Seven Rings... those are &lt;i&gt;huge&lt;/i&gt;! I wouldn't know where to begin!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-content.png">I'd sure love to rest my head between those. You could gently stroke my hair, and I could sing the tale of the girl who cried demon.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Okay... be honest. How many deals did you have to make to get those?</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">With a chest &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; big, you must give the warmest, cuddliest hugs imaginable!</state>
                <state img="#-uncertain.png">It's funny how something as simple as a pair of big ol' honkers can derail my mind and suddenly I can't think of anything else.</state>
                <state img="#-content.png">I gotta say, ~name~, your breasts are almost as big as your heart!</state>
                <state img="#-content.png">My hands get really cold at night, but I think those would keep them warm just fine.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Something tells me you don't have any trouble making your special someone happy. Just a hunch.</state>
                <state img="#-consider.png">W-wow, ~name~. You've got such enormous... dreams! Yes, I can tell you dream big just by lookin' at ya.</state>
                <state img="#-uncertain.png">Whoa, &lt;i&gt;that's&lt;/i&gt; heavy. I-I mean your burdens. Troubles and woes. Your shoulders look so tense! Maybe a massage would help ease your stress?</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">It's rude to stare, I really shouldn't. Maybe just a peek? I mean, it would be just as rude not to appreciate such a generous bosom, right?</state>
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="1108" marker="+Sing">♫ &lt;i&gt;And now I have proof, though it was clear from the start: ~name~'s bosom is as big as my heart!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="mean" role="target" />
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="706" marker="+Sing">♫ &lt;i&gt;~Name~ snaps at us all; her mood's not inviting. But without all her clothes, this game got exciting!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="shy" role="target" />
                <state img="#-uncertain.png" oneShotId="708">Trust me, I know all about how it feels to be exposed in front of other people. If you keep your spirits high, the embarrassment will fade!</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="709">Nervous? Believe me, you have &lt;i&gt;nothing&lt;/i&gt; to be ashamed of.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="714" marker="+Sing">♫ &lt;i&gt;The fires of Hell are a deep crimson hue. With your chest bare, your face sure is, too!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">It's a good thing you're not in Hell. I don't think anyone would want to leave with &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; around!</state>
                <state img="#-uncertain.png">I'm just happy I've gotten to know ~name~ as a person!</state>
                <state img="#-uncertain.png">What better company to show off your buns and thighs, right, ~name~?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-flirt.png">Mmm... keep going... just like that...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="exhibitionist" role="target" />
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="488" marker="+Sing">♫ &lt;i&gt;~Name~'s eager to strip and lacking in shame. With a body like that, she's not one to blame!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="trimmed" role="target" />
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="489" marker="+Sing">♫ &lt;i&gt;To keep yourself trimmed, I say that's respectable. And I might I just add, you're looking delectable!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="5">
                <condition status="naked" role="target" />
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="490" marker="+Sing">♫ &lt;i&gt;Try not to look, try not to stare, as ~name~ stands before us naked and bare!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="491" marker="+Sing">♫ &lt;i&gt;~Name~'s nearing the end, unveiled before us all. Despite her condition, she stands proud and tall!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="492" marker="+Sing">♫ &lt;i&gt;~Name~ looks adorable, she's cute as a button. I think I find myself in love all of a sudden!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="493" marker="+Sing">♫ &lt;i&gt;Sing till you laugh, sing till you cry. You've lost your ~clothing~, so don't be shy!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">If you ever need a cuddle buddy...</state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png">I bet I can keep you warm, ~name~. &lt;i&gt;Without&lt;/i&gt; setting you on fire. </state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png">Talk about temptations!</state>
                <state img="#-consider.png">Something tells me you attract a lot of sinners. </state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png">Careful, ~name~. You're giving me sinful thoughts. </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_lost">
            <case stage="0-8" id="92" oneShotId="30" priority="391">
                <condition role="target" character="sucrose" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="sucrose_study">You look like the studious, type, Sucrose. Do you study hearts, or rainbows, or smiles? </state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="sucrose_read">I like your glasses, Sucrose! Are you a heavy reader? Do you read any fairytales? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="93" oneShotId="31" priority="391">
                <condition role="target" character="chara_dreemurr" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-excited.png" marker="chara_knife_cake">That's a shiny knife, Chara. Did you bring it to cut the cake you baked for us?</state>
                <state img="#-smile.png" marker="chara_knife_cook">What a pretty knife, Chara! You must be an excellent cook to have one so special. </state>
                <state img="#-excited.png" marker="chara_knife_cook">Ooooh, what a pretty knife, Chara! And it's my favorite color! You must be an excellent cook.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="108" oneShotId="42" priority="391">
                <condition role="target" character="miko" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="miko_sin_free">It's a pleasure to be playing with you, Miko. I hope you're living a life free of sin!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="miko_sin_free">I love your smile, Miko! You must live a very happy, sin-free life.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="111" oneShotId="45" priority="391">
                <condition role="target" character="saki_zls" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="saki_living">I'm really enjoying your vibe, Saki. You seem like you've truly &lt;i&gt;lived&lt;/i&gt;, you know? </state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="saki_living">I enjoy your company, Saki. I get the feeling you've really been living life to its fullest!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="112" oneShotId="46" priority="391">
                <condition role="target" character="saki_zls" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-flirt.png" marker="saki_bite">Saki, I love how powerful your voice is. It really has a &lt;i&gt;bite&lt;/i&gt; to it. You'd make a good demon!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_stripping">
            <case stage="0-8" id="48">
                <condition role="target" character="wikipe-tan" stage="1" />
                <test expr="~target.costume~" value="default" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="494" marker="WikiApronStrip1">Miss... Wikipe, was it? You seem to know a lot. About... well, everything. It's kind of concerning, actually.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="99" oneShotId="34">
                <condition role="target" character="chara_dreemurr" stage="0" saidMarker="ResponseCharlieCharaMustStrip1Cook" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="chara_cake_allergy">Oh my goodness! You must have forgotten about your Dad's food allergies, huh?</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="chara_cake_allergy">Oh no! Was your Dad allergic to something in the cake? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="100" oneShotId="35">
                <condition role="target" character="chara_dreemurr" stage="0" saidMarker="ResponseCharlieCharaMustStrip1Cake" />
                <state img="#-cheeky.png" marker="chara_cake_friendship">Because baking a cake is like making a new friend! With a little mixing of the right ingredients, and some time in the oven, you get a sweet reward!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="101" oneShotId="36">
                <condition role="target" character="chara_dreemurr" stage="0" saidMarker="ResponseCharlieCharaMustStrip1CakePerish" />
                <state img="#-cheeky.png" marker="chara_cake_perish">Perish is the perfect word, Chara! I would &lt;i&gt;die&lt;/i&gt; for one of your cakes!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="62">
                <condition role="target" character="chell_wheatley" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-smile.png" oneShotId="495" marker="ChellStrip1">Does this volleyball speak for you? I can't imagine having such eccentric vocalization equipment.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6 8" id="90">
                <condition filter="musician" role="target" stage="0-1" />
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="826" marker="musician_strip">So, ~name~, I hear that you're a musician! Is that true?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_stripped">
            <case stage="0-8" id="61">
                <condition role="target" character="wikipe-tan" stage="2" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="WikiApronStrip1" />
                <test expr="~target.costume~" value="default" />
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="496">♫ &lt;i&gt;Losing your apron's not that big a mess. I cannot wait 'til you take off your dress!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6 8" oneShotId="27">
                <condition filter="musician" role="target" stage="1-2" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="musician_strip" />
                <state img="#-content.png">Well, I happen to be musically-inclined myself! I think you and I will get along nicely!</state>
                <state img="#-cheeky.png">That's so cool! You and I have so much in common already!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">It's not &lt;i&gt;always&lt;/i&gt; sinful to think about someone who's special to you, and what you like about them. </state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png">Are you normally this deviant, ~name~? </state>
                <state img="#-giggle.png">Quite an extreme way to spread joy, isn't it?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_masturbating">
            <case stage="7">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-content.png" oneShotId="577">I'm glad we're doing this at the same time, ~name~. </state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png" oneShotId="578">This is a lot more fun when I have you around as inspiration, ~name~. </state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png" oneShotId="579">I hope you're not thinking any sinful thoughts about me, ~name~. </state>
                <state img="#-content.png" oneShotId="580">Think you can last longer than me, ~name~? I have my doubts. </state>
                <state img="#-uncertain.png" oneShotId="581">This is a bit of a strange bonding moment for the two of us, isn't it, ~name~? </state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png" oneShotId="582">Are you happy we're both doing this together, ~name~? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6 8">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-giggle.png" oneShotId="589">~Name~, I must admit, watching you do this is a lot more fun than I anticipated. </state>
                <state img="#-uncertain.png" oneShotId="590">Do you do this a lot, ~name~? You sure seem to know your way around ~name~ junior. </state>
                <state img="#-giggle.png" oneShotId="591">Please don't stop, ~name~. I like where this is going. </state>
                <state img="#-uncertain.png" oneShotId="592">I hope you're okay with me watching, ~name~. I just can't help myself.</state>
                <state img="#-uncertain.png" oneShotId="593">Something about you feels very special to me, ~name~. M-maybe this is an awkward time to say that...</state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png" oneShotId="594">~Name~, be honest. Are you thinking of me as you're doing this?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6 8">
                <state img="#-excited.png">I hope you're enjoying yourself, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">You've done this &lt;i&gt;many times&lt;/i&gt; before, haven't you, ~name~? </state>
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="573">Wow, ~target.ifMale(he|she)~ is just getting &lt;i&gt;right&lt;/i&gt; into it, eh? Not even having any troubles. I'm honestly impressed.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">If ~name~ can be a good sport and masturbate in front of all of us, we can cheer ~target.ifMale(him|her)~ on at the very least!</state>
                <state img="#-giggle.png">If nothing else, at least ~name~ is having a good time! </state>
                <state img="#-delighted.png">Go get 'em, ~name~! </state>
                <state img="#-giggle.png">Don't be embarrassed, ~name~! Everyone does it. </state>
                <state img="#-uncertain.png">Imagine  how many people have wanted to see ~name~ do this.</state>
                <state img="#-sing.png" oneShotId="1141" marker="+Sing">♫ &lt;i&gt;~target.ifMale(He's doing his|She's doing her)~ best, and I think that's neat. I never thought I'd watch ~name~ beat ~target.ifMale(his|her)~ meat!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0-6 8">
                <state img="#-uncertain.png">Do you have stage fright, ~name~? I'd understand that. I might look like a natural-born performer, but I have my moments, too.</state>
                <state img="#-uncertain.png">Don't worry, ~name~, you are not alone! ...Or is that exactly the problem?</state>
                <state img="#-consider.png">Should... should I be watching this? I really don't know... It wouldn't hurt anybody, right? We're all friends here...</state>
                <state img="#-uncertain.png">Is this your first time doing this in front of others, ~name~? I can imagine how difficult that might be.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-flirt.png">If it helps, you can watch me. Consider me your encouragement!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-flirt.png">So... do you do this often, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-consider.png">Can you imagine if this game were just between the two of us?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-giggle.png">There's no way you're &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; well practiced, right, ~name~? You're a good soul, aren't you?</state>
                <state img="#-content.png">At least this time I'm not seeing it from the corner of my eye down a back alley. </state>
                <state img="#-content.png">I give you permission to think of me if you want to. </state>
                <state img="#-giggle.png">It's supposed to be a "punishment" for losing, but ~name~ isn't making his situation look bad at all!</state>
                <state img="#-content.png">I must admit this is a weird context for it, but I always enjoy seeing others happy. </state>
                <state img="#-consider.png">Is ~name~ ever going to finish?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-flirt.png">I hope you're not empty. </state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png">Did you leave any in the tank for later?</state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png">If you're not completely dry now, you will be...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">It's only sinful if you don't clean up your mess. </state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Well, then. That was a lot more than I expected. </state>
                <state img="#-uncertain.png">That's... a lot of joy!</state>
                <state img="#-uncertain.png">It's nice that you can make yourself feel so good...!</state>
                <state img="#-consider.png">You, uh... really went to town there, didn't you? </state>
                <state img="#-consider.png">You're planning on cleaning that, right? ...Gosh, now I'm just wondering what Niffty would think if you &lt;i&gt;didn't&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-uncertain.png">Wow, it looks like you, uh, &lt;i&gt;needed&lt;/i&gt; that. Um, I hope it was good!</state>
                <state img="#-content.png">I think we should all let ~name~ catch his breath. </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0-8" id="38">
                <condition role="target" character="nagisa" sayingMarker="nagisa_play" />
                <state img="#-excited.png">Yes, that's a perfect way of thinking about it, Nagisa! Imagine you're putting on a performance!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6 8">
                <condition count="2-" status="exposed" role="other" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png">If it helps, try to imagine us all naked! ...Which almost all of us are. So I guess you're not imagining much.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-uncertain.png">Is this your first time doing this in front of others, ~name~? I can imagine how difficult that might be.</state>
                <state img="#-uncertain.png">Don't worry, ~name~, you are not alone! ...Or is that exactly the problem?</state>
                <state img="#-consider.png">Should... should I be watching this? I really don't know... It wouldn't hurt anybody, right? We're all friends here...</state>
                <state img="#-uncertain.png">Do you have stage fright, ~name~? I'd understand that. I might look like a natural-born performer, but I have my moments, too.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-excited.png">Join me, ~name~! We can be masturbation buddies! ...th-that's a thing, right?</state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png">If it helps, you can watch me. Consider me your encouragement!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6 8">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">If it helps, try to imagine us all naked! ...Which some of us already are. That sounded a lot better in my head...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-content.png">You can share what you're thinking about, if you want. </state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png">Who do you normally think about when you do this, ~name~? </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8" id="50">
                <condition role="target" character="wikipe-tan" sayingMarker="wikiwiki" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="497">Does... does repeating that word help?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="32" priority="0">
                <condition role="target" />
                <alternative>
                    <condition filter="bisexual" role="target" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <condition filter="lesbian" role="target" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <condition filter="bi-curious" role="target" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-flirt.png">If you're having trouble, ~name~, feel free to think of me if you want. I don't mind.</state>
                <state img="#-delighted.png">Are you... thinking of me while doing this? I must admit, I am flattered if so!</state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png">Try to save some for later, ~name~. </state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png">How's it feeling over there, ~name~? Need anything?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-smile.png">Don't worry, ~name~. Lust is only sinful if it comes in unhealthy amounts. </state>
                <state img="#-giggle.png">I didn't expect ~name~ to get so into it! Not that I'm complaining. </state>
                <state img="#-giggle.png">You're on your way down to the third ring of Hell at this rate, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Is it rude to look? I mean, this is what we came to see, isn't it?</state>
                <state img="#-uncertain.png">I hope it's not to distasteful to like, you know, take a few quick glances...</state>
                <state img="#-uncertain.png">You don't have to worry about word getting out or anything, ~name~. I don't think anyone in Hell even knows you—not that I would do such a thing anyway!</state>
                <state img="#-giggle.png">I hope someone brought a towel or something. ~Name~'s on a roll. </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="exhibitionist" role="target" />
                <state img="#-uncertain.png">So, ~name~... was it good? I can tell you've been looking forward to this.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-uncertain.png">Wow! Are you giving lessons, ~name~? </state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png">I hope you didn't exhaust yourself &lt;i&gt;too&lt;/i&gt; much.</state>
                <state img="#-content.png">I bet this won't be the last time I see you do that. </state>
                <state img="#-giggle.png">Aren't life's pleasures beautiful and mighty? </state>
                <state img="#-content.png">I think we should all let ~name~ catch her breath. </state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Looks like &lt;i&gt;someone&lt;/i&gt; had a good time!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-smile.png">Was it everything you hoped it would be?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Congratulations... n-now just a bit more and I'll be right there with you...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate_first">
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-pout.png">&lt;i&gt;Doh!&lt;/i&gt; I really shouldn't have been so aggressive with my cards!</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Oh... oh dear, I'm first. I'm really getting put on the spot now...</state>
                <state img="#-uncertain.png">Oh well. I'm used to providing the inspiration, anyway. </state>
                <state img="#-uncertain.png">Technically, &lt;i&gt;I'm&lt;/i&gt; the winner, because I get to do this first! </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate">
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-uncertain.png">Well... self love isn't a &lt;i&gt;bad&lt;/i&gt; thing, right?</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">It's not a sin if it's the rule, right? &lt;i&gt;Right?&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">It's about time. I thought I was going to get blue balled. </state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png">Is this what you wanted, ~player~? You naughty ~player.ifMale(boy|little lady)~.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="start_masturbating">
            <case stage="6" id="88">
                <state img="#-zstripping.png">I'm getting butterflies in my stomach. Hopefully they're the pretty kind. </state>
                <state img="#-zstripping.png">Why am I so nervous? This isn't the first time I've done this with other people...</state>
                <state img="#-zstripping.png">I hope I don't accidentally make any goofy faces. </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="masturbating">
            <case stage="7" id="77" oneShotId="16" priority="666">
                <state img="#-start.png">In any case, I've had two hundred years of practice. Watch and learn. </state>
                <state img="#-start.png">Here's a little secret... I &lt;i&gt;may&lt;/i&gt; have been looking forward to this outcome...</state>
                <state img="#-start.png">Isn't it weird how this game rewards you for playing badly? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="851">There's nothing better after a long day than coming home  to a warm kiss on the cheek from someone you love...</state>
                <state img="#-delighted.png" oneShotId="852">You know your partner is special when they save the last chocolate in the box for you!</state>
                <state img="#-content.png" oneShotId="853">I think I'll add this to my fun activities list. </state>
                <state img="#-giggle.png" oneShotId="854">It's surprising how often hair ends up in your mouth when you're sharing your love with a nice lady. </state>
                <state img="#-content.png" oneShotId="855">I love it when a bilingual person gets so into it that they blurt their feelings in their native tongue. </state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png" oneShotId="848" weight="2">Do you like seeing me like this, ~player~? It's okay, we can let that sin slide. </state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png" oneShotId="849" weight="2">It's okay, ~player~. You can watch me. </state>
                <state img="#-consider.png" oneShotId="850" weight="2">I hope you're not thinking of anything &lt;i&gt;too&lt;/i&gt; naughty, ~player~. </state>
                <state img="#-consider.png" oneShotId="856">Am I putting on a good show? </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="heavy_masturbating">
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-content.png" oneShotId="834">(She kisses my neck, and plays with my hair...)</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="835">(She unbuttons my sweaty shirt and peels it off after a long day...)</state>
                <state img="#-content.png" oneShotId="836">(I pull down her dress straps, my hands running up and down her back...)</state>
                <state img="#-content.png" oneShotId="837">(My fingers run through her hair as I whisper in her ear...)</state>
                <state img="#-cheeky.png" oneShotId="838">(That birthday cake she made me was so thoughtful. It had all six of my favorite flavors!) </state>
                <state img="#-content.png" oneShotId="839">(Smooth jazz, a steamy bathtub, the smell of lilacs in the air...)</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="840">(The soft touch of her hands on my back, sliding back and forth like the falling tides on a gentle beach...)</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="841">(Her lips are so graceful and comforting...)</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finishing_masturbating">
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-finish.png">&lt;i&gt;There's a rainbow inside me!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-finish.png">&lt;i&gt;¡Te amo mi amiga de pelo blanco!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-finish.png">&lt;i&gt;My soul is smiling!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="8" id="81" oneShotId="22">
                <state img="#-towel.png" marker="towel">Mmmh... I haven't done that for so long... I've been so tense since the hotel has opened...</state>
                <state img="#-towel.png" marker="towel">W-wow... I haven't gotten to relax like that since the hotel opened...</state>
                <state img="#-towel.png" marker="towel">Self pleasure isn't a sin. Your body has needs. </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="after_masturbating">
            <case stage="8" oneShotId="17" priority="10">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="VisitHell" />
                <state img="#-uncertain.png">Now that I think of it, I wonder if tourism into Hell would be possible? A number of demons back there would definitely see it as a window of opportunity.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="82">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="fat_nuggets" />
                <state img="#-uncertain.png">I hope nobody shows up at the Hotel while I'm gone. I'm sure our friends could handle it, though. Right, Nuggy?</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">I think the first thing I'll do when I get back home is take a nice, hot shower. </state>
                <state img="#-giggle.png">I remember the first day I laid eyes on this cute little piggy. He tracked dirt on the hotel floor, but I wasn't even mad. Isn't he &lt;i&gt;precious?!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-smile.png">I bet this feels like home to Fat Nuggets with what his owner gets up to!</state>
                <state img="#-uncertain.png">I sure am glad I had a towel to wash myself off before you came here, Nuggy. This would be pretty awkward otherwise!</state>
                <state img="#-giggle.png">How is Angel doing, Nuggy? He hasn't been getting in any more trouble while I'm gone, has he?</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="626" marker="CharliePet">There really is nothing like having a companion to pet, love, and kiss! Do any of you have a pet that you cherish?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="627" marker="VisitHell">I would &lt;i&gt;love&lt;/i&gt; for any of you to visit me and this little piggy in Hell, if you could find a way to do it!</state>
                <state img="#-smile.png">Pigs are surprisingly smart! They can learn tricks and respond to commands! </state>
                <state img="#-uncertain.png">After meeting Fat Nuggets, I just couldn't bring myself to eat bacon for breakfast anymore!</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Is there anything better than a romantic dinner with gentle live music and a smoking hot date?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_victory">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-smile.png">I'm still surprised that I won! But this was still a great experience for me, ~player~, and I had a helluva time!</state>
                <state img="#-uncertain.png">You know, ~player~, I could always use a hand at the Hotel! But... that would require that you die first, so no rush or anything!</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">I hope my tremendous success at this game is inspiring all of you to think positively!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-happy.png">This was an enlightening experience, ~player~! </state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">Don't feel so down, ~player~. Now you can tell your friends you've seen a demon's underwear before!</state>
                <state img="#-sing.png">♫ &lt;i&gt;Though not lacking in skill, I'm surprised that I won. The game may be over, but it sure was fun!&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6">
                <state img="#-delighted.png">Well, you certainly saw... another side of me, but I hope you had fun, ~player~! I know I sure did!</state>
                <state img="#-smile.png">This was a good time for all, and I'm glad to finally have a taste of the human world! </state>
                <state img="#-consider.png">Phew, that was a close one... now if you'll excuse me, I need to get back to work before our patrons wreck the place!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-happy.png">The &lt;i&gt;real&lt;/i&gt; victory is the hearts I've touched with my cheer and song!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I hope I've helped all of you smile! That's more important to me than winning a game. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-dab.png">Bam! Not a single loss. That's the power of positivity!</state>
                <state img="#-dab.png">Positive thinking is undefeated!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_defeat">
            <case stage="8">
                <condition role="self" notSaidMarker="fat_nuggets" />
                <state img="#-pigless.png">Look... promise me none of you will tell my dad or anyone else about this, okay? I don't want the Hotel's reputation ruined &lt;i&gt;more&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-pigless.png">Well, ~player~, I think we all learned a lesson or two today about each other. I hope you keep that in mind after you leave!</state>
                <state img="#-pigless.png">I hope you had a good time, ~player~! Now I should probably clean off before I head back to Hell...</state>
                <state img="#-pigless.png">So I still failed... but in a way, I also won! That counts for something!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-consider.png">If any of you happen to die soon, I'd prefer that you keep this on the down low.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Well, ~player~, I think we've all learned something about each other! I hope to see you again, soon.</state>
                <state img="#-delighted.png">I hope you had a good time, ~player~! Now I should probably clean off before Nugs and I head back to Hell...</state>
                <state img="#-delighted.png">So I still failed... but in a way, I also won! That counts for something!</state>
                <state img="#-delighted.png">So I lost the game, but it doesn't count as losing if I had fun doing it!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="global">
            <case stage="8" id="83" oneShotId="8" priority="666">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="fat_nuggets" />
                <state img="#-giggle.png" marker="pig_react">You little rascal! I've grown on you quickly, haven't I? </state>
                <state img="#-giggle.png" marker="pig_react">This place must feel like home with what your owner gets up to!</state>
                <state img="#-giggle.png" marker="pig_react">How am I supposed to tell Angel Dust I played strip poker with his pig? He'd probably be upset I didn't invite him...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="84" oneShotId="23" priority="666">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="pig_react" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="pig_introduce">Everyone, I'd like you to meet Fat Nuggets! He belongs to one of my patrons. Isn't he precious? </state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="pig_introduce">This is my pal, Fat Nuggets. I hope he becomes your pal, too!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="pig_introduce">This little guy is Fat Nuggets: cutest damn pig at the Happy Hotel!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="87" oneShotId="29" priority="666">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="towel" notSaidMarker="fat_nuggets" />
                <state img="#-pigless.png" marker="pigless">My philosophy only works if you believe there's greatness in everybody. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="86" oneShotId="28" priority="666">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="pigless" />
                <state img="custom:get-piggy" marker="fat_nuggets">*Oh!* Nuggy! How did you get here?</state>
                <state img="custom:get-piggy" marker="fat_nuggets">N-Nuggy! Did you follow me here?</state>
                <state img="custom:get-piggy" marker="fat_nuggets">Huh? Nuggy? What are you doing here?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6 8" id="64" oneShotId="9" priority="142">
                <condition role="other" character="wikipe-tan" stage="8" saidMarker="Reliable_source_loop2" sayingMarker="Reliable_source_loop3" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Miss Wiki, &lt;i&gt;stahp!&lt;/i&gt; You're making my brain hurt!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="114" priority="103">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="fat_nuggets" />
                <condition role="other" character="fluttershy" saidMarker="Charlie_lovely_nuggets" sayingMarker="Charlie_pet_liitle_nuggets" />
                <state img="#-amused.png" marker="FluttershyNugs">I'm sure Nuggy would love that! He loves meeting new people!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

    </behaviour>
</opponent>
