<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<metadata>
    <owner>florina</owner>
    <noteworthy>
        <case name="Ran away from men" id="4" priority="MustTarget" min="0" max="0">
            <description>Florina has run away from the room after losing for the first time, but only if there is a man present (she's terrified of men)</description>
        </case>
        <case name="Attempted to flee" priority="Noteworthy" min="4" max="4">
            <description>When Florina has to remove her tunic, she tries to run away, but Lyn stops her</description>
            <trigger tag="stripping" stage="4" alsoPlaying="lyn" alsoPlayingStage="1-8">
                <state img="run_lyn_1.png">Ahhh! L-Lyn!!!</state>
                <state img="run_lyn_1.png">L-Lady Lyndis!!!</state>
                <state img="run_lyn_1.png">Come on, Florina. You can't always run off like that.</state>
                <state img="run_lyn_1.png">Stick around, Florina. I know you can do it.</state>
            </trigger>
        </case>
        <case name="Bee attack 1" id="5" priority="MustTarget" min="4" max="4">
            <description>A bee flies in front of Florina, causing her to panic and rip off her tunic to shoo it away.</description>
        </case>
        <case name="Bee attack 2" id="6" priority="MustTarget" min="6" max="6">
            <description>The bee makes a return, and Florina pulls off her bra in a panic.</description>
        </case>
        <case name="Singing finish" id="7" priority="Noteworthy" min="9" max="9">
            <description>Florina is singing a song to herself while masturbating to distract herself from what she's doing in front of everyone</description>
        </case>
        <case name="Butt pose" id="8" priority="Noteworthy" min="8" max="8">
            <description>Florina just took off her panties facing backwards, and will play the next hand like that.</description>
        </case>
    </noteworthy>
    <reviewed>true</reviewed>
    <responses>
        <response id="1" opponent="chihiro" opponentId="1" />
        <response id="2" opponent="chihiro" opponentId="2" />
        <response id="3" opponent="lucina" opponentId="1" />
        <response id="9" opponent="ae86" opponentId="1" />
        <response id="10" opponent="ae86" opponentId="4" />
        <response id="11" opponent="merlin" opponentId="47" />
        <response id="12" opponent="hermione" opponentId="1" />
        <response id="13" opponent="shantae" opponentId="10" />
    </responses>
    <nextId>13</nextId>
    <markers>
        <marker scope="Public" name="2corrins">Comment about both Corrins playing</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="9s_blindfold">Remark about 9S not being able to see with a blindfold</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="9s_nines">Asks if she can call him Nines</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="amalia_clothes">Asks if Amalia's clothes are made from leaves</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="apologize">Florina apologizes for saying sorry too much</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="beatrix_scared">Florina comments on it being hard to play with Beatrix scaring her</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="bee">Set when Florina first mentions seeing a bee. This is the trigger that will cause a bee to attack her when stripping her tunic</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="bee_again">2nd time commenting on seeing a bee</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="bee_lyn">Florina mentions to Lyn that the first time they met, Florina was being attacked by bees</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="bee_stop">Prevents the bee strip sequence from occuring</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="bee2">Set after stripping her tunic with a bee attacking</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="bee2b">Casual remark about hearing the bee again. It doesn't actually drive any behavior</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="bee3">Set when stripping her bra with the bee coming back</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="bee4">Use privately to comment on losing her bra later because she was too distracted during the strip sequence</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="belt">When someone else takes off a belt, Florina mentions that she wasn't sure if belts counted</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="belt_offer">Florina offers her belt to someone</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="blackrose_marks">She asks about the marks on Blackrose's legs</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="blake_mom">Remark about Blake playing with her mom</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="butt">Florina is showing her butt while stripping</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="butt_over">Florina turned her back after taking off her panties and is playing looking the other way</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="cameras">Mention about multiple cameras being at the game</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="cammy_clothes">Remark about Cammy's clothes being unconventional for fighting</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="catria_breasts">Florina comments about how she imagined Catria's breasts to be</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="catria_confess">Florina blurts out about Catria being a dream come true</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="catria_invite">She invites Catria to go riding their pegasi together</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="catria_song">While they're both forfeiting, Florina wonders if Catria is fantasizing about her</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="catria_song2">Florina starts to fantasize about Catria while they're both forfeiting. She will yell out Catria's name upon climaxing.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="chair">Florina pulls up a chair after climaxing, which she'll sit on for the rest of the game.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="chihiro_reveal">Comment when Chihiro reveals his crotch</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="clothing_socks">one-time remark about how she lost her boots but had no socks underneath</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="corrin_f_feet">Remarks about Corrin's bare feet</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="crash">Set after remarking about landing her pegasus on another character</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="dumb">Set after saying something dumb while a male reveals their crotch</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="dumb_over">Set during the next swap cards phase after realizing she said something dumb</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="dumb_say">When this is set, it means she will blurt something dumb when the next male reveals their crotch</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="dumb2">Set after saying something dumb the 2nd time a male reveals their crotch</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="dumb2_over">Set during the next swap cards phase after the 2nd time she says something dumb about a male's crotch</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="dumb2_say">Set to prep saying something dumb about a male's crotch</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="dva_cheat_reaction">Response to D.Va complaining about another character cheating</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="early_exit">Florina starts to leave after losing while in her underwear, when nobody has exposed themselves yet, thinking she is out of the game</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="early_exit_end">Used during the stripping phase after trying to leave early upon learning that she still has to strip naked</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="easter_man">Comment about her easter outfit when in front of a man</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="elizabeth_friends">Asks if she can be friends with Elizabeth</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="elizabeth_portal">Florina can't focus on playing while Elizabeth is having portal shenanigans</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="exhibitionist">Florina beings to realize that her extreme shyness actually turns her on</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="expose_chest">Florina shows her nipples for the first time and will comment on it in the next phase</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="expose_crotch">Florina shows her vagina for the first time and will comment on it in the next phass</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="exposed_chest">Once this is set, she won't comment about her nipslips anymore</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="exposed_crotch">Once this is set, she won't comment about flashing her crotch anymore</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="exposed_lyn">One time response about exposing herself around Lyn</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="fast_undies">One time response about ending up in her underwear within the first ten hands</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="finished">Used to give a one time response after finishing</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="first_deal">First time cards are being dealt</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="first_exposed">Set when Florina is the first to end up exposed</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="first_exposed2">Set when another female exposes herself after Florina was the first</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="first_loss">Contains the name of the first character to lose the game</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="first_nude">Contains the name of the first character to end up naked</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="first_partial">Contains the name of the first character to end up topless or bottomless (only bottomless for males)</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="fled">When this is set, Florina will run away during her first stripping sequence. This happens if a man is present</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="fled_lyn">Set once she attempts to run away from the game but Lyn stops her</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="fled_mulan">Tracks that she ran away from the game because Ping was there, thinking Ping was a man</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="futaba_music">Response to Futaba's question about music</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="greet_aimee">One time greeting towards Aimee</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="greet_alice">One time greeting towards Alice</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="greet_alpha">One time greeting towards Alpha</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="greet_arwen">One time greeting towards Arwen</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="greet_catria">One time greeting towards Catria</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="greet_catria2">part 2</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="greet_catria3">part 3</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="greet_catria4">part 4</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="greet_palutena">One time greeting towards Palutena</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="hair_down">After finishing, Florina's hair ties fell out so she's pushing her hair out of the way</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="hermione_lotte">When Hermione and Lotte are playing, she asks if they go to the same school</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="huey">Set when Florina remarks about having a pegasus named Huey</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="huey_catria">Response to Catria about Huey the pegasus</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="human_reaction">Florina will comment on certain player names. This flags that she has done so.</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="item_jacket">one time remark about losing her jacket</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="item_socks">one time remark about losing socks</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="jura_lyn">Response to Jura talking about her an Lyn being a copule</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="jura_men">Remark about no men where Jura is from, and how that would be nice</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="kali_mom">Remark about playing with someone's mom</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="last_item">Contains the name of the last item that an opponent removed</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="launch_nice">Remark about Launch being nicer in her blue hair form.</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="left_out">Tracks that she is playing against 3 characters who are from the same source</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="line1">Line 1 of Pegasus Counting Song</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="line10">Line 10 of Pegasus Counting Song</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="line11">Line 11 of Pegasus Counting Song</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="line12">Line 12 of Pegasus Counting Song</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="line2">Line 2 of Pegasus Counting Song</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="line3">Line 3 of Pegasus Counting Song</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="line4">Line 4 of Pegasus Counting Song</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="line5">Line 5 of Pegasus Counting Song</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="line6">Line 6 of Pegasus Counting Song</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="line7">Line 7 of Pegasus Counting Song</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="line8">Line 8 of Pegasus Counting Song</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="line9">Line 9 of Pegasus Counting Song</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="lonely">Remark about the other 3 AI players being friends and how she feels left out. Used when the other 3 are from the same group</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="lonely_player">Florina asks the (female) player if they can be friends, since everyone else in the game is from the same group</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="lost_extra">Counts how many accessories each player has lost</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="lost_major">Counts how many major items each player has lost</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="lost_minor">Counts how many minor items each player has lost</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="lyn_bottomless">Set once Lyn is bottomless</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="lyn_bouquet">Florina doesn't want Lyn's bouquet</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="lyn_streak">One time remark about Lyn losing several in a row</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="lyn_wedding">Commenting about Lyn's wedding alt</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="mahiru_bee">Florina desires to destroy the pictures of the bee that was tormenting her</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="mahiru_finish_camera">Comment about Mahiru masturbating with a camera</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="mahiru_pic">Florina worries about Mahiru taking her picture upon climaxing</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="man">Contains the name of the first man that Florina identified in game</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="marth_reveal">Florina talks about using a mask like Marth to hide from men</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="masturbater">Contains the name of the most recent person to masturbate, if anyone still is</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="mei_chinese">Remark about Mei speaking Chinese</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="mei_coat">Remark about Mei wearing a big coat</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="monika_glitch">Remark when Monika is glitching things</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="mulan_secret">When Mulan makes a challenge for the first to get naked, Florina responds dubiously because she didn't think there was any nudity in the game</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="mulan_secret_reject">When Florina is topless and Mulan makes a challenge about the first to get naked sharing a secret, Florina passes because everyone knows her secret</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="naked_early">One time remark about someone being naked before Florina has lost</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="naked_fun">One time remark when exposed with other people in various states of nudity that she might actually be having fun</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="nayru_armor">tracks that she is taking off her armor after Nayra suggested it</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="nugi_sph">One time remark about Nugi-chan saying something mean about a male's small member</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="panties_butt">Florina is going to show her butt while stripping. This might get cleared before she actually does so.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="remark_rules">Set once someone has revealed an important item and she releases it's strip poker all the way</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="remark_started">Comment about the first time someone takes something minor or higher off.</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="remark_started2">People have started taking off non-accessories, but Florina is still under the impression that players lose upon reaching their underwear</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="revy_mean">Florina asks Revy to be nicer</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="rules">Set once Florina has learned the rules involve stripping your underwear</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="rules_lyn">One time remark when Lyn isn't present about having to get naked</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="rwby">One time remark about playing with all RWBY members</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="sei_drink">One time remark about Sei offering drinks</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="shantae_dancer">Remark about Shantae being a dancer like her friend Ninian from Fire Emblem</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="shaved_for_lyn">Florina comments about shaving her pubes for Lyn's sake</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="shimakaze_robot">Florina comments about Shimakaze's robot being cute</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="started">Set after the first minor or higher item has been removed to signify that the stripping has really started</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="streak_extra">Tracks how many extra items have been removed in a row per opponent</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="streak_major">Tracks how many major items have been removed in a row per opponent</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="streak_minor">Tracks how many minor items have been removed in a row per opponent</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="strip_bottom">Tracks that a character's bottom important was removed before their top and stores the item name for usage later</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="tickle">Denotes that Florina said something about her pegasus tickling her during masturbation</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="tickled">Used right before tickle</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="topless_long">Set when Florina has been the only one topless for several rounds, indicating her embarrassment about it</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="total_extra">Tracks total accessories lost across table</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="total_major">Tracks total major items lost across table</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="total_minor">Tracks total minor items lost across table</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="tripped">She fell over when taking off her boots.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="underwear_knights">Florina suggests to Catria that they be the Pegasus Knights when both are in their underwear together.</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="underwear_knights2">2nd time she uses this if both her and Catria are topless together</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="underwear_okay">After being in her underwear multiple rounds, Florina starts to get used to it.</marker>
        <marker scope="Private" name="underwear_over">Comment about feeling sheepish for going all in with the underwear knights</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="underwear_wins">Tracks how many rounds she and Catria have won while in their underwear together</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="uniform">Comment about a character wearing a school uniform</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="videl_father">Florina comments about wanting to meet Videl's father someday, since she has met lots of strong men</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="videl_fly">Remark about Videl flying without a pegasus</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="winner_prize">Florina offers the winner a ride on her pegasus</marker>
    </markers>
</metadata>
