<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<markers>
    <marker scope="Public" name="2corrins">Comment about both Corrins playing</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="9s_blindfold">Remark about 9S not being able to see with a blindfold</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="9s_nines">Asks if she can call him Nines</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="amalia_clothes">Asks if Amalia's clothes are made from leaves</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="apologize">Florina apologizes for saying sorry too much</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="beatrix_scared">Florina comments on it being hard to play with Beatrix scaring her</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="bee">Set when Florina first mentions seeing a bee. This is the trigger that will cause a bee to attack her when stripping her tunic</marker>
    <marker scope="Private" name="bee_again">2nd time commenting on seeing a bee</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="bee_lyn">Florina mentions to Lyn that the first time they met, Florina was being attacked by bees</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="bee_stop">Prevents the bee strip sequence from occuring</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="bee2">Set after stripping her tunic with a bee attacking</marker>
    <marker scope="Private" name="bee2b">Casual remark about hearing the bee again. It doesn't actually drive any behavior</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="bee3">Set when stripping her bra with the bee coming back</marker>
    <marker scope="Private" name="bee4">Use privately to comment on losing her bra later because she was too distracted during the strip sequence</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="blackrose_marks">She asks about the marks on Blackrose's legs</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="blake_mom" />
    <marker scope="Public" name="butt">Florina is showing her butt while stripping</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="butt_over">Florina turned her back after taking off her panties and is playing looking the other way</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="butt_over2">Florina turned forward again after playing for a bit with her back turned while naked</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="cammy_clothes">Remark about Cammy's clothes being unconventional for fighting</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="catria_invite">She invites Catria to go riding their pegasi together</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="catria_song">While they're both forfeiting, Florina wonders if Catria is fantasizing about her</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="catria_song2">Florina starts to fantasize about Catria while they're both forfeiting. She will yell out Catria's name upon climaxing.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="chair">Florina pulls up a chair after climaxing, which she'll sit on for the rest of the game.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="corrin_f_feet">Remarks about Corrin's bare feet</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="crash">Set after remarking about landing her pegasus on another character</marker>
    <marker scope="Private" name="dumb">Set after saying something dumb while a male reveals their crotch</marker>
    <marker scope="Private" name="dumb_over">Set during the next swap cards phase after realizing she said something dumb</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="dumb_say">When this is set, it means she will blurt something dumb when the next male reveals their crotch</marker>
    <marker scope="Private" name="dumb2">Set after saying something dumb the 2nd time a male reveals their crotch</marker>
    <marker scope="Private" name="dumb2_over">Set during the next swap cards phase after the 2nd time she says something dumb about a male's crotch</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="dumb2_say">Set to prep saying something dumb about a male's crotch</marker>
    <marker scope="Private" name="dva_cheat_reaction">Response to D.Va complaining about another character cheating</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="elizabeth_friends">Asks if she can be friends with Elizabeth</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="elizabeth_portal">Florina can't focus on playing while Elizabeth is having portal shenanigans</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="expose_chest">Florina shows her nipples for the first time and will comment on it in the next phase</marker>
    <marker scope="Private" name="expose_crotch">Florina shows her vagina for the first time and will comment on it in the next phass</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="exposed_chest">Once this is set, she won't comment about her nipslips anymore</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="exposed_crotch">Once this is set, she won't comment about flashing her crotch anymore</marker>
    <marker scope="Private" name="exposed_lyn">One time response about exposing herself around Lyn</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="fast_undies">One time response about ending up in her underwear within the first ten hands</marker>
    <marker scope="Private" name="finished">Used to give a one time response after finishing</marker>
    <marker scope="Private" name="first_deal">First time cards are being dealt</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="first_exposed">Set when Florina is the first to end up exposed</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="first_exposed2">Set when another female exposes herself after Florina was the first</marker>
    <marker scope="Private" name="first_loss">Contains the name of the first character to lose the game</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="first_nude">Contains the name of the first character to end up naked</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="first_partial" />
    <marker scope="Public" name="fled">When this is set, Florina will run away during her first stripping sequence. This happens if a man is present</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="fled_lyn">Set once she attempts to run away from the game but Lyn stops her</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="greet_aimee">One time greeting towards Aimee</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="greet_alice">One time greeting towards Alice</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="greet_alpha">One time greeting towards Alpha</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="greet_arwen">One time greeting towards Arwen</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="greet_catria">One time greeting towards Catria</marker>
    <marker scope="Private" name="greet_catria2">part 2</marker>
    <marker scope="Private" name="greet_catria3">part 3</marker>
    <marker scope="Private" name="greet_catria4">part 4</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="greet_palutena">One time greeting towards Palutena</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="hair_down">After finishing, Florina's hair ties fell out so she's pushing her hair out of the way</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="hermione_lotte" />
    <marker scope="Public" name="huey">Set when Florina remarks about having a pegasus named Huey</marker>
    <marker scope="Private" name="huey_catria">Response to Catria about Huey the pegasus</marker>
    <marker scope="Private" name="human_reaction">Florina will comment on certain player names. This flags that she has done so.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="jura_lyn" />
    <marker scope="Public" name="jura_men" />
    <marker scope="Public" name="kali_mom" />
    <marker scope="Private" name="last_item">Contains the name of the last item that an opponent removed</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="launch_nice" />
    <marker scope="Public" name="left_out" />
    <marker scope="Private" name="line1">Line 1 of Pegasus Counting Song</marker>
    <marker scope="Private" name="line10">Line 10 of Pegasus Counting Song</marker>
    <marker scope="Private" name="line11">Line 11 of Pegasus Counting Song</marker>
    <marker scope="Private" name="line12">Line 12 of Pegasus Counting Song</marker>
    <marker scope="Private" name="line2">Line 2 of Pegasus Counting Song</marker>
    <marker scope="Private" name="line3">Line 3 of Pegasus Counting Song</marker>
    <marker scope="Private" name="line4">Line 4 of Pegasus Counting Song</marker>
    <marker scope="Private" name="line5">Line 5 of Pegasus Counting Song</marker>
    <marker scope="Private" name="line6">Line 6 of Pegasus Counting Song</marker>
    <marker scope="Private" name="line7">Line 7 of Pegasus Counting Song</marker>
    <marker scope="Private" name="line8">Line 8 of Pegasus Counting Song</marker>
    <marker scope="Private" name="line9">Line 9 of Pegasus Counting Song</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="lonely" />
    <marker scope="Public" name="lonely_player" />
    <marker scope="Private" name="lost_extra">Counts how many accessories each player has lost</marker>
    <marker scope="Private" name="lost_major">Counts how many major items each player has lost</marker>
    <marker scope="Private" name="lost_minor">Counts how many minor items each player has lost</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="lyn_streak">One time remark about Lyn losing several in a row</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="mahiru_bee">Florina desires to destroy the pictures of the bee that was tormenting her</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="mahiru_finish_camera">Comment about Mahiru masturbating with a camera</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="mahiru_pic">Florina worries about Mahiru taking her picture upon climaxing</marker>
    <marker scope="Private" name="man">Contains the name of the first man that Florina identified in game</marker>
    <marker scope="Private" name="masturbater">Contains the name of the most recent person to masturbate, if anyone still is</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="mei_chinese" />
    <marker scope="Public" name="mei_coat" />
    <marker scope="Public" name="monika_glitch" />
    <marker scope="Private" name="naked_early">One time remark about someone being naked before Florina has lost</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="naked_fun" />
    <marker scope="Public" name="nugi_sph">One time remark about Nugi-chan saying something mean about a male's small member</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="panties_butt">Florina is going to strip while showing her butt</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="revy_mean">Florina asks Revy to be nicer</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="rwby">One time remark about playing with all RWBY members</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="shaved_for_lyn">Florina comments about shaving her pubes for Lyn's sake</marker>
    <marker scope="Private" name="streak_extra">Tracks how many extra items have been removed in a row per opponent</marker>
    <marker scope="Private" name="streak_major">Tracks how many major items have been removed in a row per opponent</marker>
    <marker scope="Private" name="streak_minor">Tracks how many minor items have been removed in a row per opponent</marker>
    <marker scope="Private" name="strip_bottom">Tracks that a character's bottom important was removed before their top and stores the item name for usage later</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="tickle">Denotes that Florina said something about her pegasus tickling her during masturbation</marker>
    <marker scope="Private" name="tickled">Used right before tickle</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="topless_long">Set when Florina has been the only one topless for several rounds, indicating her embarrassment about it</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="tripped">She fell over when taking off her boots.</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="underwear_knights">Florina suggests to Catria that they be the Pegasus Knights when both are in their underwear together.</marker>
    <marker scope="Private" name="underwear_knights2">2nd time she uses this if both her and Catria are topless together</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="underwear_okay" />
    <marker scope="Private" name="underwear_over">Comment about feeling sheepish for going all in with the underwear knights</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="underwear_wins">Tracks how many rounds she and Catria have won while in their underwear together</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="videl_father">Florina comments about wanting to meet Videl's father someday, since she has met lots of strong men</marker>
    <marker scope="Public" name="videl_fly">Remark about Videl flying without a pegasus</marker>
</markers>
