<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<collectibles>
    <collectible id="silver_moon_stone" img="opponents/fina/moonstone.png" thumbnail="opponents/fina/moonstone.png">
        <title>Silver Moon Stone</title>
        <subtitle>Contains the power of void.</subtitle>
        <text>Fina slipped this gleaming, smooth silver stone into your hand before hurrying away after your game with her. Holding it makes you feel connected to life, death and the void between... maybe even in a way that would give you some related magical abilities if you beat up enough weird jellyfish while carrying it. It smells pleasantly of her...</text>
        <unlock>Finish a game where Fina loses.</unlock>
    </collectible>
    <collectible id="fina_picture" img="opponents/fina/finacollectiblephoto.png" thumbnail="opponents/fina/finacollectiblethumbnail.png">
        <title>For my newest friend...</title>
        <subtitle>A picture celebrating a special bond.</subtitle>
        <text>After you played with her---and saw her at her most vulnerable---so many times, Fina feels that you and she share a special bond. She decided to have another new experience with you, and let you take this picture of her after your game together. Promise you won't show it to anyone else...</text>
        <unlock>Hear Fina say five different phrases at her climax.</unlock>
        <hide-details>true</hide-details>
        <counter>5</counter>
    </collectible>
    <collectible id="fina_earrings" img="opponents/fina/earrings_posing.png" thumbnail="opponents/fina/earrings.png">
        <title>Fina's Earrings</title>
        <text>With your help, Fina has experienced everything the game has to offer---the thrill of winning, the pleasure of defeat, and the intimacy of losing side by side. To thank you for broadening her horizons, she gifted you her earrings. By this point, those were the only things you'd never seen her take off...</text>
        <unlock>Win a game against Fina after previously both losing a game to her, and losing a game that she also lost.</unlock>
        <hide-details>true</hide-details>
        <counter>3</counter>
        <wearable>true</wearable>
        <clothing name="earrings" generic="jewelry" position="head" type="extra" img="opponents/fina/earrings.png" plural="true" />
    </collectible>
    <collectible id="fina_letter" img="opponents/fina/old-envelope.png" thumbnail="opponents/fina/old-envelope-thumbnail.png">
        <title>A letter from Fina</title>
        <subtitle>Invitation to a special game on Crescent Isle...</subtitle>
        <text>You received this letter in the mail. It's not obvious how Fina got it to you, but it's clearly her handwriting. It reads:

"My beloved friend, thank you so much for inviting me to play with you at the Inventory. I've learned so much about myself and what I want, and I think I've learned more about who I want to be to Vyse and Aika as well. 

So, I'd like to invite you to a special game of strip poker at Crescent Isle. Vyse, Aika and I will all be playing and we hope you can make it, too. Although this will be a private game, we'll be using much the same rules as the Inventory does. However, I am interested in making some modifications to the rules... mostly pertaining to what happens to me if I lose the game. I'd like to discuss that with you in person beforehand.

I hope you'll continue to be a part of my life. I know I'm very devoted to Vyse and Aika, but I would never want you to think that somehow makes you less important to me than they are. There's plenty of room for you in my heart as well... I hope there's room for me in yours.

Fondly yours,
Fina"</text>
        <unlock>Get Fina to shout your name during her climax, then finish the game. (Hint: first obtain her earrings collectible, then lose and masturbate alongside her. This won't work if you play as a gay man or a straight woman. Also beware: Don't let her learn your history with Chara!)</unlock>
        <hide-details>true</hide-details>
    </collectible>
    <collectible id="drink_pass" img="opponents/fina/sailors-island-tavern.png" thumbnail="opponents/fina/sailors-island-tavern-thumb.png">
        <title>Sailor's Island Drink Pass</title>
        <subtitle>Good for one round of drinks at the Sailor's Island tavern.</subtitle>
        <text>After a particularly ridiculous display of stripping in an unexpected order in your last game, Fina invited you to go drinking with her at the tavern on Sailor's Island. Written on the back is a list of all the drinks this pass is good for, none of which look familiar and all of which appear to be varieties of "loqua". You'll probably have to ask her what's what...</text>
        <unlock>Make Fina laugh by stripping your clothes in an unexpected order.</unlock>
        <hide-details>true</hide-details>
        <counter>10</counter>
    </collectible>
    <collectible id="fina_veil" img="opponents/fina/2-intrigued.png" thumbnail="opponents/fina/finaVeil.png">
        <title>Fina's Veil</title>
        <subtitle>A symbolic gift for opening a young woman's eyes.</subtitle>
        <text>After her experiences at the Inventory with you, Fina was finally able to embrace her attraction toward other women. As thanks for teaching her more about herself, she gifted you one of her veils... perhaps because of the symbolism involved. Though paper-thin, the fabric seems incredibly strong; you probably couldn't tear it even if you wanted to.</text>
        <unlock>Help Fina process her feelings toward other women by having her watch 10 different female characters masturbate to completion.</unlock>
        <hide-details>true</hide-details>
        <counter>10</counter>
        <wearable>true</wearable>
        <clothing name="veil" generic="hat" position="head" type="extra" img="opponents/fina/finaVeil.png" />
    </collectible>
</collectibles>
