<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>

<!--This file was machine generated using the Character Editor v6.7.7 at 6:11:36 PM on December 10, 2022. Do not edit this file directly unless you know what you're doing.-->
<opponent>
    <version>v6.7.7</version>
    <first>Noelle</first>
    <last />
    <label>Noelle</label>
    <gender>female</gender>
    <size>medium</size>
    <timer>25</timer>
    <intelligence>good</intelligence>



    <wardrobe>
        <clothing name="panties" generic="underwear" position="lower" type="important" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="shirt" generic="shirt" position="upper" type="major" />
        <clothing name="pantyhose" generic="socks" position="lower" type="major" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="skirt" generic="pants" position="lower" type="minor" />
        <clothing name="set of armor" generic="armor" position="both" type="minor" />
    </wardrobe>


    <behaviour>
        <trigger id="selected">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="mari" sayingMarker="OppSelected_Noelle" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="mari1">It's nice to meet you, Mari. This is... what you would call a mix of the two, though I'm not a Knight yet.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="barbara" />
                <state img="#-worried.png">Barbara! Are you training here as well? How unorthodox for someone of your position.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Ooh! How exciting! A-a-ahem...hmm!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Hello! I'm Noelle: a maid in service to the Knights of Favonius.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">I will protect you! Oh wait...no one needs protection, do they?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I'm... so happy you chose me to play along. I'll make sure not to disappoint you.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_selected">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="sucrose" sayingMarker="previously_selected=1" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Sucrose!? You're here as well?!</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">Glad to see a fellow Mondstadt citizen among us! Let's do our best, Sucrose!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="asuna_yuuki" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png">A knight! &lt;i&gt;(Maybe this could be a good time to ask for advice. I'm already glad I came here.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="magma_grunt" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png">&lt;i&gt;(That girl in the red hood...doesn't look very friendly...I'd best keep an eye on her.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">&lt;i&gt;(Magma Grunt..sounds like a title than a name...she must be part of an organization then...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">That man is as big as a Fatui Legionnaire. But he seems...rather eccentric...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="barbara" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png" marker="NoelleGreetBarbaraJean">Barbara!? Does Master Jean know you are here?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="fischl" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">You call yourself &lt;i&gt;Fischl&lt;/i&gt;, right? Fancy meeting you here. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="erza" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">Ah, another knight has come to play with us! Welcome!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="barbara" sayingMarker="NoelleSucroseSelect" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Oh? Oh! It may seem like it, but I can assure you we didn't travel here together. At least not intentionally.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_start">
            <case stage="0" priority="101">
                <condition count="3-" filter="mondstadt" role="opp" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">So many familiar faces... Is this place that known by people in Mondstadt?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="sucrose" />
                <state img="#-touched.png" oneShotId="533">We may technically be opponents, Sucrose, but let's both do our best!</state>
                <state img="#-touched.png" oneShotId="580">It's rare for us to spend time together, Sucrose, but let's make the best of it!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="581">&lt;i&gt;(She may have her own reasons for being here, likely some experiment, but will she be able to handle it...?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="barbara" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">Have you come to spread your joy and song here as well, Barbara? Your presence can brighten any room.</state>
                <state img="#-serious.png">Should a Deaconess like yourself be here playing this, though? You may have your reasons, but still…</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">This is unheard of for someone of such devotion and purity...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition status="exposed" />
                <state img="#-flustered.png">Oh my, I can already see... Why would anyone come to a game like this exposed like that? Is this a special challenge?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">A true knight is ready for anything and everything! Even stripping!</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">Another step in my training to become a knight: handling embarrassment and supporting others!</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I've studied a fair share of card games in the Knights' Library thanks to Miss Lisa! I'm sure I'll do well! ...I hope.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">No telling if we'll have to do something shameless during the next Knight exam! I... I must be prepared!</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">Even if this is just a &lt;i&gt;small task&lt;/i&gt;, I'm prepared well for this: I added five games of poker before breakfast to my daily training routine.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="swap_cards">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <test expr="~cards~" value="1" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I wonder if exchanging one card will be enough...</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Just one should do.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <test expr="~cards~" value="0" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">This hand isn't any...w-wait, I change my mind!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I don't have to trade any if I don't want to, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-calm.png">~Cards.text~, if you'd be so kind, dealer.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">May I have ~cards.text~ cards, please?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I'd like to request ~cards.text~ cards.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">~Cards.text~, if it's alright.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Trading in these ~cards.text~ should do...</state>
                <state img="#-touched.png">I'd like to submit these ~cards.text~.</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Oh right! ~Cards.text~, dealer.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="good_hand">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-excited.png">The cards are in my favor this time!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Yay!</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">This hand was listed as one of the stronger ones, so I'm almost definitely safe.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I feel nice and sunny right now!</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">Time to clean up!</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">I always try to give my best! As a maid &lt;i&gt;and&lt;/i&gt; a future knight!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">It seems like I don't have to worry this round. Is there anything I can do until the cards are revealed? </state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I wonder if I can make myself a little more useful. Just waiting until the cards are revealed feels a little like I am wasting my time...</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">A good knight will win without a doubt with a strong hand!</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">Wonderful! Barbatos has smiled upon in this moment!</state>
                <state img="#-curtsey.png">For the service and good of Mondstadt, this hand will lead me forward!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="okay_hand">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-calm.png">This isn't the best hand I could get, but I'm prepared in case it's not enough.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">A middle-of-the-road hand...I'll just have to hope for the best.</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">This is far from an optimal hand, but neither is it bad. Maybe if I had trained more...</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Just average... Nevertheless, I'll make the best of it!</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">My heart is racing. Could this be excitement to see the outcome of this round? Or could it be because...</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">I have to keep training and studying...oh, but this game does have a fair amount of luck behind it.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">A hand of this quality should ensure my survival! ...Maybe.</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">I have to prepare for the worst... even if this hand should pull me though.</state>
                <state img="#-curtsey.png">No matter the situation, a maid is ready for all that awaits her!</state>
                <state img="#-curtsey.png">A true knight will press forward, no matter the situation!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="bad_hand">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">This is regular poker...so I can't ask for another hand, can I?</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">I'd rather be out in the rain than have this hand.</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Worst case! How am I supposed to become a knight if I can't even succeed in a game like this?</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">Weren't my efforts good enough? Perhaps I should have studied more books...</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I know luck is still a variable I should have taken into account, but a maid shouldn't rely on luck if it counts...</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">This is the best I could have made out of the hand I was dealt, but still it's frustrating if you can't do anything...</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I should have traded more cards... Why do I always lose my head when it counts...?</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">Mind if I clean this place a little? Making myself a little useful would let me feel a little better now.</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">I missed a spot...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="hand">
            <case stage="0-7" id="88">
                <condition character="sucrose" saying="I was wondering; is it normal that" />
                <condition gender="male" />
                <condition role="other" character="sucrose" stage="0-1" sayingMarker="noelle_men" />
                <state img="#-touched.png">U-uh... Well... I... Wouldn't say no to that, but I am primarily here for my training. I was fully expecting to be around more men, so my heart was better prepared for it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="89" totalRounds="0">
                <condition count="4" gender="female" />
                <condition role="other" character="asuna_yuuki" stage="0" />
                <test expr="~player~" value="male" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png">So I'm not the only one who thought that was weird...you'd think there would be more guys than just ~player~.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Perhaps it's &lt;i&gt;because&lt;/i&gt; there are so few men here that we don't see more...does that make sense?</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">I thought the players for the tables were chosen at random...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="248" totalRounds="4-">
                <condition role="other" character="nagamimi" stage="0-3" timeInStage="5-" sayingMarker="question_dragons" />
                <state img="#-dutiful.png" oneShotId="876" marker="NoelleNagamimiDragonsResponse">For a time, Mondstadt was under threat of Storm Terror. He was capable of manipulating the winds and cause storms to wreak havoc across the country. But thanks to the Traveler, Storm Terror was defeated soundly.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="27" priority="161">
                <condition role="other" character="sucrose" sayingMarker="sucrose_lingerie1" />
                <state img="#-shy.png">They suit you for sure, Sucrose. But I'm not sure I could wear something like that under my uniform... That could end up embarrassing while using the Wind Glider...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5" id="5" priority="156">
                <condition role="other" character="nami" sayingMarker="dreams" />
                <state img="#-touched.png">I want nothing more than to become a full fledged Knight! I've dreamed of it for so long, and I won't quit until I am one!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="250">
                <condition role="other" character="saki_zls" stage="6" timeInStage="0" />
                <state img="#-excited.png" marker="NoelleSakiZLSZombieReveal">So you're... Ah, I see! That explains the water, but how are your clothes and hair? Would you like me to hang your clothes to dry? I can also get a brush to help with your hair too!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5" id="13" totalRounds="7-10" priority="152">
                <condition role="other" character="cynthia" stage="1-2" sayingMarker="QuesExploreRuins" notSaidMarker="QuestionAndAnswer1" />
                <state img="#-excited.png">I-I'd like to go! &lt;i&gt;(Going outside of Mondstadt with the Traveler was enjoyable experience...I should try to do more adventures like that.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5" id="12" totalRounds="2-5">
                <condition role="other" character="amy_rose" stage="0-2" sayingMarker="amy_shopping_prompt" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">I often go shopping for ingredients, and sometimes to do service on my claymore.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5" id="14" totalRounds="3-">
                <condition role="other" character="pyrrha" stage="3" sayingMarker="too_serious_joke" />
                <state img="#-sad.png" oneShotId="865">I'd say someone's hard work: it's not very polite to laugh at someone's failures...even if it is multiple times...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="90" totalRounds="0">
                <condition role="other" character="perona" stage="0" sayingMarker="noelle_intro" />
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">Do you have need of my services, Ms. Perona? While can't be your personal mistress, I shall assist you in whatever it is you need help in.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="92">
                <condition role="other" character="fluttershy" stage="0-3" sayingMarker="rarity_praise" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">It looks wonderful on you, Fluttershy! Your friend is a top-notch dressmaker!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="26" priority="141">
                <condition role="other" character="sucrose" sayingMarker="sucrose_flowers" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">I really like all flowers that grow in Mondstadt, but I like roses the most. But you certainly knew that before, right, Sucrose?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="93">
                <condition role="other" character="petra" stage="0" sayingMarker="hand_okay_fear_itself" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">Are you getting along well, Petra? It must be hard to speak a foreign language. Luckily, people in Teyvat all speak only one language.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="91">
                <condition role="other" character="bernadetta" stage="0-7" saidMarker="faint==1" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Are you okay, Bernadetta? ...Bernadetta? Can you hear me? Oh no, she fainted! We have to do something quick!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="51">
                <condition role="other" character="charlie" stage="2" sayingMarker="charlie_shoes" />
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">No problem! Strip your shoes as well. I know myself how good it feels to relax after a day of hard work. One day, after I walked all the way to Liyue and back to Mondstadt again, I couldn't wait to get out of my shoes as well.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="21">
                <condition role="other" character="sucrose" stage="0-3" />
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="582">I'm not sure anything from Mondstadt could have prepared us for this, but that's exactly what will make this good training!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="253" oneShotId="4">
                <condition role="opp" character="dawn" saidMarker="DawnNeedsAMoment" notSaidMarker="DawnsBack" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">O-Oh. Miss Dawn? Oh dear...</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">Oh dear, Miss Dawn? I-Is she gone? Um, maybe I shouldn't say more...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5" id="7">
                <condition role="other" character="nagisa" sayingMarker="nagisa_inventory_spilled_drinks" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">I was thinking the same thing! I'll have to clean it up after the game is over!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5" id="10">
                <condition role="other" character="nagisa" sayingMarker="nagisa_college_or_job" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png">(Is college similar to the school Lisa attended? I'm not interested in becoming a magic user like Lisa though...)</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5" id="8">
                <condition role="other" character="nagisa" sayingMarker="nagisa_food_prompt" />
                <state img="#-worried.png">I've actually been trying to hold back on eating so much. I know it's important to eat after exercising, but I'm always worried about putting on weight...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5" id="9">
                <condition role="other" character="nagisa" sayingMarker="nagisa_only_child" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">I don't have any siblings, but all the friends I have in Mondstadt feel like my family all the same. I'm sure you feel like that with some people, Nagisa.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="43">
                <condition role="other" character="petra" sayingMarker="idle_okay_fodlan_second_language" />
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">If you have any trouble understanding the others, let me interpret for you, Petra. Looks like the language of Fódlan and Teyvat are similar enough for that, if they're not even the same.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">&lt;i&gt;(The language she's struggling with seems to be same as our own though...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="44">
                <condition role="other" character="reimu" sayingMarker="Reimu_GetRichQuick" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">Have you ever heard of Ley Line Blossoms? If the traveler needs money the "Blossom of Wealth" is a pretty good way to get a lot of money fast. I don't know if you have use for Mora where you come from, though.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="45">
                <condition role="other" character="reimu" sayingMarker="Reimu_SpouseQualities" />
                <state img="#-flustered.png">A spouse? I'm not sure I'm ready for a relationship like that yet. I'm not sure I'm good enough for anyone either...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="69">
                <condition role="other" character="fischl" sayingMarker="noelle_fischl" />
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">I'm here to prepare for some upcoming knight exams. But I'm still planning to serve as a maid during the game and not only as participant. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="240">
                <condition role="other" character="estelle" sayingMarker="EstelleFocusPrompt" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Tips for staying focused? Let's see... How about...No, that wouldn't be appropriate for a princess. Then how about...No, that won't do either in this situation... Give me a moment!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="315">
                <condition role="other" character="estelle" sayingMarker="necklace" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">It's really pretty, Estelle! Please keep it, if you feel better that way. I'll keep my roses too, because they have a special meaning for me. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="242">
                <condition role="other" character="estelle" sayingMarker="book" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">You're reading something for us? What a wonderful idea. I wonder if we have the same book in our library. I should ask Lisa when I'm back.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7" id="243">
                <condition role="opp" character="ganyu" saidMarker="GanyuNoelleAfter01" />
                <state img="#-curtsey.png" oneShotId="834" marker="NoelleGanyuCleaningOffer">Oh, Miss Ganyu! Should you ever need assistance with organizing or cleaning your office, just say the word and I'll make time to make my way to Liyue and do that for you! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="245">
                <condition role="opp" character="ganyu" sayingMarker="GanyuNoelleVision" />
                <state img="#-worried.png" oneShotId="838" marker="NoelleGanyuVisionResponse">I am grateful for the gift of a Vision from the Archons, but... Can you keep a secret? I feel dejected. Why did I get a &lt;i&gt;Geo&lt;/i&gt; Vision? Sure, those in the Knights of Favonius have varied elements, but I was hoping for an Anemo vision. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="246">
                <condition role="opp" character="ganyu" sayingMarker="GanyuNoelleKnight" />
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="840" marker="NoelleGanyuKnightReponse">I had always dreamed of becoming a Knight of Favonius ever since I was a little girl! I may not be a knight just yet, but I just &lt;i&gt;know&lt;/i&gt; I'll be able to prove myself to Master Jean yet!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="256">
                <condition role="opp" character="basil" sayingMarker="basil_flowerask" />
                <state img="#-dutiful.png" oneShotId="929" marker="NoelleBasilFlowerAskResponse">My favorite flower is the rose! In Mondstadt, the rose represents the saying "As wine bottles are corked, so too are my lips sealed." As every maid is meant to keep their secrets, the rose represents just that. Plus, they look so pretty too!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="284">
                <condition role="opp" character="blake_belladonna" saidMarker="nb25" />
                <state img="#-curtsey.png" oneShotId="946" marker="NoelleBlakeFantastic">I'd love that, Miss Blake. I swear on my honor as a maid and a knight that it will be a fantastic day!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="285">
                <condition role="opp" character="blake_belladonna" saidMarker="nb15" />
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="948" marker="NoelleBlakeGrilledFish">Actually, now that I think about it, I bet I could ask my friend, Diona, about how she makes her grilled fish! See, she's also a cat person that makes the best grilled fish I've tasted. If I can master it, I'll be more than happy to give you some!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="286">
                <condition role="opp" character="blake_belladonna" saidMarker="blake_noelle_hand2" />
                <state img="#-touched.png" oneShotId="955" marker="NoelleBlakeVigilant" font-size="small">Be vigilant for anyone who wants to use my kindness to their own nefarious advantage... I think I'm beginning to understand! So instead of going out of my way to fulfill the needs of others, I should ask what their end goal is after finishing their work! Is that right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="287">
                <condition role="opp" character="blake_belladonna" saidMarker="bn7_hand" />
                <state img="#-bashful.png" oneShotId="957" marker="NoelleBlakePlead">Please, Miss Blake! I only want to protect those in need, and make everyone I can happy! S-surely there must be something you can tell me that will help me? I promise to repay you for your kindness!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="95">
                <condition role="other" character="basil" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="628">Your camera is much the same as the Kamera where I come from. Do they both have the same functions?</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png" oneShotId="627">You kind of remind of someone from the Adventurers' Guild, Basil. His name's Bennett. Happy-go-lucky as you are, but tends to be very unlucky himself.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="94">
                <condition role="opp" character="barbara" />
                <state img="#-dutiful.png" oneShotId="799" marker="BarbaraKnight">Apologies if I am being too forward, Barbara. But I hope your sister will acknowledge me as a Knight someday. I have been training for so long and I only get better each day!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="798" marker="BarbaraThanks">Seeing you here, being your usual upbeat self, reminds me of your last performance! Your songs do cheer me up when I feel down, Barbara. Thank you for that.</state>
                <state img="#-curtsey.png" oneShotId="800" marker="BarbaraRaking">Do the leaves near the Cathedral need raking again? I can take care of that!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="873" marker="BarbaraOthers">I only hope the other nuns will be able to keep the Cathedral going while you're gone.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="874" marker="BarbaraSinging">Your singing always puts me in better spirits, Barbara. Even now!</state>
                <state img="#-serious.png" oneShotId="869" marker="BarbaraJean">Barbara, are you sure your sister will be okay with you coming here? I know it of your free will, but if I were Jean, I'd have my reservations.</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png" oneShotId="870" marker="BarbaraEffort">Do take care not to overexert yourself, Barbara...</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="871" marker="BarbaraTime">It's not often we get to spend time together, Barbara, given that we're always so busy... Let's make the most of it!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="872" marker="BarbaraCombo">You keep the others upbeat with your songs, and I'll tend to their every need! We're sure to make a great combination!</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png" oneShotId="875" marker="BarbaraCompetition">I'm going to do my best, Barbara. Even though we're competing. No hard feelings, I hope.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5" id="314">
                <condition role="other" character="sucrose" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="1114">This year's Weinlesefest is sure to be one to remember, huh Sucrose?</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="1115">Razor really liked our gift for his wine, Sucrose! Maybe you should try talking to him sometime!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5" id="316">
                <condition role="other" character="cagliostro" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="1164">You are an alchemist, Cagliostro? I know a few alchemists as well! Mr. Albedo and Sucrose would surely have much to discuss with you!</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png" oneShotId="1172">I could introduce you to the alchemists in Mondstadt, Cagliostro! You would feel right at home with them!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="1186">Alchemy has multiple areas of study, right, Cagliostro? Is there a field in particular that you specialize in?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5" id="317">
                <condition role="other" character="dark_magician_girl" />
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="1201">Magic?! It exists?! Please, could I have a demonstration, Dark Magician Girl?!</state>
                <state img="#-curtsey.png" oneShotId="1202">While we do not have magic where I come from, we who have visions can wield the elements based on which one we have. That's magical in it's own way.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="1204">So you have magic where you come from, Dark Magician Girl, and we have the elements. The world is far more vast than I imagined.</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png" oneShotId="1205">Perhaps you could teach me some magic to help calm my nerves before the Knight's Exam, Dark Magician Girl. Oh, but that might be considered cheating..</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="1203">&lt;i&gt;(Dark Magician Girl is so upbeat and bouncy! It's impossible not to smile with her around!)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5" id="318">
                <condition role="other" character="asuna_yuuki" />
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="1233">You are a Knight, Miss Asuna!? How wonderful!</state>
                <state img="#-curtsey.png" oneShotId="1234">You know how to use a sword, Miss Asuna! May I have some pointers. I need to begin training for the next Knight Exam</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="1235">&lt;i&gt;(Perhaps Asuna could give me some help in preparing for the next Exam. She gives off an aura or refinement and elegance that a knight should have.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-1" id="319">
                <condition role="other" character="darkness" />
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="1242">To see a knight of such grace and stature... I-It is an honor to meet you, Master Darkness!</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png" oneShotId="1243">&lt;i&gt;(Darkness is a proper knight as well... I wonder if I'll ever pass the exam and be like her...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-curtsey.png" oneShotId="1244">I need to maintain the same fortitude and duty to my comrades and knights, just as you do, Master Darkness!</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png" oneShotId="1245">&lt;i&gt;(Before a knight like Darkness, it feels as though my dream of becoming one by passing the exam feels so far away...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png" oneShotId="1263">Ah, a knight! And a Crusader at that! I need to compose myself...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-2" id="320">
                <condition role="other" character="mari_setogaya" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png" oneShotId="1298">Well, I-I am certainly surprised to see one so ready to lose... but I ask that you please do your best to win regardless, Mari.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png" oneShotId="1299">&lt;i&gt;(Mari's... rather shameless, isn't she... I don't think this will be on the exam...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png" oneShotId="1300">You certainly didn't leave your reasoning for being here to question, Mari. Umm... good luck... losing?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-1" id="322">
                <condition role="other" character="noire" />
                <state img="#-dutiful.png" oneShotId="1315">We are very glad you and ~player~ have joined us, Noire. Good luck to all of us!</state>
                <state img="#-curtsey.png">&lt;i&gt;(Noire gives off the air of royalty... I'll do my utmost to give her proper respect!)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-1" id="328">
                <condition role="other" character="aloy" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="1416">I had heard there was a hunter near Mondstadt recently. Would that be you, Aloy?</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png" oneShotId="1419">A hunter... would there be anything like that on the Knights' Exam next time?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="1418">&lt;i&gt;(Aloy looks like she knows much about survival. I'll should ask so I can inform anyone going out of Mondstadt for a while.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-1" id="329">
                <condition role="other" character="caitlin" />
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="1428">Psychic powers?! If I had powers like, imagine how much more I could help the people of Mondstadt.</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png" oneShotId="1429">Having powers like yours Caitlin would certainly help me, but I feel I would grow complacent in my training.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="330">
                <condition role="other" character="dawn" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png" oneShotId="1441">Even a champion is here?! The Inventory really does attract all many of people!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="331">
                <condition role="other" character="mercy" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="1444">&lt;i&gt;(Miss Mercy is a healer, yes? Perhaps she could stop by Mondstadt sometime. Barbara could use a break every now and then.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="1445">We could definitely use someone of your talent in the Knights, Miss Mercy! Would you consider joining us?</state>
                <state img="#-curtsey.png" oneShotId="1446">People with the power to heal seem in short supply where I come from Miss Mercy. I ask that you please cherish you power.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-1" id="332">
                <condition role="other" character="hatsune_miku" />
                <state img="#-dutiful.png" oneShotId="1473">An idol? Just like Barbara!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="1472">Such a fun and attractive voice you have, Miku! You and Barbara should have a duet!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="1486">Perhaps you and Barbara could compare notes on being idols!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-1" id="333">
                <condition role="other" character="rouge" />
                <state img="#-dutiful.png" oneShotId="1491">Treasure hunting is a hobby of our Honorary Knight, Miss Rouge. Perhaps you can find some more if went along with him, you could find some more.</state>
                <state img="#-serious.png" oneShotId="1492">I trust you aren't like the Treasure Horders, Miss Rouge? If you are like them, I'll have to bring you in!</state>
                <state img="#-serious.png" oneShotId="1490">You're not in the business of stealing, are you Miss Rouge? I'll need to detain you now if so!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="334">
                <condition role="other" character="sly_cooper" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="1525">&lt;i&gt;Sly is a master thief. I'll need to be cautious around him.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="5" totalRounds="10-15">
                <test expr="~human.biggestlead~" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">Goodness, ~player~, you've been playing wonderfully so far! I hope you're having as much fun as I am!</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">You're so far ahead of us, ~player~, you must be an expert at card games. Not specifically games like this, of course!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="307">
                <test expr="~background.dark~" value="true" />
                <state img="#-dutiful.png" oneShotId="1049">If you feel uncomfortable when it's dark, you're free to come closer! Day or night, I'm always ready for more! </state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="1048">It's rather late, isn't it? &lt;i&gt;(Did get all of the laundry in and finish doing the Knights' dishes? They made need some help the bars later...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png" oneShotId="1052">Uhm... Maybe I should have picked a better time to play. Hopefully no one will notice I'm gone at this hour.</state>
                <state img="#-serious.png">Be sure you are all careful on the way home afterwards! There's no telling if a hilichurl or some other enemy may attack you!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="308">
                <test expr="~background~" value="romantic" />
                <state img="#-shy.png" oneShotId="1056">I'm still rather... inexperienced in the means of romance and love. This could be my chance to learn more about it, I suppose.</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png" oneShotId="1057">Should any of you find yourselves looking for a maid after the game for a date, I am at your beck and call! ...I-I mean, for your partner, not me as the date!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="1077">Roses are a sign of love, so I'd like to think I dressed for the occasion...</state>
                <state img="#-curtsey.png" oneShotId="1078">Maybe the Inventory is a sign of bringing people together. I wish you luck in finding someone special while you are here.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition gender="male" status="crotch_visible" role="opp" />
                <state img="#-shy.png" oneShotId="903">Do I keep my eyes averted? There isn't anything I can really do to offer assistance. U-unless...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition filter="celebrity" role="opp" />
                <state img="#-curtsey.png" oneShotId="1152">Oh, ~target.ifMale(Mister|Miss)~ ~target~, please let me know if you require any assistance with anything! It's quite an honor to be playing with someone such as yourself, so I'd like to make sure you're comfortable.</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png" oneShotId="1153">Would you like anything to drink, ~target.ifMale(Mister|Miss)~ ~target~ ? I can even clean and take care of any clothing or accessories after the game for you! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition filter="drunk" role="opp" />
                <state img="#-dutiful.png" oneShotId="1156">Should you find yourself too inebriated, I'd be happy to escort you to a hotel or back home, ~target~. Mondstadt is has no shortage of drunkards, and I'm always prepared to help them!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="dark_magician_girl_summertime_fun" role="opp" />
                <state img="#-excited.png">You're certainly ready for the beach, Dark Magaician Girl!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="583">I feel as though Miss Lisa would be good at this game for some reason. Ah, Miss Lisa is the Knights' Librarian. She's in charge of keeping the records and books in Mondstadt, but always has this relaxed air about her.</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png" oneShotId="584">Oh no! Everyone's laundry is still on the line! May I be excused to fetch it in? ...No? V-very well.</state>
                <state img="#-curtsey.png" oneShotId="585">Would anyone like some tea? I'll brew you some. Do you take sugar? One cube, or two?</state>
                <state img="#-curtsey.png" oneShotId="586">Is anyone hungry? I could make some pancakes! You simply must try one, it's my specialty.</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png" oneShotId="587">I devote myself freely to all that I do. A maid, to me, is the most liberating job there is. I'm a chef, a gardener, a warrior, a guide... I can be &lt;i&gt;anything&lt;/i&gt; you need me to be!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="588">This game is pretty exciting, but this will take some time from my regular schedule... I'll just have to double my effort for all my other tasks!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="589">I wonder why the people in Mondstadt stopped playing cards with me? Did I do something wrong? All I wanted was to do my best. Even in a game of cards.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="590">Hard work always pays off. If anyone wants to train with me, I can make you a workout schedule and you can accompany me on my daily routines. I usually start at 5:00 a.m., with an easy warmup of 100 sit-ups and push-ups.</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png" oneShotId="644">I hope the Knights are doing well without me to clean the messes and help out right now. I'm sure they are, but still, I feel uneasy.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" priority="0">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="default" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="591">My armor may not serve much purpose in terms of protection here, but a knight must always be ready for anything!</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png" oneShotId="592">I had my armor custom made so I could still appear as a maid. It protects me and is still aesthetic. Neat, don't you think?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-5">
                <state img="#-dutiful.png" oneShotId="593">I may not look ready for a fight anymore, but I can still serve with everything that I have.</state>
                <state img="#-serious.png" oneShotId="657">The Knights' of Favonius are sure to be hard at work protecting Mondstadt and dealing with outside threats. I'll honor them by playing my best here!</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png" oneShotId="658">Well, I certainly could do my duties inside the city, such as cleaning and doing the Knights' laundry, but I would dare not leave the city like this.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="660">I can certainly keep the peace here like the Knights' of Favonius do for Mondstadt while I'm at it, right? This'll give me training in staying vigilant!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="661">This is almost like the expeditions the Knights' go on for patrols and commissions! I hope I'll be able to join them on one soon after I become one! &lt;i&gt;(That is, if I become one...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png" oneShotId="659">If anyone needs anything heavy moved, please don't be afraid to ask! Despite how I look, I'm very strong thanks to my training! </state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="670">Perhaps Master Jean will praise me for handling this by myself! Acting Grand Master Jean is the one in charge of the Mondstadt while Grand Master Varka is away. She's extremely capable and responsible! </state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="709">I don't hold a position in the Knights, per se, but  this kind of game may fall under their jurisdiction one day. Though, they may need a new section for it...</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="710">Thankfully, the Knights' library had some books on card games. I read them before coming here, so don't expect me to go down easy!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-1" priority="0">
                <condition count="1" gender="male" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="594">I was wondering; is it normal that there's only one man with us? Is this game not popular with men at all? I could have sworn men enjoy games like this...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-1" priority="0">
                <condition count="0" gender="male" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="595">I was wondering; is it normal that there are women among us? Is this game not popular with men at all? I could have sworn that men would prefer games like this a lot...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" priority="0">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="default" />
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="596">My armor was custom-made for me, since I'm not a Knight of Favonius. But I will be one someday!</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">I may look more like a maid than a Knight-in-training, but it won't put a damper on my spirits!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="697">Armor is an important part of any Knights' equipment. Though I may not be a Knight, I must be ready for anything. It also serves as good weight training to constantly wear it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="597">A Vision is believed to be given to those who the gods smile upon. However, the reason is not always clear as to why, nor is the reason clear as to which element someone gets.</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png" oneShotId="598">Still, why was I given a Geo Vision? I'm happy that it allows me to protect myself, but Geo is the farthest element from wind, or Anemo?</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">I'm not used to being so exposed, so I hope you'll bear with me.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Fighting hilichurls is nothing compared to this... </state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Perhaps I should study up on other cards games in addition to the rest of my studies.</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">I have to bear with this embarrassment. Nothing makes for better training! ...I think.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I'd rather not refrain from assisting everyone here, but dressed like this... will make it a bit of a challenge to move as swiftly...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-shy.png">It's cold... And yet... &lt;i&gt;(My body feels like it's warming up from this game...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-touched.png">It's sort of... reassuring to have others play this game with me. Enduring the embarrassment and playing through each hand makes me feel like we're getting closer.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">You keep staring at me, ~player~... I know I'm not in the best shape right now, but...</state>
                <state img="#-touched.png">~Player~, you keep staring at me... Am... Am I, um, pleasant to look at?</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">I know I only have myself to blame for getting to this point. Perhaps one of the other Knights would have played better.</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">It feels rather unsettling like this...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">P-please refrain from staring so much. I know I'm down to nothing, and I'm sure you all would get great... pleasure from looking at me naked, but please restrain yourselves.</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">&lt;i&gt;(~Player~ is still staring at me... Perhaps, I should let myself show a bit more then...)&lt;/i&gt; </state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">For once, I'm the one in need of aid...</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">Just one more loss... How disgraceful for a Knight trainee.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">I need to stay positive! This fight's not over yet!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5" priority="0">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="noelle_chicken_and_madame" />
                <state img="#-curtsey.png" oneShotId="760">Are you thirsty? I could bring you something. If nothing sugary suits you, we also have free water.</state>
                <state img="#-serious.png" oneShotId="761">I don't mind if anyone takes meals during the game, but do be careful with your drinks, otherwise they'll spill onto you! </state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="775">Should I go around and ask if anyone wants to order something to eat? ~Player~ doesn't look like ~player.ifMale(he|she)~ would say something, but ~player.ifMale(he|she)~ sure looks hungry.</state>
                <state img="#-touched.png">J-just to make sure: I'm not on the menu by the way... &lt;i&gt;(I really said it...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip">
            <case stage="4" id="181">
                <condition role="other" character="senko" stage="0-5" sayingMarker="senko41" saying="sex" />
                <state img="#-flustered.png">T-that is is pretty direct question! ...W-well, I-I'm a woman after all, so... How is a knight supposed to answer such a question properly?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4" id="182">
                <condition role="other" character="senko" stage="0-5" sayingMarker="senko41" saying="bed" />
                <state img="#-touched.png">"Take you to bed"? Sure, I think that also is part of a maid's duty. I can even sing you a good night song if you want. ...Or did you mean it like...?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="154">
                <condition role="other" character="sucrose" stage="0-2" sayingMarker="sucrose01a" />
                <state img="#-mustStrip.png">The same goes for me, Sucrose! It's not often we're together, so we should both make the best of it. I'm not sure what kind of experiment you're doing here, but if you need me to do something, just say the word!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4" id="167">
                <condition role="other" character="sucrose" stage="3-4" sayingMarker="sucrose01b" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">
                    <alt-img stage="0">#-mustStrip.png</alt-img>
                    <text>No, not at all! You're often in your lab, so I rarely got to see you. I don't think you have anything embarrassed about, Sucrose. They are a part of you.</text>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="157">
                <condition role="other" character="sucrose" stage="5-9" sayingMarker="sucrose01c" />
                <state img="#-mustStrip.png">It's quite alright, Sucrose! A maid aims to please! And if taking off all my armor will help you feel a little more comfortable, there's nothing more to think about!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="168">
                <condition role="other" character="sucrose" stage="0-4" sayingMarker="sucrose11a" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">Regarding my Vision, Sucrose? Or is it something else about me?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="173">
                <condition role="other" character="sucrose" stage="0-4" sayingMarker="sucrose21a" />
                <state img="#-shy.png">Ah, well, about that... I had a custom pair made for me so that they wouldn't tear no matter how much they stretched. I don't think I could deal with my hosiery tearing in public... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="178">
                <condition role="other" character="sucrose" stage="0-4" sayingMarker="sucrose31a" />
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I... hadn't really seen the need to. But since my breasts are getting bigger, perhaps I should...</state>
                <state img="#-touched.png">Until recently, my breasts were about your size... So I didn't really think about wearing one.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4" id="183">
                <condition role="other" character="sucrose" stage="0-4" sayingMarker="sucrose41a" />
                <state img="#-touched.png">I try not to wear too much, Sucrose, so my reflexes for requests and battle are as swift as possible. This would probably be the only situation where few clothes would backfire on me...</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">I thought I would have done better than this, Sucrose... I studied plenty of card game books before coming here, so I was feeling fairly confident.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="153">
                <condition role="other" character="meia" stage="0-5" sayingMarker="noelle0" />
                <state img="#-mustStrip.png">Well... I've haven't become a knight yet... But the Knights of Favonius are full of so many great people, and becoming a Knight is allow me to do even more!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="169">
                <condition role="other" character="meia" stage="0-5" sayingMarker="noelle1" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Miss Lisa does an amazing job taking care of the Library at the Knights of Favonius Headquarters. That said, I don't ever see doing very much. She claims to be saving her strength for something...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="152">
                <condition role="other" character="jura" stage="0-6" sayingMarker="noelle0" />
                <state img="#-mustStrip.png">You have maids where you come from, Jura? I hope they get as much joy as I do out of serving others. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="166">
                <condition role="other" character="jura" stage="0-6" sayingMarker="noelle1" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">The Knights of Favonius practice on training structures and in mock duels. However, I practiced on my on with a claymore. It took the blacksmith a number of tries before he created a sword I couldn't break though.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="155">
                <condition role="other" character="revy" stage="0-7" sayingMarker="noelle0" />
                <state img="#-mustStrip.png">I-I'm not an escort, Revy; I'm a maid in service to the Knights. I'm not a Knight just yet... And what's a tit-job...?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="171">
                <condition role="other" character="sucrose" stage="5-9" sayingMarker="sucrose11b" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">It's my turn, right? ...Oh, what do you need, Sucrose? I something the matter?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="177">
                <condition role="other" character="sucrose" stage="5-9" sayingMarker="sucrose31b" />
                <state img="#-shy.png">Usually my breastplate supports my chest enough too, so I don't wear anything under this shirt either...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="176">
                <condition role="other" character="mari" stage="0-2" sayingMarker="Noelle_QuestionBusy1=1" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">It's quite the opposite, Mari. I never get tired of helping anyone with anything they might need. Nothing makes me happier!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="175">
                <condition role="other" character="mari" stage="3-5" sayingMarker="Noelle_QuestionBusy1=2" />
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">Though it may be hard to believe Mari, this too is part of my training to be a knight. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4" id="180">
                <condition role="other" character="senko" stage="6-9" sayingMarker="senko41b" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">You mean that we should perform the forfeit together? Is that even allowed? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="163">
                <condition role="other" character="petra" sayingMarker="petra_noelle_strip0a" />
                <state img="#-mustStrip.png">I'm still training to become one, Petra. The next exam to become is coming up soon, so I need to be prepared for anything the exam can throw at me. I could even be a strip game like this!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="156">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Noelle_ILikeAGirlWhoCanBenchpressMe1" />
                <state img="#-mustStrip.png">200 kilos? I usually prefer sit-ups and push-ups for my training, but people always call me when they have to move heavy stuff like cargo, bookshelves and so on. I have no idea how heavy those are, though.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="158">
                <condition role="other" character="fina" sayingMarker="FinaNoelleStart1" />
                <state img="#-mustStrip.png">Don't worry about me, Fina! I don't mind fulling my duties. Sometimes I have difficulties to relax a little, though...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="30">
                <condition role="other" character="takatoshi" sayingMarker="NoelleArmor1" />
                <state img="#-mustStrip.png">I may seem small, but I'm actually a knight in training and have to protect the citizens of Mondstadt from monsters and bandits. This armor is more of a symbol than for protection though.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="159">
                <condition role="other" character="miko" sayingMarker="NoelleArmor1" />
                <state img="#-mustStrip.png">I may be a maid, but I'm also a knight in training. This armor is a symbol of my ambition to become a full knight of the Order of Favonius.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="161">
                <condition role="other" character="nami" sayingMarker="noelle0" />
                <state img="#-mustStrip.png">The knights aren't lazy whatsoever, Nami. They are hard-working and righteous in their duty. It is my honor to serve them, and cleaning is just of the many things I'll happily take care of!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="170">
                <condition role="other" character="nami" sayingMarker="noelle1" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">Though I have been offered time off on multiple occasions, I don't feel I could ever take a day off. Serving people is my greatest joy, so I hardly feel like I'm working as it is. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="160">
                <condition role="other" character="perona" sayingMarker="noelle0" />
                <state img="#-mustStrip.png">(I don't intend to serve anyone personally but...), I can be anything you want me to be, Miss Perona.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="53">
                <condition role="other" character="hu_tao" sayingMarker="hutao01a" />
                <state img="#-mustStrip.png">Corpses? Oh, you mean like drunk people? I often have to bring some people back home after they overdid it a little. Unfortunately I can only carry two people at the same time. I wish I had more arms sometimes...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="54">
                <condition role="other" character="hu_tao" sayingMarker="hutao01b" />
                <state img="#-mustStrip.png">If you need my help, you normally just have to call my name and I'll do my best to come and help. Unfortunately this doesn't happen anymore in the last time, because of a new paragraph in the Order's handbook. I wonder why they added that one.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="60">
                <condition role="other" character="hu_tao" sayingMarker="hutao11a" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Mnnn... I'm rarely off duty, to be honest. Last time I took a break together with the traveler, we spent the day helping others who needed my help anyway...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="61">
                <condition role="other" character="hu_tao" sayingMarker="hutao11b" />
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">I wouldn't say skilled, but I can say that hard training will always pay off. If you're not good at something, you can do a lot with effort to get better.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="62">
                <condition role="other" character="hu_tao" sayingMarker="hutao21a" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">When I had... Oh, isn't that a little too private to talk about? Not that it would bother me, but the knights codex says that it's bad to talk about others and I'm not sure the other person involved would appreciate it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="63">
                <condition role="other" character="hu_tao" sayingMarker="hutao21b" />
                <state img="#-shy.png">T-that's a little private, to be honest... I'm not sure a maid and future knight should talk about her sex life in public.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="164">
                <condition role="other" character="syrenne" sayingMarker="noelle_0" />
                <state img="#-dutiful.png" marker="syrenne1">The Knights of Favonius are kind and wonderful people who dedicate their everything to defend our city. That said, they do enjoy a good drink, just like you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="162">
                <condition role="other" character="reimu" sayingMarker="NoelleArmor1" />
                <state img="#-flustered.png" marker="reimu1">A-a suitor? N-n-no! I'm here as training to better myself at handling embarrassing situations... A suitor... I can't even imagine such a life when I have all of Mondstadt to serve!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="179">
                <condition role="other" character="mari" sayingMarker="Noelle_QuestionStress1=1" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I've never really found my work to be stressful Mari. Though my workload may be a lot at times, I always remember there are those working even harder than me, so I need to keep pushing myself.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="165">
                <condition role="other" character="senko" sayingMarker="senko01" />
                <state img="#-mustStrip.png">I'm a maid, but I goal is to become a knight one day. My armor helps me to protect myself and others while... well, cleaning the enemy's fronts.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="172">
                <condition role="other" character="senko" sayingMarker="senko11" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">Giving my best in all things I do is the least I can do. It's good to see that you appreciate my attitude, Senko.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="174">
                <condition role="other" character="senko" sayingMarker="senko21" />
                <state img="#-shy.png">A-as a barer of a Geo Vision, I can actually take care of myself, Senko. But I also know that in life there are a lot of things you can't do alone. No matter how hard your efforts are...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4" id="75">
                <condition role="other" character="fischl" sayingMarker="fischl_noellepantsu" />
                <state img="#-shy.png">I... I actually made those myself, Fischl...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="236">
                <condition role="opp" character="barbara" sayingMarker="NoelleArmor1" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="BarbaraEarlyBird1">Oh, don't worry about any of my usual duties, Miss Barbara! I made sure that any of my scheduled tasks were completed before I came here. By getting up an hour early, I was able to finish everything before lunch!</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png" marker="BarbaraEarlyBird1">No need to fret, Barbara! All of my scheduled duties were done before lunch, thanks to waking up at 4 am sharp! I should do it more often.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="235">
                <condition role="opp" character="barbara" sayingMarker="NoelleSkirt1" />
                <state img="#-touched.png" marker="BarbaraFlatter1">Ah, Miss Barbara. You flatter me, truly. I don't believe I'm skilled enough to perform on stage alongside you. But I would be more than happy to give it a shot!</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png" marker="BarbaraFlatter1">Oh, thank you very much, Miss Barbara. But I don't think I am skilled enough to perform next to someone as talented as you. If you had the time, however, I'd be more than happy to learn from you!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="234">
                <condition role="opp" character="barbara" sayingMarker="NoellePantyhose1" />
                <state img="#-dutiful.png" marker="BarbaraNoArmor1">I-it's quite alright, Miss Barbara. If I am to ever become a knight, I should be able to adapt to any situation. With, or without my armor!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="237">
                <condition role="other" character="estelle" sayingMarker="EstelleNoelleStart1" />
                <state img="#-mustStrip.png">Hearing those words from a princess like you really makes me happy. I would prefer becoming a &lt;i&gt;reliable&lt;/i&gt; knight over a &lt;i&gt;cute&lt;/i&gt; knight though.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="saki_zls" sayingMarker="NoelleArmor1" />
                <state img="#-mustStrip.png" marker="NoelleSakiRate01">My rate? Oh! I don't charge a single Mora when it comes to helping others with cleaning! Though I'm afraid my busy schedule wouldn't allow me to help with cleaning your mansion. Who will attend to all of my other duties while I am away?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="288">
                <condition role="opp" character="blake_belladonna" sayingMarker="bn1" />
                <state img="#-mustStrip.png" marker="NoelleBlakeGrandMaster01">Oh, the Knights of Favonius only serve the Acting Grand Master! It is our duty to uphold the ideals of freedom  for the Anemo God, Barbatos. That no one should be shackled by any means and the people should live life to the fullest!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="291">
                <condition role="opp" character="blake_belladonna" sayingMarker="bn4" />
                <state img="#-dutiful.png" marker="NoelleBlakeEvil01">If I am to be to become a knight, I must be strong enough to protect the citizens of Mondstadt. We mostly deal with monsters, but we have also been on high alert against another nation known as Snezhnaya, and their diplomats called the Fatui.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="294">
                <condition role="opp" character="blake_belladonna" sayingMarker="bn8" />
                <state img="#-sad.png" marker="NoelleBlakeFreedom01" font-size="small">I can see why you are so assertive about this after now knowing the context. I assume the best in people because I believe that freedom is the greatest thing someone can offer. I offer it every time I assist someone. Whether it be saving them from a dangerous monster, or even helping with a simple chore.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="297">
                <condition role="opp" character="blake_belladonna" sayingMarker="bn11" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="NoelleBlakeUnderstand01" font-size="small">Don't assume the best out of everyone, question someone's motives if I think there is something wrong, and keep an eye out if I don't fully believe their response. Okay, I think I got it now! Thank you so very much, Miss Blake! If there's anything I can do for you, just say the word and I will have it done in no time at all!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4" id="300">
                <condition role="opp" character="blake_belladonna" sayingMarker="bn15" />
                <state img="#-flustered.png" marker="NoelleBlakeMistress01">O-oh dear... I-I don't know what to say to that! Um, th-thank you, Miss Blake.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="303">
                <condition role="opp" character="meia" sayingMarker="noelle2" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="NoelleMeiaSelfless01">Is that what you think, Miss Meia? I only wish to help everyone around me by being there for them as both a maid and as a knight. How could that possibly be what is keeping me from achieving my goal of becoming a knight?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="305">
                <condition role="opp" character="dawn" sayingMarker="DawnNoelleArmor01" />
                <state img="#-mustStrip.png" marker="NoelleDawnArmor01">It can get a little heavy by the end of the day, especially after training. But I am used to wearing it all day, even when I'm just doing maid duties for the knights.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="70">
                <condition role="other" character="fischl" />
                <state img="#-mustStrip.png">Why I strip my whole armor first? Isn't it the natural thing to do? It's usually the first thing I strip when I get ready to bed too.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="self" consecutiveLosses="2-" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Just one round after losing my skirt? Now people will think I'm in a hurry to lose after all. I'm actually not!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="self" consecutiveLosses="2-" />
                <state img="#-shy.png">Losing twice in a row is already bad... but in a situation where I have to lose my shirt next...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="215">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="noelle_chicken_and_madame" />
                <state img="#-mustStrip.png">It's me? I have no other choice, but to strip then... Though I may be taking off my work uniform, feel free to place any orders in the meantime!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="36">
                <state img="#-mustStrip.png">My turn? Let me get out of my armor. It's a lot of effort, but I can remove it quite fast.</state>
                <state img="#-mustStrip.png">My turn? Very well, allow me to remove my armor. Yes, &lt;i&gt;all&lt;/i&gt; of my armor. Just a moment!</state>
                <state img="#-mustStrip.png">A shame, but now is the time for me to take off my armor. And I mean all of it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-3">
                <state img="#-surprised.png" oneShotId="909">If I must, I must. As a kni... no, as a mai... no, that isn't it either...</state>
                <state img="#-curtsey.png" oneShotId="910">As a dutiful maid would.</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png" oneShotId="911">I will follow through, as a good knight should.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png" oneShotId="921">V-very well. To be a Knight of Favonius means I must know what freedom means.  But I'm beginning to think that the definition is a little different for others.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">My last line of defense...</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">How unbecoming of a knight to be pushed this far...</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I-I will adhere to the rules, just as I adhere to the Knight's code.</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">Will this mean being truly free?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-surprised.png">I lost again? My skirt this time then... Yes, the whole skirt.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Ah, very well then. What next? Hmm... My skirt should suffice. May as well remove the whole thing too.</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">Another loss? Hmm... I believe getting rid of my whole skirt should be serviceable. </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_winning">
            <case stage="2-3">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I have been doing well...perhaps it's only right that I should lose some.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_normal">
            <case stage="2-3">
                <state img="#-sad.png">If I have any hope of taking the lead, I'll have to hope for the best and better cards.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_losing">
            <case stage="2-3">
                <state img="#-sad.png">I'll catch up! That's a promise!</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I may be behind now, but I'll turn this around...I hope.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripping">
            <case stage="0" id="186">
                <condition role="other" character="sucrose" stage="0-2" sayingMarker="sucrose02a" />
                <state img="#-strip.png">Enticing me? What do you mean by that?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4" id="189">
                <condition role="other" character="sucrose" stage="3-4" sayingMarker="sucrose02b" />
                <state img="#-strip.png">You don't feel judged by me, Sucrose, or for anyone for that matter. Walk the path that you wish to walk. Just I as will not stop to become a knight, you keep doing what you love!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="190">
                <condition role="other" character="sucrose" stage="0-4" sayingMarker="sucrose11a" />
                <state img="#-strip.png">Have I stripped like this? No...but if I could learn a new way of assisting others, I wouldn't say no...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="192">
                <condition role="other" character="sucrose" stage="5-9" sayingMarker="sucrose12b" />
                <state img="#-strip.png">You mean besides the other girls in the dressing room of the Knights of Favonius? ...Let me think about it while I get out of my skirt.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="195">
                <condition role="other" character="sucrose" stage="5-9" sayingMarker="sucrose32b" />
                <state img="#-strip.png">It's alright, Sucrose. I know that I gained a little weight there too. They just won't stop getting bigger...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4" id="196">
                <condition role="other" character="sucrose" stage="5-9" sayingMarker="sucrose42b" />
                <state img="#-strip.png">I actually worried a lot if it would look okay without hair... Your support actually means a lot, Sucrose.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4" id="199">
                <condition role="other" character="sucrose" stage="0-4" sayingMarker="sucrose42a" />
                <state img="#-strip.png">Elegant? I actually don't know if it looks better after removing my hair there, but if you say so...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="185">
                <condition role="other" character="meia" stage="0-5" sayingMarker="noelle01" />
                <state img="#-mustStrip.png" oneShotId="640">There is no greater honor than defending Mondstadt and its people, Meia. I only wish to serve people even better than the day before, and being a knight will let me do just that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="191">
                <condition role="other" character="meia" stage="0-5" sayingMarker="noelle12" />
                <state img="#-strip.png" oneShotId="674">Would it not be better for her to join you in battle, Ms. Meia?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="184">
                <condition role="other" character="kyou" stage="0-5" sayingMarker="kyou_noelle_armor" />
                <state img="#-strip.png" marker="kyou1">My armor is considered to be every piece, Kyou. I do thank you for your patience as I remove it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="188">
                <condition role="other" character="kyou" stage="0-7" sayingMarker="kyou_noelle_rest" />
                <state img="#-strip.png">Well... I'm not "eager to get to it" Kyou. While this is training to be better prepared for embarrassment, I do intend to win this game.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="197">
                <condition role="other" character="kyou" stage="0-7" sayingMarker="kyou_noelle_encourage" />
                <state img="#-strip.png">You... you really think so, Kyou? I don't look like I've eaten a lot?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="55">
                <condition role="other" character="hu_tao" sayingMarker="hutao02a" />
                <state img="#-strip.png">I think you have a pretty wrong idea about "freedom"... The Knights of Favonius do their best to keep law and order in Mondstadt. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="56">
                <condition role="other" character="hu_tao" sayingMarker="hutao02b" />
                <state img="#-strip.png">A mess? Well, if I can be at any help, I'll give you a hand of course! I hope I don't need my armor for it, do I?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="64">
                <condition role="other" character="hu_tao" sayingMarker="hutao22a" />
                <state img="#-strip.png">T-thank you very much for your effort to help, Hu Tao. But please don't worry about me! My p-panties won't come off this turn anyway.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="65">
                <condition role="other" character="hu_tao" sayingMarker="hutao22b" />
                <state img="#-strip.png">Eh? B-but aren't we both women and... Not that I haven't heard about two women doing it from... No, I shouldn't be sharing any Knight's private information.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="66">
                <condition role="other" character="hu_tao" sayingMarker="hutao12a" />
                <state img="#-strip.png">A boyfriend? Y-you mean like someone you l-love? ...I'm rather focused on my duties as a maid, and to try to make as many people happy as possible. I don't know I have time for a boyfriend right now...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="67">
                <condition role="other" character="hu_tao" sayingMarker="hutao12b" />
                <state img="#-strip.png">Oh, I'll be happy to exchange experiences with you, Hu Tao. I'm sure I can still learn a little from you. I was always curious how people in Liyue do their laundry and such. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="187">
                <condition role="other" character="senko" sayingMarker="senko02" />
                <state img="#-strip.png">Me? In a hurry? No, I just take this very seriously! If I strip my armor, I have to strip all of it. I know this won't be an advantage for me, but a good maid shouldn't make half things.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="193">
                <condition role="other" character="senko" sayingMarker="senko12" />
                <state img="#-strip.png">Now... you flatter me, Senko. &lt;i&gt;(Good no one can see me blushing, while I turn around to strip my skirt.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="194">
                <condition role="other" character="senko" sayingMarker="senko22" />
                <state img="#-strip.png">I-I'm not sure if I can accept that, Senko. At... at least not while I'm still in the game and others might need my service. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4" id="200">
                <condition role="other" character="senko" sayingMarker="senko42" />
                <state img="#-strip.png">I, er... I really appreciate your offer. E-especially because you want to teach me new things, but can I really accept this?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4" id="198">
                <condition role="other" character="senko" sayingMarker="senko42b" />
                <state img="#-strip.png">T-touch your tail? I actually... would like to do... I mean, it's for learning new things, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="71">
                <condition role="other" character="fischl" sayingMarker="fischl_noellearmorstrip" />
                <state img="#-strip.png">But that's the natural thing to do too, Fischl. It's just one set of armor after all. You would do the same, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="73">
                <condition role="other" character="fischl" sayingMarker="fischl_noellehosestrip2" />
                <state img="#-strip.png">My pantyhose are special made. They can resist all elements. Though, getting wet could end up becoming a problem in this game.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4" id="76">
                <condition role="other" character="fischl" sayingMarker="fischl_noellepantsustrip2" />
                <state img="#-strip.png">You need help shaving? If you want, I can show you, or even shave you myself the first time. Though, I think you look absolutely cute the way you are, Fischl.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="289">
                <condition role="opp" character="blake_belladonna" sayingMarker="bn2" />
                <state img="#-strip.png" marker="NoelleBlakeGrandMaster02" font-size="small">Actually, Grandmaster Jean is the hardest working person I know. She deals with almost everyone's problems on her own time, and is the kindest leader anyone can ask for. I see her as a model example of what it means to be a Knight of Favonius!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="292">
                <condition role="opp" character="blake_belladonna" sayingMarker="bn5" />
                <state img="#-strip.png" marker="NoelleBlakeEvil02">Goodness... Uhm. I don't recall reading about evil being those things in the library. Maybe I didn't catch it when I read it last...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="295">
                <condition role="opp" character="blake_belladonna" sayingMarker="bn9" />
                <state img="#-strip.png" marker="NoelleBlakeFreedom02" font-size="small">That sounds an awful lot like how the Fatui operate... I have been told to watch out for them. But before then, I had made it my duty to be extra welcoming to any outsiders visiting Mondstadt. Taking care of any travel bags they had, preparing them a welcoming feast, giving them a tour of the city...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="298">
                <condition role="opp" character="blake_belladonna" sayingMarker="bn12" />
                <state img="#-strip.png" marker="NoelleBlakeUnderstand02">R-right... Oh my, I didn't realize I was only down to my shirt and panties! Well, it's the least I can do for you helping me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4" id="301">
                <condition role="opp" character="blake_belladonna" sayingMarker="bn16" />
                <state img="#-strip.png" marker="NoelleBlakeMistress02">I... wanted to be mentally prepared for anything knighthood would throw at me. And now, after this game, I think I am far more ready than I ever been. And I have you to thank, M-Mistress Belladonna.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="306">
                <condition role="opp" character="dawn" sayingMarker="DawnNoelleArmor02" />
                <state img="#-strip.png" marker="NoelleDawnArmor02">Gosh, everyone said the same thing before. I just don't quite see it myself.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="216">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="noelle_chicken_and_madame" />
                <state img="#-strip.png">If you haven't decided, I recommend the Sweet Madame or the Mondstadt Grilled Meat.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="217">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="noelle_chicken_and_madame" />
                <state img="#-strip.png">It's a little embarrassing... I've gained a little weight. Do you mind if I turn around until I feel comfortable?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="218">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="noelle_chicken_and_madame" />
                <state img="#-strip.png">These have been feeling tighter lately...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="219">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="noelle_chicken_and_madame" />
                <state img="#-strip.png">I often hear that bigger chests are considered attractive, but lately they hardly fit into my bra anymore... as you have probably noticed.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4" id="220">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="noelle_chicken_and_madame" />
                <state img="#-strip.png">As much as I can recommend the food we serve, please look out for your health! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="37">
                <state img="#-strip.png">I could strip those in different turns? No, I can't do that! It all counts as my armor, so it's one item after all.</state>
                <state img="#-strip.png">My armor is just a piece of my outfit. It doesn't make me any less of knight! But it does make me look more in line with being a maid.</state>
                <state img="#-strip.png">It wouldn't be fair to the others if I removed every little bit of my armor. That'd be far too many layers!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="39">
                <state img="#-strip.png">It's not my intention to quickly strip; my belt holds my skirt up. I can't strip them separately.</state>
                <state img="#-strip.png">I can't take off my skirt without taking off the whole thing. Please don't assume I'm trying to undress as quickly as possible!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-strip.png">My pantyhose are flexible, ready to run, clean, whatever anyone needs!</state>
                <state img="#-strip.png">I don't need to be careful with my pantyhose. They're made especially for me, so they're as durable as I am. </state>
                <state img="#-strip.png">Some of the duties in Mondstadt require us to use wind gliders a lot. Without pantyhose, everyone could see... what you're about to see now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="40">
                <state img="#-strip.png">I've done my best to keep in shape, but still... I'm still a little unsure about my body.</state>
                <state img="#-strip.png">My armor normally gives enough support to my chest, so I usually don't wear anything under my shirt.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-strip.png">I did my best to keep myself tidy down here...but I'd still appreciate if you didn't stare...</state>
                <state img="#-strip.png">I won't give up! A Knight of Favonius never gives up, even with their backs against the wall!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripped">
            <case stage="1" id="201">
                <condition role="other" character="sucrose" stage="3-4" sayingMarker="sucrose03b" />
                <state img="#-after.png">Special? Special how? I'm still not a Knight yet? Though I'm ready to assist anyone with anything they ask, I'm still so far from my dream.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="204">
                <condition role="other" character="sucrose" stage="0-4" sayingMarker="sucrose11a" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I...can't say that I have. B-but, there's no telling what will be on the next Knight exam! I need to be prepared for anything! What if it's a matter of resolve through how far someone will strip?!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="203">
                <condition role="other" character="sucrose" stage="5-9" sayingMarker="sucrose13b" />
                <state img="#-shy.png">O-oh! I think I know what you mean by that. ...I never have been in such a situation before...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4" id="209">
                <condition role="other" character="sucrose" stage="5-9" sayingMarker="sucrose33b" />
                <state img="#-after.png">You think they're still okay? I sometimes wish they were as well-shaped as yours, Sucrose.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5" id="210">
                <condition role="other" character="sucrose" stage="5-9" sayingMarker="sucrose43b" />
                <state img="#-after.png">I-if you like. I actually never talked about it. Maybe that's why I'm still so unsure about it. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5" id="211">
                <condition role="other" character="sucrose" stage="0-4" sayingMarker="sucrose43a" />
                <state img="#-after.png">I see... It certainly looks tidy now, but I also liked the mature look they gave me. Should I let mine grow back too, Sucrose?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="58">
                <condition role="other" character="hu_tao" sayingMarker="hutao03b" />
                <state img="#-after.png">So it's even better not to be dressed for it? Well, I wanted to strip the whole armor anyway, but don't worry about my clothes. I don't mind getting dirty as long as I can help.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="57">
                <condition role="other" character="hu_tao" sayingMarker="hutao03" />
                <state img="#-after.png">Oh, yes! I remember that legal adviser from Liyue, who was having business with Eula. We don't have people like that in Mondstadt, but it's far from a lawless place, so much I can assure you. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="206">
                <condition role="other" character="hu_tao" saidMarker="hutao22a" />
                <state img="#-after.png">M-maybe I can be at your service instead. Even though I don't have much experience to make other girls' "panties wet" to be honest...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="208">
                <condition role="other" character="hu_tao" saidMarker="hutao22b" />
                <state img="#-after.png">B-but... If you don't mind, I'm always willing to learn new things. So...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5" id="68">
                <condition role="other" character="hu_tao" sayingMarker="hutao43b" />
                <state img="#-after.png">I... I think that was a praise, right? I-I actually wanted to let it grow in again next time.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="202">
                <condition role="other" character="senko" sayingMarker="senko03" />
                <state img="#-after.png">I better take off my hair dress too, to show how serious I really am. Though, I'm always open to learn things I don't know.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="205">
                <condition role="other" character="senko" sayingMarker="senko13" />
                <state img="#-after.png">Of course! If you need my service at some point, please let me know if I can assist you. But I guess I won't need my Vision for it, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="207">
                <condition role="other" character="senko" saidMarker="senko22" />
                <state img="#-after.png">&lt;i&gt;(Oh! Did I just indirectly told her to pamper me once I'm out of the game?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5" id="214">
                <condition role="other" character="senko" sayingMarker="senko43" />
                <state img="#-after.png">I... If one of us is already out of the game, I don't see why we shouldn't offer to help each other with the forfeit...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5" id="212">
                <condition role="other" character="senko" sayingMarker="senko43b" />
                <state img="#-touched.png">If... If you're okay with it, I don't see why if one of us is already out shouldn't help the other with the forfeit...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="72">
                <condition role="other" character="fischl" sayingMarker="fischl_noellevision" />
                <state img="#-after.png">I'm glad you're worried about me, Fischl, but I think I'll be fine. Even without my Vision.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="74">
                <condition role="other" character="fischl" sayingMarker="fischl_noelletailor" />
                <state img="#-after.png">Oh, well... I can tell you who made them later. It could end up embarrassing to both of us, if I tell you know, because it's a person you wouldn't expect to make clothes for women at the first place.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5" id="238">
                <condition role="other" character="estelle" sayingMarker="EstelleNoelleShaved" />
                <state img="#-after.png">It's not that I don't like it like this, Estelle. It's just that I'm... not sure if it might be better if I'd let it grow again. I'm so unsure what would be best...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="244">
                <condition role="opp" character="saki_zls" saidMarker="NoelleArmor1" />
                <state img="#-after.png" marker="NoelleSakiRate03">There we are! Now, what was it you mentioned earlier, Saki? Something regarding "living dead"?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="290">
                <condition role="opp" character="blake_belladonna" sayingMarker="bn3" />
                <state img="#-after.png" marker="NoelleBlakeGrandMaster03">I'm only doing my part as a maid, and a future Knight of Favonius. The thought of that I was able to help a stranger see what the Knights are about puts a smile on my face.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="293">
                <condition role="opp" character="blake_belladonna" sayingMarker="bn6" />
                <state img="#-shy.png" marker="NoelleBlakeEvil03">But--- I train every day on top of taking care of everyone around me, to live up to Master Jean's example! If I am too naïve to become a knight, then... How do I fix that?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="296">
                <condition role="opp" character="blake_belladonna" sayingMarker="bn10" />
                <state img="#-after.png" marker="NoelleBlakeFreedon03">I... think I understand what you're saying, Miss Blake. Correct me if I slip. So, I should question those around me about their true intentions? But also make sure to be kind to outsiders still?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4" id="299">
                <condition role="opp" character="blake_belladonna" sayingMarker="bn13" />
                <state img="#-after.png" marker="NoelleBlakeUnderstand03">Um, i-it's okay. I must apologize though, no matter how much I train, I always tend to put on a little weight. Especially after cooking for a festival in Mondstadt.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5" id="302">
                <condition role="opp" character="blake_belladonna" sayingMarker="bn17" />
                <state img="#-after.png" marker="NoelleBlakeMistress03">... I said I wanted to repay you for your kindness. So, if there is &lt;i&gt;anything&lt;/i&gt; you would like me to do for you, please don't be afraid to ask.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="opp" character="dawn" saidMarker="DawnNoelleArmor02" />
                <state img="#-after.png" marker="NoelleDawnArmor03" font-size="smaller">Hmm, I don't want to overwhelm you, but I have listed off my list of responsibilities to others and some have even fainted from hearing. There is dusting every room in the knight's hall, tending to the garden, preparing the meals for the knights, and laundry to name a few things!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5" id="213">
                <condition role="other" character="hatsune_miku" />
                <state img="#-touched.png">...Thank you very much, Miku.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="221">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="noelle_chicken_and_madame" />
                <state img="#-after.png">Do my shoes count as part of my uniform as well? ...Better safe than sorry! A true waitress doesn't do things by half-measures.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="222">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="noelle_chicken_and_madame" />
                <state img="#-after.png">I really need to start cutting back on eating our meals so much, but I need to make sure they taste right!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="223">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="noelle_chicken_and_madame" />
                <state img="#-after.png">At least they didn't rip. Oh, that would have been embarrassing...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4" id="225">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="noelle_chicken_and_madame" />
                <state img="#-after.png">Try not to let these distract you from the game or a meal, please.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5" id="224">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="noelle_chicken_and_madame" />
                <state img="#-after.png">I'm sorry I can't show you myself in perfect shape right now. I hope you enjoy the view anyway...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="38">
                <state img="#-after.png">Does my headdress also count as my armor? ...Better safe than sorry! A true Knight doesn't do things by half-measures.</state>
                <state img="#-after.png">Surely my headdress counts as a piece of my armor. No piece left behind!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="41">
                <state img="#-after.png">My Vision will have to go, too. Oh! Right! My Vision allows me to create a shield and enhance my claymore with the power of Geo -- the power of earth -- but I won't need that here.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-after.png">Before, these would rip due to how much I moved around, so I had specialty ones made that can keep up with me. Doesn’t help me forget the embarrassment though…</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-after.png">&lt;i&gt;(I hope they don't see I've gained a little weight...Even though I've kept up my training schedule every day.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-after.png">One of Mondstadt principles is the spirit of freedom...i-if I look at it that way, I don't feel so embarrassed!</state>
                <state img="#-after.png">I know this game is about seeing and being seen, but... Don't stare too much please... I gained a little weight after making sure all food at the last festival met my standards...</state>
                <state img="#-after.png">My chest has grown again lately. Probably because I was eating too much... I hope it doesn't bother you, that I'm not in perfect shape.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5" id="42">
                <state img="#-after.png">My hair down there always looked messy and untidy. But after I shaved, I'm not sure that was the right thing to do...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_strip">
            <case stage="0-7" id="226">
                <condition role="target" character="basil" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="631" marker="NoelleBasilGoAgain01">It's alright, Basil. Just get up and go again. Much like how I keep trying to be a Knight!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="227">
                <condition role="target" character="basil" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png" oneShotId="632" marker="NoelleBasilSick01">You're feeling warm? You're not getting sick are you, Basil? Is there anything I can do?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="257">
                <condition role="target" character="basil" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="935" marker="NoelleBasilSupport01">You're doing wonderfully so far, Basil! Don't be afraid to bow out if you need to, I won't hold it against you. I'm here for you if you need support!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="304">
                <condition role="target" character="ignatz" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-curtsey.png" oneShotId="961" marker="NoelleIgnatzSquire01">Am I mistaken, or did you mention you are a knight in training too? It's an honor to meet you, fellow squire!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I know I'm here for training and to win, but better luck in the next round, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">Forgive me, ~name~, but I must win! ...Which means you'll have to lose. Sorry...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="599">I'm a little curious as to what men wear to this sort of occasion: a lot, or a little? How about you, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">Don't let this loss get you down, ~name~! There's always next time!</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I made it through the round! But that means that...oh, please forgive me, ~name~...</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">Perhaps some tea will cheer you up, ~name~. I'll prepare it right away! Just say the word!</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">This is so conflicting:  as a Knight, I should aim for victory, but this is a failure for me as a maid to help others... how conflicting...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">&lt;i&gt;(How can I best assist the one who doesn't have the best hand each round?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">~Name~ lost? I shall give you the room you need to take off what you choose.</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Ooh! I survived this hand! ...U-umm, forgive me, I got excited for a second.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Stand proud and firm like a knight, ~name~! I'm not a full knight yet, but that's an advice I can give you.</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">A shame that ~name~ is the loser of this round. Perhaps I can lose next round to make you feel better?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Don't fret too much, ~name~. There's always next round. Maybe you'll get a string of good luck to pull you through!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Y-you can still win, ~name~, don't give up! And even if you do, it's not that bad either.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">~Name~ lost...and all of a sudden, my body is heating up...</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">&lt;i&gt;(I want to see more of ~name~. But as a maid and future knight I shouldn't say that out loud.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-serious.png">P-please...don't give up, ~name~! You only lose for real if you lose your hope.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">I-I may have fallen, ~name~, but that's no reason for you to follow this path as well.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">~Name~'s lost... Is this strong urge to be at help now because of my duties or because I'm touching myself right now?</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">~Name~ stripping is for some reason making me feel excited...</state>
                <state img="#-touched.png">All I can do now is hope for the best...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I'd prefer if you'd take off some more, ~name~... It would raise my confidence for the next knight exams again, if I see that I'm not the only one doing that badly.</state>
                <state img="#-touched.png">I'm like this, ~name~...so please, take off something that makes us feel closer...i-in pieces left!</state>
                <state img="#-touched.png">I'm pretty... Excited to see what you take off next, ~name~. ...I mean, maybe it will help me for my knight exam.</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">I wonder if I should offer ~name~ a tea... A tea would certainly help to calm down, but is this really the time for it?</state>
                <state img="#-serious.png">We both must stand firm, ~name~! I have been in grim battles before, so I know you must never give up. </state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I have turned around so many battles until now, I know there's always hope. You shouldn't give up either, as long you still have something left to strip, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">Find it in your heart to forgive me, ~name~. I can't afford to lose anymore. </state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">&lt;i&gt;(There's still hope for a win yet! How much has ~name~ left again?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-serious.png">Even in the face of defeat, I'll fight with all I have! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-sad.png">It's somehow sad that I'm already out. It feels like I'm left out...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I'm not sure if I lost before ~name~ because I'm worse at poker or I'm not used to the part where we get naked. I should watch ~name~ carefully and learn from him.</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">I think I should make the best out of the situation and watch ~name~ strip this round. M-maybe it will help me to become a good knight in some way.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_strip">
            <case stage="0-7" id="80" totalRounds="0">
                <condition role="target" character="reimu" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">I think you're a shrine maiden, right, Reimu? I heard about them from merchants who traveled to Inazuma. But you're not from Inazuma, are you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-1" id="79">
                <condition role="target" character="fluttershy" stage="1" sayingMarker="Noelle_strip_reply2" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="714">Thank you, Fluttershy! Hearing you say that makes it all worth it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="86">
                <condition role="target" character="sucrose" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">Don't feel down, Sucrose! I'm right here if you need any support!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="82">
                <condition role="target" character="fluttershy" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">If you feel that you need a moment to calm yourself, Fluttershy, let me know. I'm at your service!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="83">
                <condition role="target" character="fluttershy" stage="1-2" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">There you go, Fluttershy! I'm delighted to see you be braver!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="31">
                <condition role="target" character="ms.fortune" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png">It's not unusual to find cat-folk people in Teyvat, but I certainly haven't seen someone like you before. But I don't get around much outside of Mondstadt after all.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="81">
                <condition role="target" character="bernadetta" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">You are Bernadetta, right? If you feel nervous or uncomfortable, let me know and I'll do my best to help! As a maid and future knight, it's my duty to make this game as enjoyable as possible for everyone.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="84">
                <condition role="target" character="hu_tao" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-shy.png">You're from Liyue, aren't you? I've been in Liyue before to do some business, but fortunately I never needed to consult the Wangsheng Funeral Parlor.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="85">
                <condition role="target" character="senko" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="senko00">Judging from your clothes you would come from Inazuma... But what did you say before? You come from... Japan?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="77">
                <condition role="target" character="fischl" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">I must say, Miss Fischl, I hardly took you for someone who would partake in a game like this! I'm excited you decided to join us! Now then, I can take care of your clothes if need be.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="78">
                <condition role="target" character="dawn" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="831" marker="DawnExhausting01">It's always a pleasure to meet another so dedicated to their work! I do wonder though, how exhausting does it get dealing with these Pokémon every day? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="87">
                <condition role="target" character="mikan" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Please don't take offense, but is that red streak part of the design of your apron? If it's blood, I know a neat trick to get blood out of white apron, no matter how long it's been stained!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="230">
                <condition role="target" character="dawn" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="833" marker="DawnPoffin01">You had mentioned before that these Poffins are a treat for animals, as well as people too. Would you describe them more as a biscuit, or a pastry? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="ganyu" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="ganyu00">You work for the Qixing, don't you? I imagine you're very busy then. I know how busy our Acting Grand Master Jean is and she once told me that things are way busier in Liyue than in Mondstadt.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="estelle" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-touched.png" marker="estelle00">It... It would be an honor if I could make myself a little useful, Lady Estellise. I never served a true princess before, but I'll do my best to be as good as the maids who regularly serve you. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="estelle" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-dutiful.png" marker="estelle30">I think taking off the pantyhose now is totally within the rules. By the way, do you want me to lift your dress in such a way that you won't flash your...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="255">
                <condition role="target" character="amy" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-sad.png" marker="NoelleAmyWebs01">Ah, Miss Amy? I hope you don't think ill of me when I admit that I have had my share of spiders I have had to... dispose of. I always feel so bad too, they put so much effort into their webs that look so intricate!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="rosa" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-dutiful.png" marker="NoelleRosaCute01">Ah, Miss Rosa? If you don't mind, I just want to let you know you look so cute in that outfit!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="258">
                <condition role="target" character="blake_belladonna" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-excited.png" marker="NoelleBlakeWarrior01">So, Miss Blake! You are a warrior yourself, yes? What sort of things do you do battle with? Monsters? Other people?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="262">
                <condition role="target" character="blake_belladonna" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png" marker="NoelleBlakeVisionless01">For someone without a Vision, you seem very capable in combat. It's not often I get to meet someone like you: Vision-less and still formidable.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="265">
                <condition role="target" character="blake_belladonna" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-sad.png" marker="NoelleBlakeGeo01">Only the Archons are capable of granting Visions to those they deem worthy to wield them. It is not an easy task to earn the favor of an Archon. Which is why I feel so detached from my own.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="268">
                <condition role="target" character="blake_belladonna" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-dutiful.png" marker="NoelleBlakeGrimm01">Goodness! I've been gabbing on about my own problems that I have barely gotten to know you beyond asking if you are a warrior! Allow me to start over. Are you a mercenary, or part of a guild of fighters?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="271">
                <condition role="target" character="blake_belladonna" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-dutiful.png" marker="NoelleBlakeSushi01" font-size="small">If you don't mind me asking: what is your favorite food? I always try to get everyone's favorite meal memorized so that I can make it for them as a gift! I'm sure you know how wonderful it is to have your favorite meal gifted to you if you've been having a bad day.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="274">
                <condition role="target" character="blake_belladonna" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="NoelleBlakeAdepti01">It's a shame to think that people like you aren't widely accepted back where you are from. In the nation of Liyue, they praise the Adepti as demi-gods. Adepti being humans with a few different animal features on them.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="277">
                <condition role="target" character="blake_belladonna" stage="6" />
                <state img="#-touched.png" marker="NoelleBlakeRelaxed01">Miss Blake? How are you feeling now? I can tell by your body language that you're much more relaxed than when you were at the start of the game.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="280">
                <condition role="target" character="blake_belladonna" stage="7" />
                <state img="#-touched.png" marker="NoelleBlakePats01">So, you said before that I can touch your ears later. Would you like it if I did it for you? My friend I mentioned before always says she dislikes it, but secretly loves it! I think I even figured out how she likes it best.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="meia" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-dutiful.png" marker="NoelleMeiaService01">I can tell by your demeanor that you must be an extremely hard working person, Miss Meia. If you would like any assistance, look no further than a maid in service of the Knights of Favonius!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="heris" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-dutiful.png" oneShotId="959" marker="NoelleHerisCleanliness01">Miss Heris, I must say, your coat looks so pristine. All of your clothes do in fact! Might I ask how you wash them so i can learn how to do the same?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="325">
                <condition role="target" character="darkness" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">I believe we won't be needing any weapons here Darkness, but I too wanted to bring my claymore just to be safe.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="254">
                <condition role="target" character="dawn" sayingMarker="DawnsBack" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">Aww, isn't this sweet? May the Anemo Archon bless your new found relationship, you two!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Ohh! Love knows no bounds, it seems! May Barbatos bless you two with a loving relationship!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-serious.png">P-please...don't give up, ~name~! You only lose for real if you lose your hope.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">I-I may have fallen, ~name~, but that's no reason for you to follow this path as well.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">~Name~ lost... Is this strong urge to be at help now because of my duties or because I'm touching myself right now?</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">~Name~ stripping is for some reason making me feel excited...</state>
                <state img="#-touched.png">All I can do now is hope for the best...</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">&lt;i&gt;(I want to see more of ~name~. But as a maid and future knight I shouldn't say that out loud.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Y-you can still win, ~name~, don't give up! And even if you do, it's not that bad either.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Mmmph... ~Name~ lost...? Wh-why am I... (&lt;i&gt;Suddenly feeling so hot..?&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">Ah, ~name~'s turn? Good... W-wait, don't take that out of context! I meant to say I feel very g-good!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I'd prefer if you'd take off some more, ~name~... It would raise my confidence for the next knight exams again, if I see that I'm not the doing that badly.</state>
                <state img="#-touched.png">I'm like this, ~name~...so please, take off something that makes us feel closer...i-in pieces left!</state>
                <state img="#-touched.png">I'm pretty... Excited to see what you take off next, ~name~. ...I mean, maybe it will help me for my knight exam.</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">I wonder if I should offer ~name~ a tea... A tea would certainly help to calm down, but is this really the time for it?</state>
                <state img="#-serious.png">We both must stand firm, ~name~! I have been in grim battles before, so I know you must never give up. </state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I have turned around so many battles until now, I know there's always hope. You shouldn't give up either, as long you still have something left to strip, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">Find it in your heart to forgive me, ~name~. I can't afford to lose anymore. </state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">&lt;i&gt;(There's still hope for a win yet! How much has ~name~ left again?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-serious.png">Even in the face of defeat, I'll fight with all I have! </state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">Ah, ~name~'s turn then? I was worried I would be next. Considering my only option left is...</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">&lt;i&gt;Phew!&lt;/i&gt; I was hoping my hand was enough to win. Ah, please don't think I'm trying to rub it in, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Did I dust the library today? Hmm... I don't remember if I did... Oh! Sorry, I was a little distracted. Go ahead, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">I must apologize, ~name~. Normally I would protect those in need, but this is merely a game. I-If you're feeling uncomfortable, feel free to step out!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">Don't let this loss get you down, ~name~! There's always next time!</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I made it through the round! But that means that...oh, please forgive me, ~name~...</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">Perhaps some tea will cheer you up, ~name~. I can make some ready in no time.</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">This is so conflicting:  as a Knight, I should aim for victory, but this is a failure for me as a maid to help others... how conflicting...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">&lt;i&gt;(How can I best assist the one who doesn't have the best hand each round?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">~Name~ lost? I shall give you the room you need to take off what you choose.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Ooh! I survived this hand! ...U-umm, forgive me, I got excited for a second.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Stand proud and firm like a knight, ~name~! I'm not a full knight yet, but that's an advice I can give you.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I know I'm here for training and to win, but better luck in the next round, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">Forgive me, ~name~, but I must win! ...Which means you'll have to lose. Sorry...</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">A shame that ~name~ is the loser of this round. Perhaps I can lose next round to make you feel better?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Don't fret too much, ~name~. There's always next round. Maybe you'll get a string of good luck to pull you through!</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="1045">It is ~name~'s turn to remove something because their hand was weaker, correct? Got it! I  just wanted to make sure I got it right with what I had studied.</state>
                <state img="#-curtsey.png">No need to worry, ~name~. As both a maid &lt;i&gt;and&lt;/i&gt; a knight, I can make sure you're in good company.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-sad.png">It's somehow sad that I'm already out. It feels like I'm left out...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I'm not sure if I lost before ~name~ because I'm worse at poker or I'm not used to the part where we get naked. I should watch ~name~ carefully and learn from her.</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">I think I should make the best out of the situation and watch ~name~ strip this round. M-maybe it will help me to become a good knight in some way.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I know the focus is on ~name~ now, but I also like to watch  the players with the better hands to see what they made better than her. It's a good way to learn about the game and maybe for my plans to become a knight as well.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Even in my current state, I promise to make myself a proper knight. I just need to observe ~name~ and how they handle their next strip.</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">Since I'm not in the game anymore, would any of you care for tea? I'd be happy to make some for everyone!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="tie">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Hold on...the hands are the same! The chances of a tie happening are incredibly low.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-sad.png">He's done wonderfully this whole time if he's only taking his ~clothing~ now...Hah, I still have so far to go...</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">How could I have lost by so much...? I should double my efforts from now on!</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">This...isn't making me feel anything right now...and my self-confidence doesn't seem to like that.</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">Master Jean would be so disappointed to see me lose like this...</state>
                <state img="#-touched.png">All I can do is carry on, despite having been defeated...good luck, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Perhaps I should pray at the Church next time for more luck next time I play.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-sad.png">If he's only taking off his ~clothing~ now...Perhaps ~name~ would make for a more capable knight than me...</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">If he still has some small stuff to strip, does that mean I'm doing completely worse than ~name~, or is this just part of his strategy to unsettle me? Whatever it is, it's working...</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">I'll try not to disgrace myself any further with more victories...so please forgive me, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">My opponent is stripping some small stuff while I'm already exposed... I wonder what the most appropriated way to react as a maid would be.</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">Perhaps getting to this point re-enforces how good a maid I am: letting others win...</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">A knight doesn't give up! Even it's a small blow now, there's still a chance!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">The non-essentials are usually the first to go, right?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">~clothing.ifPlural(Do|Does)~ your ~clothing~ have any special meaning to you, like my roses do? If so, you maybe should keep ~clothing.ifPlural(it|them)~ and strip something bigger.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">It's always the armor that takes the hit for you. Just as your ~clothing~ took the loss for you now.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I always try to not to worry about small mistakes, but in the end I keep worrying all day if I did something wrong...</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I try not to keep any small things on me; they could be lost as I'm fighting.</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">Knights try to keep only their essentials on them; there's no telling if they could be damaged while on patrol.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-calm.png">It's okay, ~name~. I'd rather focus on myself than on others right now anyway.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">It doesn't look you need any assistance with something as small as your ~clothing~, right? I'm currently busy anyway...</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">That's good, nothing big happens right now, so I can take it easy.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">No need to worry, ~name~. There is still time for me to turn it around... maybe...</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">I wonder what exactly I did wrong to not have something like his ~clothing~ left... Was it because I stripped the armor in one round? Or did I just use a wrong strategy? I wish I had prepared more for this...</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">What's done is done, no use crying over it... but even so... If this is preparation for the upcoming knights exam, I'll probably fail again...</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">I still have so far to go in my training...&lt;i&gt;(Should I ask ~name~ for advice?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-serious.png">I'm not giving up yet, ~name~! Just like any Knight of Favonius, I'll fight to end!</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">I'll need to study twice as much if I'm to have a chance next time...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-calm.png">On to the next battle! Prepare yourself, ~name~! I'm more durable than I l appear, I assure you.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Be sure to place your belongings in a place where they won't get dirty.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Perhaps I should take more small things with me the next time I play...</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">Your ~clothing~ suited you quite well, ~name~. But sacrifice is sometimes necessary for victory!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I wonder if Mondstadt is capable of making something like that...maybe the others could enjoy them.</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">I don't think I'd have anything more than I'd have on usually. I have to keep my load light, save for my sword.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Would Kaeya or any of the other Knights wear something like ~name~'s ~clothing~? I'll have to ask when I see them.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">Keep your defenses up, ~name~! I won't lower mine any time soon.</state>
                <state img="#-serious.png">Even if the loss of yours doesn't have big consequences, you should try to avoid becoming careless, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-shy.png">To be left so defeated...disgraceful...</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">~Name~ would be far more ready for such an embarrassing exam than I would be...</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I'll have to better next time...if I can handle next time...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-happy.png">I hope, you don't mind if I just continue? </state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">Don't worry about me! I'm doing fine without any help. Please, continue the game!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Where was I...ah, yes! &lt;i&gt;(I love what comes next.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0-7" id="17" priority="483">
                <condition role="other" character="perona" sayingMarker="nami_negative2" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">She's casting a curse?! Be careful, Nami!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="16" priority="381">
                <condition role="target" character="florina" stage="0" saidMarker="fled" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">It's okay, come back!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="2">
                <condition role="target" character="nami" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png">That's an interesting weapon. It can even grow smaller or bigger! How convenient! Though, why does your weapon not just appear and disappear like mine does?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="3">
                <condition role="target" character="nami" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Something fell out...is that a...wanted poster?!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="104">
                <condition role="target" character="fina" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">Perhaps you should get custom-made boots, Fina. Mine always ended up worn out until I did.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Still, you can't deny that walking is great exercise!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="103">
                <condition role="target" character="fina" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-serious.png">You should be careful of accessories you take into battle, Fina. It's why I try to keep as few on me as possible.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="105">
                <condition role="target" character="asuna_yuuki" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">That's an interesting accessory. I've never seen anything like an Augma before...</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">The technology from the city you come from must be incredible if you're describing it as such, Asuna...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="108">
                <condition role="target" character="sucrose" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-serious.png">Be careful not to damage the fabric of your gloves when you hold them with your teeth. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="34">
                <condition role="target" character="ms.fortune" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">That is a lovely bell around your neck. I know Diona doesn't like if people treat her like a cat, but I think something like that would suit her as well.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="107">
                <condition role="target" character="petra" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png">If I'm not mistaken, only the Hilichurls have their own language. A girl in Mondstadt named Ella Musk tries to learn it and it certainly isn't easy...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="50">
                <condition role="target" character="charlie" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">A hotel like that sounds like a good idea. Do you need more personal? I could help out on my free days. ...Wait, when do I actually have free days? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="59">
                <condition role="target" character="hu_tao" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png" marker="huTao01">Is that a real ghost? I never seen one like that before. Is it connected to your Pyro Vision, or is it because of your work at the funeral parlor?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="106">
                <condition role="target" character="senko" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="senko01">It is strange because I heard they worship fox spirits in Inazuma too. I'm sure you would be very popular over there!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="ganyu" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-bashful.png" marker="ganyu31">I hope I'm not asking about a delicate topic, but those horns... Do they ever get in your way?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="estelle" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-shy.png" marker="estelle01">Is it really okay to call you "Estelle"? Mondstadt doesn't have a royal family, so I'm not sure if it would be appropriate for a maid to address a princess by her nickname.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="326">
                <condition role="target" character="darkness" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">I'd be happy to hold onto your sword and belt for the time being, Darkness! Caring for the Knights' weapons is one of my many duties.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I always try to not to worry about small mistakes, but in the end I keep worrying all day when I made something wrong...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="600">Does that hold any special meaning to you, like my roses do? If so, you maybe should keep it and strip something bigger.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I try not to keep any small things on me; they could be lost as I'm fighting.</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">That's a shame... Your ~clothing~ looked good on you.</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">Knights try to keep only their essentials on them; there's no telling if they could be damaged while on patrol.</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png" oneShotId="601">She's taking off her ~clothing~...perhaps I should have come with more items to give myself a better chance.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Accessories shouldn't be worn to battle unless they are important to you. ~clothing.ifPlural(Are|Is)~ your ~clothing~ important to you?</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">I'd love to wear something like ~name~'s ~clothing~ when I'm not in battle, but there's no telling if I will see combat or not every day.</state>
                <state img="#-curtsey.png">Take care not to drop your ~clothing~, ~name~! I can clean ~clothing.ifPlural(it|them)~ if you do.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-sad.png">She's done so well for herself...this is unbecoming of a knight in training.</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">Perhaps getting to this point re-enforces how good a maid I am: letting others win...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">&lt;i&gt;(~Name~... I wonder if I should ask her for advice on how to do better...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">A knight doesn't give up! Even it's a small blow now, there's still a chance!</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">If she's only taking off her ~clothing~ now... Perhaps ~name~ would make for a more capable knight than me...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">My opponent is stripping some small stuff while I'm already exposed... I wonder what the most appropriated way to react as a maid would be.</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">I'll try not to disgrace myself any further with more victories... so please forgive me, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">If she still has some small stuff to strip, does that mean I'm doing completely worse than ~name~, or is this just part of her strategy to unsettle me? Whatever it is, it's working...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-sad.png">She's done wonderfully this whole time if she's only taking her ~clothing~ now...Hah, I still have so far to go...</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">How could I have lost by so much...? I should double my efforts from now on!</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">This...isn't making me feel anything right now...and my self-confidence doesn't seem to like that.</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">Master Jean would be so disappointed to see me lose like this...</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">All I can do is carry on, despite having been defeated...good luck, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Perhaps I should pray at the Church next time for more luck next time I play.</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">Just your ~clothing~ then? A shame, ~clothing.ifPlural(they|it)~ looked lovely on you too.</state>
                <state img="#-curtsey.png">I can make sure your ~clothing~ is thoroughly cleaned and taken care of! That is to say if ~clothing.ifPlural(they|it)~ need to be.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-calm.png">It's okay, ~name~. I'd rather focus on myself than on others right now anyway.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">It doesn't look you need any assistance with something as small as your ~clothing~, right? I'm currently busy anyway...</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">That's good, nothing big happens right now, so I can take it easy.</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">Something small... I'm sad to see your ~clothing~ go. ~clothing.ifPlural(They|It)~ really completed your look.</state>
                <state img="#-touched.png">It's a wonder how something as simple as your ~clothing~ can make you look so beautiful, ~name~...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="0-7" id="1">
                <condition role="target" character="nami" stage="3" sayingMarker="pirate" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">A pirate?! I didn't know those were around anymore...and what is that bounty?! Are you truly so evil?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="29">
                <condition role="target" character="sucrose" stage="3" sayingMarker="sucrose_ears" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">Even if ears like that aren't unusual in Teyvat, yours are special among them. I really like them as I like you, Sucrose.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="112">
                <condition role="target" character="sucrose" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">Not that I couldn't fix them, but you should be careful with your stuff. If you have difficulties undressing them or anything else, you know, I'm happy to assist you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="35">
                <condition role="target" character="ms.fortune" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Oh no! What happened to your head! I'm trained in first aid, but the books never mentioned what to do if the whole head goes... I-I don't know what to do now! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="111">
                <condition role="target" character="petra" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-excited.png">So I really look up to people who do stuff in a foreign language. They are working so hard! We all should worship that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="110">
                <condition role="target" character="charlie" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-worried.png">Let's see... On Mondays I have to... Tuesday I need to... Wednesday? No, I already have so many things to do on Wednesdays... Maybe on...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="109">
                <condition role="target" character="hu_tao" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="huTao02">I actually heard some stories about people seeing ghosts before, but they never described one like that... Maybe ghosts in Liyue look totally different to the ones in Mondstadt.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="113">
                <condition role="target" character="senko" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png" marker="senko02">Your clothes even look a little like the clothes from the shrine maidens from Inazuma, now that I think about it. It's amazing how Inazuma and the land you're from are matching each other.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="ganyu" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-shy.png" marker="ganyu32">It's just... I know how &lt;i&gt;certain parts&lt;/i&gt; of my body can be bothersome already. I don't want to imagine where those horns bump into if you aren't careful...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="estelle" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="estelle02">As you wish, Lady Es--- I mean, Estelle. But even if I address you less formally, I will still give you the treatment a princess deserves. ...Or would that still be too much?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="327">
                <condition role="target" character="darkness" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-worried.png">Though, I hope you'll still be comfortable without your means of fighting. I know some knights who feel antsy if their weapons isn't at their waste.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-shy.png">To be left so defeated... disgraceful...</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">~Name~ would be far more ready for such a embarrassing exam than I would be...</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I'll have to do better next time...if I can handle a next time...</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Good job for doing so well, ~name~. I'll need to study up my poker game.</state>
                <state img="#-touched.png">If &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; were training for knight exams, I'd say you'd pass with flying colors! If your poker skills translated to that well enough.</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">R-right! Is anyone hungry? I can see about preparing snacks, even in my current state.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-shy.png">I think I could use something like ~name~'s clothing right now... I can't afford to let myself be pushed around like this...</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">What's done is done, no use crying over it... but even so... If this is preparation for the upcoming knights exam, I'll probably fail again...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I still have so far to go in my training...&lt;i&gt;(Should I ask ~name~ for advice?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-serious.png">I'm not giving up yet, ~name~! Just like any Knight of Favonius, I'll fight to end!</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">She's done much better than I have with saving her ~clothing~ until now...  Did I not study hard enough?</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">I'll need to study twice as much if I'm to have a chance next time...</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">No need to worry, ~name~. There is still time for me to turn it around... maybe...</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">I wonder what exactly I did wrong to not have something like her ~clothing~ left... Was it because I stripped the armor in one round? Or did I just use a wrong strategy? I wish I had prepared more for this...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-calm.png">On to the next battle! Prepare yourself, ~name~! I'm more durable than I look at the first sight.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Be sure to place your belongings in a place where they won't get dirty.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Perhaps I should take more small things with me the next time I play...</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">Your ~clothing~ suited you quite well, ~name~. But sacrifice is sometimes necessary for victory!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I wonder if Mondstadt is capable of making something like that...maybe others could enjoy them.</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">I try not carry small things on me when I'm out and about. It's best to keep your load light for battle and for quick responses.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Would Amber or any of the other Knights wear something like ~name~'s ~clothing~? I'll have to ask when I see them.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Keep your defenses up, ~name~! I won't lower mine any time soon.</state>
                <state img="#-serious.png">Even if the loss of yours don't have big consequences, you should try to avoid to become careless, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">If your ~clothing~ gets dirty, just say the word and I'll be more than happy to clean it for you!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-happy.png">I hope, you don't mind if I just continue? </state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">Don't worry about me! I'm doing fine without any help. Please, continue the game!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Where was I...ah, yes! &lt;i&gt;(I love what comes next.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">She only took off her ~clothing~... And yet... </state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Maybe losing that round will be enough to help you find the courage to win! Just ah, don't let me distract you...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_minor">
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-shy.png">I'm not blaming ~name~ for stripping his ~clothing~ now, but it had could have been earlier... </state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">If I had done better, perhaps we'd be in each other's shoes, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">~Name~ still going strong...perhaps I'm not meant to be a knight if I'm defeated so easily...</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">K-keep trying...~name~...</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">How could I have been so defeated... I was training and learning so hard for this...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-flustered.png">You're catching up, ~name~...but that's not a good thing! ...Or is it?</state>
                <state img="#-serious.png">Be sure to keep clothes organized, ~name~. I don't have many left to do so...</state>
                <state img="#-touched.png">&lt;i&gt;(~Name~ grows closer to my state! Though, he's still far away...from being this exposed...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">As though it weren't bad enough that I'm so close to being out... I'm not recognizable as a maid right now, am I?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I'll probably put all my clothes into the laundry after the game, since I stripped them anyway. Maybe ~name~ wants me to wash her ~clothing~ too, given the opportunity.</state>
                <state img="#-touched.png">A true knight would never leave something done half. I'm glad you don't quit now midway too, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">You may have taken a loss this time ~name~, but perhaps the gods will favor you next hand. I'm afraid I won't make it easy for you though. This is training for me after all.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Your ~clothing~ now, ~name~? The game seems to be picking up a little.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I don't think he'll need any privacy if he's only removing his ~clothing~ this time.</state>
                <state img="#-serious.png">No battle is won easily, ~name~. Remain calm and steady. &lt;i&gt;(...I should take my own advice in my next exam...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Get ready for the next round, ~name~! You've still got clothes left, so you can still fight!</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">Don't forget to keep yourself motivated to keep going, ~name~! Losing is also a part of the game. Even though I know that it can be pretty... embarrassing to lose here.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">It's just one loss, ~name~! Nothing else to do but to get up and try again! &lt;i&gt;(Like I do with my exams...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">Keep faith in your luck, and it's sure to turn around! Though I rather rely on effort than on luck myself.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">~Name~'s ~clothing~ somehow got my interests... ~clothing.ifPlural(A-are they|I-is it)~ that special?</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">&lt;i&gt;(Normally I don't care about my surroundings when I'm... but watching ~name~ isn't bad either...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">A-as a knight...no, as a maid, I have the duty to watch you to strip your ~clothing~...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_minor">
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">If you have any difficulties removing any significant items, I'll gladly assist you. I would even take a break from my current task for that.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Was that all? I mean just... &lt;i&gt;(Somehow I was hoping for more.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">~Name~'s only taking his ~clothing~ off now and nothing more? How...disappointing.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-excited.png">Good job on hanging in there, ~name~. But don't relax just yet!</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">That really doesn't help me at this point.</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">I still have so far to go...~name~ taking off his ~clothing~ only goes to reinforce that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-touched.png">I mustn't give up yet...~Name~ may have only taken off his ~clothing~ just now, but a true knight won't lose hope...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I'm sure ~name~ must have studied hard before coming here. I wonder if he played more than 17 rounds per day to be prepared for this...</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">Make sure to put your ~clothing~ down anywhere that ~clothing.ifPlural(they|it)~ won't get dirty. Though, I think I could wash ~clothing.ifPlural(them|it)~ too after the game is over. </state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">&lt;i&gt;(Keep fighting, Noelle! Nothing is lost yet. I should raise my efforts a little bit though.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-happy.png">I'm doing good so far, I just need to stay focused! ...Oh, you should stay focused too, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">As a knight, I must strive for victory, but as a maid, I'll keep hoping for your success.</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">You may be down now, ~name~, but there's still a battle to fight! Maybe I'm your opponent, but if you need help, I'm here for you.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">All you can do is move forward, ~name~. </state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">The competition is heating up, ~name~! Let's do our best and face the next hand together!</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">I once again realized where this game will lead to... Is this even the right place for a future and honored knight to be at?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0-7" id="115">
                <condition role="target" character="ms.fortune" stage="0" saidMarker="Noelle_Catfolk_0A" sayingMarker="Noelle_Catfolk_0B" />
                <state img="#-dutiful.png" oneShotId="641">Teyvat is the land that I come from, Ms. Fortune. I live in the city of freedom known as Mondstadt. As for Ferals, no, I can't say we've heard of such beings.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="18">
                <condition role="target" character="shantae" stage="1" sayingMarker="monkey" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">She...transformed into a monkey!? Incredible!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="6">
                <condition role="target" character="sakura" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">A...zombie? Someone who has already died and returned? I know there are spirits out there, but the dead can retain a body?!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="118">
                <condition role="target" character="fina" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="CupilStrippingChirp">What's that chirping sound?</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png" marker="CupilStrippingChirp">Did you just imitate a bird, Fina?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="121">
                <condition role="target" character="sucrose" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-sad.png">Even I'm really happy about my Geo Vision, I always wanted to have an Anemo vision like you. I mean, Geo's the furthest thing from Anemo, and for a Knight of Favonius... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="32">
                <condition role="target" character="ms.fortune" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">I've heard stories about all kinds of places from travelers and merchants, though. So I can't tell if there aren't people like you in Teyvat at all.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="119">
                <condition role="target" character="bernadetta" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-excited.png">And don't worry about your safety! If anyone really would do try to harm you, I'll be here to protect you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="117">
                <condition role="target" character="bernadetta" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">Your last name indicates that you're a noble, right? Do you have maids where you normally live? If you miss some maid service, just ask me. A good maid is always on duty.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="120">
                <condition role="target" character="hu_tao" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-dutiful.png" marker="huTao21">I heard people in Liyue only use the best materials to make their clothes, so you need to be extra careful with them. If you need some help with your coat, I can help you to untie it. Even I'm not that familiar with the lacing in Liyue...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-1 7" id="116">
                <condition role="target" character="senko" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="senko20">It's alright to let your apron go now. As long as I'm here, I can take over your duties as well. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-6" id="122">
                <condition role="target" character="senko" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="senko20a">It's alright to let your apron go now. If I lost my apron, you don't need it either.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4" id="114">
                <condition role="target" character="senko" stage="6" />
                <state img="#-excited.png" marker="senko60">I know it's not the best time when you're about to lose your last item, but how would you like a bet? Whoever loses first has to help the other with her forfeit.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="ganyu" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-dutiful.png" marker="ganyu01">If you want, I can help out a little. I don't know much about contracts and other paperwork, but I could take over some of your delivery duties and such. I can come over to Liyue and...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="ganyu" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="ganyu11">I wonder if there are any other ways I could support her, if I can't visit Liyue on a regular basis...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="estelle" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png" marker="estelle11">Are you okay, Estelle? Do you want me to help you with your dress? I'm sure there's a better way than pulling it over your head like that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-shy.png">I'm not blaming ~name~ for stripping her ~clothing~ now, but it had could have been earlier... </state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">If I had done better, perhaps we'd be in each others shoes, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">~Name~ still going strong...perhaps I'm not meant to be a knight if I'm defeated so easily...</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">K-keep trying...~name~...</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">How could I have been so defeated... I was training and learning so hard for this...</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">I can take that here if you'd like!</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">&lt;i&gt;(If I had brought more minor things, maybe I may have won...) &lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-touched.png">&lt;i&gt;When I start to encourage her...maybe it'll help me gain the confidence I need to play the next round...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-touched.png">A true knight would never leave something done half. I'm glad you don't quit now midway too, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Perhaps I should ask ~name~ about what I should wear next time, seeing as she's only taken her ~clothing~ off just now...</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">As though it weren't bad enough that I'm so close to being out... I'm not recognizable as a maid right now, am I?</state>
                <state img="#-serious.png">Be sure to keep clothes organized, ~name~. I don't have many left to do so...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I'll probably put all my clothes into the laundry after the game, now I stripped them anyway. Maybe ~name~ wants me to wash her ~clothing~ too, given the opportunity.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">You may have taken a loss this time ~name~, but perhaps the gods will favor you next hand. I'm afraid I won't make it easy for you though. This is training for me after all.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Your ~clothing~ now, ~name~? The game seems to be picking up a little.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I don't think she'll need any privacy if she's only removing her ~clothing~ this time.</state>
                <state img="#-serious.png">No hard battle is won easily, ~name~. Remain calm and steady. &lt;i&gt;(...I should take my own advice in my next exam...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Get ready for next round, ~name~! You've still got clothes left, so you can still fight!</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">Don't forget to keep yourself motivated to keep going, ~name~! Losing is also a part of the game. Even though I know that it can be pretty... embarrassing to lose here.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">It's just one loss, ~name~! Nothing else to do but to get up and try again! &lt;i&gt;(Like I do with my exams...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">Keep faith in your luck, and it's sure to turn around! Though I rather rely on effort than on luck myself.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Your ~clothing~ really suited your outfit, ~name~. A shame you had to take it off, but next round is bound to be better.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">As a maid, I will always have the urge to assist others, but...right now I I fear that I can't. I don't want to make your ~clothing~ dirty...</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">I hope you get along, ~name~. I'm a little out of service right now.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">~Name~'s ~clothing~ somehow got my interests... ~clothing.ifPlural(A-are they|I-is it)~ that special?</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">Ooh, to be so defeated. ~Name~ still had her ~clothing~ to take off...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">&lt;i&gt;(Why do I feel... disappointed that she's taking off her ~clothing~ now?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">P-perhaps... ah... I should ask ~name~ for advice on... hah... how to do better next time.</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">That's too bad... I-I mean...! That I was beaten so badly! Yes!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_minor">
            <case stage="0-7" id="46">
                <condition role="target" character="bernadetta" stage="1" />
                <test expr="~target.costume~" value="default" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Well, if you look at it that way, it's just &lt;i&gt;one&lt;/i&gt; uniform after all... Oh, but I think you should be fine to strip it in two phases if you feel more comfortable that way, of course!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="123">
                <condition role="target" character="bernadetta" stage="1" />
                <test expr="~target.costume~" value="bernadetta_war_outfit" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">I think there's no need to strip the dress too. Your cape and your dress maybe are part of the same set of clothes, but are different enough to stripped in two phases.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="47">
                <condition role="target" character="bernadetta" stage="2" />
                <test expr="~target.costume~" value="default" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">Don't worry about it! It's actually not unusual to wear spats, pantyhose, or shorts under a skirt in Teyvat. I'm very much, well, used to that view.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="124">
                <condition role="target" character="bernadetta" stage="2" />
                <test expr="~target.costume~" value="bernadetta_war_outfit" />
                <state img="#-excited.png">You're totally good, Bernadetta. If you want to see it like that, you actually stripped &lt;i&gt;two&lt;/i&gt; gloves this round. That should be enough for now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="125">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="CupilStrippingChirp" />
                <condition role="target" character="fina" stage="3" saidMarker="FinaNoelleCupilStripping" sayingMarker="FinaNoelleCupil" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="675">I've seen the Honorary Knight have a Seelie follow them once or twice, but I don't believe it needed any feeding like Cupil does.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="25">
                <condition role="target" character="fina" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">Oh, that is something like those mini Seelies, right? They are very cute, but I don't have much time to take care of one. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="129">
                <condition role="target" character="sucrose" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-touched.png">But your Vision actually isn't the only thing I envy you for. &lt;i&gt;(With small breasts like those, I could be even more efficient with my tasks.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="33">
                <condition role="target" character="ms.fortune" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Maybe I should broaden my horizon a little from time to time. But what will happen to my duties if I'm traveling around the world?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="127">
                <condition role="target" character="hu_tao" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png" marker="huTao22">Those are... beautiful! This time it's an elemental skill from your Vision, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="126">
                <condition role="target" character="senko" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-dutiful.png" marker="senko21">What do you usually do, Senko? Washing? Cooking? Cleaning? I can do that too. And I can show that I... can do all other services you do just as good as you do too.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="128">
                <condition role="target" character="senko" stage="7" />
                <state img="#-bashful.png" marker="senko61">I-I'm sorry if that was a little direct. I hope I didn't go too far with that suggestion. &lt;i&gt;(But that could be the last chance to feel how fluffy she really is.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="ganyu" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-flustered.png" marker="ganyu02">Oh, no! I forgot how long the way from Mondstadt to Liyue is by foot. If I want to arrive in time, I had to leave Mondstadt at... What will happen to my duties at home? And the last time I was in Liyue I took so long, Jean was worried about me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="ganyu" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-excited.png" marker="ganyu12">I know! When I visit Liyue next time to buy something, I can deliver some cargo on my way back. Don't worry, I can carry a lot!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="estelle" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="estelle12">Oh, no! Now your hair got a little messy... I should have prevented that by acting faster. I failed as a maid...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-excited.png">Good job on hanging in there, ~name~. But don't relax just yet!</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">That really doesn't help me at this point.</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">I still have so far to go...~name~ taking off her ~clothing~ only goes to reinforce that.</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">I can keep it in safe place right over here if you so desire, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">To have only taken off your ~clothing~ now... you're very talented at poker, ~name~! Could you tutor me?</state>
                <state img="#-serious.png">No time to think you're going to win just because you still have minor pieces to take off, ~name~! Stay focused!</state>
                <state img="#-curtsey.png">I humbly request that you do your best!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-happy.png">I'm doing good so far, I just need to stay focused! ...Oh, you should stay focused too, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">As a knight, I must strive for victory. As a maid, however, I'll keep hoping for your success.</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">You may be down now, ~name~, but there's still a battle to fight! Maybe I'm your opponent, but if you need help, I'm here for you.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">All you can do is move forward, ~name~. </state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">Forgive me, ~name~. Not letting the others win in a simple game like this isn't very knightly...</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">I once again realized where this game will lead to... Is this even the right place for a future and honored knight to be at?</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">The competition is heating up, ~name~! Let's do our best and face the next hand together!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">&lt;i&gt;(Keep fighting, Noelle! Nothing is lost yet. I should raise my efforts a little bit though.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">&lt;i&gt;(She's losing more significant items...If I had counted my armor as several pieces instead, then...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-touched.png">I mustn't give up yet...~Name~ may have only taken off her ~clothing~ just now, but a true knight won't lose hope...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I'm sure ~name~ must have studied hard before coming here. I wonder if she played more than 17 rounds per day to be prepared for this...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-worried.png">She's nowhere close to losing...That doesn't exactly help my current situation...</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">You don't mind If I go on? I usually don't distract myself when I touch myself. </state>
                <state img="#-touched.png">I think I'll wash your ~clothing~ when we're done too. I'm in the mood for that.</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">I'd offer to hold onto it, but I'm afraid I'm a bit preoccupied at the moment...</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">You're still so far away from my position, ~name~...</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Do you think it would be best if I brought something else to wear as extra, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">I feel as though I should cover myself up since it was only something small that you took off...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_major">
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">W-would you mind if I undress you, ~name~? That's also part of my duty as a maid.</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">Could you turn more my way, ~name~? I need to make sure you strip your ~clothing~ properly. That's...my duty as a maid.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">&lt;i&gt;(I can feel my body reacting to the events of the game. Watching others has a way stronger effect than I imagined.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-shy.png">~Clothing.a~ ~clothing~...that might have helped me stave off being so exposed right now...</state>
                <state img="#-touched.png">~Name~'s catching up...though I feel both sad and happy about that...</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">I should look on the bright side. I still have a chance to win!</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">We're coming down to the wire, huh? Though, it's still to early to give up, the situation isn't in our favor.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">~Name~ may have caught up, in a sense, but I can't let my guard down. A knight always has to stand on guard.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-happy.png">I'm doing well so far! I'll keep it up! I can only recommend training hard every day to reach your goals.</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">You may be close to losing, ~name~, but you still have a chance! Nothing is over until the last hand is dealt.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">&lt;i&gt;(Should I offer to wash his ~clothing~ afterward? Or maybe that's too insensitive...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I should be sad that I'm already out, but the thought of ~name~ taking off his ~clothing~ makes me feel a lot better all of the sudden.</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">What should I do? Am I even allowed to shamelessly watch ~name~ stripping when I'm already out?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_major">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <test expr="~clothing.position~" value="lower" />
                <alternative>
                    <condition filter="huge_penis" role="target" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <condition filter="large_penis" role="target" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">That bulge in his underwear...c-could it be that that's already his...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-flustered.png">Ahh...don't give up, ~name~...even if...I'm enjoying...your loss...sorry...</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">&lt;i&gt;(I need to remember him stripping his ~clothing~  the next time when I'm...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">It's getting so warm...Ah, sorry, about that...~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-touched.png">I'm feeling a little closer to ~name~...(&lt;i&gt;and not because he's low on clothes either.&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">~Name~ is almost out of clothes... And so am I!</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">If ~name~ keeps this up, his...thing...will be showing... I have to keep focused!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-touched.png">W-well, best not to lose heart ~name~, even if you've lost a lot.</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Oh! You're really coming close to being naked, ~name~...</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">A few more losses and he'll be... showing his...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-happy.png">I think, considering how good ~name~ looks, it would be improper not to look at him. I think I can arrange that with my virtues.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">On the other hand, not looking would mean never to progress in this topic. M-may I take a look at you, ~name~?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_major">
            <case stage="0-7" id="131">
                <condition role="target" character="pinkie_pie" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-flustered.png">She's starting with her shirt?! Does she want to lose?!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="133">
                <condition role="target" character="pinkie_pie" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-flustered.png">&lt;i&gt;(First, her shirt, and then right to her skirt?! Is she shameless?!)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="130">
                <condition role="target" character="charlie" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-serious.png">I noticed that you are pretty skinny, Charlie. I hope you're eating right.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="132">
                <condition role="target" character="senko" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-dutiful.png" marker="senko10">Say, Senko: The way you want to help the others to feel good; could it be that you're a Japanese equivalent of a maid? I can understand that you want to satisfy ~player~ and the others, but you can relax and leave that to a &lt;i&gt;real&lt;/i&gt; maid.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="estelle" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png" marker="estelle31">Ah, you're already... I was too late again...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="estelle" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="estelle41">Do you need help this time? You should tell me, so not another mishap happens. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="134">
                <condition role="target" character="barbara" />
                <state img="#-bashful.png" oneShotId="804" marker="BarbaraRepent">Promise me that my loss can be forgiven, Barbara. I may have to repent if this keeps up…</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-sad.png">She's taking off her ~clothing~ after all...I was so close...</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">Should I draw all attention to me while she strips her ~clothing~? I mean, a true knight shields her allies, even if it's just from gazes.</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">Rest assured, you clothing will stay safe while you finish the game!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Keep your wits about you, ~name~! You may be down to your last few pieces, but you can still pull out a victory!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I may have to get a mop if ~name~ is down this far now...</state>
                <state img="#-curtsey.png">Feel free to give yourself a pep talk if that's what it takes, ~name~! I am also here to support your as well!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-shy.png">~Clothing.a~ ~clothing~...that might have helped me stave off being so exposed right now...</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">~Name~'s catching up...though I feel both sad and happy about that...</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">I should look on the bright side. I still have a chance to win!</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">We're coming down to the wire, huh? Though, it's still to early to give up, the situation isn't in our favor.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">~Name~ may have caught up, in a sense, but I can't let my guard down. A knight always has to stand on guard.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">&lt;i&gt;(She uses her ~clothing~ to cover her skin... Perhaps I should try wearing more underneath my armor from now on.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">&lt;i&gt;(Should I offer to wash her ~clothing~ afterward? Or maybe that's too insensitive...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">There's not much left to protect her privates, is there? I would bring you new clothes, but this is against the point of the game...</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Hopefully she still has more to cover herself after that...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">&lt;i&gt;(I can feel my body reacting to the events of the game. Watching others has a far stronger effect than I imagined.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">So close, and yet so far...and yet...I'm feeling...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">&lt;i&gt;(This excitement...would it be even stronger if I saw a man taking of his ~clothing~?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-touched.png">&lt;i&gt;(She's getting closer to joining me... I'm getting hotter...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Y-you may be down to your last few items, b-but... don't... &lt;i&gt;(I don't know whether I should cheer ~name~ on or not now.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">Keep fighting, ~name~! Or m-maybe... don't... and join me...</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">If I can off everything, so can you!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_major">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="estelle" stage="4" sayingMarker="completestrip" />
                <state img="#-flustered.png">You don't know? We have to strip all the way until we're... Why is my face so hot all of the sudden?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="135">
                <condition role="target" character="pinkie_pie" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-shy.png">Y-you do have the choice of what you strip, Pinkie Pie. B-but aren't you embarrassed at all?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="137">
                <condition role="target" character="pinkie_pie" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I guess this is just the way you are, Pinkie Pie. Forgive me for what I said earlier.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="52">
                <condition role="target" character="charlie" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">For a healthy diet it's not only important what you eat, but how much you eat it as well. If you want, I can make you a nutrition plan if you want. I could even cook you a meal or two too. Or do you want me to teach you how to cook healthy food for yourself?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="136">
                <condition role="target" character="senko" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-dutiful.png" marker="senko11">It is &lt;i&gt;my&lt;/i&gt; duty as a maid and a good way to prepare for the next knight exam to help the others. As much as I can understand you, &lt;i&gt;I&lt;/i&gt; should be enough to make everyone happy today.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="estelle" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-shy.png" marker="estelle32">I'm sorry... I saw them while you were lifting your skirt. A good maid should have told you before, or at least shouldn't have looked.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="estelle" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-touched.png" marker="estelle42">I'm amazed at how good those look. You rarely see underwear like that in Mondstadt. Maybe not even in Teyvat. I know a lot of people who don't even wear that much underwear at all...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="138">
                <condition role="target" character="barbara" />
                <state img="#-dutiful.png" oneShotId="807" marker="BarbaraCute">I'm sure everyone agrees that you’re very cute, Barbara. Myself included.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition filter="athletic" role="target" />
                <test expr="~clothing.position~" value="upper" />
                <state img="#-touched.png">I would be more athletic if I didn't taste all the foods I cooked to make sure they're good... Do you have any advice for staying fit?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition filter="chubby" role="target" />
                <test expr="~clothing.position~" value="upper" />
                <state img="#-serious.png">That's not good, ~name~! You should take more care of your body than that! From now on I'll involve you in my daily training and will cook every day for you to make sure you eat properly. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <test expr="~clothing.position~" value="upper" />
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">Your body looks pretty healthy. Keep at it, ~name~! Let's keep in shape together!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-serious.png">I think it's okay to cover yourself, but don't forget this game is about being seen as well. </state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">Is everything alright? You're not feeling cold, are you? I'm not allowed to bring you something to cover you up, but how about something hot to drink?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">If I may say so, you look beautiful even without your ~clothing~. And I'm not just saying so because a maid has to do so.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-touched.png">I'm feeling a little closer to ~name~...(&lt;i&gt;and not because she's low on clothes either.&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">~Name~ is almost out of clothes... Is victory still possible for me?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Is it still good to feel joy over victory if ~name~ is in a position like that? Is there paragraph in the codes about that?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">P-please handle your stuff yourself, while...I handle my stuff over here...</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">&lt;i&gt;(I shouldn't care why I'm feeling excited. The fact is that I am, is most important, right now!)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">&lt;i&gt;(Her skin looks so smooth...What exactly am I thinking about right now?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">You may be down, but you're not out... unless you... want to be out...</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">~name~, if it's any consolation, losing isn't bad as you think... This feels heavenly right now, and you just made it better.</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">If nothing else, ~name~, you're certainly helping me right now with this duty...</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">I promise I'll take good care of your ~clothing~... as soon as finish over here.</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">I'm wavering between wanting you to lose and want you to win... which would you like?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-sad.png">She's not only better at poker, she also looks beautiful. I still have such a long way to go...</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">Is there a way I can make myself useful, ~name~? Maybe that will alleviate the loss of your ~clothing~.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Perhaps poker is neither of our strong suits. Regardless, keep going!</state>
                <state img="#-curtsey.png">~name~, I will be ready to assist you in any matter. Win or lose, I am here to aid and please!</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">Should you require any services cleaning your ~clothing~ afterward ~name~, I am at the ready!</state>
                <state img="#-cleaning0.png">I should make a clean spot for her ~clothing~. Certainly wouldn't want that getting dirty.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-7" id="24">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Oh no, your clothes! They are all ripped apart! That won't be easy to repair again...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-happy.png">I really want to see this right now...</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I'm hoping you have a knight's physique...</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Even if I wanted to relax, my hearts starts beating faster...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-excited.png">Finally your ~clothing~...W-well, at least this makes the game a little closer, right?</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">If you want, I... How exactly am I supposed to react now? Why haven't I trained for situations like this?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-surprised.png">You're getting down to the last of your clothing, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">&lt;i&gt;(This really can't be helped...I'd like to assist, but this is for my training...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">I-it appears that I'm that much closer to victory...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-touched.png">A good body is proof of your training and self-discipline. I'm already out, so I probably lack both...Mind if I check yours anyway?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-7" id="139">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" />
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">Nothing I couldn't handle, though! Give me a moment and I'll collect the parts for you and sew them together in no time!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5 7">
                <condition filter="muscular" role="target" />
                <state img="#-bashful.png">You're certainly trained way more efficiently than me. Even with all my training I was never able to look that magnificent! Wow...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5 7">
                <condition filter="chubby" role="target" />
                <state img="#-serious.png">That's not good, ~name~! You should take more care of your body than that! From now on I'll involve you in my daily training and will cook every day for you to make sure you eat properly. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5 7">
                <condition filter="athletic" role="target" />
                <state img="#-touched.png">Oh my...thin, but defined muscles, a well toned stomach, with a solid base... Your body is amazing, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">You... you certainly have been putting in the proper work on your body, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <condition filter="athletic" role="target" />
                <state img="#-touched.png">Wow, ~name~! &lt;i&gt;(S-should I say that his body looks really arousing, or is that not very knightly?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <condition filter="muscular" role="target" />
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">After done work, a good rest is really important. W-would you mind if I rest a little on your muscles, ~name~? &lt;i&gt;(Did I just say that?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <condition filter="chubby" role="target" />
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I have the urge to train your body right now...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5 7">
                <state img="#-flustered.png">Men don't need to be embarrassed about their chests, right? Good for you, because I already am embarrassed enough for two...</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I'm happy to see you take care of yourself, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">You look good, ~name~! So...&lt;i&gt;(I think "sexy" is the right word for now, but I think a maid and future knight shouldn't use such a word...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">I... really like it... I mean, if you're keeping your body in shape and so...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-5 7" oneShotId="1" priority="300">
                <state img="#-flustered.png">What now? The knight's codex didn't say how I should react in this situation! Should I look? Should I avert my eyes? I should have been prepared more for this!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5 7">
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="602">This is a man's delicate muscle, correct? If it's a muscle, you could certainly see how much ~name~ has trained it, right? &lt;i&gt;(Though I have no idea how you would train it.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png" oneShotId="603">Don't worry, ~name~! A maid is required to keep everyone's secrets. That's why my favorite flower is the rose. In Mondstadt, the rose represents the saying "As wine bottles are corked, so too are my lips sealed."</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png" oneShotId="604">You don't have to be shy, ~name~! No matter the size, your penis is in good hands while I'm here. I meant that metaphoric, by the way...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">D-do you need any help? I-I know that you can probably undress yourself but...&lt;i&gt;(I want to take a closer look at it.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_small_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-5 7">
                <state img="#-surprised.png">I didn't know they could be so small, but if you put some effort in, I'm sure it can become bigger...somehow...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Perhaps their sizes were exaggerated...or perhaps ~name~ is naturally way beyond the average... Should I feel bad for him?</state>
                <state img="#-touched.png">Is there a method to train your...p-penis to grow bigger than that? Perhaps I can support you in that endeavor.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">...If you're tiny friend needs a maid's service, maybe there's something I can do. Don't worry, I'm used to handle &lt;i&gt;small&lt;/i&gt; tasks.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_medium_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-5 7">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">At the Angel's Share, I overheard that it's all about size... But is it really all there is? Isn't there something more...romantic?</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">Is it flaccid? Or is it hard already? How hard will it even become? Steady as stone? I-I just wonder because of my Geo Vision!</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">As a knight, I should give ~name~ some privacy. But as a maid, I should ask if ~name~ is feeling well... I wonder what I should do now?!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">That looks like a pretty good size, if I may say so. &lt;i&gt;(I wonder how ~name~ thinks about the "No touching rule"...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_large_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-5 7">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I believe I can handle that just fine. I'm used to handling...big things...l-like my claymore, I mean!</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">A-a true knight will never falter or be fazed, no matter... how huge... the task is...</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I won't back down, even in the face of big opponents! ...Hopefully...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">That reminds me, I found a debate club in front of the Angel's Share yesterday... It's not yours by any chance? &lt;i&gt;(It would match his size...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-flustered.png">Big...is good...Just ask if you need a hand...Or two.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-7" id="15" priority="302">
                <condition role="target" character="florina" saidMarker="bee2" sayingMarker="bee3" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">J-just relax! If you leave it alone, it will leave you alone!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="141">
                <condition role="target" character="sucrose" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Actually, I think many women in Teyvat don't wear any additional support around the chest. I wonder where this kind of fashion comes from.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="140">
                <condition role="target" character="senko" />
                <state img="#-touched.png" marker="senko40">I know bras can be tricky to open. If you need my help again, I can help you to get out of it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="estelle" />
                <state img="#-sad.png" marker="estelle51">You asked ~player~? Oh, no problem with that, but I thought I, as a maid, would be...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5 7">
                <state img="#-shy.png" oneShotId="605">&lt;i&gt;(Just think of yourself in the Knights' changing room. You've seen Jean and Lisa and Eula and...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png" oneShotId="606">I've never usually compared, but given the situation... </state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png" oneShotId="607">We all keep them covered in different ways, but it's important to be prepared if you've been pushed this far.</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png" oneShotId="1044">I'll give you the privacy you need to reveal your breasts. But make sure to ask if you need me!</state>
                <state img="#-touched.png" oneShotId="1043">T-try to be proud, ~name~! </state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I'm sure they're beautiful, ~name~, s-so, go ahead!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-excited.png">Just try to relax and make the best out of it. I have seen all sizes of chests in the dressing room of the...Oh, I'm not supposed to talk about it, right?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">If you're having problems exposing yourself, think of it as a task you'll carry out with pride. At least, that's what I did. </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_small_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-7" id="142">
                <condition role="target" character="sucrose" />
                <state img="#-touched.png">Do you mind if I hold them for you? ...I mean the vials!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5 7">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Small breasts are admirable. I sometimes wish mine were that small...I could fight better that way.</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">If I were that size, I could move faster...even if it was just a small amount more.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I wonder if there's anything I could do to make mine smaller... then I'd be a better fighter...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="608">I heard smaller chests are more sensitive. That's what Mona said at least when...Oh, can you please keep that a secret?</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">What I can tell you, breast envy for bigger breasts is completely unnecessary. When I was younger I wanted to grow up fast too and now they're almost too big...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_medium_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-7" id="143">
                <condition role="target" character="senko" />
                <state img="#-shy.png" marker="senko41">Oh, right! Of course you don't need me for that. I don't have much experience with bras anyway... &lt;i&gt;(I wanted to take the chance and fluff the tail a little, but it's probably better I didn't.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="239">
                <condition role="target" character="estelle" />
                <state img="#-flustered.png" marker="estelle52">What am I even thinking about? Was I jealous of ~player~? That's not how a maid or a knight should behave! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5 7">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I wonder how heavy your breasts are... Huh, oh, just because we're about the same size and mine are pretty heavy sometimes...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I wonder if you would fit into my armor, ~name~. It was made especially for me, but we're about the same size. I regularly grow out of my old ones, so you can have one of them.</state>
                <state img="#-touched.png">On the flip side, we could wear the same bra size! ...I thought it'd be better to be positive in a moment like this...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-surprised.png">How beautiful... Oh, I mean...this is the size that is considered "beautiful", right? &lt;i&gt;(But even if others don't say so, I think they are.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png" oneShotId="609">I think it's a pretty good size. At least Barbara has a similar one and she's extremely...I didn't want to to say that, Barbara...Sorry!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_large_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-5 7">
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Don't those get in your way when you're on duty? I don't think I could see below my feet for cleaning if I had breasts like that.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I'd need larger armor  to hold them steady if mine were that size. Is it even possible to make one like that? My breastplate doesn't cover mine completely already, but I think that could be for an &lt;i&gt;aesthetic&lt;/i&gt; reason.</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">I wonder if Wagner would be able to make something that size. It's already hard enough to maintain my stature enough to not need a new one too often. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="610">Those are really pretty, ~name~! Even though women with bigger chests like Lisa often complain about the disadvantages, I know they secretly love to be admired for them. Wait, I shouldn't have told you about Lisa's, right?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I always hear how men love to talk about big chests when I help out at the Angel's Share. You can be really proud of yourself, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-7" id="144">
                <condition role="target" character="senko" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="senko50">About your tail... I have actually seen people with tails before in Mondstadt. A very prominent example would be Diona, the bartender at the Cat's Tail. But her tail isn't as fluffy as yours to be honest.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="ganyu" />
                <state img="#-touched.png" marker="ganyu51">I heard in Liyue they take extra care of their bodies. I wonder if Ganyu is...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="1035">Should I turn away for you? I can if you want.</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png" oneShotId="1036">Don't worry, ~name~! A maid is required to keep everyone's secrets. That's why my favorite flower is the rose. In Mondstadt, the rose represents the saying "As wine bottles are corked, so too are my lips sealed."</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png" oneShotId="1037">While we do go into the game knowing this can happen, it's still a little unsettling.</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png" oneShotId="1038">&lt;i&gt;(Remain calm, Noelle: this also means you're taking a huge step toward the win.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">&lt;i&gt;(~name~'s going bottomless... I hope we can both keep it together...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">I feel like it's going to get a lot hotter in here all of a sudden.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-7" id="147">
                <condition role="target" character="sucrose" />
                <state img="#-bashful.png">So pretty... Your hair is just as fluffy as your other hair. It really suits you! Mine was just as curly, even though my head hair is straight...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="145">
                <condition role="target" character="reimu" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">It's all hairy but it's... so beautiful! Have shrine maidens a special way of caring for them? Now I really regret that I removed my hair down there...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="146">
                <condition role="target" character="senko" />
                <state img="#-touched.png" marker="senko51">I would... Oh, it's nothing! (&lt;i&gt;I wonder if that part is as fluffy as her tail is.&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="ganyu" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png" marker="ganyu52">Oh, I didn't expect you to be that... It looks so beautiful!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition filter="shaved" role="target" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="611">So I'm really not the only one who removed their hair. What a relief! I was so worried when I shaved it...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition filter="hairy" role="target" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png" oneShotId="612">And I thought, &lt;i&gt;I&lt;/i&gt; was looking untidy... I really wonder if I should have maintained them...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7" oneShotId="2" priority="140">
                <condition filter="pubic_hair" role="target" />
                <state img="#-shy.png">So you keep your hair down there... May I ask you: do you think they look weird? Does everyone's hair down there curl like that? Should I let mine grow again?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5 7">
                <state img="#-shy.png">Whenever I see someone else's... &lt;i&gt;(as rare as that is...)&lt;/i&gt; I wonder if mine looks weird...</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">I'm not really sure what to say, or if I should look...</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Y-you're still in this, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">Aaaah... I knew this was coming, but now that the moment has arrived, it's hard to keep calm!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="613">Being shaved or not, both have their advantages. I like being smooth when I touch myself, but I also loved to run my hand through my...Is that too much information?</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">&lt;i&gt;(Looking at hers while touching mine is almost like... I better not say this to her. It's not very knightly.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">She's not far from joining me, is she...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_lost">
            <case stage="0" id="97" priority="501">
                <condition status="exposed" role="target" character="human" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-shy.png">I don't know where you're from, but is it natural not to have &lt;i&gt;certain parts&lt;/i&gt; of your body covered where you live, ~name~? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="99">
                <condition status="decent" role="target" character="human" stage="0" />
                <test expr="~human.gender~" value="male" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">Ah! You're one of the few males who frequent the Inventory! ~player~, correct? It's nice to meet you. Let's both do our best!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">&lt;i&gt;(~Player~ hasn't said anything yet... Perhaps he's one of the strong and silent types... Maybe encouraging him will help him speak up.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="102">
                <condition status="decent" role="target" character="human" stage="1" />
                <test expr="~human.gender~" value="male" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png">&lt;i&gt;(He's still on the quiet side... though, he's keeping up with the game.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">You remind me of a Traveler that had recently come through Mondstadt, ~player~. Quiet, but kind and helpful. I hope you are the same.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="101">
                <condition status="decent" role="target" character="human" stage="2" />
                <test expr="~human.gender~" value="male" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">I'll pray for your next victory, ~player~! &lt;i&gt;(I hope this gets him to open up some.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">W-we may be here for different reasons, ~player~, but let's both play our best and go as far as we can!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="100">
                <condition status="decent" role="target" character="human" stage="3" />
                <test expr="~human.gender~" value="male" />
                <state img="#-bashful.png">&lt;i&gt;(Ah, ~player~ smiled at me! Despite losing! My cheering is working! He has a nice smile too...)&lt;/i&gt; </state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Keep up the fight, ~player~! I'm right beside you! Smiling in the face of defeat... I'll try to follow your example!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="98">
                <condition status="decent" role="target" character="human" stage="4" />
                <test expr="~human.gender~" value="male" />
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Perhaps we should study how to become better at the game together, ~player~. The library would be a suitable place for us to both improve.</state>
                <state img="#-touched.png">&lt;i&gt;(His loss makes me feel happier... But is that good or bad?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="3">
                <condition filter="maid_uniform" role="target" />
                <state img="#-dutiful.png" oneShotId="1526">That's a beautiful maid uniform, if I may say so. We maids should totally give our best today and try to learn from each other.</state>
                <state img="#-curtsey.png" oneShotId="1527">A fellow maid! Let us serve the others to the best of our ability. Whatever it is, we'll handle it!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="armor" role="target" />
                <state img="#-excited.png">Looks like you came fully equipped to, ~name~! Armor is a must have for any knight!</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I felt a little awkward coming in my armor, but I'm relieved to see I'm not alone in this regard.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Proper armor is always the first line of defense against any attack that gets through! Just like it for ~name~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition filter="adventurer" role="target" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">An adventurer that doesn't belong to our guild... ~name~, do you belong to a guild?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I'm always excited to meet adventurers! I don't leave Mondstadt often, so I'd like to hear about your stories, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">What kind of sites and exciting places have you been, ~name~? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="criminal" role="target" />
                <state img="#-serious.png">Any sort of crime is terrible, ~name~. I'll see that the Knights of Favonius try you for your actions.</state>
                <state img="#-serious.png">Crime, no matter the gravity or purpose, is still wrong, ~name~. Care to explain why you choose to commit such wrong?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="fighter" role="target" />
                <state img="#-excited.png">You appear to know how to handle yourself in combat, ~name~. Perhaps we could spar after this is over? I need to train harder for the next Knights' exam!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">&lt;i&gt;(It's a high possibility that there are fighting style I'm still not familiar with... I need to keep an open mind in case Mondstadt should be attacked!)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Fighting is certainly the way of some... but it is not good to fight without a good reason behind it!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="royalty" role="target" />
                <state img="#-curtsey.png">To think that I would meet royality here... A pleasure to meet you, ~name~. I'm Noelle a maid in service to Knights of Favonius.</state>
                <state img="#-curtsey.png">May you enjoy your time here, ~name~. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition filter="quiet" role="target" />
                <state img="#-curtsey.png">It's ok if you can't talk at first, ~name~. Please open up to us whenever you feel comfortable.</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">Don't feel rushed to talk because you lost this one, ~name~. This game is enough to make any some talking, I'm sure.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="smart" role="target" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">&lt;i&gt;(~name~ seems to have a good head on their shoulders...)&lt;/i&gt; Would you have any tips for studying, ~name~?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="long_hair" role="target" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Such long hair... aren't you afraid it will get in the way, ~name~?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="weapon" role="target" />
                <state img="#-excited.png">A means to protect yourself and others never fails to come in handy, right ~name~?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <condition role="self" hasHand="High Card" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png" oneShotId="614">Your hand is worse than my ~self.hand.noart~? I was sure I would lose the round as punishment for my mistakes this time.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png" oneShotId="615">I really need to try harder. Luck can't save me from my mistakes all the time.</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png" oneShotId="616">~Name~ lost even against my high card? I somehow feel sorry for you. Can I do anything for you to feel better, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png" oneShotId="908">Oh, I'm sorry, ~name~. I should have lost that hand instead. Please, if there is anything I can do to alleviate your frustrations, don't be afraid to tell me!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_stripping">
            <case stage="0-7" id="259">
                <condition role="target" character="blake_belladonna" stage="0" saidMarker="nb1" />
                <state img="#-dutiful.png" marker="NoelleBlakeWarrior02">It's always been my dream to become part of the Knights of Favonius, so I was hoping you had any pointers you could give me to improve my training!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="263">
                <condition role="target" character="blake_belladonna" stage="1" saidMarker="nb4" />
                <state img="#-excited.png" marker="NoelleBlakeVisionless02">Wow, that's incredible! If I had multiples of me, I'm sure I could get so much done! I could clean the entire library, rake the leaves at the cathedral, and get in some training all before lunch!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="266">
                <condition role="target" character="blake_belladonna" stage="2" saidMarker="nb7" />
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="NoelleBlakeGeo03" font-size="small">I really shouldn't be complaining, considering some people would do anything for a Vision. But I spent my entire life praying to and upholding the ideals of freedom from the Anemo Archon, Barbatos, only to receive a &lt;i&gt;Geo&lt;/i&gt; Vision. Why? Geo is the furthest from Anemo!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="269">
                <condition role="target" character="blake_belladonna" stage="3" saidMarker="nb10" />
                <state img="#-excited.png" marker="NoelleBlakeGrimm02">Ooh, how exciting! The Knights of Favonius do something similar by keeping the roads safe from the Abyss Order and the Hilichurls. If ever the chance comes, I'd love to try to fight one of these Grimm myself!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="272">
                <condition role="target" character="blake_belladonna" stage="4" saidMarker="nb13" />
                <state img="#-flustered.png" marker="NoelleBlakeSushi02">Sushi? I can--- Wait, you mean you're... Oh my!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="275">
                <condition role="target" character="blake_belladonna" stage="5" saidMarker="nb17" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="NoelleBlakeAdepti02">I'm sure you'd be the talk of the town if you visited Liyue Harbor! I hear that all sorts of Adeptal people walk among the civilians of Liyue. You might even be be praised and looked up to!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="278">
                <condition role="target" character="blake_belladonna" stage="6" saidMarker="nb20" />
                <state img="#-bashful.png" marker="NoelleBlakeRelaxed02">W-well... &lt;i&gt;Ahem!&lt;/i&gt; Oh my... G-give me a minute to find the words.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="282">
                <condition role="target" character="blake_belladonna" stage="7" saidMarker="nb23" />
                <state img="#-shy.png" marker="NoelleBlakePats02">You're talking about... &lt;i&gt;That&lt;/i&gt;, right? To be truthful, I am not the most experienced when doing it to another. But if you want me to, I can at least do my best to encourage you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="228">
                <condition role="target" character="dawn" saidMarker="NoelleExhausting01" />
                <state img="#-dutiful.png" oneShotId="821" marker="DawnExhausting02">Oh that must be lovely indeed! I don't work with animals too often, but when I do see one, I'm always willing to spend a few minutes to pet and play with them!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="231">
                <condition role="target" character="dawn" saidMarker="NoellePoffin01" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="823" marker="DawnPoffin02">Oh my! These Poffins really sound like you can get as creative as you like with them! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="310">
                <condition filter="shy" role="target" />
                <state img="#-shy.png">O-oh goodness... ~name~, you don't need to keep playing if you do not want to! I hope you don't feel too pressured to keep going like this.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">You're certainly braver than most for playing this game with us, ~name~! I just want you to realize that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="311">
                <condition filter="clothing_destruction" role="target" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png" oneShotId="1112" weight="5">Ah- oh my goodness! Uh, um... Don't worry, I'll make sure to fix it for you!</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png" oneShotId="1111" weight="4">Wha- oh no, not again! ~Name~, you must be more careful with your clothing!</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png" oneShotId="1113" weight="3.001">... I-it's okay, N-Noelle can handle it. I'll fix it after the game.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="312">
                <condition filter="vanishes_clothes" role="target" />
                <state img="#-excited.png">Oh my! That's incredible, ~name~! Tell me, where do your clothes go when you do that? Do they get put in with the dirty laundry?</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">My, wouldn't it be a huge help if &lt;i&gt;I&lt;/i&gt; could teleport clothes to the dirty laundry like that! Would you mind teaching me, ~name~?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="313">
                <condition filter="chuunibyou" role="target" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">(&lt;i&gt;~name~ is just too adorable with how they put on an exaggerated personality. I wonder if I could pull off a personality like theirs.&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_stripped">
            <case stage="0-7" id="261">
                <condition role="target" character="blake_belladonna" stage="1" saidMarker="nb2" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="NoelleBlakeWarriors03">I prefer to use two handed weapons, mainly claymores. Ooh, I'm looking forward to learning from someone outside of the knights! I hardly get the chance to do so.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="264">
                <condition role="target" character="blake_belladonna" stage="2" saidMarker="nb5" />
                <state img="#-dutiful.png" marker="NoelleBlakeVisionless03" dialogue-layer="over" font-size="small">Visions are gifts from the Archons that grant varying powers. Mine allows me to protect myself and others with a shield using the power of Geo. Each Vision is a representation of the Archon's element and the user's ambitions. Mine was granted to me by uh... Morax, the god of contracts...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="267">
                <condition role="target" character="blake_belladonna" stage="3" saidMarker="nb8" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="NoelleBlakeGeo03">My dedication to knighthood? Hmm... I don't think I've ever thought of it that way. If that is the case, then maybe I should be more considerate of my Vision. It's what helped me protect so many people thus far.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="270">
                <condition role="target" character="blake_belladonna" stage="4" saidMarker="nb11" />
                <state img="#-curtsey.png" marker="NoelleBlakeGrimm03">I promise to protect any and all from the Grimm, just as I would for people against the Abyss Order. I am eager to see how well I'd do!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="273">
                <condition role="target" character="blake_belladonna" stage="5" saidMarker="nb14" />
                <state img="#-bashful.png" marker="NoelleBlakeSushi03">O-oh! I uh--- Ohh, that explains it. Your change in body language is akin to a cat! I am happy that you are getting more comfortable and opening up to us, Miss Blake.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="276">
                <condition role="target" character="blake_belladonna" stage="6" saidMarker="nb18" />
                <state img="#-excited.png" marker="NoelleBlakeAdepti03">I would just need to make sure all of my duties are done before we'd set out, and I could bring back any unique ingredients from the harbor to Mondstadt to share! Ooh, that sounds like fun! I'm in!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="279">
                <condition role="target" character="blake_belladonna" stage="7" saidMarker="nb21" />
                <state img="#-shy.png" marker="NoelleBlakeRelaxed03">I-I didn't come to look for a partner of my own. But--- Ah! I'm gabbing again! Y-you look beautiful, Miss Belladonna...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="283">
                <condition role="target" character="blake_belladonna" stage="8" saidMarker="nb24" />
                <state img="#-touched.png" marker="NoelleBlakePats03">M-Miss Blake, I... Thank you. I-I feel the same way about you. Despite your hard shell at first, you are beautiful and kind. It's been lovely playing with you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="96">
                <condition role="target" character="mikan" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Oh! Mikan, I don't mean to embarrass you, but you should fix your skirt before... (&lt;i&gt;Anyone notices!&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="229">
                <condition role="target" character="dawn" saidMarker="NoelleExhausting02" />
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="817" marker="DawnExhausting03">Oh, I love learning new recipes! Thank you very much, Dawn!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="232">
                <condition role="target" character="dawn" saidMarker="NoellePoffin02" />
                <state img="#-dutiful.png" oneShotId="819" marker="DawnPoffin03">Goodness! It seems there's much to these Poffins! I should make note of every batch I make, to get the flavors down and see which of the knights like which flavors the best!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="260">
                <condition role="target" character="zoe" saidMarker="OrderPizza" />
                <state img="#-worried.png" oneShotId="937" marker="NoelleZoePizza">Oh! I can make us a pizza while we play! What sort of--&lt;br&gt; ...Ah, I don't think I've heard of toppings like that before.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-excited.png">I somehow want him to start now...as I am now, it should assist him greatly...</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">This will assist him...and this may very well assist me...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">He's going to pleasure himself now...perhaps I should assist him however I can...</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">~Name~'s going to masturbate...while I'm like this...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-flustered.png">One down! B-b-but now this means he has to...p-pleasure himself...</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Oh...r-right, the forfeit... &lt;i&gt;(I'm not sure what exactly the forfeit part of self pleasuring is, though. Maybe it's because we're watching?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">I'm already out of the game, so if you want me at your service, just let me know how I can help you. Do you want a cup of tea?</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">I don't have much else to do right now, so I can assist you a little...with some encouraging words, of course! Or would it be enough to just take a look at me?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">He's going right at it...!</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">So he holds it...and then...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5 7">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I'm not exactly sure how I could be any help for you, but don't hold back if you need something from me.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">If...i-if it's not in a too improper kind, I will still fulfill my duties as a maid. Even if you're in a state like that.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_masturbating">
            <case stage="6">
                <test expr="~target.size~" value="large" />
                <state img="#-touched.png">Stroking your huge thing with two hands... ~name~, are you used to wielding large weapons...?</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">It's so big... Your penis is clearly a muscle you've been working hard on...</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">&lt;i&gt;(If I can handle a claymore, I should be able to handle ~name~'s... Big... Oh my...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-touched.png">&lt;i&gt;Amazing... It's so big and hard, yet ~name~ is handling it with no problem... Perhaps I should ask him if I can... Learn how to do the same...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-curtsey.png">I'm used to handling large weapons, but ~name~'s might be a little tough.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5 7" priority="0">
                <condition filter="large_penis" role="target" />
                <state img="#-touched.png">It seems ~name~ also wields a claymore... Though not one that I was expecting...</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I'm used to handling large weapons, but ~name~'s might be a little tough.</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">Stroking your huge thing with two hands... ~name~, are you used to wielding large weapons...?</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">&lt;i&gt;(Amazing... It's so big and hard, yet ~name~ is handling it with no problem... Perhaps I should ask him if I can... Learn how to do the same...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-touched.png">Y-you wouldn't happen to need any help with your big... penis, would you, ~target~? It seems like it's a lot to handle...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">~Name~ looks like he's working hard...I only hope my state of dress is taking that further.</state>
                <state img="#-curtsey.png">Should I try to be exposed for him? It's embarrassing...but it's the only way I can help him...</state>
                <state img="#-curtsey.png">Aren't you getting tired? If you feel exhausted just say the word and I'll take over.</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">Mmn... (&lt;i&gt;I can feel my breath get shaky every time I look at ~name~ while he's doing... That. And I feel so much warmer too.&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">(&lt;i&gt;It would be rude if I were to interrupt ~name~'s forfeit by taking over for him. But the way he looks at me... No, I shouldn't assume what he would want without their consent!&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5 7">
                <state img="#-excited.png">Is there anything I can do for you, ~name~? Whenever you need me, I'll be there.</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">Are you hungry? Just let me know when you need a break. It's a maid's duty to satisfy the needs of the people around her.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Those up and down movements remind me of cleaning surfaces. I'm usually a lot faster than you, though. I can show you if you want.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">You basically just need to rub it carefully, right? ...I'm asking for no particular reasons.</state>
                <state img="#-touched.png">&lt;i&gt;(I know this would never be part of an exam, but...is it right to just stand there and look? Would ~name~ even let me..?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5 7" priority="0">
                <condition filter="small_penis" role="target" />
                <state img="#-touched.png">Can you even hold our small friend with your big hands properly? I have pretty small hands, if you haven't noticed.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I'm not a full knight yet, so I'm often take care of the small stuff. But it looks like you take care of your &lt;i&gt;small stuff&lt;/i&gt; as well, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_heavy_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-5 7">
                <state img="#-surprised.png">He's going really fast...that usually means...he's close to releasing..?</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">D-don't worry about the mess you'll make. I'll clean it. Just release as much as you like at your heart's content.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I'm actually not sure how to remove sperm stains from textiles... Please make sure to not aim at any, ~name~, when you're about to release!</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Do you prefer to release your semen freely, or would you rather prefer if I give you something to shoot them in to make less of a mess? I wonder if I have something like that on me, though...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">If you don't want to make a too big mess, you should think of a place where you can shoot your sperm otherwise. That would help me in this situation too...</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I'm actually not sure how to remove sperm stains from textiles... So you maybe should aim for someone who doesn't wear any...</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">Don't hold back! I have to clean the floor when I'm done anyway, so it doesn't matter if you make everything dirty with me.</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">He's going really fast...that usually means...he's close to releasing...with me?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-touched.png">&lt;i&gt;(So much sperm...and no way to clean it up...perhaps...my mouth could get it...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">You've made a real mess of yourself, ~name~...would you like help with...cleaning it up...?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5 7">
                <state img="#-flustered.png">So much shot out...~Name~ can never clean it up all by himself. ...Maybe I could help him with my...</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">&lt;i&gt;(It will take some time to clean all that up...and I forgot my cleaning materials... What should I do?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-surprised.png">I knew it would get dirty, but... He's made quite a mess of himself...and the ground...</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">It sprayed everywhere, and with such force...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="7" id="149" priority="600">
                <condition role="target" character="senko" />
                <state img="#-touched.png" marker="senkoStartLewd">I lost first, so I think I have to keep my promise now. Are you ready, Senko?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="148">
                <condition role="target" character="bernadetta" />
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">Your pillow? Sure, no problem! Make yourself comfortable!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="estelle" />
                <state img="#-worried.png">This place is really not fitting for a princess to... Quickly! I need to think of something!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-surprised.png">She's going to do that...just like me...</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">It feels good, ~name~! But you might know that better than me.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I wouldn't go so far to say that it's fun to lose this game, but it certainly doesn't hurt. You should look forward to what comes next!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I'm not far from being in ~name~'s place...I need to try harder!</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">~Name~ is out? I've already seen me in that position, if I may be honest...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">&lt;i&gt;(Should I consult ~name~ because she's out, or should I encourage her to give her best and enjoy her forfeit? I better not show how glad I am, that I'm still in the game...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">&lt;i&gt;(I wonder how often girls like ~name~ pleasure themselves. For someone who does it daily like me, this is hardly a forfeit, but maybe I'm an exception...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-flustered.png" oneShotId="617">A step closer to victory! But that also means that ~name~ has to...</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png" oneShotId="618">If you need me to look away so you can have some privacy, ~name~, please speak up.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I can cheer you on if you'd like ~name~, though I'm not really sure what I should say.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-surprised.png">You're out too? But don't worry! The only bad part about the forfeit is that we others can see you while... I can also look away, if you want.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I know it hurts to fail, but at least you can forget about it during your forfeit now.</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">&lt;i&gt;(I wonder how often girls like ~name~ pleasure themselves. For someone who does it daily like me, this is hardly a forfeit, but maybe I'm an exception...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="7" priority="600">
                <condition role="target" character="senko" saidMarker="noelle_forfeit" />
                <state img="blank.png" marker="forfeitHelp">~blank~</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="11">
                <condition role="target" character="chara_dreemurr" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">U-umm...maybe you should put that down...before you really hurt yourself...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="19">
                <condition role="target" character="nami" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">She created a cloud without a Hydro or Electro Vision?! How far has technology come outside of Mondstadt?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="20">
                <condition role="target" character="bernadetta" />
                <state img="#-touched.png">Do whatever makes you feel comfortable, Bernadetta...we're in no position to judge.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="49">
                <condition role="target" character="charlie" />
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">You're using a chair? That's fine? It looks a little bit hard. though. Do you need me to bring you a cushion?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="241">
                <condition role="target" character="estelle" />
                <state img="#-touched.png">If you want to sit comfortably while you're doing it, w-would you like to sit on my... Oh, there's a chair for you! T-that works too of course. I think...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">It's not as bad as you think it is... but no less embarrassing...</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">&lt;i&gt;(I probably should be more embarrassed about the whole situation. Seems like not everyone is okay with being watched as I am.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">A maid should help with anything...but I wouldn't know what to say here...</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">I know it should be a &lt;i&gt;forfeit&lt;/i&gt;, but let me know if I can do something good for you.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Make sure to make yourself comfortable. Preparation is always important.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I'm not exactly sure how I could be any help for you, but don't hold back if you need something from me.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">T-try your best... not to make a mess... Or actually, don't worry about that. There's nothing that can't be cleaned afterward. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">I'm currently doing the same thing, so I may help out if you need any help.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">I maybe have to do my own forfeit right now, but let me know if I should show you a few efficient ways to relax I discovered. </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-7" id="247">
                <condition status="masturbating" role="target" character="ganyu" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="862">I can't imagine how stressful it must be to work without actually &lt;i&gt;sleeping&lt;/i&gt;! I at least try to make up for any time spent sleeping. You don't need to worry about that!</state>
                <state img="#-touched.png" oneShotId="861">I hope you don't mind me saying, but... The faces you are making are simply adorable, Miss Ganyu.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5" id="28" priority="306">
                <condition role="target" character="sucrose" sayingMarker="sucrose_howdo" />
                <condition count="2-" status="masturbating" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png">How I get into the mood? Well, usually when I've had a hard day and I need some time to relax, I usually get into the mood pretty fast. But I'm not sure if... if that helps you in your current situation...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-worried.png">If it assists you, ~name~...you are welcome to look at me...&lt;i&gt;(Even if I'm not much to look at...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-touched.png">&lt;i&gt;(Do I feel as good as she does right now? I mean, it already feels plenty good for me.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">&lt;i&gt;(I somehow want to help her with her forfeit. Is it just because a knight has the urge to help others, or is it...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">Just say the word, a-and I'll do my best to help you from here. A-as a dutiful maid would.</state>
                <state img="#-touched.png">~Name~... I-I don't quite know how to describe how you make me feel watching you, a-as you look at me while doing it as well...</state>
                <state img="#-touched.png">&lt;i&gt;(If I watch what ~name~ is doing, maybe I can make this feel better.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">Can I assist you in any way, ~name~? Though, I'm really sure what I can do like this...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-touched.png">Do be careful of how much you...let out along the way...I can clean it up afterward, though.</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">Do I look...? A-ah, I think I'm more embarrassed than her! &lt;i&gt;(Even though I wouldn't mind to be watched myself.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">~Name~'s going at it with such enthusiasm...does it feel that good?</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">I have to stay focused...or I'll end up doing the same... &lt;i&gt;(Not that I mind after a hard day...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">Don't forget, I'm always here for you. As a maid, you have my full support.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">&lt;i&gt;(Does she do this often? More often than me? Should I ask her how she enjoys it the most?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Make sure to take your time and enjoy every second. This is something you shouldn't rush. </state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">If you are feeling uncomfortable at all about being watched, let me know and I'll turn away!</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">I-I would help, but I am still in the game. Please forgive me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-flustered.png">Was I...was I making the same faces...? Oh dear...</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">She looks like she's in heaven... You totally should enjoy this like this.</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Despite being in front of others...she keeps going with such vigor.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Would it be rude if I commented on how ~name~ looks while they're doing this? Or would it be rude if I &lt;i&gt;didn't&lt;/i&gt;?</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">How ah, &lt;i&gt;creative&lt;/i&gt; do you get when it comes to your imagination while doing this? O-on second thought, I should let you focus! Apologies!</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">That's--- Oh! I should try that for myself if it made ~name~ reel like that.</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">Is there any I can... say to assist you, ~name~? The rules prevent me from physically helping, but maybe some words will help...</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">This can't really be left me, but I'll still support you to the end!</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I'll ensure that you can... um... finish... without trouble, ~name~! Keep at it!</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Perhaps I should find a mop in case ~name~ makes a mess afterward...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="150" priority="0">
                <condition status="masturbating" role="target" character="barbara" />
                <state img="#-touched.png" oneShotId="849">My lips are sealed, Barbara. I swear on my honor as a kn---… a maid that Master Jean will never know.</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png" oneShotId="850">Do be careful not to wear yourself out, Barbara. I’m not sure if you have the same stamina I do.</state>
                <state img="#-serious.png" oneShotId="851">As unbecoming this is of you, I shan't tell a soul, Barbara. Your secrets are safe with me!</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png" oneShotId="852">Forgive me if I am being too forward, but would you um... Consider this a part of your "daily routine"? I won't judge regardless of your answer!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_heavy_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-5 7">
                <state img="#-surprised.png">She's going so fast, like she's burning up...</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">This means...~name~'s almost...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Should I get a mop ready...?</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">Don't worry about the mess you'll make. I'll clean it. Just release as much as you like at your heart's content.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-flustered.png">She's going so fast, like she's burning up...</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">This means... ~name~'s almost... I still have time, though.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">If ~name~ is about to make a mess while I'm still... Nobody will mind if I don't clean it immediately...</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">Don't worry about the mess you'll make. I'll clean it. Just release as much as you like at your heart's content.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-7" id="252">
                <condition role="target" character="ganyu" sayingMarker="fallingasleep" />
                <state img="#-touched.png">Oh my, did she fall asleep? Ohh, if only I had a blanket handy for her. Poor dear must be exhausted.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Goodness! Oh, she fell asleep... Please, for her sake, we should be a little more quiet. I can imagine the relief she felt knocked her already exhausted self out.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="151">
                <condition role="target" character="bernadetta" />
                <state img="#-touched.png">Do you want me to wash your pillow after the game? If you need anything else, like if you want to rest your head on my lap, I'll do my best to help you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-surprised.png">That's one more mess to clean up...on top of myself...</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">L-let me at least clean you. That's the least I can do as someone who was out before you.</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">&lt;i&gt;(That looked so satisfying... Even in this area, I still have much to learn.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">Should I get you a cloth to wipe you down with?</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">Messes are things maids are experts at cleaning up...even these kinds.</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">She came...everywhere...</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Ah...I need to avoid a similar fate by winning...even if she looked like she was enjoying herself.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">P-perhaps losing may not be so bad...n-no! I need to win and prove I'm prepared for the exam!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-happy.png">That's always the best part, isn't it? You can somehow feel how all the tension leaves your body...along with some other things.</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">I hope you feel satisfied now. If not, I can still be at your service as a maid.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate_first">
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">The first one down...I still have so far to go...</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I should have studied more...</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">It was an honor...playing with you...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate">
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="opp" character="blake_belladonna" sayingMarker="blake_noelle_mastintro1" />
                <state img="#-bashful.png" marker="NoelleBlakeMastStart01">Ah... I want to show my gratitude to you, and if this is how you'd like me to, then I'll give it my all, M-Mistress Belladonna...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="noelle_chicken_and_madame" />
                <state img="#-sad.png">The last supper... for myself...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-sad.png">It was an honor...playing with you...</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">How could I have been so careless...</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">A-at least I wasn't the first one out...</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Perhaps if I had trained more for this... So be it.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="start_masturbating">
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="opp" character="blake_belladonna" saidMarker="blake_noelle_mastintro1" />
                <state img="#-start.png" marker="NoelleBlakeMastStart02">Oh, oh goodness... Miss Blake--- I mean, Mistress Belladonna, I feel so flushed... I'll ah, do what I can to describe what I am thinking.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <test expr="~background.surface~" value="sand" />
                <state img="#-start.png">If I had time I would make sure that I'd sit more comfortably here. I only hope I won't get any sand into... No! I have to relax now! Try not to worry for once, Noelle!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <test expr="~background.surface~" value="road" />
                <state img="#-start.png">Is it really safe to take a seat here? The surface doesn't look half as comfortable as the place where I normally... I should better just relax and focus on enjoy myself as good as possible! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <test expr="~background.surface~" value="grass" />
                <state img="#-start.png">The grass around here reminds me at the hills around Mondstadt... I haven't ever done something like this there though.</state>
                <state img="#-start.png">I am reminded of my home of Mondstadt with the soft grass here. I've never done something as risque as this before... On bare grass at least.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-start.png">Normally I wouldn't sit on the ground before I cleaned it and... No! I have to relax now! Try to not think about work for some time, Noelle!</state>
                <state img="#-start.png">I personally would prefer to do this in a soft bed than on this dirty floor, but e-even at this, I will give the best of my ability!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="masturbating">
            <case stage="6">
                <condition role="opp" character="blake_belladonna" sayingMarker="blake_noelle_mastintro3" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="1001" marker="NoelleBlakeMastStart03">Okay... I think I'm ready. It feels wrong to not do something in return, but I promise to give it my all.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <condition role="opp" character="blake_belladonna" sayingMarker="Blake_Noelle_Bondage" />
                <state img="#-shy.png" oneShotId="1003" marker="NoelleBlakeBondage01">I don't think I've given it enough thought to try that out. But umm... I-I would want to try to be blindfolded. And maybe make sure the rope you use is of good quality, or use chains if you must...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <condition role="opp" character="blake_belladonna" sayingMarker="blake_noelle_bondage2" />
                <state img="#-curtsey.png" oneShotId="1005" marker="NoelleBlakeBondage02">Y-yes, the thought of not knowing what to expect makes me shiver a little... I also mentioned chains in case I break the rope. I have a tendency of underestimating my own strength.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <condition role="opp" character="blake_belladonna" sayingMarker="blake_noelle_bondage3" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="1010" marker="NoelleBlakeBondage03">&lt;i&gt;Ahhnn...&lt;/i&gt; Oh my, the thought of that made my heart skip a beat. I-if you would rather use rope, that might be more comfortable anyways. Maybe even s-squeeze me a bit.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <condition role="opp" character="blake_belladonna" sayingMarker="blake_noelle_bondage4" />
                <state img="#-flustered.png" oneShotId="1012" marker="NoelleBlakeBondage04">&lt;i&gt;Haahh!&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br&gt;U-uh... Yes! I mean, yes to having the rope squeeze my wrists and ankles. And maybe just squeeze me a bit too?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <condition role="opp" character="blake_belladonna" sayingMarker="blake_noelle_bondage5" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png" oneShotId="1018" marker="NoelleBlakeBondage05">M-Mistress Belladonna! I could never bring myself to harm you in any way. I'd only want to care for you. M-massage you, rub you, a-and... K-kiss you? Oh goodness, I'm not as good at this as you are.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <condition role="opp" character="blake_belladonna" sayingMarker="blake_noelle_bondage6" />
                <state img="#-bashful.png" oneShotId="1021" marker="NoelleBlakeBondage06">W-well... If that's what you &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; want, I can try it. I just feel awful about hurting someone dear to me...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">Ahhh.... I can feel all the pressure rolling off of me.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="619">It feels like Electro is running through me... Is that why some people enjoy getting shocked by Lisa?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Go at a steady pace... I have all the time I want.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I'm not sure what feels best, but this does feel...good...</state>
                <state img="#-touched.png">This always feels like I'm flying, in a way... Even though I'm on the ground right now.</state>
                <state img="#-touched.png">Nothing is better after a busy day. Mnn...</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">If you work hard, you should always try to find ways to release your stress. That's very important!</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png" oneShotId="620">People usually don't talk about it, but I think self pleasuring is very underrated. It's like a reward and a way to relax. At least that's how I see it.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">No need to hurry. This is time I should take for myself.</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Ahh, that's... &lt;i&gt;(If I touch there too often, I would finish way too fast...but it felt so good!)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-touched.png">I actually don't mind if people are watching me when I'm... It's nothing I have to be...ashamed of...</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Is it really okay if I... I shouldn't worry about that now. I need to stay focused! </state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">&lt;i&gt;(It feels better when you're totally exhausted after a hard day, but I won't complain...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Oh dear, I just remembered the clothes out on the line! But... I couldn't possibly pull away from this now.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Mmn...! Sorry, I tried to keep quiet, but couldn't quite hold it back. Or were you wanting to hear me?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">At very least, perhaps you can take something away from this, ~player~.</state>
                <state img="#-curtsey.png">&lt;i&gt;(Hopefully I still can clean up after this... I remember reading that... the finish leaves you exhausted afterward...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">Dear me... I feel like I'm gliding...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">&lt;i&gt;(Should I moan? I've read that it makes you more appealing...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">This feels both wonderful and relaxing... I should study up on how to make this feel better!</state>
                <state img="#-touched.png">This is... making quite the mess...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="heavy_masturbating">
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-heavy0.png" oneShotId="621">S-something's coming...!</state>
                <state img="#-heavy1.png" oneShotId="622">&lt;i&gt;(This is going to leave a big mess!)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-heavy2.png" oneShotId="623">What is...I...I can't stop! Ahh!</state>
                <state img="#-heavy1.png" oneShotId="624">&lt;i&gt;(I'm feeling hotter and hotter! And yet...!)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-heavy2.png" oneShotId="625">I...I promised...I'll...give...my...all...!</state>
                <state img="#-heavy1.png" oneShotId="881">L-Let me be of s-service...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy2.png" oneShotId="880">Mmnn...! S-so... Good...!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finishing_masturbating">
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-finish.png">Ahhhhhhh!!!</state>
                <state img="#-finish.png">This feels...too good! Ahh!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-finish.png">That felt ...unreal...</state>
                <state img="#-finish.png">I feel so relaxed... (&lt;i&gt;Perhaps I should do this before I sleep too, to help me sleep sooner.&lt;/i&gt;)</state>
                <state img="#-finish.png">I'd better ...clean myself ...real quick...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="after_masturbating">
            <case stage="7" priority="500">
                <condition role="self" notSaidMarker="apronOn" />
                <state img="#-end.png" marker="apronOn">While the game isn't over, I'll try to make myself a little useful. I guess it's okay if I put my apron back on for this, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">&lt;i&gt;(While I wait for the others, should I work on something? Should I offer help? But how could I help someone like this?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I wish I brought something to do with me. Just waiting and doing nothing feels wrong...</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">*Yawn* &lt;hr&gt; Oh, I'm sorry! Normally I go right to sleep after I... well...</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">Does anyone have a job for me to do? I can do anything you want as long as I have something to do. </state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">Should I start to clean the floor? It's embarrassing what kind of mess I made here... But I probably should wait for the others to finish the game first.</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Is anyone thirsty? I can--- A-actually, let me rephrase that. Does anyone want something to drink?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I'm usually more comfortable doing that on a bed, but today was the exception I suppose. I never knew it would've been that exciting doing it anywhere else.</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">Was there anything I was supposed to do after I finished? Hmm...&lt;br&gt; I'm afraid I'm a little too relaxed to remember.</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">I still feel a little woozy after that... Haa...</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">Despite having finished, I feel like I could go again... That would count for doing something, right?</state>
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">You can give me any of your clothes for safe keeping, everyone! I'll fold them up if you wish!</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">&lt;i&gt;(I can't let this loss get me down! Rather, I should everyone else!) &lt;/i&gt; Good luck for the rest of the game!</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">This is surely an experience I won't be forgetting any time soon... For a myriad of reasons...</state>
                <state img="#-curtsey.png">I can only hope my... u-um... performance was all to your liking.</state>
                <state img="#-touched.png">Thank goodness I still have the strength to move... I've never had a session feel so, um, &lt;i&gt;intense&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">I still have much more training and studying to do than I thought...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7" priority="0">
                <test expr="~background.location~" value="indoors" />
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="default" />
                <state img="#-cleaning0.png">I hope I don't bother anyone if I clean the floor a little? If I disturb someone, please let me know if I can make myself useful in another way.</state>
                <state img="#-cleaning1.png">I guess it's okay if I clean the floor back there a little? Please don't mind if I have my rear to you while I do that.</state>
                <state img="#-cleaning2.png">There's a part of the floor that is pretty hard to clean... I wonder what happened there...</state>
                <state img="#-cleaning2.png" oneShotId="633">Why do I have the feeling the place isn't cleaned as often as it should be? I better give the floor some extra careful cleaning while I'm here.</state>
                <state img="#-cleaning0.png">This floor must have seen a lot up until now. I guess everyone would enjoy the game even more if it was cleaner, though.</state>
                <state img="#-cleaning1.png">I guess everyone is happy if the back is clean and neat too. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7" priority="0">
                <test expr="~background.location~" value="indoors" />
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="noelle_chicken_and_madame" />
                <state img="#-cleaning0.png">I have brought a lot of chicken. Does anyone... Wait! Before I offer some, I should look if they are okay enough...</state>
                <state img="#-cleaning1.png" oneShotId="796">Mnnn... I can assure you, this is top quality! The Honorary Knight brought the chicken herself. Looks like there's great place to get it right before the gates of Mondstadt.</state>
                <state img="#-cleaning2.png">Do you want some, ~player~? They taste wonderful! Say "aaahhh"!</state>
                <state img="#-cleaning2.png">Do you want some breasts, ~player~? ...I mean chicken breasts of course!</state>
                <state img="#-cleaning0.png">I know I have to resist, but those look so tasty... I have to try one!</state>
                <state img="#-cleaning1.png">Those are &lt;i&gt;so&lt;/i&gt; good. ...Please, anyone! Take some too, or I have to eat them all myself and gain even more weight...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_victory">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-dutiful.png">If anyone needs their laundry done, please let me know. I happily volunteer to wash your clothes for you!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I...I did it! That's one more test I'll be ready for! Does anyone want to play another round?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_defeat">
            <case stage="7">
                <condition role="self" notSaidMarker="apronOn" />
                <test expr="~background~" value="holiday lodge" />
                <state img="#-end.png" collectible="pancakes">Now that the game is finished you should all sit on the couch and I'll serve you the drinks. Just let me get dressed first and... No, I think my apron should be enough until everyone is satisfied with a drink.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <condition role="self" notSaidMarker="apronOn" />
                <test expr="~background~" value="inventory" />
                <state img="#-end.png" collectible="pancakes">Congratulations, ~name~! Now, if you don't mind me, I would like to clean the mess we all, including myself, have made. Stains like that should be removed quickly. Just let me get dressed first and... No, I think my apron should be enough for now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <condition role="self" notSaidMarker="apronOn" />
                <test expr="~background~" value="library" />
                <state img="#-end.png" collectible="pancakes">As much as I'd like to start reading some of the books now, I think I should take care of the mess we all, including myself, have made. Stains like that should be removed quickly. Just let me get dressed first and... No, I think my apron should be enough for now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <test expr="~background~" value="alley" />
                <state img="#-end.png" collectible="pancakes">If we have finished... Does anyone mind if I clean this allay a little bit? It looks a little challenging, but nothing I can't do.  I just need to pick up the rubbish, and clean the walls a little. Give me two hours and this allay will look cleaner than ever. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <test expr="~background~" value="armory" />
                <state img="#-end.png" collectible="pancakes">Mind if I sort the weapons behind us, now that we have finished the game? I think they could be stored better. I also should move those cupboards around to... Oh, are those spider webs? I better give this place a full cleaning!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <test expr="~background~" value="beach" />
                <state img="#-end.png" collectible="pancakes">I noticed some sharp stones and shells while playing the game. Mind if I take care of those? It would be bad for someone to step on them, now that the game is finished.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <test expr="~background~" value="inventory" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" collectible="pancakes">Congratulations, ~name~! Now, if you don't mind me, I would like to clean the mess we all, including myself, have made. Stains like that should be removed quickly. Just let me get dressed first and... No, I think my apron should be enough for now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <test expr="~background~" value="holiday lodge" />
                <state img="#-dutiful.png" collectible="pancakes">Now that the game is finished you should all sit on the couch and I'll serve you the drinks. Just let me get dressed first and... No, I think my apron should be enough until everyone is satisfied with a drink.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <test expr="~background~" value="library" />
                <state img="#-excited.png" collectible="pancakes">As much as I'd like to start reading some of the books now, I think I should take care of the mess we all, including myself, have made. Stains like that should be removed quickly. Just let me get dressed first and... No, I think my apron should be enough for now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-worried.png" collectible="pancakes">How awful of me...I'll need to train and study even harder...</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png" collectible="pancakes">M-may I try again? I feel I can win the next time.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="global">
            <case stage="7" priority="600">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="forfeitHelp" />
                <condition role="opp" character="senko" notSaidMarker="noelle_finished" />
                <state img="blank.png">~blank~</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="48">
                <condition role="other" character="charlie" sayingMarker="fat_nuggets" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">Oh, what a lovely piggy! It's not as big as the wild boars around Mondstadt, but I'm sure it will grow up into a wonderful pig someday. &lt;i&gt;(I better not say, that most boars around Mondstadt are hunted and cooked eventually...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

    </behaviour>
    <epilogue hint="Win a game against Noelle" gender="male" version="2" status="unlisted" unlock="player-win">
        <title>With All My Heart</title>
        <scene name="Afterword" color="#000000" x="0" y="0" width="500" height="500">
            <directive type="text" id="text" width="45%" x="25%" y="29%">Noelle did her best to hide it, but you could see she was really distraught over losing.  You remember hearing her saying she was going to the library to research and study more, so you head for Mondstadt. </directive>
            <directive type="pause" />
        </scene>
        <scene name="Mondstadt (Front)" x="0" y="0" width="500" height="500">
            <directive type="text" id="text" width="47%" x="24%" y="8%">You arrive just as night falls. Upon your arrival, however, you see the guards.</directive>
            <directive type="text" id="text1" width="47%" x="24%" y="16%">You were worried how you would explain who you were, but when you said your name, they let you through, saying that a Lisa was expecting you.</directive>
            <directive type="text" id="text2" width="47%" x="24%" y="27%">You somewhat remember Noelle talking about Lisa once or twice…</directive>
            <directive type="text" id="text3" width="33%" x="31%" y="36%">Did Noelle tell her what happened?</directive>
            <directive type="text" id="text4" width="47%" x="24%" y="43%">Meanwhile, you were escorted to the Knights of Favonius Headquarters.</directive>
            <directive type="pause" />
        </scene>
        <scene name="Inside Knights' HQ" x="0" y="0" width="500" height="500">
            <directive type="text" id="text" width="20%">New text</directive>
            <directive type="pause" />
        </scene>

    </epilogue>

</opponent>
