<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>

<!--This file was machine generated using the Character Editor v6.7 at 4:39:59 PM on September 30, 2021. Do not edit this file directly unless you know what you're doing.-->
<opponent>
    <version>v6.7</version>
    <first>April</first>
    <last>O'Neil</last>
    <label>April</label>
    <gender>female</gender>
    <size>large</size>
    <timer>25</timer>
    <intelligence>average</intelligence>



    <wardrobe>
        <clothing name="panties" generic="underwear" position="lower" type="important" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="jumpsuit bottoms" generic="bodysuit" position="lower" type="major" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="jumpsuit top" generic="bodysuit" position="upper" type="major" />
        <clothing name="bra" generic="bra" position="upper" type="important" />
        <clothing name="boots" generic="shoes" position="feet" type="minor" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="belt" generic="belt" position="waist" type="extra" />
    </wardrobe>


    <behaviour>
        <trigger id="selected">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-reporting.png">This April O'Neil reporting live from the Inventory!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_start">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-reporting.png">This April O'Neil reporting live from the Inventory!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="swap_cards">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-happy.png">I'll get ~cards~ delivered, please.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">~cards~ cards.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Time to trade ~cards~.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">I'm going to need ~cards~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Give me ~cards~. Make them GOOD cards.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="good_hand">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="gwen" timeInStage="0" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">Spider-Woman, do you have time for an interview after this?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-happy.png">I don't know. Sometimes I just get a good feeling about things.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I knew covering the World Series of Poker would give me an edge!</state>
                <state img="#-reporting.png">Breaking news, reporter has a good hand.</state>
                <state img="#-reporting.png">This just in, reporter has a kick ass hand.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">These cards are better than a good scoop!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Someone's going to be losing something, and I'm getting the story!</state>
                <state img="#-reporting.png">Breaking news! Reporter's hand causes someone to strip.</state>
                <state img="#-reporting.png">This just in, reporter gets a good hand. Makes other players strip.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">Woot! I haven't been this excited since I took the Turtle Van for a joy ride!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-excited.png">My feet maybe cold, but these cards are not!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Looks like the practice round I played with Casey was a good idea.</state>
                <state img="#-reporting.png">Shoe-less reporter turns tables on opponents.  More after this hand.</state>
                <state img="#-reporting.png">This just in.  Reporter gets a good hand.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-reporting.png">Bra-less reporter gets good hand, humiliates opponents.</state>
                <state img="#-large_nips.png">These definitely make up for my lost bra. Well, maybe not for support.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">Yes! These cards are going to prevent me from loosing my shell!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-happy.png">These cards are going to be my ninja weapons!</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">These are better than having your tits out in the wind!</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">I think that this is going to be my best report yet!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Topless reporter gets another good hand. Humiliates increasingly undressed opponents.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-happy.png">These cards are game changers, just like four mutant turtles!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Honestly, this how I spend pizza night with Irma.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">Great cards always come when I'm in my favorite panties!</state>
                <state img="#-reporting.png">Reporter in favorite panties about to kick major ass.  More after this hand!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-happy.png">This would have been a better hand when I still had clothes, but I'll keep it.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">Maybe my clothes were holding me back, because these cards kick ass!</state>
                <state img="#-reporting.png">This just in. Nude reporter humiliates opponents with great hand!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="okay_hand">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="gwen" timeInStage="0" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">Spider-Woman, do you have time for an interview after this?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-calm.png">These are...workable?</state>
                <state img="#-jealous.png">Not the best, but I guess they'll have to do.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Nothing to report home about.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Maybe, just maybe, these will turn out alright</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-calm.png">A good reporter can work with anything.</state>
                <state img="#-jealous.png">Not bad, not bad...</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I can see a story developing with these cards.</state>
                <state img="#-jealous.png">I wonder if I can make these cards work?</state>
                <state img="#-jealous.png">Well, I guess I'm loosing something</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-sad.png">I'm not sure if this is enough. What did everyone else get?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Hmm, maybe I can work with these...</state>
                <state img="#-jealous.png">These are OK. They're the red bandanas of cards.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-jealous.png">I could make these work as long as I have the focus of Leo.</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">Relax April, these aren't bad cards to get.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3 5">
                <state img="#-calm_nips.png">
                    <alt-img stage="5">#-calm.png</alt-img>
                    <text>What's the worst thing that could happen here, really?</text>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Totally not sweating this one.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-happy.png">OK, maybe my panties will be OK with this hand.</state>
                <state img="#-jealous.png">Splinter told me to turn disadvantages into advantages, so these cards should be OK.</state>
                <state img="#-jealous.png">Did I get these cards by accident, or is it fate?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-calm.png">This should be fine. And if it's not, I'm already naked.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I know these cards aren't good, but I'm enjoying the breeze.</state>
                <state img="#-jealous.png">I learned from Splinter how to make a disadvantage, be an advantage. So these cards will work for me.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="bad_hand">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="gwen" timeInStage="0" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">Spider-Woman, do you have time for an interview after this?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-angry.png">How do I get these cards!</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">Did you switch my cards, dealer? I can and will write an exposé on this!</state>
                <state img="#-jealous.png">Did someone mess with my cards...</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">So what's the rule on stripping? Asking for a friend...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-angry.png">These are worse than Mikey's pizza breath.</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">Looks like my feet are going to be cold...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-angry.png">What's a girl got to do to get some good cards around here!</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">I thought the games I played with the guys would help...</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">These are worse than when I found Donny's spy cam in my shower!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-jealous.png">I'd need more than luck to improve this hand to "poor".</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">Come on! These are like daggers to my clothes!</state>
                <state img="#-shocked_nips.png">I'm beginning to think these cards are cursed!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-angry.png">One more bad hand and I'm going to show you some of the moves Raph taught me!</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">I'm just mad I have sucky cards &lt;i&gt;and&lt;/i&gt; no back support</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">This is my favorite jumpsuit and these cards aren't helping me keep it.</state>
                <state img="#-jealous.png">This is worse than the time my editor didn't believe in sewer monsters!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-sad.png">Well, with these cards I'm going to be a literal panty dropper.</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">This is worse than everytime I have to do laundry after being in the sewers...</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">Can an ace reporter keep her panties for a change!</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">Damn it! Looks like my panties are going to be collateral for this report.</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">I see the headline now. Ace reporter loses panties due to another bad hand.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-angry.png">With these awful cards, I'm probably going to give a special report.</state>
                <state img="#-jealous.png">This game stopped being fun sometime around when I picked up these cards.</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">My chances just went down the drain like so many baby turtles.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_winning">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-happy.png">My turn already? Whatever, I'm still winning.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I guess it's only fair considering I'm ahead.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-excited.png">Honestly, I don't care. I still have an advantage in this story.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Not to worry I'll win this quickly and won't have to show anything off.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-excited.png">Wow, I can't believe it took me this long to loose like you guys.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">For a moment, I didn't think it would come to this.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-excited.png">It's OK, I'm getting a great story out of this game.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I was hoping I could win before it came to this. At least I still have the lead.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-happy.png">I suppose I should level the playing field. Makes my report more interesting.</state>
                <state img="#-jealous.png">Are you sure we can't bend the rules just a little?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I mean, I'm ok with this, considering I'm in the lead!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-excited.png">At least I've got the lead on this story!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">The things I do for a story.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_normal">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-happy.png">No big deal. A good reporter knows she needs to prepare for the worse.</state>
                <state img="#-jealous.png">We all gotta lose at some point.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-calm.png">No big. I still have a giant freaking jumpsuit.</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">I have been in worse situations than this one.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-jealous.png">Maybe those boots should have counted as one each.</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">Lady luck is diffidently not on my side today</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-calm_nips.png">My turn? Hopefully my editor doesn't ask me how much I lost.</state>
                <state img="#-jealous.png">I wasn't excepting my quest for a good scoop would lead to this</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-jealous.png">Seriously, this is the most in-depth I've went for a story before.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">April O'Neil has once again bit off way more than she can chew.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-angry.png">Damn, there goes my modesty...and credibility.</state>
                <state img="#-reporting.png">Looks like this is April O'Neil reporting, &lt;i&gt;gulp&lt;/i&gt;, in the nude.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_losing">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-sad.png">Not a big deal. This is just part of getting the story.</state>
                <state img="#-jealous.png">If you wanna get a scoop you gotta take a few hits.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-angry.png">Shit, I'm beginning to think I'm over my head on this report.</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">What have I gotten myself into?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-angry.png">So, am I like the only one playing here!?</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">Come on guys, help a girl out here...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-shocked_nips.png">God, it's starting to look like I'm over my head.</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">My father wanted me to become an engineer but nooo... i just had to become a journalist.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-sad.png">But...this is my favorite jumpsuit...</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">There is loosing and then there is loosing this badly.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-sad.png">You mean...I have to be naked.</state>
                <state img="#-jealous.png">You know how some people say keep your panties on, yeah I'm not very good at that.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripping">
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="other" character="mahiru" stage="7" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">A selfie Maihru? Ok let's do it!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="other" character="mahiru" stage="9" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">Well...since you do have a camera...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Well, I think my belt has to go.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Just my boots. Boots aren't a big deal.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="donny">I forget how hard it is to unzip...</state>
                <state img="#-stripping_l.png" marker="leo">Man this jumpsuit is tight!</state>
                <state img="#-stripping_m.png" marker="mikey">I kinda miss that yellow t-shirt I wore last time.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping_r.png" marker="raph">You know, I just thought of something...</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">I guess I'll just take off my ~clothing~...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Well, looks like it's time for me to free the girls.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Last time I played, I saw Gwen do this trick. Jumpsuit counts as two.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Looks like it's time for this turtle to get out of her shell.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Well, this easier than the zipper...</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Well, this is April's Jumpsuit, signing off.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Well I got a scoop for you guys. But you can't tell anyone...</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">I can't say this is the first time I took off my panties here.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripped">
            <case stage="6">
                <condition role="other" character="mahiru" stage="7" />
                <state img="#-blank.png">This better not get out though. Journalistic integritty needs to be kept.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <condition role="other" character="mahiru" stage="9" />
                <state img="#-blank.png">Just don't share it with everyone.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="donny" />
                <state img="#-stripped.png">Adios bra, you don't cover me as well as my jumpsuit.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="leo" />
                <state img="#-stripped_l.png">What? My jumpsuit covers more, and is really too tight.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="mikey" />
                <state img="#-stripped_m.png">But this is better than being topless!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="raph" />
                <state img="#-stripped_r.png">I'm basically wearing two bras with the jumpsuit anyway...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-stripped.png">What? I only wear it to break up the color.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-stripped.png">I'd make a "Foot Soldier" joke, but I'm better than that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-sad.png">I miss my ~clothing~ already...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-stripped.png">What? We both know these were spilling out of that suit.</state>
                <state img="#-stripped.png">It wasn't like the jumpsuit was hiding anything.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-stripped.png">You got my jumpsuit down to my ankles and get to see what I wear on pizza night.</state>
                <state img="#-stripped.png">At least these are better than those old green panties I used to wear.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-stripped.png">April O'Neil isn't a real brunette. No one takes redheads seriously...</state>
                <state img="#-stripped.png">I started dying after college, Irma calls it my pizza bush.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_human_must_strip">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-happy.png">One of us has to lose something ~player~. And it's not going to be me.</state>
                <state img="#-reporting.png">~player~ is over is head as he must remove an item.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">It's not like you didn't know what you were getting into, ~player~. Strip!</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">It's not like you didn't know what you were getting into, ~player~. Strip!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-happy.png">The faster you strip, the faster I can report this.</state>
                <state img="#-reporting.png">This just in, local reporter might get to see some beef cake.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I need to see your body if I'm going to report on this</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-happy.png">This is why some are playing, ~name~. I'm just here for the story.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Well, looks like I'm going to have to report on the male anatomy...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">I'm not going to lie, this is both buisness &lt;i&gt;and&lt;/i&gt; pleasure.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Go on, ~name~. Don't mind us if we pay a little extra attention.</state>
                <state img="#-jealous.png">You know it's been &lt;i&gt;way&lt;/i&gt; too long since a guy stripped for me</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Maybe you can tell me why you're staring at me when you strip, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Hmm, the bigger question is why the bulge in your crotch is getting larger...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Hmm, I'm begining to realize why it's getting so hot in here...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-excited.png">This is April O'Neil giving the inside scoop on the male anatomy. More on this after ~name~ strips!</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">I had a bet with my camera man what you were going to take off, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-horny.png">This just in. Reporter's panties wet with anticipation over a lost item.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6">
                <state img="#-calm.png">
                    <alt-img stage="6">#-happy.png</alt-img>
                    <text>I promise I'm not going to include this in my report, ~name~.</text>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-horny.png">It make a better story if I wasn't the only one naked, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">You still have clothes, ~name~?!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Every little bit of stimulation helps.</state>
                <state img="#-reporting.png">Yup, the breaking news is I'm going to get off on you, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-excited.png">Just gonna relax and enjoy the show from here. Take it off, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">Seriously! I'm dripping wet and you're still stripping.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_strip">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-excited.png">This is why we are playing, ~name~. Let's take 'em off.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Not going to lie, males stripping gives us a ratings boost in women 18-40.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Don't worry, we're all going to stare.</state>
                <state img="#-reporting.png">This just in, my female viewers are about to get an eyeful.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-excited.png">This is good for the story, ~name~. You don't see me whining about my belt.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-angry.png">This is good for the story, ~name~. You don't see me whining about my boots, and this floor is cold!</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">Please strip already, ~name~, I need an interesting report.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-reporting.png">Just asking for my viewers. What are you taking off?</state>
                <state img="#-reporting.png">This is April O'Neil, hopefully getting a full view of ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-happy.png">When you lose this next item, I'd like a quote from you, ~name~</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-reporting.png">Tell me, does it feel weird to strip in front of a girl in only her panties, ~name~. I think my audience wants to know.</state>
                <state img="#-reporting.png">Is it just me, or is it &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; getting hot in here.  I should make a report.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-sad.png">I really don't want to be the only person feeling the breeze on their skin, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-excited.png">Every little bit of stimulation helps.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Today's special report is on how stripping turns me on, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Just gonna relax and enjoy the show from here. Take it off, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">Well that's a little anti-climatic, I finished before you took everything off...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_human_must_strip">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Them's the rules, ~name~. What's it gonna be?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Them's the rules, ~name~. Tell me, how do you feel? I need a quote for this report...</state>
                <state img="#-reporting.png">~name~ must take something off, more after her clothing hits the floor.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Don't be shy, I need this exclusive look...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-2">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Trust me when I say you're going to be front page news...</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">Yup, time to lose something else.  My viewers want some skin...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Well someone has to strip, and as a reporter, I'm writing down everything.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Don't worry ~name~, no one is going to ever hear about this.  Well maybe my audience.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-3">
                <state img="#-calm.png">At least it's not me, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-happy.png">I just need to get a good look to get some viewers, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-calm_nips.png">Maybe you can focus on looking at yourself when you strip, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-calm_nips.png">Maybe as you lose some clothes you can explain why everyone is staring at me.</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">This will definitely distract people enough for me to get a good report...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-excited.png">This just in, local contestant must strip!</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Hmm, need to check my sources on what item you're going to lose, ~name~</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">Look at it this way, my tits won't be the main story for a change, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">This will definitely distract people enough for me to keep my jumpsuit</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-excited.png">Man, here I am in my panties and I'm about to get the scoop on what's coming off next, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Well, I'd like to think the main story here is that I get to keep my panties, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">Look at it this way, one reporter gets to stay clothed!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">This will definitely distract people enough for me to keep my panties.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-jealous.png">My viewers may want to see more girls naked, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Look at it this way, my pussy won't be the main story for a change, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Just adding fuel to my fire, ~name~...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">This just in, masturbating reporter finds new inspiration</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Just gonna relax and hope I can go another round later. For my report of course.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_strip">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="gwen" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-excited.png">You're a walking scoop Spider Woman.  Who are you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="gwen" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-reporting.png">This just in, Spider-Woman must take something off.  Will her secret be reveiled?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="gwen" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">Well Gwen, after giving me the scoop of the life time, what's next?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="gwen" stage="3" />
                <state>
                    <alt-img stage="0-6 8">#-calm.png</alt-img>
                    <alt-img stage="7">#-happy.png</alt-img>
                    <text>Look at it this way Gwen, the more you have to strip, the more people will be interested in your demo.</text>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="gwen" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-sad.png">So Gwen has to strip again? I thought she had a spider sense or something?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="gwen" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">Wow, I might get another scoop. How much flesh is Gwen willing to show?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="mahiru" stage="0" />
                <state>
                    <alt-img stage="0-6 8">#-calm.png</alt-img>
                    <alt-img stage="7">#-happy.png</alt-img>
                    <text>Wow Mahiru, keeping your camera? That shows dedication to the craft, trust me I know.</text>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="mahiru" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">Don't worry Mahiru. Us journalists have to forage ahead even in the face of adversity.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="mahiru" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-sad.png">You lost again Mahiru? Just don't give them the satisfaction of taking something good off. Make em wait.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="mahiru" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-jealous.png">Your dress? This is why all reporters should wear jumpsuits. Two parts.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="mahiru" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-sad.png">Is there anything your journalistic mentor could do for you? Striping in front of people is never fun...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="mahiru" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-horny.png">So is it going to be T or A, Mahiru? Protip, viewership will be up either way...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="mahiru" stage="6" />
                <state img="#-horny.png">Don't be afraid some of us &lt;i&gt;admire&lt;/i&gt; reports on human anatomy.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Them's the rules, ~name~. What's it gonna be?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Note to self, report on the increasing heat in the room after ~name~ strips.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-jealous.png">Beginning to realize why I would play this game twice...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Come on, join me in my nudity, ~name~. It's not like I haven't seen a naked girl before.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Time to give back to the others ~name~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Let's see if this was worth me loosing my belt ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Naked time for you, loser!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I'd love to get an interview after you take this off, ~name~,</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-jealous.png">Some of us have taken real clothes off already. Let's get on with it!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-calm.png">You can actually see my tits now, care to return the favor, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Care to join a panty clad journalist in this investigation?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Maybe if you take something good off, I won't feel so vulnerable?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-happy.png">You have a naked reporter asking you questions, ~name~. Care to return the favor...</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">This is crap. I'm TOTALLY naked! You can't take something good off, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-sad.png">Give me some inspiration for this touching report, ~name~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-calm.png">I'm already done. I'm not in any hurry anymore.</state>
                <state img="#-jealous.png">I mean, better late than never.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Any chance you could do more for a naked girl?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-calm.png">This reporter thought you wanted to play strip poker.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-sad.png">Breaking news, it wasn't.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-jealous.png">Of course as a reporter I should've realized you'd start small.</state>
                <state img="#-reporting.png">Tell me ~name~, why take off something so small?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-angry.png">I can feel the breeze on my tits and that's what you take off!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-angry.png">Seriously! Good to know you want help a topless reporter out, ~name~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-sad.png">Take that as a no then, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">Yup, figured it was going to be something small...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-sad.png">Apparently not, ~name~.  Expect unfair press treatment</state>
                <state img="#-jealous.png">Seriously, I should've expected you to only take off your ~clothing~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-sad.png">A small piece of a bigger story, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-jealous.png">*Sigh* It's fine. I'm not that interested anyhow.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="gwen" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-reporting.png">This just in. Spider-Woman is about to reveal her identity</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="mahiru" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">It's a lovely tie Mahiru, is it a clip-on?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="mahiru" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-horny.png">It's not stares, more like...observations...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="mahiru" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-sad.png">Poor choice Mahiru.  Reporters need to have comfort &lt;i&gt;and&lt;/i&gt; support on their feet.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <condition role="target" character="mahiru" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-horny.png">It's not stares, more like...observations.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-1">
                <state img="#-happy.png">My story needs more excitement. The only way to do that is for you to strip, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-happy.png">This game isn't about who's winning. It's about YOU losing, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-reporting.png">Rest of table waits in bated breath as ~name~ decides to take something off.</state>
                <state img="#-reporting.png">This just in, ~name~ has to take something off.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-sad.png">Come on, I need to make this story exciting, ~name~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Hopefully my breasts won't distract you from taking something good off...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-sad.png">Help a girl out here ~name~, I'm starting to feel the stares...</state>
                <state img="#-jealous.png">Come on, show a little solidarity, nudity sells.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-reporting.png">This just in. Naked reporter hopes, ~name~, joins them in nudity in order to take the attention off of her.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">It's a little cold in here, if you strip I can report on body heat...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-sad.png">I'm not going to lie, the microphone is only getting me half way there.  Lose something big and I'll finish this "story".</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-sad.png">I guess you could just take that off.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="gwen" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-reporting.png">I'm sorry she only took off her hood, hopefully we'll see more later.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-1">
                <state img="#-calm.png">At this rate, you'll be showing skin by the time my story is over.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-sad.png">Unfortunately, ~name~ was all talk</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">She is, however, still clothed.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-jealous.png">That's fine. I'm running around in my bra, you're just removing your ~clothing~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-sad.png">Guess they did...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-angry.png">Thanks to you I feel even more naked, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-jealous.png">This is completely unfair to my report, ~name~...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-jealous.png">Unfortunately, that did not happen.</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">Looks like I'm going to shelve this report...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-sad.png">Looks like I'm still going to be working on this report, ~name~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-jealous.png">That's right. Let's not rush into anything like a crazy person.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-happy.png">So I'm finally going to get something good for my report, ~name~...</state>
                <state img="#-reporting.png">Name is about to take something off, more after it comes off.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Are you actually taking something off this time around?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Tell me, what's it like to actually remove real clothing,~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Well looks like it's up to you to make my report exciting, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Some of us have taken real clothes off already. Let's get on with it!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-sad.png">Looks like it's time to show us alot more skin, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-angry.png">This is crap. I'm TOTALLY naked and you're barely removing your ~clothing~?</state>
                <state img="#-jealous.png">I could use some company, the stares are getting awkard, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-sad.png">Okay, maybe not EVERY bit.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-sad.png">How many layers did you start with?!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_minor">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-calm.png">That's a start, ~name~.  But I'm going to need something more for my report.</state>
                <state img="#-reporting.png">The crowd is &lt;i&gt;mostly&lt;/i&gt; happy.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-jealous.png">I mean, I guess that counts as clothing. Technically.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-jealous.png">Go at your own pace, ~name~. This report goes all game.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-angry.png">I'm bearing my breasts and you only took that off ~name~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4 6">
                <state img="#-sad.png">How in the world did you still have your ~clothing~ on?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-sad.png">Yup, I feel much better in my panties now that you took ~clothing~ off, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-sad.png">I'm jilling off publicly and you're just now stripping off your ~clothing~?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Hey, look. Something that counts as actual clothes.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="mahiru" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-jealous.png">But you do you Mahiru.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="gwen" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">So do you prefer a zipper or velcro back there? I'm more of a zipper girl myself.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="mahiru" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">Good. You use logic really well, definately reporter material.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0 2">
                <state img="#-happy.png">
                    <alt-img stage="2">#-calm.png</alt-img>
                    <text>I'm curious, will a lack of clothing warm me...I mean the room up?</text>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-jealous.png">Jeez, it seems you &lt;i&gt;are&lt;/i&gt; starting to lose larger items ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Are you actually taking something off this round, ~name~?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-sad.png">
                    <alt-img stage="4">#-calm.png</alt-img>
                    <text>Some of us have taken real clothes off already. Let's get on with it!</text>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-calm.png">I think you could warm me up name if you take something good off.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-happy.png">So what's next in The Exciting World of ~name~?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-sad.png">Okay, maybe not EVERY bit.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-finished.png">I'm done playing, so it's not like I care how slowly you strip anymore.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_minor">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="gwen" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-jealous.png">Honestly I'm just happy you still have clothes on.  The only heroes I know run around naked.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="mahiru" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-angry.png">Mahiru you do know you'll eventually run out of clothes. Right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0 2">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Guess it is getting warmer already, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-horny.png">It's a start ~name~...</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">But it seems you still have things left, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-sad.png">Well, that did fit the dictionary definition of 'clothing.'</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-jealous.png">Well, that did fit the dictionary definition of "clothing".</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-calm.png">That's fine. I'm running around with my tits out and you're just removing your ~clothing~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-sad.png">How in the world did you still have your ~clothing~ on?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-sad.png">Yup, feeling warmer already</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-sad.png">Really? Something so minor? You don't see people pointing at &lt;i&gt;me&lt;/i&gt; saying "minor", do you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-sad.png">I'm jilling off publically and you're just now stripping off your ~clothing~?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-finished.png">Let's speed things up here a tad.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_major">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Here we go. I finally have something for my story, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-reporting.png">~name~ is about to take something off again.  Let's hope for something major.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Well looks like this reporter is finally getting a "major" story.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-reporting.png">Breaking news, ~name~ takes something major off.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-5">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Well, looks like this reporter is going to have a great shot...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Hey, look. You're almost caught up with me. Sorta.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Yes. Take it off nice and slowly for me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-sad.png">Welp, this doesn't help me now, ~name~</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_major">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-jealous.png">I can't possibly be the only reporter here...</state>
                <state img="#-reporting.png">Holy shi...~name~ has actually taken something important off.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-jealous.png">That's a lot of skin to report on, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-horny.png">I can't possibly be the only one enjoying this...for story reasons of course.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Yup, having a clear view is important as a journalist.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-angry.png">Wow you're losing just as fast as me and you're still looking at my breasts</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-calm.png">I'll be more excited when you keep losing, ~name~</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Niiiice. Sooo veeery niiiice.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-jealous.png">Keep going like this and I may have to file another "report"</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_major">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="gwen" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-reporting.png">This just in. Spider-Woman is &lt;i&gt;actually&lt;/i&gt; about to reveal her identity</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="gwen" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-angry.png">Please Gwen my jumpsuit is practically sprayed on. I wish I had your lycra problems.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="mahiru" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-jealous.png">Reaching for your dress already? The smart reporter would have taken off her panties first.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="mahiru" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">Buttons? Here's another protip. The zipper is way superior due to the fact it allows easy stripping.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0 2">
                <state img="#-angry.png">
                    <alt-img stage="2">#-happy.png</alt-img>
                    <text>I'm a journalist. I should be allowed to film this.</text>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-reporting.png">And now we prepare for a satisfying stripping demonstration by ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-happy.png">This isn't a big story considering I know what a female body looks like, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Welcome to the "Indecently Dressed" party!</state>
                <state img="#-horny_nips.png">let's see what your hiding, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-angry.png">It's about time you take something big off!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-reporting.png">Hey, look. You're almost caught up with me. Sorta.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-angry.png">It's about time. Too late for me, but still.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Was this as enjoyable when I was the one stripping?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_major">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="gwen" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-reporting.png">Spider-Woman is actually...Gwen Stacy? Stacy is the police captain's daughter and drummer of a punk band.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="gwen" stage="4" />
                <state>
                    <alt-img stage="0-6 8">#-calm.png</alt-img>
                    <alt-img stage="7">#-happy.png</alt-img>
                    <text>And being comfortable in this game is key. Did you know boy shorts are more popular? I did a report on it.</text>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="mahiru" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-angry.png">What? A dress covers way more than that tiny thong...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="mahiru" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-horny.png">Seeing you now...you'd be perfect for the reporters' swimsuit calandar...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-horny.png">On second thought...I think all I need are my eyes, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Thanks, ~name~. The more you strip, the more our male audience goes up!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-horny.png">On second thought there maybe something here after all...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-3">
                <state img="#-jealous.png">
                    <alt-img stage="3">#-sad.png</alt-img>
                    <text>I'd be mortified if I were you.</text>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-shocked_nips.png">Wow, this is making my last report look small.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-happy.png">See, was that so bad?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Better you than me, really.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-reporting.png">I'll be more excited when you keep losing, ~name~</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-sad.png">Look over here at me. Embrace your fate.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Coming down to the wire.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Sucks for you that you're practically naked and I haven't lost anything yet.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-2">
                <state img="#-calm.png">
                    <alt-img stage="2">#-horny.png</alt-img>
                    <text>Sucks for you that you're practically naked and I've barely lost anything yet.</text>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-excited.png">Now we are getting down to the things I came here to see!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-sad.png">You're starting to look cold. Need a hug?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-jealous.png">It's not that I'm not looking forward to seeing this, but it doesn't really help me much.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-excited.png">It's a bit too late for me to win, but I'm still going to watch this closely!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-happy.png">You can already tell how badly I want to see this.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Welp. That's a news worthy chest, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-2 5-6">
                <state img="#-jealous.png">I've seen harder abs, but I do usually hang around ninjas. And turtles.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Damn, looks like we both are bearing our chests, ~name~</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Yes, compared to you, I'm soft in the stomach. That's not news!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-happy.png">
                    <alt-img stage="8">#-horny.png</alt-img>
                    <text>I've seen harder abs before, but I do usually hang around turtles. And ninjas.</text>
                </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-horny.png">
                    <alt-img stage="6">#-happy.png</alt-img>
                    <text>Well, well, ~name~, we're about to see if you're carrying a sai or a katana in your pants.</text>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Mmm hmm. Take that off for me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-excited.png">SHOWTIME!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_small_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="6">
                <condition role="target" character="fred" />
                <state img="#-sad.png">Nice.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2 4">
                <state img="#-happy.png">That is not a newsworthy dick, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-happy.png">That's smaller than my mic, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Don't worry. I hang around with male turtles. I've seen smaller cocks.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-sad.png">Wow, a dick that small IS newsworthy...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-jealous.png">Oooh. You're reminding me of that one time with Casey...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-happy.png">I would like to pet him. He's so cute!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_medium_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Breaking news! ~name~ has an average penis...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-happy.png">And me here with all my clothes still. I knew this was going to be a good assignment!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-horny.png">And me here with most my clothes still.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-6">
                <state img="#-reporting.png">This just in, ~name~ is averaged size...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-horny.png">I can think of a good use or two for that thing right now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Mmmmm. Hello there.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_large_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0 2 4-6">
                <state img="#-horny.png">
                    <alt-img stage="5-6">#-excited.png</alt-img>
                    <text>Well, well. It looks like Donatello isn't the only one carrying a giant staff!</text>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Well, that could double as a boom mic, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-jealous.png">Well, that's a definite news worthy dick, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-excited.png">I've got to get my hands on that incredible dick of yours!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-excited.png">I've got to get my hands on that incredible bo-staff of yours!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="7">
                <condition role="target" character="mahiru" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-horny.png">Don't worry Mahiru, it's common for reporters to compare notes. (And bodies...)</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="gwen" />
                <state img="#-reporting.png">Live from the Inventory!  The hero known as Spider Woman will be the first superhero to show her breasts live!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6 8">
                <condition role="target" character="mahiru" />
                <state img="#-horny.png">Don't worry Mahiru, it's common for reporters to compare notes. (And bodies...)</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Don't worry, the lighting in this room doesn't hide anything, ~name~</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-jealous.png">It's not like I don't know what breasts look like, ~name~. Don't be shy now...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-5">
                <state img="#-excited.png">I hang out with too many guys. Time for you to free The Girls.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-happy.png">I hang out with too many guys. Hanging out with your breasts out is fun.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-happy.png">My boobs have been out for quite some time. Your turn.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-horny.png">About time you took part in this little exposé.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_small_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-1">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Don't worry, small breasts can be newsworthy too, ~name~</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-3 5-6">
                <state img="#-jealous.png">
                    <alt-img stage="3">#-excited.png</alt-img>
                    <alt-img stage="5-6">#-calm.png</alt-img>
                    <text>Well, those certainly aren't mutant-sized, but they are still very nice.</text>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-calm.png">I know I might be distracting you, but those are great breasts too, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-jealous.png">Those breasts are like local news, only important to the person who has to live with them.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-happy.png">I'd like to get my hands all over those right now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-reporting.png">Tonight's top(less) story: ~name~.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_medium_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="gwen" />
                <state img="#-jealous.png">Well those are average. Are you sure we couldn't get She-Hulk to show off?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="mahiru" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">Be proud Mahiru, when I was your age I only had misquito bites.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-happy.png">
                    <alt-img stage="3">#-excited.png</alt-img>
                    <alt-img stage="5">#-horny.png</alt-img>
                    <text>Now that's what I'm talking about!</text>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-jealous.png">Hey, you've been checking me out, it's my turn to repay the favor.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-horny.png">I'd like to get my hands all over those right now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-reporting.png">Tonight's top(less) story: ~name~.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_large_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Wow, I think I know the two big stories for tonight...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Damn. Those might be bigger than a certain reporter, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Wow, those are large enough to carry an entire story, ~name~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3 5">
                <state img="#-excited.png">COWABUNGA!!!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-excited.png">Oh my god, those titties are divine! I might have to write a report on them...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-excited.png">Now that's worthy of a news story ~name~...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-happy.png">I'd like to get my hands all over those right now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-reporting.png">Tonight's top(less) story: ~name~.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="gwen" />
                <state>
                    <alt-img stage="0-6 8">#-calm.png</alt-img>
                    <alt-img stage="7">#-happy.png</alt-img>
                    <text>So, Gwen, I'm thinking about what to title this report.</text>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="mahiru" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">It's a trial of fire Mahiru.  Everyone here has been naked in front of each other.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="blonde" role="target" />
                <state img="#-reporting.png">Are you a &lt;i&gt;true&lt;/i&gt; blonde ~name~?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="princess" role="target" />
                <state img="#-reporting.png">This just in. ~name~ is about to show off the royal genitals.</state>
                <state img="#-reporting.png">Tell me ~name~. By showing off the your buisness, does that hurt the royality?</state>
                <state img="#-reporting.png">April O'Neil here, reporting on the live revealing of ~name~'s royal genitals.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0 4-5">
                <state img="#-horny.png">You seem cold. Which is weird, because it's hot in here.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Wow, that's a solid pussy, ~name~. Too bad you can't cover it like I can.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Your pussy seems cold, like my feet.  Maybe you should've played better.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-horny.png">It seems like your taking the attention away from me with that pussy, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-horny.png">The view's pretty hot from over here, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Could be worse, you could be humiliating yourself too.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Tonight on News 5: Naked people running rampant.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="gwen" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">Does "To skin a spider" sound about right to you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="mahiru" />
                <state img="#-excited.png">Was that so bad? Just think of being naked like an in-depth report.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="hairy" role="target" />
                <state img="#-jealous.png">Ever hear the one about the tortoise and the hare?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="shaved" role="target" />
                <state img="#-reporting.png">Tell me, why do you prefer being smooth down there, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-reporting.png">~name~, which razor do you use to stay so smooth down there?</state>
                <state img="#-reporting.png">Do you prefer not having hair down there?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="superhero" role="target" />
                <state img="#-reporting.png">Does being naked in front of us limit your credibility, ~name~?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="trimmed" role="target" />
                <state img="#-reporting.png">~name~, how often do you groom down there?</state>
                <state img="#-reporting.png">Do you trim that yourself, or does someone else do that. ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-reporting.png">Coming up the importance of grooming with, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-8">
                <condition filter="hairy" role="target" />
                <state img="#-reporting.png">Did you not want to shave, or is it just a choice, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-reporting.png">My viewers want to know: why haven't you cut down that jungle?</state>
                <state img="#-reporting.png">Breaking news, ~name~ has brought back the 80's bush.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0 3-6">
                <state img="#-happy.png">
                    <alt-img stage="4">#-jealous.png</alt-img>
                    <alt-img stage="5">#-horny.png</alt-img>
                    <text>No hiding in your shell now, ~name~.</text>
                </state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">No hiding in your shell now, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-sad.png">Wow, it's a fine line between clothing and nudity.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-reporting.png">Breaking news, ~name~ has a fine pussy.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-excited.png">I'll have a hand or two free here in just a second.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-happy.png">You're almost done. All that's left is the humiliation.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-happy.png">You really have bad luck ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">Let's get this over...I guess.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">You have no idea how long it's been since I've seen something like that</state>
                <state img="#-reporting.png">Tell me ~name~, are you an exhibitionist?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-happy.png">I forgot, it's nudity &lt;i&gt;and&lt;/i&gt; masturbation.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">Time to see if this matches earlier reports.</state>
                <state img="#-jealous.png">Some of us have seen this already, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-reporting.png">Tell me, are you looking forward to this ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">You don't seem eager to start ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-4 6">
                <state img="#-happy.png">
                    <alt-img stage="3-4">#-reporting.png</alt-img>
                    <alt-img stage="6">#-sad.png</alt-img>
                    <text>Breaking news from The Inventory: Things are about to get HOT!</text>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-jealous.png">Hey don't be mad you got to do this. I still have my jumpsuit.</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">You are really bad at this game...</state>
                <state img="#-reporting.png">Mostly clothed reporter gets to see ~name~ jack off.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Now lets get to the good stuff for my report.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-horny_nips.png">Well...give us a show, ~name~</state>
                <state img="#-confident_nips.png">Damn, I didn't think you'd go through with it.</state>
                <state img="#-shocked_nips.png">Woah, you're &lt;i&gt;seriously&lt;/i&gt; going to jack that.</state>
                <state img="#-large_nips.png">Why are you staring at me? You've got more important stuff to do.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Well, at least you have two things to stare at, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">It's pretty hot in here, and it looks to get even hotter.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">Damn! Looks like it's ok to stare if you need some help!</state>
                <state img="#-jealous.png">Wow...looks like someone is going to get a bit harder.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-excited.png">Finally some real action to report on!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">And here I thought it was going to be me. Thanks for the save ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-reporting.png">And ~name~ will give us a specially report on masturbation.</state>
                <state img="#-jealous.png">And ~name~ will give us a specially report on masturbation.</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">Wow, I never thought you were actually going to do it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Yes! We can get through this with teamwork!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-happy.png">You apparently enjoyed watching me. I'm going to enjoy the hell out of watching you.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0 2-3 5-6">
                <state img="#-happy.png">
                    <alt-img stage="2-3 5-6">#-horny.png</alt-img>
                    <text>I have a feeling we are going to be here a while. Not that I'm complaining.</text>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-jealous.png">Let's get to it, this isn't the first time I've seen someone jacking off in the Inventory.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Your hands moved fast to hold your dick, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">Finally some action, &lt;i&gt;I&lt;/i&gt; like.</state>
                <state img="#-reporting.png">What is you prefered style of masturbating ~name~? I guess we'll find out.</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">I'm still suprised people have to do this for the game.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Better grab that shaft ~name~. Use it like a bo staff.</state>
                <state img="#-reporting.png">This just in, ~name~ must masturbate in front of three other people.</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">I knew you were going to do it, but I din't know you were actually going to do &lt;i&gt;it&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">Way better than the VHS tape I've got at home...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Wow...this should be...&lt;i&gt;informative&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-calm_nips.png">I still don't get why you're staring at me, it can't help you with &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-reporting.png">This just in, ~name~ reaches for his shaft.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">I think I appreciate this more than the last time was here.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Seriously, it's completely fine to look at my chest,~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-reporting.png">As ~name~ moves his hands down to his penis, all eyes are on him.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">Get ready to work that bo-staff ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">I feel like I should cover my breasts when you do this.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-jealous.png">Not going to lie...it's been a while since I saw someone doing this.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Look at it this way, you have me to look at.</state>
                <state img="#-reporting.png">This just in, ~name~ has to start jacking it.</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">I'm guessing I'm not the first girl you've done this with.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Oh yeah! Can you keep up with me?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Just let me know if you need a hand. Or anything else.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_masturbating">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-jealous.png">Wave. your flesh mic away from me...</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Keep at it ~name~, this place is getting hotter!</state>
                <state img="#-reporting.png">Fully clothed reporter watches ~name~ masturbate. More on this soon.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">I spend all day with reptiles, I never get action until now!</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Keep at it ~name~. A good report needs some action.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-excited.png">This is the stuff the guys never teach me about!</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Slow and steady wins the race...and the way into my jumpsuit.</state>
                <state img="#-reporting.png">Breaking news! ~name~ masturbates in front off bootless reporter.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">This is better than the bootlege betamax Donnie found.</state>
                <state img="#-jealous.png">You seem to be taking your time, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-5">
                <state img="#-happy.png">
                    <alt-img stage="3">#-excited.png</alt-img>
                    <alt-img stage="5">#-jealous.png</alt-img>
                    <text>There's a lot of people watching. No pressure.</text>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Damn. Irma would love this!</state>
                <state img="#-reporting.png">Tell me, how does it feel to jack it front of strangers?</state>
                <state img="#-jealous.png">Wait, are you looking at me for inspiration? Not sure how I feel about that...</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">You're just going at it...(and I can't even join in...)</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-happy.png">This is way better than pizza nights with my VCR...</state>
                <state img="#-large_nips.png">You're still going at it, &lt;i&gt;and&lt;/i&gt; still staring at me.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Please don't stop, ~name~...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-jealous.png">You really &lt;i&gt;are&lt;/i&gt; staring at my tits, aren't you?</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">Damn! This is way better than another night on my computer!</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">Man, it seems you really are going at it...</state>
                <state img="#-reporting.png">This just in, ~name~ has perfected his stroke.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Wow, that's some good motions, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">Damn, that got stiff fast!</state>
                <state img="#-jealous.png">Man, I'm really hoping I don't have to that.</state>
                <state img="#-reporting.png">This just in, ~name~ is pretty good at masturbating.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-happy.png">I should be recording this for the archives.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Here's some motivation. Not that you seem to need it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-mast1.png">I... I... I'm close. Are you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-excited.png">Slow down. I don't want this to end anytime soon.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Go ~name~, GO!</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Need someone to rest with after that?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Hmm, it is just like a firehose. Good to know for future reports.</state>
                <state img="#-reporting.png">~name~ finishes in front of clothed reporter.</state>
                <state img="#-jealous.png">Jeez, you finished fast. Trying to get away ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">That went &lt;i&gt;everywhere&lt;/i&gt;...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1 5-6">
                <state img="#-excited.png">
                    <alt-img stage="5">#-happy.png</alt-img>
                    <alt-img stage="6">#-reporting.png</alt-img>
                    <text>Go ninja, go ninja, GO!</text>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-angry.png">You couldn't make sure it didn't get everywhere, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">(Wow, when was the last time you saw a man finish April?)</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Maybe later, we could get some pizza, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-reporting.png">Was this your first time masturbating in front of someone, ~name~?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-reporting.png">Tell me, is it like a fire hose ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">That went everywhere!</state>
                <state img="#-jealous.png">Jeez, first time I meet a non-reptile guy and he finishes everywhere...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Maybe we should make a report...together.</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">That was not like that VHS I picked up.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-sad.png">I didn't realize it would be that much. What, I don't really go on a lot of dates.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-shocked_nips.png">Damn! That went everywhere</state>
                <state img="#-horny_nips.png">Maybe I should take off the jumpsuit and help you go another round...</state>
                <state img="#-jealous.png">I swear that guys these days are so impatient.</state>
                <state img="#-reporting.png">And now back to the game as ~name~ remains a sticky mess</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Tell me, did my breasts help, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">DAMN!</state>
                <state img="#-jealous.png">Jeez, (You couldn't wait for me?)</state>
                <state img="#-reporting.png">This just in, it is raining jizz.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-excited.png">Now &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; was a show!</state>
                <state img="#-reporting.png">And so ~name~ finished successfuly. Back to the game.</state>
                <state img="#-jealous.png">You couldn't wait for me...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-angry.png">Dammit! I'm not ready yet!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-horny.png">WHOA! That was SO HOT!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0-1">
                <state img="#-excited.png">Penalty time, ~name~. Ready... GO!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Maybe it'll be looking at a mirror?</state>
                <state img="#-reporting.png">Tell me ~name~, where did you go wrong this game?</state>
                <state img="#-jealous.png">Look at it this way, you get rid of built up stress.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">The room &lt;i&gt;is&lt;/i&gt; heating up...</state>
                <state img="#-jealous.png">Look at it this way, you get rid of built up stress...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-calm_nips.png">Hey! Quit staring at me, you have more important work to do!</state>
                <state img="#-reporting.png">We're back as ~name~ realizes it's time to get her hands dirty.</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">Guess you to to do &lt;i&gt;it&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I guess it's your turn!</state>
                <state img="#-jealous.png">Let's get this over with. I need to get this report back quickly.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Wow, guess it's time to get down to buisness ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-reporting.png">We now go live, as ~name~ learns that she has to play with herself.</state>
                <state img="#-jealous.png">Jeez, it's not like you have to fight ninjas...</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">I guess it's your turn...</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">Finally, I get to see some demonstrations!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-happy.png">You go girl!</state>
                <state img="#-reporting.png">This just in, ~name~ has to get down to buissness.</state>
                <state img="#-jealous.png">Maybe I wanted to go first ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">Wow, I can't believe you &lt;i&gt;are&lt;/i&gt; going to do it.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">Don't be afraid a reporter likes to see &lt;i&gt;all&lt;/i&gt; the angles.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Unfortunately, I'll probably be joining you soon, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Yes! We can get through this with teamwork!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-jealous.png">It's not that bad once you get started.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-jealous.png">
                    <alt-img stage="1-2">#-sad.png</alt-img>
                    <text>Wait. Hold on. I thought we were kidding. I'd better win now.</text>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Hopefuly this isn't like looking into a mirror.</state>
                <state img="#-jealous.png">Someone seems eager to start...</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">You're going to be more active than my last few reports, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-reporting.png">This just in, ~name~ has started masturbating in front of me. More to come soon.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Go to town girlfriend.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Quick question. How long before you finish ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">Let's get a show for this report, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-jealous.png">Seems like you have expierience, ~name~...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-excited.png">About time you get started down there ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-jealous.png">If only this report was a first hand expierience</state>
                <state img="#-horny_nips.png">Don't mind me, my jumpsuit is...scratchy,..</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">Gulp.  Guess you got to start now ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3 6">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Don't stare, April. Don't stare.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Well...don't leave a girl hanging...</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I didn't expect you to go through with it, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-reporting.png">Everyone awaits as ~name~ begins to play with herself.</state>
                <state img="#-jealous.png">Someone seems ready to go...</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">Didn't realize I might have to show off my technique.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-horny.png">If you're anything like me, we're going to be here for awhile...</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">At least It's not me ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-reporting.png">And name begins drawing her hands closer to her vagina.</state>
                <state img="#-jealous.png">You seem eager to start ~name~...</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">Your really &lt;i&gt;are&lt;/i&gt; going to town.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-horny.png">We could always switch off, if you're interested, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">Don't stare, April. Don't stare</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Slow and steady wins the race.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_masturbating">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-angry.png">Go finish before I have to, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Wow. It &lt;i&gt;is&lt;/i&gt; like looking into a mirror</state>
                <state img="#-jealous.png">Jeez, this reminds me of what I did on saturday night.</state>
                <state img="#-reporting.png">This just in. ~name~ is pretty good at masturbating</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1 3">
                <state img="#-happy.png">
                    <alt-img stage="3">#-horny.png</alt-img>
                    <text>Go ninja, go ninja, GO!</text>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Damn, that's hot!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-happy.png">You know those hands look like they've done this before.</state>
                <state img="#-confident_nips.png">Now this is a &lt;i&gt;show&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-large_nips.png">I have no idea why you're staring at me when you're playing with yourself down there?</state>
                <state img="#-reporting.png">This just in, ~name~ is still going strong.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-reporting.png">Name continues to go to town on herself.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">Finally, some action!</state>
                <state img="#-jealous.png">You seem...relaxed.</state>
                <state img="#-reporting.png">We are still watching ~name~ playing with herself.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-reporting.png">This just in, ~name~ is really good at masturbating.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I may steal that for mys...I mean a friend.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">Come on, I need this action for my report!</state>
                <state img="#-jealous.png">That...doesn't look fun at all</state>
                <state img="#-reporting.png">This just in, ~name~, is still going at it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-excited.png">It's about to get messy over here!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-reporting.png">Too... much... going on. Too... excited...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-calm.png">I'm a pro at this sort of thing now. Let me know if you need any help.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-1 3">
                <state img="#-horny.png">
                    <alt-img stage="3">#-happy.png</alt-img>
                    <text>You're hot, sticky and messy, ~name~. Kinda like a pizza.</text>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-excited.png">DAMN. You look like you could use a towel.</state>
                <state img="#-reporting.png">Was that the hardest you ever climaxed? My audience wants to know.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Maybe you could use some help...next time?</state>
                <state img="#-jealous.png">Jeez, finish without me I guess.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">You're just as wet as Irma when she stays over.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-sad.png">Damn. That was intense.</state>
                <state img="#-jealous.png">At least you finished &lt;i&gt;your&lt;/i&gt; story.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">This is the action I needed!</state>
                <state img="#-horny_nips.png">Man you're getting this reporter reved up!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-excited.png">Best. Report. Ever!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Damn. That was informative.</state>
                <state img="#-reporting.png">She has finished masturbating, now back to the game.</state>
                <state img="#-jealous.png">Do you want me to get you a towerl, or something?</state>
                <state img="#-jealous.png">It's not like...I wanted to do that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Wow, that was definitely worth the wait.</state>
                <state img="#-reporting.png">~name~ has finished, now we return to the game.</state>
                <state img="#-jealous.png">Man those juices are everywhere. And I mean everywhere.</state>
                <state img="#-jealous.png">You couldn't wait for me...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-angry.png">S0 that's the performance I'm going to have to beat, eh?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-jealous.png">So much for working as a team.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Now if you could turn and smile at Camera 2. There ya go.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate_first">
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-sad.png">Fine. But the rest of you losers had better give me an interview after this...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate">
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-sad.png">Whelp! Time for me to go! Oh, yeah. That.</state>
                <state img="#-jealous.png">Become a reporter they said, It will be fun they said...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="start_masturbating">
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-starting.png">Looks like I can use my mic to report on this touching story.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="masturbating">
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Having an audience is new. Usually this is how I end pizza night...</state>
                <state img="#-reporting.png">I remember a report on how to do this. It may have been late at night...</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">There goes my status as an upstanding reporter...</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Didn't realize how good a mic feels against my pussy. Might need to file a report later...</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">Fuck! Ah...Shit, I don't think I can say that in a report...</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">Damn, this feels way better than filing reports!</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">This is more action than any other report I have done!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="heavy_masturbating">
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-excited.png">This is horrible and awesome and embarrassing and thrilling all at the same time!</state>
                <state img="#-mast1.png">AHH! Fuck that mic is good!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finishing_masturbating">
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-finishing.png">Really...hoping my...audience...didn't see this report!</state>
                <state img="#-finishing.png">AHHH...AHHH...TURTLE POWER!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-reporting.png">This has been April O'Neil, masturbating. Back to the studio.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_victory">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Well that was an interesting report!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-excited.png">Whoa! Close one! You all wear so many layers compared to my usual group.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_defeat">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-reporting.png">Tune in next week for another round of poker with your fearless reporter!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

    </behaviour>
</opponent>
