<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<metadata>
    <owner>kimberly</owner>
    <noteworthy />
    <hidden />
    <responses />
    <notes />
    <labels />
    <prefixes />
    <nextId>0</nextId>
    <markers>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Corrin_Awkward">There are two Corrins... and it's about to get weird</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Corrin_Question">There are two Corrins... and Kimberly has some questions</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="DD_Amy_Sonic">Amy and Kimberly should totally set up a double date!</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="DD_Arwen_Aragorn">Arwen and Kimberly should totally set up a double date!</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="DD_Ash_Misty">Misty and Kimberly should totally set up a double date!</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="DD_Daisy_Luigi">Daisy and Kimberly should totally set up a double date!</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="DD_Daphne_Fred">Daphne and Kimberly should totally set up a double date!</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="DD_Hermione_Ron">Hermione and Kimberly should totally set up a double date!</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="DD_Jasmine_Aladdin">Jasmine and Kimberly should totally set up a double date!</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="DD_Korra_Asami">Korra and Kimberly should totally set up a double date!</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="DD_Peach_Mario">Peach and Kimberly should totally set up a double date!</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="DD_Wanda_Vision">Wanda and Kimberly should totally set up a double date!</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="DD_Zelda">Zelda and Kimberly should totally set up a double date!</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="DD_Zelda_Link">Zelda and Kimberly should totally set up a double date! (Link is playing too)</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="game night">A game night would be crazy fun!</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="GNO_D.Va">D.Va could use a good old fashioned Girls' Night Out!</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="GNO_Mercy">Mercy could use a good old fashioned Girls' Night Out!</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="GNO_Pinkie">Pinkie could use a good old fashioned Girls' Night Out!</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="GNO_Samus">Samus could use a good old fashioned Girls' Night Out!</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="kimberly_pinkie_hi" />
        <marker scope="Public" name="Picture_Request">Kimberly wants a copy of Mahiru's pictures... for reasons...</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="revy_smoking">Kimberly asks Revy to not smoke...</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Revy_the_Ranger">Could Revy be a Power Ranger? No. But stranger things have happened.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Revy_Weapon">Revy and Kimberly discuss weapons.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="Revy_zord_offer">If Revy is interested in the rangers' weapons maybe she'd like to see the zords.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="SD_Zoey">Zoey lives a stressful life and could really use a spa day.</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="SO_Gwen">Gwen seems cool. Maybe she and Kimberly could have a sleep over some time?</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="SO_Marinette">Marinette seems cool. Maybe she and Kimberly could have a sleep over some time?</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="SO_Nagisa">Nagisa seems like she could use a little help coming out of her shell. Maybe a sleep over would help?</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="SO_Ochako">Ochako seems cool. Maybe she and Kimberly could have a sleep over some time?</marker>
        <marker scope="Public" name="towlette">This is a utilitarian tag that helps Kimberly stand up after she finishes.</marker>
    </markers>
    <recipes />
</metadata>
