<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<markers>
    <marker name="anankos" scope="Public">Lore stuff, in short: Anankos is both evil and not evil at the same time because reasons. Mentioning both in the same game might be confusing.</marker>
    <marker name="arco" scope="Public">Taking off her armor is quite a hassle for Corrin.</marker>
    <marker name="arthur" scope="Public">Arthur is a character in FE:Fates, known for his terrible luck.</marker>
    <marker name="backcare" scope="Public">Big breasts are heavy and might hurt your back later on in life.</marker>
    <marker name="booksdontlie" scope="Public">Quote "Those books weren't lying!" when a male large crotch is visible. It's been hinted at that Nyx (character in FE:Fates, the one I referenced to about the Strip Poker book in Corrin's other lines) likes reading erotic novels.</marker>
    <marker name="camp" scope="Public">Corrin's army camp. She spent quite a bit of time here in between battles.</marker>
    <marker name="cardcombos" scope="Public">Quote: "These cards don't match with any of the combos I read about... Maybe it is a hidden one?" When she has a bad hand.</marker>
    <marker name="chainsawsword" scope="Public">Corrin's sword is basically a magical chainsaw.</marker>
    <marker name="chrltpose" scope="Public">"Charlotte Pose" Charlotte is a character in FE:Fates. Her official art has her in an... interesting pose, a pose I tried to recreate as the 6-help pose</marker>
    <marker name="chunlifollowup" scope="Private">Used to continue lines towards Chun-Li.</marker>
    <marker name="comfygloves" scope="Public">1-stripped: "Here you go! you can try [my gloves] on if you like, they are really comfy!" Probably doesn't do anything, but hey.</marker>
    <marker name="cursed" scope="Public">Giant penises are scary, especially kisekae's giant penises. Corrin fears you might be cursed.</marker>
    <marker name="demstratz" scope="Public">Corrin asks if a character is intentionally taking something bigger off.</marker>
    <marker name="demstratz2" scope="Private">Followup to the "demstratz" marker.</marker>
    <marker name="dragon" scope="Public">Corrin can turn into a dragon (well, more like a deer-dragon hybrid), that's basically it.</marker>
    <marker name="dragonstone" scope="Public">A dragonstone is needed for Corrin to transform into a dragon.</marker>
    <marker name="finishmas" scope="Private">Used so her 9-finished pose doesn't reappear until the game is over.</marker>
    <marker name="forgot" scope="Public">Because she gets really competitive in stage 4, Corrin forgets that losers have to masturbate.</marker>
    <marker name="fuckme" scope="Public">Corrin gets really horny when a guy starts masturbating when she's masturbating as well.</marker>
    <marker name="goingeasy" scope="Public">Corrin doesn't want people to go easy on her in this game.</marker>
    <marker name="goodchoice" scope="Public">Quote "Your ~clothing~? That's a good choice!" After someone takes something off.</marker>
    <marker name="haiku" scope="Public">Referencing Mitama, a character in FE:Fates who basically only speaks in haiku.</marker>
    <marker name="hotsprings" scope="Public">Corrin's army camp has hot springs. The springs are unisex so it's possible (and likely) for you to "accindentally" walk into the springs when members of the opposing gender are bathing.</marker>
    <marker name="justillusion" scope="Public">"Justice is just an illusion" is a quote in FE:Fates, I referenced it.</marker>
    <marker name="launchsplit" scope="Private">Corrin comments on Launch's split personality.</marker>
    <marker name="kindofmagic" scope="Private">responding to corrin_m's presence, "This is so weird... What kind of magic is this?"</marker>
    <marker name="learnbydoing" scope="Public">Quote: "I'm just going to call this "learning by doing"". When she has a bad hand.</marker>
    <marker name="lookatmashirt" scope="Private">She mentions her shirt in a "good_hand" quote, mentioning it again in a stripping quote is not needed.</marker>
    <marker name="lookgudwitdat" scope="Public">"Oh you looked good wearing that..." type of lines when someone takes something off.</marker>
    <marker name="looklikehi" scope="Public">Corrin makes this comment when someone reveals their small breasts. "Hi..." in this sentence is Hinoka, Corrin's older sister and also best Hoshido girl, fight me.</marker>
    <marker name="luckycharm" scope="Public">Corrin thinks of her hairband as her Lucky Charm. A character in FE:Fates, called Benny, makes Charms for people he likes, so it is a bit of a reference to him.</marker>
    <marker name="mirror" scope="Public">Referencing the "Dragon Looks in Mirror, Falls in Love w/Reflection" thing because it's cute.</marker>
    <marker name="necklacestrip" scope="Private">Marks her specifically mentioning her necklace in 3-strip.</marker>
    <marker name="neoquiet" scope="Public">Responding to Neo's muteness.</marker>
    <marker name="nomoreforget" scope="Private">Calls back on the "forgot" marker.</marker>
    <marker name="notallowed" scope="Private">Calls back on the "fuckme" marker.</marker>
    <marker name="odin" scope="Public">She mentions Odin, a character in Fire Emblem Fates.</marker>
    <marker name="onedoesnotneed" scope="Public">Quote "It is just like the book said, "To win one does not need the best hand, simply not having the worst hand is enough to achieve victory." She shouldn't repeat this line.</marker>
    <marker name="onefortheteam" scope="Public">Corrin is fine with losing a few rounds if she can help other players with it.</marker>
    <marker name="playsafer" scope="Public">Corrin encourages the player to "play safer", as if that's possible in strip poker, but whatever, what does she know.</marker>
    <marker name="rinkahmiss" scope="Public">Referencing Rinkah's low hitrate in FE:Fates.</marker>
    <marker name="shantaereply" scope="Private">Speaks for itself. RIP Azura.</marker>
    <marker name="smallcount" scope="Public">Quote "Small things count? That's nice to know!" When someone takes off a small thing.</marker>
    <marker name="sph" scope="Public">"Small Penis Humiliation". Appearently some people are into that so yeah.</marker>
    <marker name="strategyguide" scope="Public">Strategy guides for Strip Poker are a thing, appearently.</marker>
    <marker name="surmas" scope="Private">At first, Corrin is surprised people have to masturbate in this game.</marker>
    <marker name="surmas2" scope="Private">Followup to the "surmas" marker.</marker>
    <marker name="takinglonger" scope="Public">This line plays only after the game has gone on for quite a while after Corrin is finished.</marker>
    <marker name="war" scope="Public">Corrin was the commander (sort of) in a war, this war was the main plot point in FE:Fates.</marker>
    <marker name="warminhere" scope="Public">Commenting on how warm it is in wherever they are playing.</marker>
    <marker name="wasfun" scope="Public">Corrin thanks the player for inviting her to their table.</marker>
    <marker name="whatisbending" scope="Public">Korra's "Bending" is not something Corrin is familiar with.</marker>
    <marker name="youarenotprepared" scope="Private">Responding to corrin_m's presence. "Gods, I wasn't prepared for this"</marker>
    <marker name="yourfateisclear" scope="Public">One of Corrin's more memorable battle quotes, also a taunt in Smash 4.</marker>
    <marker name="ztan" scope="Private">Reacting to zone-tan's markers.</marker>
    <marker name="ztd" scope="Private">Reacting to zone-tan's markers.</marker>
    <marker name="ztps" scope="Private">Reacting to zone-tan's markers.</marker>
    <marker name="ztt" scope="Private">Reacting to zone-tan's markers.</marker>
    <marker name="zttd" scope="Private">Reacting to zone-tan's markers.</marker>
</markers>
