<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<collectibles>
    <collectible id="mari_date" img="opponents/mari_setogaya/Mari_date.png" thumbnail="opponents/mari_setogaya/Red_Hearts.png">
        <title>A date with Mari</title>
        <subtitle>Surprisingly, nothing lewd happens!</subtitle>
        <text>And so, after the game you and Mari spend the night in a theme park! You discover that Mari is very cuddly, and easily amused. Sadly the date is cut short, as Mari's mother calls her to ask why she has not returned. Turns out, Mari didn't even tell her she went out! Before she left though, Mari asked you to take a picture of her. She also asked you to call her sometime, so that you two may go out again. And lastly, she gave you a goodbye kiss on the cheek. What a day!</text>
        <unlock>Win a game against Mari.</unlock>
        <hide-details>true</hide-details>
    </collectible>
    <collectible id="cattus_pendant" img="opponents/mari_setogaya/cattus_pendant.png" thumbnail="opponents/mari_setogaya/cattus_pendant.png">
        <title>Cattus Pendant</title>
        <subtitle>For lovers of catgirls.</subtitle>
        <text>This pendant will allow you to trigger Mari's catgirl transformation. If you bring it to the game, Mari will transform when she has to take off her bra. But make sure you're a male, and that you're not also wearing the Abundantia Pendant! Mari can only transform in one of the two!</text>
        <unlock>Win a game in which Mari is playing with at least two opponents that are catgirls. This collectible will allow you to trigger Mari's cat form!</unlock>
        <hide-details>true</hide-details>
        <wearable>true</wearable>
        <clothing name="pendant" generic="" position="neck" type="extra" img="opponents/mari_setogaya/cattus_pendant.png" />
    </collectible>
    <collectible id="abundantia_pendant" img="opponents/mari_setogaya/abundantia_pendant.png" thumbnail="opponents/mari_setogaya/abundantia_pendant.png">
        <title>Abundantia Pendant</title>
        <subtitle>For lovers of chubby girls.</subtitle>
        <text>This pendant will allow you to trigger Mari's chubby transformation. If you bring it to the game, Mari will transform when she has to take off her bra. But make sure you're a male, and that you're not also wearing the Cattus Pendant! Mari can only transform in one of the two!</text>
        <unlock>Win a game in which Mari is playing with at least two opponents that are females with large breasts. This collectible will allow you to trigger Mari's chubby form!</unlock>
        <hide-details>true</hide-details>
        <wearable>true</wearable>
        <clothing name="pendant" generic="" position="neck" type="extra" img="opponents/mari_setogaya/abundantia_pendant.png" />
    </collectible>
</collectibles>
