<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<collectibles>
    <collectible id="arcana" img="opponents/lyralei/c-arcana.png" thumbnail="opponents/lyralei/c-arcana.png">
        <title>Lyralei's Arcana</title>
        <subtitle>The Compass of the Rising Gale</subtitle>
        <text>A magical artifact posessed with the powers of the guardian wind. It not only grants these powers, but makes the wearer become one with the wind, which reflects on their appearance as well.</text>
        <unlock>If you want Lyralei's precious Arcana, you have to win against her 3 times.</unlock>
        <counter>3</counter>
    </collectible>
    <collectible id="bow_and_quiver" img="opponents/lyralei/c-bow_and_quiver.png" thumbnail="opponents/lyralei/c-bow_and_quiver.png">
        <title>Lyralei's Bow and Quiver</title>
        <subtitle>Peregrine Flight</subtitle>
        <text>The only warning your enemies will receive with these will be the slight breeze that puffs their cheek as the arrow that kills them finds its mark. If you're as skilles as Lyralei, of course.</text>
        <unlock>Win in a game against Lyralei to get her famous bow and quiver.</unlock>
    </collectible>
    <collectible id="bottle" img="opponents/lyralei/c-bottle.png" thumbnail="opponents/lyralei/c-bottle.png">
        <title>Lyralei's Bottle</title>
        <subtitle>A magical Bottle</subtitle>
        <text>An old bottle that survived the ages, the contents placed inside become enchanted.
 It seems to be mostly filled with water, but possibly some other liquids as well.</text>
        <unlock>Beat Lyralei in a heads up situation to get her trusty bottle.</unlock>
    </collectible>
    <collectible id="postcard" img="opponents/lyralei/c-postcard_content.jpg" thumbnail="opponents/lyralei/c-postcard_logo.png">
        <title>Lyralei's Postcard</title>
        <subtitle>A cute postcard sent from a tropical island</subtitle>
        <text>There is a note on back of the photo:



 &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;"&lt;i&gt;Hey there! Remember me?
 

&lt;br&gt;

&lt;br&gt;We played that little game of strip poker (which went a bit too far...) on that great beach some time ago. 

&lt;br&gt;Well, I loved that place so much that I had to visit it again with some friends.
 
Being here made me think of you… maybe we can visit it together some time? 

&lt;br&gt;

&lt;br&gt;

Alright, Traxex wants me to stop writing that 'stupid postcard', so I gotta go. 
Hopefully I can convince some of them to join the next game of strip poker... wouldn't that be great?! 

&lt;br&gt;They're all preeeeeetty hot! 



&lt;br&gt;

&lt;br&gt;Kisses,
 Lyralei&lt;/i&gt;" &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;br&gt;(Original art by DJComps, Edit by n949)</text>
        <unlock>Lyralei always wanted to visit a beach...</unlock>
        <hide-details>true</hide-details>
    </collectible>
</collectibles>
