<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>

<!--This file was machine generated using the Character Editor v6.7.7 at 9:31:22 PM on June 20, 2022. Do not edit this file directly unless you know what you're doing.-->
<opponent>
    <version>v6.7.7</version>
    <first>Nanoko</first>
    <last>Sakura</last>
    <label>Nanoko-chan</label>
    <gender>female</gender>
    <size>large</size>
    <timer>17</timer>
    <intelligence>bad</intelligence>

    <intelligence stage="3">average</intelligence>

    <intelligence stage="6">good</intelligence>



    <wardrobe>
        <clothing name="bra" generic="bra" position="upper" type="important" />
        <clothing name="shorts" generic="shorts" position="lower" type="important" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="skirt" generic="skirt" position="lower" type="major" />
        <clothing name="shirts" generic="shirt" position="upper" type="major" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="socks" generic="socks" position="feet" type="minor" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="shoes" generic="shoes" position="feet" type="extra" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="tie" generic="tie" position="neck" type="extra" />
    </wardrobe>


    <behaviour>
        <trigger id="selected">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-fear.png">I'm... not really sure what's going on in this place, but I'm desperate enough to play strip poker with strangers...&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;(...Who are also fictional characters, apparently?)&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;...So, why not?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_selected">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="supernova" />
                <state img="#-wtf.png" marker="supernovaselect">Wh-... hello? Excuse me? Was that a fucking wormhole just now?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_start">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="zenobia" saying="You're so normal that it's almost scary" />
                <state img="#-fear.png">That... probably shouldn't offend me as much as it does.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-smuggywuggyuwuwuuwu.png">Eh, I may not understand all this... i-interdimensional nonsense... but, if it's a challenge you want, then Nanoko-chan is more than willing to provide, no matter the circumstances!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="swap_cards">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-thinky.png">Can I get ~cards.text~ ~cards.ifPlural(cards|card)~?</state>
                <state img="#-thinky.png">Uh, ~cards.text~?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-pose.png">Your cards, hand 'em over.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">~Cards.text~ ~cards.ifPlural(cards|card)~ cards over this way, please!</state>
                <state img="#-smuggywuggyuwuwuuwu.png">Draw ~cards~!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="good_hand">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-shy.png">Huh, I thought I'd be having a harder time with this...</state>
                <state img="#-hmm.png">&lt;i&gt;(I guess beginner's luck is real, there's no way I'm&lt;/i&gt; actually &lt;i&gt;this good at poker on my first try...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-thinky.png">Do solitaire skills carry over to poker at all? I used to play it on my dad's computer all the time before I got my own.</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">&lt;i&gt;(People better think being good at poker is at least&lt;/i&gt; sort of &lt;i&gt;impressive, it's not like I have much else going for me...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">Oh, thank god. I thought I blew it for a second...</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">W-wait, how'd I do that? How do I do it again?</state>
                <state img="#-hmm.png">So &lt;i&gt;this&lt;/i&gt; is where all of my luck went... would've liked if I was lucky in a way that actual matters, but this works too.</state>
                <state img="#-niconii.png">Hot damn, this hand's as good as... some... thing...? Something good? I dunno.</state>
                <state img="#-panic.png">...Okay! Sure!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="21">I'd say I was gifted at cards, but my parents used to say I was gifted. Turns out, it was just undiagnosed autism.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-smuggywuggyuwuwuuwu.png">If you're looking for the poker master... they're probably somewhere else. This hand's good, though.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">Hah! Would'ya look at that!</state>
                <state img="#-smuggywuggyuwuwuuwu.png">Pssh... nothin' &lt;i&gt;personnel&lt;/i&gt;, kid.</state>
                <state img="#-pose.png">Bragging about how good your hand is actually isn't that bad of a strategy. It makes people panic and make bad plays. Or, at least that's what I've convinced myself because I can't bluff for shit.</state>
                <state img="#-pose.png">Damn, I shouldn't have worried about losing so much if I get better at poker the more naked I get.</state>
                <state img="#-smuggywuggyuwuwuuwu.png">Finally, my comically oversized tits are good for something. Looks like Lady Luck has a thing for gigamilkers.</state>
                <state img="#-niconii.png">You know... playing this game kinda makes me feel like a cowboy. One of those cool cowboys from westerns, that is. Not the weird, racist ones.</state>
                <state img="#-niconii.png">Let it be known that if you pretend like you know what you're doing for long enough, &lt;i&gt;you too&lt;/i&gt; can become a poker expert!</state>
                <state img="#-pose.png">&lt;i&gt;Bazinga.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-smuggywuggyuwuwuuwu.png">You know what's a good way to make some easy money? Buy lots of broken video game handhelds. The fixes are usually pretty simple, and then you can sell one for the same price that you bought the whole lot for.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-fear.png">I... t-totally meant to do that...</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">&lt;i&gt;(Shit, there's no way I'm gonna be able to do this good the whole game...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">&lt;i&gt;(...Can you hold off on the good hands until I figure out what the hell's going on?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-panic.png">&lt;i&gt;WHY AM I ONLY GETTING LUCKY WHEN I'M ABOUT TO LOSE?&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-panic.png">&lt;i&gt;(Maybe if they just stare at my tits for the rest of the game, I'll be able to win...?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-panic.png">Does it really count as a win if you win when you're already naked...?</state>
                <state img="#-niconii.png">&lt;i&gt;Second wind, baby!&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;Or... seventh wind! Sixth wind? I forgot how many times I've lost.</state>
                <state img="#-smuggywuggyuwuwuuwu.png">Yeah, this is big brain time.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="okay_hand">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-fear.png">I think I'd  be a lot more okay with an okay hand if I knew &lt;i&gt;where the hell I-...&lt;/i&gt; uh. This hand's mid.</state>
                <state img="#-panic.png">&lt;i&gt;(How the fuck am I supposed to play a normal game of poker after falling face-first into the backrooms?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">...&lt;br&gt;I'm not good at small talk.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-thinky.png">It's been a few years since I got diagnosed, but I still have no idea what "high-functioning autism" means. What's high-functioning? Me, or the autism?</state>
                <state img="#-niconii.png" oneShotId="1">I run a video game console repair service at my dad's shop, you know. If any of you need anything fixed, I'll tell you where to find us!&lt;br&gt;...Just, don't tell him where we met, okay?</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png" oneShotId="19">Wait, fuck. A-am I gonna have to talk about this during therapy? My therapist always tells me to get out and meet new people, maybe I can just lie and say this was normal poker...</state>
                <state img="#-neutral.png">Hmm... maybe I should get my nails done. I'll probably end up chipping it all off in a few days like I always do, but at least I'd feel cute for those few days. </state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">It's... really nice to hang out with other people for once. People at school don't really invite me to anything.</state>
                <state img="#-thinky.png">This might actually be good training for when I go to college. My sister would always tell me about people holding crazy parties with poker and stuff. Maybe I'll actually get invited to some of them.</state>
                <state img="#-hmm.png">&lt;i&gt;(I'm on my own for dinner again tonight... maybe I'll just get takeout on the way back. I don't feel like doing dishes.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png" oneShotId="20">&lt;i&gt;(Huh... the novelty of these people being fictional characters is kind of wearing off.  It's like they're just... normal people. And I guess they are, from their perspective.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">&lt;i&gt;(Is having big boobs even that impressive here? It's a lot more common in fiction than in reality... maybe that's a good thing. It's usually the first thing people notice.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-displeased.png">Do you know how many people sell their "broken" consoles on eBay, when the issue is actually pretty easy to fix? Half these people don't even try cleaning out the cartridge slot before they toss it... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-3">
                <state img="#-calm.png">...So. Nice weather we're having...? Actually, I don't know if the weather here is the same as the weather back home. And if it is, I just lied right to your faces, because San Francisco weather is terrible.</state>
                <state img="#-neutral.png">&lt;i&gt;(I should really buy one of those fidget toy things... my nails are gonna be bleeding by the time this game is over.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-neutral.png">Just to be clear, I'm not &lt;i&gt;completely&lt;/i&gt; incapable of holding a conversation... i-it's mostly starting one that I struggle with. Not like you couldn't tell already...</state>
                <state img="#-smuggywuggyuwuwuuwu.png" oneShotId="3">&lt;i&gt;(What's something that'll make them think I'm cool...?)&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;So... I work at my dad's video game store part-time. And, not to brag or anything, but I can carry a &lt;i&gt;lot&lt;/i&gt; of boxes at once.</state>
                <state img="#-hmm.png">Has anyone ever won a game of poker with &lt;i&gt;only&lt;/i&gt; mediocre hands? You'd have to rely on your opponents getting shitty hands every turn, but it's not impossible.</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">&lt;i&gt;(Should I have worn something other than my uniform? All of my cute clothes are in the wash, though...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-thinky.png">Is there a way to win every game of poker, without fail? Or at least be really, &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; good at it? My only other real talent is repairing video game consoles, and even if it's more practical than poker, it's not that exciting.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="17">Um... not sure if anyone cares, but my name is literally just Japanese for "girl". It was supposed to be a placeholder until my parents came up with a better name, but they... didn't.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="bad_hand">
            <case stage="1-3">
                <state img="#-fear.png">...You know, I always wondered what getting fisted felt like.</state>
                <state img="#-panic.png">Ladies and gentlemen, &lt;i&gt;fuck my ass!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-panic.png">I really should've read some kind of guide on how to play poker, huh?</state>
                <state img="#-panic.png">Is... is there any math involved in poker? Because if there is, that explains a lot.</state>
                <state img="#-wtf.png">&lt;i&gt;FUCK!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">If I don't start getting better hands, I might hurl from stress. Don't say I didn't warn you.</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">Maybe... maybe I &lt;i&gt;should&lt;/i&gt; have just stayed home and done my homework...</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">...Yeah, socializing is overrated, now that I think about it. This shit sucks.</state>
                <state img="#-thinky.png">This hand's as bad as... I dunno. Sonic '06? Do people even like those jokes anymore? There's &lt;i&gt;way&lt;/i&gt; worse games out there at this point...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-6">
                <state img="#-flustered.png">Shitty hands aren't as scary as they were a few rounds ago... but they're still not great.</state>
                <state img="#-displeased.png">Fuck, I thought I was good at this now...</state>
                <state img="#-neutral.png">No point crying about it when somebody probably has something worse...&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;(At least I hope they do...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-neutral.png">&lt;i&gt;(Just calm down, Nanoko, you're gonna be fine... just keep telling yourself that...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">&lt;i&gt;(Come on, it's not like you got the worst possible hand or something. You're gonna be fine. And even if you're not, you've already gotten this far. It's no big deal.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png" oneShotId="4">I bet my sister would've given me good tips on how to play poker... and it's not like I can ask her when I get home either.&lt;br&gt;...S-sorry, you guys don't need to hear about all that.</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png" oneShotId="5">Does anyone else ever wish they were just... a cat? Not in the catgirl way, just a straight up housecat. Sleeping all day, and doing nothing. That'd be nice, right about now...&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;(...I want a cat so bad.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-panic.png">&lt;i&gt;(I used to eat paper all the time as a kid; maybe I can just eat these cards, and nobody will notice...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-thinky.png">Kinda fucked up how the rules call masturbating when you lose "forfeiting." It makes it sound so serious.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-fear.png">&lt;i&gt;ALREADY?&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;...Yeah, that's pretty on-brand for me.</state>
                <state img="#-wtf.png">A-aren't you supposed to get really shitty hands &lt;i&gt;later&lt;/i&gt; in the game?</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">...Guh.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-fear.png">...Saving the worst for last, I see.</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">I don't even care about having to masturbate in front of people. I just don't wanna lose.</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">I mean... losing isn't &lt;i&gt;so&lt;/i&gt; bad at this point, is it...?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="hand">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="other" character="scm" sayingMarker="scm_nanokochan" />
                <state img="#-pissed.png">...I'm Nanoko-chan. That's really all there is to say on the matter, you... South Park reject. Yeah. Take &lt;i&gt;that!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="other" character="jessie" sayingMarker="JessieQA_DarkSecrets" />
                <state img="#-sad.png" marker="jessiesecrets1">Dark secrets? Absolutely. I'm terrible at keeping them though, &lt;i&gt;everyone&lt;/i&gt; at school knows why I was absent for two months a few years back. And they still think I'm a basket case because of it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="other" character="jessie" sayingMarker="JessieQA_LittleLies" />
                <state img="#-panic.png" marker="jessielies2" dialogue-layer="over">I mean... what teenager &lt;i&gt;doesn't&lt;/i&gt; lie to their parents? On a daily basis. Especially when her mom tries to clean her room and she's gotta hide her vibrators and Jotaro Kujo cum jar. That doesn't have cum in it, but she really doesn't wanna have to explain it. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="other" character="jessie" sayingMarker="JessieQA_Smokers" />
                <state img="#-thinky.png" marker="jessiesmokers1">Eh. My dad smoked throughout my whole childhood, and I still love him to death. Hating someone just because they smoke is petty as hell.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="other" character="jessie" sayingMarker="JessieQA_Family" />
                <state img="#-sad.png" marker="jessiefamily1">&lt;i&gt;Family...&lt;/i&gt; Jessie, if I wanted to answer that honestly, I would talk to my therapist. Nobody here needs to know about that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="other" character="jessie" sayingMarker="JessieQA_Million" />
                <state img="#-smuggywuggyuwuwuuwu.png" marker="jessiemillion1">I'd probably go halvsies on it. 500k for college, 500k for whatever the hell I want.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="other" character="jessie" sayingMarker="JessieQA_StupidMistakes" />
                <state img="#-panic.png" marker="jessiestupid1">How stupid are we talking? Are we talking &lt;i&gt;"got into drugs a few years ago and then quit"&lt;/i&gt; stupid, or... &lt;i&gt;"the stuff my mom said to me when she was drunk"&lt;/i&gt; stupid?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="other" character="jessie" sayingMarker="JessieQA_Lights" />
                <state img="#-smuggywuggyuwuwuuwu.png" marker="jessielights1">Lights on, obviously. I'm not a nun who only has missionary sex with the lights off for the purpose of reproduction.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="other" character="jessie" sayingMarker="JessieQA_SleptAround" />
                <state img="#-fear.png" marker="jessieslept1">That... would require anyone wanting to date me in the first place.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="other" character="jessie" sayingMarker="JessieQA_Open" />
                <state img="#-thinky.png" marker="jessieopen1">I'd probably only be okay with it if they were &lt;i&gt;just&lt;/i&gt; having sex with other people. I wanna be the only person they're romantic with. And if they were doing all of that without telling me first, I'd kill them.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="other" character="jessie" sayingMarker="JessieQA_Masturbate" />
                <state img="#-panic.png">I'm not dating anyone right now, but if I was...? I'd... probably still masturbate a lot. I already do it every time I wake up and every night before I go to sleep.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="other" character="jessie" sayingMarker="JessieQA_Porn" />
                <state img="#-thinky.png" marker="jessieporn1">Not too often, believe it or not. My imagination's way more versatile than 99% of porn sites.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="other" character="jessie" sayingMarker="JessieQA_SexNumber" />
                <state img="#-flustered.png" marker="jessiesex1">Um... it would depend on my mood, I guess? Some days I just wanna be cuddled and stuff.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="other" character="jessie" sayingMarker="JessieQA_SexPosition" />
                <state img="#-panic.png" marker="jessieposition1">N-not sex, but... uh... heh. Both holes at once. Yeah.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="other" character="jessie" sayingMarker="JessieQA_Backdoor" />
                <state img="#-panic.png">Oh... oh, I've &lt;i&gt;"considered"&lt;/i&gt; it alright. &lt;i&gt;"Considered"&lt;/i&gt; it pretty much every time I'm home alone with a lot of free time, and I'm in the mood for it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="other" character="meia" sayingMarker="pilot_recruitment" />
                <state img="#-fear.png" marker="meiapilot1">...I appreciate the offer, but I can't even sit in the passenger's seat of a car without getting nervous anymore. You don't want me piloting a mech.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" totalRounds="0">
                <state img="#-neutral.png">&lt;i&gt;(Do the people here know they're fictional, or is this just another facet of the multiverse? Being real in some universes, and fictional in others? Whatever, I'll just... try not to think about it. I don't wanna stick out too much.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" oneShotId="2">
                <condition filter="weapon" role="opp" />
                <state img="#-fear.png">I-I mean, I understand wanting to be able to defend yourself in a place full of coomers, but... can you at least be more discreet about it?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="meia" stage="0-7" sayingMarker="nanako0" />
                <state img="#-fear.png" marker="meia_nanoko0">I... I-I think it's pretty normal to be nervous when you're playing strip poker for the first time, actually! Just give me a few rounds, and I'll be &lt;i&gt;completely&lt;/i&gt; chill and normal!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="jura" stage="0-8" sayingMarker="nanoko0" />
                <state img="#-panic.png" marker="jura_nanoko0">Th-that's easier said than done, you know! Sexy tall women are one of my &lt;i&gt;MANY&lt;/i&gt; weaknesses!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="gloria" stage="0-6" sayingMarker="gloria_nanoko_strip0a" />
                <state img="#-flustered.png" marker="gloria_nanoko0">Uh... I'm not actually... in any clubs.&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;(Mostly because I don't think anyone would want me in their club...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="gloria" stage="0-6" sayingMarker="gloria_nanoko_strip1a" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="gloria_nanoko3">In real life...? No. But I've got some people online that I talk to pretty regularly, so it's not like I'm a &lt;i&gt;complete&lt;/i&gt; hermit.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="hu_tao" stage="0-6" sayingMarker="tao01" />
                <state img="#-fear.png" marker="hutao_nanoko0">...&lt;br&gt;Uh... y-you gonna say something, or...?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="leon" stage="0-7" sayingMarker="leon01" />
                <state img="#-thinky.png" marker="leon_nanoko0">Does... d-does manga count as reading? Because if not, then I haven't read anything that wasn't required reading for school in years. I can't focus on reading text unless there's something else going on. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="leon" stage="0-7" sayingMarker="leon11" />
                <state img="#-excited.png" marker="leon_nanoko3">O-oh, I like all kinds of different games! I mostly play RPGs and action games, but if I'm too stressed out to do either of those, life simulator games are fun too! I'll play anything that isn't boring, honestly! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="revy" stage="0-7" />
                <state img="#-fear.png" marker="revy_nanoko1">...D-dude, I live in San Francisco. You think I'm not used to inhaling garbage?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="miko" saying="ordinary human being" />
                <state img="#-thinky.png">...Well, you could've been nicer about it, at least. But yeah, pretty much.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="miko" saying="You fascinate me in your plainness, Young Nanoko. At least ~player~ has the good sense to say as little as possible." />
                <state img="#-smuggywuggyuwuwuuwu.png">I don't know if I should take that as an insult or not, but, if I fascinate you that much, I &lt;i&gt;could&lt;/i&gt; rattle off some facts about myself...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="miko" saying="Young Nanoko, as for your future plans: what hope you to accomplish with what little time your mortal body gives you?" />
                <state img="#-thinky.png">Hmm... well, I know I want to go to university.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="yuno_uno" sayingMarker="yuno_nanoko_strip0a" />
                <state img="#-thinky.png" marker="yuno_nanoko_0">Well, I play video games, watch anime... watch people play video games... watch videos about anime...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="turandot" sayingMarker="nanoko_0" />
                <state img="#-fear.png" marker="turandot_nanoko0">...W-will do, ma'am.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="larachel" sayingMarker="Nanoko1" />
                <state img="#-fear.png" marker="larachel_nanoko0">P-protection from... what, exactly?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="mari_setogaya" sayingMarker="Nanoko-chan_strip1" />
                <state img="#-panic.png" marker="mari_nanoko0">A-aren't you &lt;i&gt;supposed&lt;/i&gt; to be at least a little bit nervous when you get naked in front of strangers...?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="sucrose" sayingMarker="sucrose21" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="nanoko_sucrose3">M-my... &lt;i&gt;expertise?&lt;/i&gt; That makes it sound so... professional. B-but, I'm mostly into video game related stuff, mainly repairing consoles.&lt;br&gt;...D-do you even have those where you're from?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="critical_darling" sayingMarker="Nanoko_RhythmGames1" />
                <state img="#-smuggywuggyuwuwuuwu.png" marker="cd_nanoko0">O-oh, &lt;i&gt;can&lt;/i&gt; you, now? We'll see what my 300+ hours across all Project Diva games has to say to that!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="critical_darling" sayingMarker="Nanoko_Music1" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="cd_nanoko3">Uh... I &lt;i&gt;guess&lt;/i&gt; I have a preference for Vocaloid? I'll listen to anything that sounds good, but there are &lt;i&gt;very&lt;/i&gt; few Vocaloid songs that I don't like.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="lux" sayingMarker="lux_nanoko_strip0a" />
                <state img="#-fear.png" marker="lux_nanoko0">I-I'm, uh.... okay, what the fuck is a Poro? Is that like a Porg or something?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="senko" sayingMarker="senko01" />
                <state img="#-excited.png" marker="senko_nanoko0">Y-yeah, I'm just... &lt;i&gt;woah.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt; You're... you're super cute!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="senko" sayingMarker="senko11" />
                <state img="#-thinky.png" marker="senko_nanoko3">W-well, I like video games, anime... anime video games. You know, typical nerd shit. Not sure how you'd help me with any of those besides helping me get Pokemon that you need to trade to evolve...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="blake_belladonna" sayingMarker="blake_nanoko_checkin" />
                <state img="#-fear.png" marker="blake_nanoko0">H-how is everyone so composed about all this...? Y-yeah, I'm good, just... gimme a bit to get my bearings.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="blake_belladonna" sayingMarker="blake_nanoko_struggles" />
                <state img="#-sad.png" marker="blake_nanoko1">I-I guess you've got a point, but... I dunno. I guess I was just hoping to have more friends or be more accomplished by the time I graduated, and that's definitely not happening at this rate...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="mari_setogaya" sayingMarker="Nanoko-chan_strip2" />
                <state img="#-fear.png" marker="mari_nanoko3">...It's that obvious, huh?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="miko" />
                <state img="#-displeased.png">It's no... hey! I'm not a peasant! I'll have you know my family's &lt;i&gt;solidly&lt;/i&gt; middle class!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-displeased.png">Alright, no more playing around.&lt;br&gt;...Not that I was playing around before this, but I'm gonna stop playing around even harder.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-panic.png">Sh-shit, I forgot how little I had left...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-fear.png">Y-you... you'd believe  me if I said that I meant to do that, right?&lt;br&gt;...Ugh, who am I kidding?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-confused.png">Shit... guess it's the socks next.&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;(It'd be hot if I saved them for last, but I don't want them thinking I'm some kinda weird exhibitionist...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-fear.png">...Oh. I-it's fine, I've still got... stuff. Small stuff.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-panic.png">H-huh? Me? Y-yeah, I can do that! I-I mean, I came here, I knew I'd have to at some point...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-fear.png">If I win after this, it's gonna be a goddamn miracle.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripping">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="gloria" stage="0-6" saidMarker="gloria_nanoko_strip0a" sayingMarker="gloria_nanoko_strip0b" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="gloria_nanoko0" />
                <state img="#-strip.png" marker="gloria_nanoko1">I-I guess... there aren't really any clubs dedicated to my interests, though. The closest thing to what I'd want probably &lt;i&gt;is&lt;/i&gt; the film club, but I don't wanna spend hours around guys who think Joker is peak cinema.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="hu_tao" stage="0-6" sayingMarker="tao02" />
                <state img="#-strip.png" marker="hutao_nanoko1">I... y-yeah...? I-I think almost everyone who comes here has... &lt;i&gt;some&lt;/i&gt; sort of interest in that sort of business. Wh-why would you play this game if you &lt;i&gt;weren't&lt;/i&gt; trying to get laid, at least a little bit?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="mari_nanoko0" />
                <condition role="other" character="mari_setogaya" sayingMarker="Nanoko-chan_strip1_cont" />
                <state img="#-strip.png" marker="mari_nanoko1">N-not... &lt;i&gt;super&lt;/i&gt; insecure, it's just... w-well, I guess it'd make sense if succubi were more open about that kind of stuff. Humans, not so much.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="miko" saying="That &lt;i&gt;is&lt;/i&gt; odd. I’ve grown accustomed to Gensokyo’s magical beings as my bedfellows. All the humans I know are magicians and shrine maidens." />
                <state img="#-strip.png">That's... interesting? I'm no shrine maiden or magician, I just work part-time at my dad's video game store.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="miko" saying="Perhaps this is a good idea to get to understand the common people better. To understand their hopes and concerns, so I might yet further improve myself as a leader." />
                <state img="#-strip.png">My full name is Nanoko Sakura, I'm 18, I live in America but my parents both came from Japan, I'm in my final year of high school, my dad taught me how to repair video game consoles which inspired me to major in engineering once I graduate, my favorite anime is Jojo's Bizarre Adventure (mostly Stardust Crusaders), I'm allergic to seafood but not enough that it'll kill me, I have 300 hours logged on Animal Crossing: New Horizons and my island finally reached five stars yesterday, I had an extra tooth growing out of the roof of my mouth that I had to have extracted when I was two, I want to learn how to speedrun Donkey Kong 64, I've never broken a bone so I'm probably immune, I hate when people send bug reports for things that are intentional, I have, well, had an older sister and a niece...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="miko" saying="What is your family’s line of work? Are you rice farmers? Fishermen? Those are peasant sort of jobs, yes?" />
                <state img="#-strip.png">My dad goes fishing with my uncle every Saturday during the summer, but it's not his job. He runs a video game store, and my mom works at a pet parlor.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="miko" saying="Young Sumireko oft tells of a place known as “University” that has abolished the use of rest and sleep. She intends to be exiled to there." />
                <state img="#-strip.png">Yeah, there! It's pretty expensive to go to university, so I'm saving up money working at my dad's store and helping my brother in-law take care of his niece.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="miko" saying="I had been worried that because Buddhism had fallen out of favor in Japan, the populace would not be sufficiently mollified." />
                <state img="#-strip.png">Uh, well...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="sucrose" sayingMarker="sucrose12" />
                <state img="#-strip.png" marker="nanoko_sucrose1">H-hey, don't worry about it... it's not like you're yelling at me and telling me to stop being a pussy bitch or something.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-strip.png">I'd say you guys are the first people to see me naked, but... so have the girls at my school whenever we change for gym. And my dad, because he keeps forgetting to knock. A-and my mom, because she gave birth to me...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-strip.png">That's right! We're doing boobs last, because they're arguably the hottest part of my body! Were you expecting that? I don't know, I don't know you!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-strip.png">Just so we're clear. Even if I &lt;i&gt;wasn't&lt;/i&gt; stupid and unprepared for this, I still wouldn't wear underwear under my spats. I tried for a while, but they kept bunching up and making my life a living hell.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-strip.png">I know I'm being boring, but... there really isn't all that much that's interesting about me, alright? I go to school, I work a part-time job, I like anime and video games... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-strip.png">&lt;i&gt;(I wish I'd known about the multiversal stuff before I got here... I could've come up with some cool bit and made everyone here think I'm the baddest bitch alive. But no, here I am, being a sweaty loser who can't talk to people. Maybe I should be more daring next time...?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-strip.png">I... uh, hope you weren't expecting to see my underwear. Too many guys at my school were being horny on main, and now all the girls have to wear shorts or spats under their skirts...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-strip.png">&lt;i&gt;(What's the best play here? Should I try and blend in with everyone? I don't wanna be that weird guy at the table who won't shut up about wormholes and polygons, and I DEFINITELY don't wanna be an annoying fangirl...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripped">
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="gloria" stage="0-6" saidMarker="gloria_nanoko_strip0b" sayingMarker="gloria_nanoko_strip0c" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="gloria_nanoko1" />
                <state img="#-displeased.png" marker="gloria_nanoko2">You don't know the half of it, dude. If I have to see one more guy do that shitty little dance down the stairs, I'm gonna lose it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="hu_tao" stage="0-6" sayingMarker="tao03" />
                <state img="#-flustered.png" marker="hutao_nanoko2">...Goddamn, you don't beat around the bush, do you...?&lt;br&gt; &lt;i&gt;...N-NOT LIKE THAT-&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="leon" stage="0-7" sayingMarker="leon03" />
                <state img="#-flustered.png" marker="nanoko_leon1">R-really, I'm fine, it's just... w-well, it's not exactly &lt;i&gt;danger&lt;/i&gt; that scares me.&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;(It has the complete opposite effect, actually.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="mari_nanoko1" />
                <condition role="other" character="mari_setogaya" sayingMarker="Nanoko-chan_strip1_end" />
                <state img="#-stripped.png" marker="mari_nanoko2">Y-yeah... I sure hope so...&lt;i&gt;(Oh, fuck, what if nobody cares about me enough to wanna see me naked? Would I even survive that kind of humilation?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="miko" saying="My interactions with the human village’s citizens are mostly limited to speeches and official business. Being with a… &lt;i&gt;normal person&lt;/i&gt; in so intimate a setting is new to me." />
                <state img="#-smuggywuggyuwuwuuwu.png">If that's the case, I'll teach you everything you need to know about us "normal" folk! Ask me anything! I know everything there is to know about being boring!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="miko" saying="Yes. Mmhmm. I see. Alright, I’m bored now. Thank you for your time, Young Nanoko." />
                <state img="#-displeased.png">&lt;i&gt;...I wasn't done.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="miko" saying="Wait, Young Sumireko tells me the serfs of the modern world all work in “IT Support.” How well supported are the ITs of your family?" />
                <state img="#-fear.png">That's... not what that means.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="miko" saying="I’m glad. For society to function, the common-folk must strive to be hard-working, contributing, and sufficiently pacified." />
                <state img="#-panic.png">I-I mean, most of that money &lt;i&gt;does&lt;/i&gt; end up going into buying figures and spare console parts, b-but that's by choice! I'm totally responsible with my money when I want to be!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="other" character="miko" saying="However, I needn’t fear. It seems in the modern world, religion has been replaced by that which you call “anime”. I thank you for your cooperation, Young Nanoko." />
                <state img="#-calm.png">...I think we need to talk after we're done here.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <condition role="other" character="miko" saying="Oh dear, are you so poor you’ve been forced to sell the hair around your privates? If ever you have money problems, I’d be glad to lend any amount." />
                <state img="#-wtf.png">What? No! I just shave because I think it looks nice!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="sucrose" sayingMarker="sucrose03" />
                <state img="#-fear.png">&lt;i&gt;(...Wait, did that catgirl just call me a virgin?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-stripped.png">...Huh? Me? S-sorry, I was just... thinking about something...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-stripped.png">Uh... hey, what if I took my sweater &lt;i&gt;and&lt;/i&gt; my shirt off next round? I'm probably gonna win, so there's no reason to drag this out...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-stripped.png">A-and, uh... most girls still wear underwear under their shorts, but I... don't. Do with that what you will, I guess...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-stripped.png">I-it's not weird that I shaved, right? I just thought, y'know... since I'm coming here. Might as well look nice.&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;(Actually, would it be weirder if I didn't shave...?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-stripped.png">Eh, whatever... at least my boobs are bigger than most people's. That's gotta count for something, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-stripped.png">&lt;i&gt;(Oh, fuck. These are basically skin tight, aren't they? I basically just pulled my entire ass out...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-stripped.png">H-hopefully you guys are happy with how I look... I am, for the most part.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_strip">
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="kamina" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-flustered.png">Oh, hey! Would'ya look at that, it's... the really sexy guy... with the mechs and stuff... uh...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="glass_joe" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-fear.png">&lt;i&gt;(If I lose to the man who's whole gimmick is losing, I'll kill everyone in this room, and then myself.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="shou_tucker" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-wtf.png">&lt;i&gt;(Of... of ALL the Fullmetal Alchemist characters to be here, why this guy? Even I'M not enough of a degenerate to jerk off to this!)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="death" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-horny.png">&lt;i&gt;(Huh. If I'd known Death was this twunkish and lowkey breedable beforehand, I probably wouldn't still be in therapy.)&lt;/i&gt; </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="yuno_uno" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-flustered.png" marker="nanoko_yuno0">&lt;i&gt;(...There's an Uno anime? And it's got cute boys in it? How have I never heard of this?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="anatoly" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="nanoko_anatoly0">How good are you at cooking, Anatoly? Good enough to throw enough pointers my way that I won't starve to death when I'm living on my own? Really, anything would help at this point...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="leon" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-panic.png" marker="nanoko_leon0">&lt;i&gt;(Leon's the most generic pretty boy out there, but that doesn't mean he's not...)&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;...Z-zombies, am I right? C-can't say I've ever met one myself... what's it like?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-3">
                <state img="#-panic.png">Hah... wow, this is a lot more stressful in real life than I expected.</state>
                <state img="#-wtf.png">A-at least I'm not the only person stupid enough to lose... n-not that you're stupid, I mean-!</state>
                <state img="#-pose.png">Should've done your reading, ~name~.&lt;br&gt;...U-unlike me, of course,  who definitely &lt;i&gt;isn't&lt;/i&gt; also coming into this game completely blind with no idea how to play. Not at all.</state>
                <state img="#-panic.png">&lt;i&gt;(Why is the fact that I'm winning any amount of hands so exciting? How low are my standards for myself?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-hmm.png">&lt;i&gt;(It's kinda like winning a single minigame in Mario Party. It's rewarding, but you could still get fucked in the next ones. Except strip poker won't give you blisters unless you jerk off WAY too hard.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-hmm.png">&lt;i&gt;(If I can just keep this good luck going through the whole game... it'd probably get really boring, actually. I think the pants-shitting fear is part of the fun.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-smuggywuggyuwuwuuwu.png">If this was somehow the result of me falling down the stairs and getting knocked unconscious... this is a nice dream to have. One where I'm good at poker, and surrounded by hot guys.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-pose.png">No hard feelings, right?</state>
                <state img="#-smuggywuggyuwuwuuwu.png">Heh. Sucks to suck.</state>
                <state img="#-thinky.png">I should've brought some cash to throw at people like they're strippers... but that'd be a waste of money. Maybe I could just bring Monopoly money next time.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">Come on, ~name~! Look! Big bazoongies! That's enough to make you wanna strip something good, right?</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">Is this... more or less awkward now? Since I'm not wearing as much...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-neutral.png">N-no, pressure, ~name~, but... gimme something to work with here...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Imagine &lt;i&gt;not&lt;/i&gt; stripping something for the decently cute girl masturbating in front of you... y-you would never do something like that, right...?</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">I-if it's any incentive for you to show me something good... I-I've fit four fingers inside myself before... a-and I'd be willing to show you.~</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">F-fuck, dude, I need something good, don't leave me hanging here...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Not gonna lie, there was a part of me that thought I would be the first person to lose, and I'd keep losing until I was completely out of the game, and everyone would think I was stupid.&lt;br&gt;...So, thanks?</state>
                <state img="#-smuggywuggyuwuwuuwu.png">People stripping for me, and I didn't even have to lose any clothes for it. Nice.</state>
                <state img="#-pose.png">So... &lt;i&gt;this&lt;/i&gt; is how it feels to git gud.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-calm.png">...I think I used up all my cool one-liners when I was still playing.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I-I'm still a little too cumbrained to come up with something witty... sorry.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">It's a little less satisfying to watch people lose now that I'm out... but that doesn't make it &lt;i&gt;bad&lt;/i&gt; or anything...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">And now I get to watch cute guys strip without putting in any effort of my own... just how I like it.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_strip">
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="hu_tao" stage="0" sayingMarker="nanoko01" />
                <state img="#-excited.png" marker="nanoko_hutao0">I always thought funeral directors were musty old people who smelled like dust... b-but you're super cute!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="yukari" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-horny.png">Sheesh, did it just get super hot in here, or is that woman just &lt;i&gt;RADIATING&lt;/i&gt; with big MILF energy?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="azami" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-hmm.png">&lt;i&gt;(Oookay, now what is SHE from? I've seen her in something, but...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="supernova" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-thinky.png">&lt;i&gt;(Man, first the wormhole shit, and now I don't even recognize this girl from anything...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="supernova" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-hmm.png">Okay, see, I get the superhero thing. My problem is that I can't recognize you &lt;i&gt;in&lt;/i&gt; your costume. Which is weird, because most superheroes are famous to some degree. &lt;i&gt;(And... don't really exist in my world.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="kora" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-fear.png">&lt;i&gt;(Hooo, boy. That outfit's... a Xenoblade 2 outfit. Like somebody pressed the random button in a NSFW character creator and threw what came out in a blender.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="amy" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-fear.png">...&lt;i&gt;Who the fuck...?&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="wikipe-tan" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-flustered.png">Erm... is this a bad time to apologize for never donating to keep your site up?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="rogue_x-men" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-thinky.png">Okay... I don't know much about the X-men, but I'm pretty sure Rogue didn't constantly have her nips poking through her suit. Or her gooch.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="sannytess" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-hmm.png" marker="sannyko1">Uh… hm. Okay, can I ask you a maybe really weird question?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="sannytess" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-displeased.png" marker="sannyko4">...Fucking hell, I still can't think of what article I saw you guys on.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="sannytess" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="sannyko7">...Yeah. Okay. That was a waste of a hint, I've still got no idea.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="mari_setogaya" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-flustered.png" marker="nanoko_mari0">S-so, about succubi... can you &lt;i&gt;only&lt;/i&gt; feed off of sex with men, or...?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="petra" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-thinky.png" marker="nanoko_petra0">I have no idea how people can bother to learn English... I'm a native speaker, and even &lt;i&gt;I&lt;/i&gt; can barely form coherent sentences sometimes.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="ahri" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-flustered.png" marker="nanoko_ahri0">When succubi and succubi adjacent beings like you fuck... is it &lt;i&gt;guaranteed&lt;/i&gt; to kill your partner? I'm just... curious. No real reason for asking.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="sakura" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-flustered.png" marker="nanoko_sakura0">A-aren't... I thought idols weren't supposed to play these kinds of games...&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;(Isn't she a zombie? What's gonna happen when she has to...?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="nico_robin" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-fear.png" marker="nanoko_robin0">...W-wow, okay.&lt;br&gt;You... are &lt;i&gt;very tall...&lt;/i&gt; a-and I'm not sure how to hold a conversation with someone whose boobs I'm eye level with.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="revy" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="nanoko_revy0">&lt;i&gt;(Should I even bother trying to talk to her, or...?)&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;...Y-your tattoo's cool. Goes with your whole... &lt;i&gt;"don't fuck with me"&lt;/i&gt; vibe.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="meia" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-flustered.png" marker="nanoko_meia0">U-um, is your home planet really just... an entire planet of &lt;i&gt;just&lt;/i&gt; lesbians? That sounds... pretty epic, honestly.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-flustered.png">I-it's like... changing in a locker room, right?&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;(Except whenever I change for gym, I do it facing the wall so I can't see the other girls staring at me...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">&lt;i&gt;(Is ~name~ into girls in any capacity? Or is she gonna think it's weird that I'm staring at her?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-panic.png">Th-this shouldn't be too hard for you, right, ~name~? B-because, you're really pretty and stuff... n-not that I'm hitting on you! I didn't mean for it to sound like I was!</state>
                <state img="#-panic.png">&lt;i&gt;(Why is it scarier to watch other girls stripping? I lean more towards  guys, anyways...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">I'm... reminded of this one time where all the girls in my school were comparing boob sizes in the locker room, and one girl said I got breast implants because &lt;i&gt;"all Asian girls have no tits."&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;And I &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; didn't want to remember that.</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">So... girls, huh? You're certainly one of them.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-smuggywuggyuwuwuuwu.png">It's like... beating a nuzlocke deathless. Which I've never managed to do. But I'm sure this is what it feels like.</state>
                <state img="#-smuggywuggyuwuwuuwu.png">Finally! I'm better at another girl at something instead of being &lt;i&gt;extremely&lt;/i&gt; mediocre!</state>
                <state img="#-panic.png">&lt;i&gt;(Shit, I can't get too excited, I'll lose my focus...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-panic.png">&lt;i&gt;(Don't let the stress get to you, Nanoko! You can get through this, go home, and pretend like this was all some weird dream!)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-pose.png">It's nice that only one person loses per round here. Makes the odds &lt;i&gt;much&lt;/i&gt; more favorable.</state>
                <state img="#-niconii.png">&lt;i&gt;BOOM!&lt;/i&gt; Get got!</state>
                <state img="#-pose.png">Don't worry, ~name~. Losing isn't the end of the world. Take it from someone who's lost... a lot. In various games throughout her life, not just this one.</state>
                <state img="#-smuggywuggyuwuwuuwu.png">I'm not gonna beat myself up for staring. You came here, you knew what was up. And what's up is me looking at hot girls.</state>
                <state img="#-pose.png">So, ~name~... how's it feel to be beat by somebody who's only &lt;i&gt;kind of decent&lt;/i&gt; at poker? Is it embarrassing? &lt;i&gt;Humiliating, even?&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-horny.png">&lt;i&gt;(I'm pretty much... at eye level with her crotch... nice...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-neutral.png">Losing i-isn't actually that bad, ~name~.. m-might as well just strip everything and g-get on with it... hah...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">I-I can look away if you want... i-it might be kinda hard, though...</state>
                <state img="#-neutral.png">D-don't mind me, just... sh-show us your ass and titties and stuff...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-horny.png">&lt;i&gt;(Even when I'm not masturbating... ~name~ is still really cute...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-displeased.png">Bluh... of course all the cool stuff happens when I'm already down and out...</state>
                <state img="#-neutral.png">Um... s-sorry, it's just kinda hard to stay focused now that I've... y'know...</state>
                <state img="#-neutral.png">...H-huh? Oh, right. Game's still going.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="tie">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-fear.png">Uh... do we &lt;i&gt;all&lt;/i&gt; get naked now or something?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="nanoko_leon0" />
                <condition role="target" character="leon" stage="0" sayingMarker="nanoko02" />
                <state img="#-panic.png" marker="nanoko_leon1">W-what? I-I'm not worried! I-I'm just... having such a good time that I just &lt;i&gt;look&lt;/i&gt; like I'm fearing for my life!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="kamina" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-hmm.png">U-um... just... just give me a minute here...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="yuno_uno" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-panic.png" marker="nanoko_yuno1">&lt;i&gt;(SHIT, he saw me staring?!)&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;N-nothing! Don't worry about it! I was just, uh... you know, I've only ever played the online version of Uno. How much of that skill do you think would carry over to the physical version?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-displeased.png">Boo to that. Boo to your ~clothing~. Boo to your parents for raising such a pussy.</state>
                <state img="#-thinky.png">If I brought something like that to school with me, It'd probably get taken away because I kept fidgeting with it. Hell, not even my tie is safe from my grubby little fingers, it's starting to fray at the ends.</state>
                <state img="#-neutral.png">Getting more comfortable with this game is kind of a double-edged sword... mostly because it makes things like this &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; boring.</state>
                <state img="#-displeased.png">I know this is supposed to get me all pent up for later, but...</state>
                <state img="#-thinky.png">...Whatever. It'd be kinda hypocritical of me to complain, since I started with my tie.</state>
                <state img="#-hmm.png">&lt;i&gt;(I wonder how my villagers doing right now... I haven't opened that game in ages. The island's probably full of weeds and garbage...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-3">
                <state img="#-flustered.png">&lt;i&gt;(Now that I think about it, this is all just buildup for... hoo boy.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">&lt;i&gt;(Why is this still... kind of hot?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-panic.png" oneShotId="8">...S-so! Let's talk about something else! Some kid at my school got suspended for stealing an entire drinking fountain last week, isn't that crazy?</state>
                <state img="#-thinky.png">Right, right, you can't just whip your dick out right away... I keep forgetting that, for some reason.</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">Is it rude to bring stuff to do while you play? Like, u-um... I dunno. A game, or something? N-not that I think you're boring-!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-displeased.png">...Hey. Masturbating down here. Because apparently, you didn't notice.</state>
                <state img="#-neutral.png">Wh-whatever... I'll just keep thinking about... h-hah, wouldn't you like to know?</state>
                <state img="#-neutral.png">&lt;i&gt;(I guess it'd be different if it was somebody taking it off for you... fuck, I love small, intimate shit like that...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-neutral.png">Hah... boring...</state>
                <state img="#-neutral.png">You're such an idiot, ~name~...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-thinky.png">I just had one of the best orgasms of my life, and you're still taking off your ~clothing~. What a world we live in.</state>
                <state img="#-hmm.png">Not like it'd do me much good at this point anyways...</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png" oneShotId="10">&lt;i&gt;(That big box out back... Dad ordered more Funko Pops, didn't he? There's no way they sell as well as he says they do...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">&lt;i&gt;(Shit, what if I go pick up my clothes, and they're all covered in cum and other gunk? Do they have a place where you can wash your clothes here? I don't wanna go to school with cumstains on my shirt...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-panic.png">...Oh, y-yeah. That makes sense.&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;(Of course they're not gonna take everything off right away, you dumbass!)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">...I don't know what to say in this situation. Not because I'm scared, but because this is... s-surprisingly boring.</state>
                <state img="#-panic.png" oneShotId="6">I thought strip poker was... I dunno... a "get all your junk out right away" type of deal. N-not that I'm some kind of exhibitionist or anything! I'm just... maybe kind of a little bit stupid!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="kamina" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-excited.png">Wait-! &lt;i&gt;GALO! THE GAY FIREFIGHTER GUY!&lt;/i&gt; I knew i'd get it eventually!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-fear.png">L-listen, ~name~. Real life men won't talk to me, and I don't need that kind of treatment from you... my self-esteem is already in shambles.</state>
                <state img="#-panic.png">You're not doing that because I'm annoying you, right? If I'm annoying you can just tell me. &lt;i&gt;Please tell me. I genuinely can't tell...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-panic.png">&lt;i&gt;(Would he have stripped something bigger if I wasn't here? Is my very existence some kind of massive turn-off?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">Better put that somewhere you won't lose it... you know. Because it's so small. And stuff.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-horny.png">&lt;i&gt;(Would that be small enough... for him to put in my mouth and gag me with?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-neutral.png">Whatever... the crazy gay sex that's going on in my head right now is more interesting than you'll ever be, anyways...</state>
                <state img="#-thinky.png">Wh-, oh, great. I forgot what I was fantasizing about. And it wasn't even because of something good. Thanks for that...</state>
                <state img="#-neutral.png">Hmm...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-hmm.png">&lt;i&gt;(When was the last time I booted up my Tomodachi Life save? Weren't my Mii and Jotaro supposed to be having another kid?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">I'm going to become the Joker.</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">I'm hungry... th-that's not me hitting on you, by the way. I just forgot to eat before I came here.</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">&lt;i&gt;How did I fuck up this bad?&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-hmm.png">&lt;i&gt;(Actually, I'm the asshole here. I only came here with my tie and shoes to use as fodder. Bringing small, useless garbage is the real big brain play here.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-thinky.png">...I wonder where the best place to buy GBA parts is. Probably eBay, right? I'm running out of spare batteries.</state>
                <state img="#-thinky.png">I should've gotten something to eat before we started... I'd kill for some Bugles right now.</state>
                <state img="#-hmm.png">...Now that I think about it, it's kinda weird that the Wii U can't also play Gamecube games. It can play Wii games, and the Wii could play Gamecube games. They all use discs, so why didn't it carry over? I should mod that...</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">I used to be one of those really annoying "pick-me" girls, you know. None of the girls wanted to be my friend, so I tried really hard to be "one of the boys." It... didn't work out.</state>
                <state img="#-thinky.png">Sometimes I think about fucking off into a cabin in the woods with no wifi for the rest of my life... but then I wouldn't have anyone to talk about anime guys and their big fat nuts with.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="hu_tao" stage="0" sayingMarker="nanoko02" />
                <state img="#-wtf.png" marker="nanoko_hutao1">&lt;i&gt;H-HUH?&lt;/i&gt; What?! No! I-I was just trying to be nice! And I've already had enough near-death experiences for one lifetime, thank you very much!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="yukari" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-hmm.png">&lt;i&gt;(You know, I never had the skill or attention span or time needed to get into Touhou, but if THIS is what it's like?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="azami" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-wtf.png">&lt;i&gt;Shit, you're the Uzumaki girl!&lt;/i&gt; The one who's face gets eaten by her scar thing!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="kora" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-panic.png">O-oh, yeah, t-totally! I really like the way it accentuates your... ass?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="mari_setogaya" saidMarker="Nanoko_succubusQuestion_reply" />
                <state img="#-hmm.png" marker="nanoko_mari1">Oh, interesting... s-so, are blowjobs like spraying whipped cream directly into your mouth for you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-3">
                <state img="#-panic.png">&lt;i&gt;(Would it be weird if I asked her where she got that? That's what girls talk about together, right? Or is this not the right place to do that?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">Uh, I'm... really not sure what I'm supposed to say here...</state>
                <state img="#-neutral.png">Okay... makes sense. I-I won't complain...</state>
                <state img="#-neutral.png">&lt;i&gt;(I know I should get better at making eye contact, but it's easier said than done...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-panic.png">I guess it's less weird when I'm used to girls taking stuff off in front of me... e-except the girls in my class aren't trying to seduce me. N-not that I think you are! U-unless, you are...? Uh...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-confused.png">Should I buy more small accessories and stuff? My wardrobe's pretty limited, I spend most of my money on figures and console repair parts.</state>
                <state img="#-thinky.png">I used to think other girls were shallow for wearing tons of random accessories for no reason. Hot Topic wasn't selling Jojo themed jewlery back then, though.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">My school's dress code isn't really that strict... I could probably get away with wearing something like that.&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;(Then again, that would mean more people noticing my existence... not sure how I feel about that.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-hmm.png">I've still got some gift cards left over from Christmas... maybe I could buy myself some stuff. Stuff that won't just sit on my shelves and gather dust like my figures.</state>
                <state img="#-hmm.png">&lt;i&gt;(Do people still make those kandi bracelets? I could always give it a shot...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-confused.png">I-it's probably for the best that girls taking off accessories doesn't do it for me... ch-changing in the locker room is awkward enough as-is...</state>
                <state img="#-neutral.png">I-I guess you don't wanna end up down here like me... sucks to be you...</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">&lt;i&gt;(Man, I wanna buy a Super Sonico figure so bad... but I don't need Dad asking why I have figures of a girl with her tits half out...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-displeased.png">I'm gonna be finished by the time you're naked at this rate... u-unless I edge myself. But I don't think I'm allowed to stop once I start...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-pissed.png">I can't think of any funny insults to call you, so I'll just... &lt;i&gt;gahhhhhh.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-displeased.png">...?</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">Is murder legal in this dimension?&lt;br&gt;...Th-that was a joke, I swear. </state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">...Wow. I fucked up &lt;i&gt;hard.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-panic.png">...Oh, y-yeah. That makes sense.&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;(Of course they're not gonna take everything off right away, you dumbass!)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">...I don't know what to say in this situation. Not because I'm scared, but because this is... s-surprisingly boring.</state>
                <state img="#-panic.png" oneShotId="6">I thought strip poker was... I dunno... a "get all your junk out right away" type of deal. N-not that I'm some kind of exhibitionist or anything! I'm just... maybe kind of a little bit stupid!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="hu_tao" stage="1" sayingMarker="nanoko03" />
                <state img="#-fear.png" marker="nanoko_hutao2">A-and-... &lt;i&gt;oh.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;I guess that... that &lt;i&gt;is&lt;/i&gt; one benefit to being dead.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="yukari" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-fear.png">&lt;i&gt;(...I'll probably just watch a let's play or something. I'm super broke.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="azami" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-panic.png">W-wait, uh, I mean... hey, Azami! I've heard rumors about your town! Did you know that it's haunted by spirals and you're... &lt;i&gt;maybe&lt;/i&gt; gonna die if you don't leave?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-fear.png">...I-I just realized how few accessories I brought. I could have stalled you all out with my mood rings from middle school if I wasn't &lt;i&gt;STUPID.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">...Would that be tournament legal? &lt;i&gt;A-are&lt;/i&gt; there strip poker tournaments...?</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">This is just like Smash 4's EVO 2018 finals, right guys?&lt;br&gt;...D-do any of you even understand what I just said...?</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">...Maybe I &lt;i&gt;should&lt;/i&gt; have brought my 3DS with me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-displeased.png">You know what sucks? I've gotta watch anime legally if I wanna watch it in my living room. I mean, I &lt;i&gt;guess&lt;/i&gt; I could subscribe to Crunchyroll, but they never have the anime I actually &lt;i&gt;want&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-hmm.png">&lt;i&gt;(Does the local library have manga? Mostly old people hang out there, but there's gotta be at least one grandma out there who likes shonen or yaoi.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">&lt;i&gt;(Could I get away with stealing people's stuff here? Maybe I could pawn some stuff off as cosplay props... no. No, I'm not THAT desperate...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-hmm.png">&lt;i&gt;(I've been spending too much money on random garbage lately... I need to save up for a better computer. I'm not sure how much longer this one's gonna hang on for.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-displeased.png">...Dude, I could be &lt;i&gt;gaming.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-fear.png">&lt;i&gt;(I wonder if she'd let me sniff that... wh-, NO? What the hell is wrong with me?!)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-neutral.png">&lt;i&gt;(I wish my phone wasn't all the way over there in the pile... I could be reading all kinds of smut right now...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">I-I just need to channel my inner victorian peasant, and find it in me to masturbate to any single square inch of bare skin... &lt;i&gt;th-then&lt;/i&gt; I'll be satisfied...</state>
                <state img="#-wtf.png">W-wait, if you're taking that off, and I've already lost... &lt;i&gt;holy shit, I'm TERRIBLE at poker!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-displeased.png">...I'm gonna have to do this &lt;i&gt;again&lt;/i&gt; when I get home, aren't I? Because  this isn't satisfying in the slightest.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-calm.png">...I'm at a loss, actually. Not with you. With myself.</state>
                <state img="#-niconii.png">Wow! Go fuck yourself!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">...And I still have homework to do after this. Great.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">I don't know how you're gonna live with yourself after pulling a dick move like that when I'm like this, but, sure.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">...I should go to IHOP later.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-flustered.png">Y-yeah, this game would be... k-kind of unfair if we had to take everything off after one loss, wouldn't it?&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;(It'd be... kinda fun, though.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-thinky.png">A-at least it's not... I dunno. A ring, or something. Those shouldn't even count...</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">At least that exposes... &lt;i&gt;s-some&lt;/i&gt; amount of skin. Taking off anything that doesn't would be a dick move.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">Is that considered... fashionable where you're from? I only know how to dress well if I'm wearing my uniform...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-confused.png">How much stuff like that did you bring? How much stuff like that &lt;i&gt;should&lt;/i&gt; someone bring? Small enough to keep you covered, but not so small that you piss people off...</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">Do you wear stuff like that often? If I'm not in my uniform or at work, I usually just wear a t-shirt and pajama shorts.</state>
                <state img="#-thinky.png">I'm always wanting to buy more clothes, but I have to be &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; specific with fabrics and stuff. And I always have to cut the tags out of my shirts...</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">...It's kinda weird that we're all just throwing our stuff on the floor, y'know? The floor that people are constantly cumming and squirting and creaming onto? I assume they clean it regularly, but still.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Okay... okay... I-I can &lt;i&gt;kind&lt;/i&gt; of work with this...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">I-is it possible to take that off... &lt;i&gt;extra sexily, somehow...?&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-neutral.png">&lt;i&gt;(Maybe I can just... pretend he's taking off something bigger. And pretend I know what he looks like naked...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-displeased.png">D-dammit, I'm trying not to get distracted here...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-calm.png">I dunno how fun it is to just... &lt;i&gt;watch&lt;/i&gt;, and not be playing...</state>
                <state img="#-hmm.png">&lt;i&gt;(What if I just took a nap at one of those tables, and asked somebody to wake me up when someone loses again? I've slept naked before, it wouldn't be the first time...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">Ugh, I'm always really tired after I cum... I should've considered that before coming here.</state>
                <state img="#-thinky.png">...Is post-nut &lt;i&gt;boredom&lt;/i&gt; a thing? Because now that I'm out, everything feels really boring and slow. Or maybe I just have an iron deficiency.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_minor">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-flustered.png">&lt;i&gt;(Am I really so much of a degenerate that ~name~ taking off his ~clothing~ is enough to turn me on a little...?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">...S-sorry if I stare off into space, suddenly. It's a bad habit.</state>
                <state img="#-hmm.png" oneShotId="18">&lt;i&gt;(Maybe I could convince Dad to let me start up my own console repair business in the store... wait, no, focus!)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Y-yeah, just... put that over there.&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;(This was the wrong place to try and get better at talking to people...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-thinky.png">We're back in that weird period where nothing happens now, I guess...</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">I think I cummed out my last brain cell. I can't think of anything to say about your ~clothing~.</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">Was me masturbating not enough for you? Do I need to suck my own tit or something?</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">I thought I was out of the boring part by now...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Could you do me a favor and just... th-throw that at me? Just, bean me right in the face with it?</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">&lt;i&gt;(If I just stare hard enough, maybe I'll unlock some kinda chakra and develop x-ray vision...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Hah... man hot...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">&lt;i&gt;(Just the act of him taking off his clothes... is so hot...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-niconii.png">No point in dwelling on the small stuff, right? Because it's boring, and it's lame!</state>
                <state img="#-smuggywuggyuwuwuuwu.png">Here I was, thinking I'd get absolutely smoked the second the game started. And now, I'm managing to get people out of some sorta-maybe important stuff.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">...I should &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; dust off my figures when I get home.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">Would it be rude to listen to music while we play? Like, with headphones. It's kinda noisy in here, it's starting to give me a headache...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="supernova" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">Uhhhh, Supernova, right? Cool name, by the way. Do you mind if I ask what your whole... &lt;i&gt;deal&lt;/i&gt; is?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="sannytess" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="sannyko2">Do you guys model for Wikipedia or something? Because I swear I’ve seen you on an article somewhere. Can’t remember which, though…</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="sannytess" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-hmm.png" marker="sannyko5">I mean, I know &lt;i&gt;why&lt;/i&gt; I can't think of it. When I go on Wikipedia, it's always when I'm half asleep and a little delirious.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="sakura" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-fear.png" marker="sakurastrippingmakeup">I guess you had to take off your makeup at some-... uh.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-fear.png">Being "not like other girls" isn't as fun as I thought it'd be when I was younger... I'm not cute like you. I-I mean, I don't have cute clothes like you!</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">&lt;i&gt;(I don't think I've ever gone on a shopping trip with other girls before... I feel like I've missed out on a crucial part of my adolescence.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">S-so... where'd you buy that? O-or, I guess, &lt;i&gt;"did you buy that"&lt;/i&gt; is a more appropriate question... I don't know your life...</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">&lt;i&gt;(Wait, why am I wasting my time in an interdimensional nexus point playing POKER? I could write a whole essay on this place... actually, nevermind. People already think I'm insane.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-fear.png">H-hey, can I go wash my hands real quick? My hand's all sticky now, and it's driving me insane.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">I don't know if it's just the post-nut fuzzies talking, but... you still look &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; hot, even when you're just taking off your ~clothing~...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Hah... I am &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; bad at this game.</state>
                <state img="#-hmm.png">&lt;i&gt;(Could I get away with buying another vibrator? I'm already running out of places to hide the ones I have...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-horny.png">H-hopefully this doesn't sound creepy, but... I-I think you could be a stripper if you really wanted to...</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">W-wait... th-this won't turn me into some kind of pervert who g-gets off on watching girls undress, right? I-I mean, in situations where it's not a-acceptable or expected...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">I-I wish I was as pretty as you... I mean this in both the gay way, and the "I have low self-esteem" way...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">I'm not even upset, I-I'm just happy I get to look at pretty girls... in any state of undress...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-thinky.png">Don't take it personally if I'm not looking at you. I'm just... &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; bad at paying attention. In general.</state>
                <state img="#-hmm.png">&lt;i&gt;(Should I look around this place some more after this game is done? I doubt we're the only people in the building right now, maybe I can meet more people that way.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-hmm.png">&lt;i&gt;(If I end up being friends with anyone here... how would I keep in contact with them? I don't think you can text interdimensionally, and that's only if they DO have a phone... dammit.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-thinky.png">How good is the wifi here? Most of my gachas only work with an internet connection...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_minor">
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="azami" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-fear.png">&lt;i&gt;(Ohhhh, that's no good.)&lt;/i&gt; ...You're not lookin' too good, Azami. Maybe you should, uh... have a sit down. Drink something. Hydration's important.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="supernova" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-fear.png">Like, with the wormhole-portal-travel stuff and the... being completely unrecognizable? Just, explain everything. I'm very confused and frankly, a little frightened.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="sannytess" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-panic.png" marker="sannyko3">Oh, thank god. I would've looked like a dumbass if you didn't.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="sannytess" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-hmm.png" marker="sannyko6">Okay, uh... is it... some kind of hentai?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="sakura" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-panic.png" marker="sakurastrippedmakeup">&lt;i&gt;Wow! Geez, ain't that wacky? Wasn't expecting to see that tonight! Not at all!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-horny.png">&lt;i&gt;W-wow, ~name~...&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;...That's it. That's all I have to say.</state>
                <state img="#-neutral.png">I should buy more yuri manga...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">C-could you take it off... &lt;i&gt;slower&lt;/i&gt;, next time...?</state>
                <state img="#-neutral.png">&lt;i&gt;(I wonder what it'd be like... to be with another girl... and undress each other...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-confused.png">People always say that if you want something done right, you've gotta do it yourself. And nobody else is gonna write the extremely specific doujn I'm looking for...</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">Wait, I just realized! I get paid soon! I can buy that Miku figure I've been wanting!&lt;br&gt;...O-or I can keep saving up for a new computer. Like a responsible person...</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">Yeah, that settles it... I'm getting new clothes next time I get the chance. I can't remember the last time I went shopping for them.</state>
                <state img="#-hmm.png">&lt;i&gt;(I know you can de-yellow plastic using UV lights, but you have to have a whole set-up to do it. Maybe that'll finally get me to clean my room.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">Did you know that the Wii's only around 50% more powerful than the Gamecube? I guess that's sorta admirable, considering how most companies prioritize processing power over a good selection of games...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-flustered.png">&lt;i&gt;(Wait, what if ~name~ notices I'm staring at her? What if she's not into girls? What if she thinks I'm a creep? She totally thinks I'm a creep, doesn't she?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Does... a-anyone wanna hear some fun video game history? Because I have... a lot of knowledge that I really don't need...</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">&lt;i&gt;(...I wonder if anyone else here knows that the Nintendo PlayStation almost existed.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png" oneShotId="22">Did the auction for that original Game &amp; Watch end yet...?&lt;br&gt;O-oh, sorry, I was just... thinking about... a thing...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-hmm.png">&lt;i&gt;(Is there a market for people who need their Virtual Boys repaired? Do enough people have one for it to exist?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">I-, dammit, I'm gonna have to do laundry when I get home, aren't I?</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">When I get home, I'm gonna hunker down and read every poker guide I can find. Because clearly, you know something I don't.</state>
                <state img="#-pose.png">Eh, it's a little too late to pretend I don't think you're hot as hell, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_major">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Y-you're not even naked yet, but I'm still...</state>
                <state img="#-neutral.png">You &lt;i&gt;r-really&lt;/i&gt; know how to treat a lady, ~name~...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">T-take that off slowly, ~name~,,, I-I wanna savor it as long as possible...</state>
                <state img="#-neutral.png">I-I guess... it's not really possible to &lt;i&gt;lose&lt;/i&gt; at this game...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-wtf.png">&lt;i&gt;Wh-what? While I'm still fully clothed?!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-wtf.png">Wh-what's going on? My luck is usually &lt;i&gt;WAY&lt;/i&gt; worse than this!</state>
                <state img="#-wtf.png">Th-this feels... &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; unfair...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-3">
                <state img="#-flustered.png">I-I thought this game would be scarier when I was doing &lt;i&gt;worse...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">I-I guess this is my reward for being... halfway decent at poker...</state>
                <state img="#-smuggywuggyuwuwuuwu.png">H-hah! Yes! Strip for your master!&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;(Is he falling for it...?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">I-I'm not usually wearing my skirt or spats when I watch people do this... o-on the internet, that is...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-excited.png">&lt;i&gt;Yeahhh, baby, that's what I've been waiting for! That's what it's all about!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Yeah, I think all those losses are about to be worth it...</state>
                <state img="#-smuggywuggyuwuwuuwu.png">I don't know about you guys, but I am &lt;i&gt;very&lt;/i&gt; excited to ogle some half-naked men.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">I am looking disrespectfully.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-smuggywuggyuwuwuuwu.png">Heh, looks like you're on a one way trip to the same floor I was on just a minute ago.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">And to think, I was worried I'd regret coming here...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Honestly, you could take off a single shoe and I'd still be &lt;i&gt;super&lt;/i&gt; horny right now.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Go on...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_major">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-panic.png">I don't know if I'm horny, or if I'm having a panic attack...</state>
                <state img="#-panic.png">&lt;i&gt;(I'm already freaking the fuck out! What am I supposed to do when he's actually naked?!)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">M-my heart's in my throat, I feel like I'm on a roller coaster... e-except masturbating on roller coasters is generally frowned upon.</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">Y-you get so used to people having clothes on, you forget what the goal of this game actually is...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-horny.png">&lt;i&gt;(He only took off his ~clothing~, but... I'm already so goddamn horny...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">&lt;i&gt;(Being such a degenerate's starting to bite me in the ass... I don't know how I'm gonna stay focused long enough to get him naked.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-panic.png">S-so! Uh... those old GBA SP models without backlights. What's the deal with those? Why'd they think that was acceptable?</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">&lt;i&gt;(Focus, Nanoko! He isn't even naked yet!)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Y-you're cool with me staring, right? Right?</state>
                <state img="#-neutral.png">C-can you keep losing, please? For me?</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Y-you know, I'm so pale, that if you spanked me, it'd leave a &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; obvious  mark... I-I'm just putting that out there...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">I-if you need somewhere to put that, you can always stuff it in my mouth...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">I fucking... &lt;i&gt;love&lt;/i&gt; objectifying men...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-horny.png">...Yeah. Coming here was a good idea.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">I don't know how I'm ever gonna go back to normal porn after this...</state>
                <state img="#-panic.png">I-I'm trying to think of cool trivia to share in-between rounds, but... my brain's a little pre-occupied.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Don't mind me... just stashing that in the spank bank for later.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_major">
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="yukari" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-excited.png">Oh boy, here we go! MILF titty central, here we-!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-flustered.png">M-making you strip like this while I'm fully clothed... i-it's kind of like I'm at a strip club...&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;(Well, I mean... I kind of am, I guess.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">I-it's kind of early for that, right?&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;(There's no way I'm really that good at poker...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-panic.png">Sh-shouldn't I have stripped something at this point? You're not going easy on me, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-3">
                <state img="#-flustered.png">&lt;i&gt;(Watching someone like ~name~ take off her ~clothing~... I'm not nearly cool enough to be here...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">I-I don't know if I'm scared, or aroused... scaroused, maybe...</state>
                <state img="#-panic.png">I-I've only seen girls do this in the locker room before... o-or in porn.</state>
                <state img="#-panic.png">H-honestly, I kinda hate when porn jumpcuts to the actors being naked... watching people undress is just as hot as-...&lt;br&gt;...I should stop talking.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-shy.png">Just putting it out there, ~name~... I wish I was as pretty as you.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">My chest is throbbing with anticipation... my throb is chesting, even...</state>
                <state img="#-panic.png">I d-don't know if it's obvious, but... I'm not used to girls undressing &lt;i&gt;for&lt;/i&gt; me...</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">&lt;i&gt;(I wonder what it'd be like if I was the one undressing her... nwgh.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-displeased.png">You know what kinda sucks about being bi? Whenever I see a pretty girl, I never know if I wanna fuck her, or if I just wanna &lt;i&gt;be&lt;/i&gt; her...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">If I ever find out who invented girls, I-I'm gonna track them down and give them the sloppiest toppy known to man...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">&lt;i&gt;(I'm gonna have to go on a striptease video binge after this...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-neutral.png">Girls have such pretty skin... th-that maybe makes me sound like a serial killer, b-but I'm just saying what I'm thinking...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Is this a win for feminism? I think so. Because I'm a female, and I'm having a &lt;i&gt;great&lt;/i&gt; time.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">&lt;i&gt;Girls... hot... wanna kiss 'em...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-smuggywuggyuwuwuuwu.png">I'm both proud &lt;i&gt;and&lt;/i&gt; horny right now. All in all, a pretty good combination.</state>
                <state img="#-smuggywuggyuwuwuuwu.png">You and me, ~name~? We're not so different. We're both bad at this game.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_major">
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="yukari" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-fear.png"> GOD DAMN IT ALL TO HELL.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Most eroge just teleport the girl's clothes off, so this... is a nice change of pace from what I'm used to.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">I-I would've liked that more if I were still masturbating, but... eh. I'll just do it again when I get home.</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">I'm trying to multitask and figure out what my next project should be after I finish fixing this GBA SP, but... between the post-nut clarity and you doing... that, it's kinda hard...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">It's rude not to watch... not that I'm complaining.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-horny.png">&lt;i&gt;(Maybe if I just... rub my thighs together... nobody'll notice...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">I-I feel like one of those shitty anime perverts who peeps on girls in the hot springs... a-and I like to think I'm at &lt;i&gt;least&lt;/i&gt; better than that...</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">Th-this feels like when my mom almost found my vibrator drawer... s-so, kind of terrifying, and vaguely related to sex in some way.</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">A-at least you aren't hitting me over the head and calling me a pervert and a baka... m-makes me feel a little bit better about my current situation.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-fear.png">&lt;i&gt;(Wait, what if this game causes me to have some kinda pavlovian response to getting changed with other girls? Oh, fuck...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">S-so, um... are you busy after this, ~name~? N-not a purely sexual thing, I just wanted to know if you wanted to... hang out, or something...&lt;br&gt;...I-it could be a sexual thing if you want it to be, though...</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">U-uh... I'm really bad at flirting, so if you can just pretend I said something hot and go "wow, Nanoko", that'd be nice...</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">Th-there's something kinda... &lt;i&gt;intimate&lt;/i&gt; about all this buildup and waiting, isn't there?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-horny.png">&lt;i&gt;(If I'm this turned on just from watching her take off her ~clothing~, I don't even wanna know what I'll be like once she's naked...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-neutral.png">Thanks for the gold, kind stranger...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">I-I don't wanna be demanding, but... c-could you do that a little... &lt;i&gt;sexier&lt;/i&gt; next time? Y-you're already sexy, but... I-I'm a hopeless degenerate who'll never be satisfied, alright?</state>
                <state img="#-neutral.png">I-it's like watching a camgirl strip... e-except I'm also masturbating for you... s-so we're &lt;i&gt;both&lt;/i&gt; the camgirl...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-horny.png">It's good that masturbating helps me relax, I can watch this without... I dunno. Dying.</state>
                <state img="#-smuggywuggyuwuwuuwu.png">Yeah, what can I say? I'm just so hot, men can't help themselves around me.</state>
                <state img="#-thinky.png">Normally I've gotta spam click to see this... well, I guess masturbating is its own kind of spam clicking.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">U-um, you know, ~name~... I'm pretty tired after all that, and I could use a pillow...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-wtf.png">&lt;i&gt;I'M GONNA SEE IT! I'M GONNA SEE A SHIRTLESS MAN! AND I DON'T KNOW WHAT EMOTION I SHOULD BE FEELING RIGHT NOW SO I'M JUST GONNA CROSS THAT BRIDGE WHEN WE GET TO IT!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">I-I'm not really sure if I prefer men's chests or women's chests... I-I guess this is a good way to find out...</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">S-so, um... my favorite part of a guy's body is the chest, most of the time... j-just warning you in advance in case I start getting unreasonable...</state>
                <state img="#-panic.png">I wonder... do guys compare chest sizes like girls do? N-not that I've ever done that!&lt;br&gt;...O-okay, maybe a few times... b-but only because the other girls roped me into it!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-excited.png">Hah! &lt;i&gt;Titty time!&lt;/i&gt; People might think titty time is only for girls, but I beg to differ!</state>
                <state img="#-smuggywuggyuwuwuuwu.png">My mom would probably get on my case about not waiting until I'm married to the guy to see this... but she's not here right now, obviously.</state>
                <state img="#-pose.png">A man's chest... &lt;i&gt;"nature's bongos"&lt;/i&gt;, some might call them.&lt;br&gt;Okay, only I call them that. But more people should!</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">Time to burn a hole into your chest with my eyes!&lt;br&gt;...I was trying to flirt. I don't know what happened there, I'm sorry.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-horny.png">&lt;i&gt;F-fuck yes,&lt;/i&gt; this is &lt;i&gt;EXACTLY&lt;/i&gt; what I wanted...</state>
                <state img="#-neutral.png">Masturbating to half-naked men... it's like a normal ~weekday~ for me, &lt;i&gt;but so much better...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-neutral.png">F-forgive me if I die of joy right here... I-I'm just really into men's tits...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">C-can't find stuff like this on Rule 34...&lt;br&gt;...I guess you can get &lt;i&gt;close&lt;/i&gt;, but it's not as &lt;i&gt;real&lt;/i&gt;...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-horny.png">It's kinda unfair that people with boobs can't be shirtless in public because it's "too sexual"... I'm just as turned on looking at you as I would be if I was looking at giant mommy milkers.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Dammit, ~name~... don't make me wanna go again. I'm gonna give myself carpal tunnel...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">It's a good thing I don't have to focus on the game anymore...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">It's about damn time...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-panic.png">&lt;i&gt;AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA-&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-wtf.png">&lt;i&gt;I WASN'T READY! I WASN'T READY!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">I don't think I've ever fainted before... th-there's a first time for everything, I guess.</state>
                <state img="#-panic.png">&lt;i&gt;(Normal men are never this hot! Why are all fictional men so GODDAMN attractive ALL THE TIME?!)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-flustered.png">&lt;i&gt;(He'd... let me touch it if I asked, right?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-wtf.png">&lt;i&gt;It'd be cool if guys could lactate...&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;H-huh? I DIDN'T SAY ANYTHING!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I'd say your chest was "poggers", but... I-I wanna keep &lt;i&gt;some&lt;/i&gt; amount of my sex appeal...</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">&lt;i&gt;(I should probably start working out more, but... my boobs would probably keep getting in the way...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-horny.png">C-can I bury my face in it? Please?</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Y-you could probably date any girl you wanted... p-please tell me I'm one of them...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">I-is it possible to dry-hump somebody's chest? I-is that a thing?</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">I-is your chest really sensitive, ~name~? M-mine is... y-you could come over here and see for yourself, if you wanted...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-wtf.png">W-WAIT, NO! I haven't earned this yet!</state>
                <state img="#-wtf.png">&lt;i&gt;THE FUCK?!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-wtf.png">A-are you sure you don't have anything left? I-I mean, I'm still fully dressed!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-shy.png">Better late than never, y'know?</state>
                <state img="#-smuggywuggyuwuwuuwu.png">I didn't just show you mine, I gave a &lt;i&gt;full scientific demonstration.&lt;/i&gt; So you better make this good, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-pose.png">So &lt;i&gt;this&lt;/i&gt; is the law of equivalent exchange...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-horny.png">&lt;i&gt;Fu-uck, this is just what I've been needing...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">As long as you don't have a literal chode, I-I'll be happy with whatever you pull out...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">&lt;i&gt;Come onnn&lt;/i&gt;, just show me already...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-horny.png">I  mean... I-I can kind of already get a vibe for how big it is through your ~clothing~...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">There's a lot of figures out there where the clothes are so tight, you can kinda see the girl's junk through it... not so much for guys.&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;(They should make figures of guys in bunnysuits...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-niconii.png">Yeah! Whip it out!&lt;br&gt;...Th-that wasn't too much, right...?</state>
                <state img="#-smuggywuggyuwuwuuwu.png">And to think, people pay to watch camboys and go to strip clubs... and here I am, about to see ~name~'s dick for free.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-3">
                <state img="#-flustered.png">I-I'll look away if you want... w-wait, why would you want that? You came here to show off, right? &lt;i&gt;Right?&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">I-is... you being here enough permission to look? I-I don't like making people uncomfortable...</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">I-I know I can be kind of a perv sometimes, but I'm not the kinda perv who sneaks into the boy's locker room at school... th-that's just a roundabout way of saying I'm not used to this.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_small_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-horny.png">I don't get why people think small dicks are worse than useless... maybe I'm just desperate.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">&lt;i&gt;Just from eyeballing the length... and where I'm pretty sure my g-spot is...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-horny.png">D-dude, I don't even care about size at this point, &lt;i&gt;I just need SOMETHING inside me...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Th-there's a lot of perks to smaller dicks... like being to fit them down your throat if you haven't had as much practice...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Don't worry, ~name~... I'm not picky. I-I'm open to pretty much anything, actually.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-shy.png">Size is relative, y'know? You might be "small" for most people, but you could be hung like a horse for... I dunno. A goblin? Or just a normal, human short person.&lt;br&gt;...I'm slightly below average height. Just putting it out there.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">I-I'm more into &lt;i&gt;"so big it presses against your cervix"&lt;/i&gt; stuff, but... that's just a preference. Not a requirement.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">&lt;i&gt;(Not big enough for me to paizuri him, but I'll make it work...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Uh... I guess country boys make do, and all that.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">H-hey, don't worry, it could be worse! You could have no dick, just balls!</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">Um... a-are you into SPH, ~name~? Since you chose to play this knowing you were... I-I'm not good at being dominant, but I can &lt;i&gt;try...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_medium_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-horny.png">I might be finished, but... w-we can always go somewhere &lt;i&gt;after&lt;/i&gt; the game's finished.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">I already lose, but I don't think that stops me from lending a hand if someone needs it... or my mouth.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">I-I might not have any actual real-life experience, but... I watch a &lt;i&gt;lot&lt;/i&gt; of porn. And I'm a visual learner...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-horny.png">I can throw my legs over my head really easily... I-I've been practicing in case someone ever wanted to fold me in half and fuck me that way...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">D-do you think you'd be able to game while a girl's riding you, ~name~? Wanna find out...?</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">I-I'm pretty good at multitasking, ~name~... so if you ever wanted to bend me over and use me like a fleshlight while I watch anime or play games or something... I'd be more than willing.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">N-nobody asked, but I have a &lt;i&gt;surprising&lt;/i&gt; amount of stamina for a girl who sits around and does basically nothing in her spare time...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-flustered.png">U-um... am I your type, by any chance? I-I know I'm nothing special, but...</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">S-so, um... d-did you play this just for fun, or are you trying to... &lt;i&gt;meet someone?&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">&lt;i&gt;(I wonder what it'd be like to play something while getting fucked from behind... )&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;...H-heh.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-horny.png">&lt;i&gt;(I'm not naked yet, but... maybe he's into thighjobs.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">&lt;i&gt;(Maybe I should just throw and-... huh?! No! I'm not gonna look like an idiot just for some dick!)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">&lt;i&gt;(If I start getting wet... they won't be able to see it through my spats, right?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_large_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Fuck it, I didn't see any kind of official rule saying I'm &lt;i&gt;not&lt;/i&gt; allowed to cum twice... or get bent over the table while the game's still going.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Some people bring sex toys for when they lose, right? Because if you didn't bring one... well, I'm available.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">It'd take a while before you could push in all the way... b-but that just makes it better, right?</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Do you know if it's big enough to make someone's stomach bulge when you push it in all the way?&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;...Do you wanna find out?&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Th-there's no rule saying you can't just... wreck me right here, ~name~. As long as you don't cum... unless you don't care about winning anymore.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">F-for the record, I &lt;i&gt;am&lt;/i&gt; on birth control... so don't be shy, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">I-it'd probably hurt if I tried to take that whole thing... joke's on you, though. I'm into that shit.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Y-you'd probably be able to get &lt;i&gt;dangerously&lt;/i&gt; close to my cervix if you went all the way in... it'd hurt, but in a good way...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-horny.png">This might be TMI, but... for me, feeling yourself get stretched out is always the best part.&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;(And you look like you're more than capable of that.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">D-do you ever have problems with it... not fitting?&lt;br&gt;...Do you want to... &lt;i&gt;not have that problem?&lt;/i&gt; Because... I'm not going anywhere.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">U-um... does anyone else ever try and see how far back they can get their toothbrush before they gag while they brush their teeth? You know... for practice?</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">&lt;i&gt;(Hopefully ~name~ prefers anal and vaginal over oral... I dunno if my gag reflex can handle all that.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-flustered.png">...Hoo boy.</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">&lt;i&gt;(I'm pretty sure I have a vibrator that's around that size...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">I-I'm...&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;...Pretty sure I could take that whole thing.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">&lt;i&gt;(Of course his dick is big! What author or animator gonna create a whole character just to give them a mid dick?)&lt;/i&gt; </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition filter="huge_penis" role="target" />
                <state img="#-horny.png">&lt;i&gt;(...Yeah. I can take that.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">...Well, my mother didn't raise a quitter.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-flustered.png">I-I'm not usually allowed to watch other girls do this... let alone &lt;i&gt;encouraged...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">&lt;i&gt;(Hopefully it's not too obvious that I'm staring...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">D-don't worry, I can already kind of tell how big they are... o-or I can pretend that I don't! Whatever you want!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-horny.png">U-um... you'd... let me touch them, right? If I asked? It's fine if you wouldn't, but you miss 100% of the shots you don't take.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">D-don't be afraid, alright? I'm not super happy with how big my boobs are, but I still managed to do... all that.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">&lt;i&gt;(I can't look away... I've reached peak monkey brain...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-neutral.png">I-I normally prefer men's chests, b-but that doesn't mean I'm &lt;i&gt;not&lt;/i&gt; excited for this... far from it...</state>
                <state img="#-neutral.png">&lt;i&gt;(I've always wanted to press my chest up against another girl's... no matter how big her's are...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Oh, thank god... I n-need a &lt;i&gt;lot&lt;/i&gt; more than just your cleavage right now...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-pose.png">A wise man once said, &lt;i&gt;"I love your titties, because they prove I can focus on two things at once."&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Yeah... no point in acting like I'm not excited for this.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">I used to not understand why guys in anime were so desperate to look at titties... then I saw some titties for myself. &lt;i&gt;I know now.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">I... made it obvious that I'm into girls too, right?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_small_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-displeased.png">~name~, if anyone ever makes fun of you for being flat, just remember that I'm suffering from severe back pain before I'm even finished with high school. &lt;i&gt;You're&lt;/i&gt; the lucky one here.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">&lt;i&gt;(It's hard to find art of girls with small chests that doesn't make them look like infants... but maybe I should look harder.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Maybe I should broaden my porn horizons...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-horny.png">S-so... how do you feel about asymmetrical docking?</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Don't be jealous, ~name~... because I think you look &lt;i&gt;great.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">If a tittymonster like me likes how you look... that's gotta count for something, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-horny.png">I-I've been taking small tits for granted... you're &lt;i&gt;super&lt;/i&gt; hot...</state>
                <state img="#-neutral.png">A-anyone who doesn't like small tits is stupid... shallow... dumb... &lt;i&gt;very dumb...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">S-small chests are more sensitive, right...?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-flustered.png">&lt;i&gt;(I didn't think I was into small chests, but ~name~... kind of makes it work?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-thinky.png">I remember when my chest was that small... d-don't take sleeping on your chest for granted, okay?</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">&lt;i&gt;(What's the tag for that, again...? Asymmetrical docking?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-hmm.png">&lt;i&gt;(I've seen art of men with bigger chests than her...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_medium_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-panic.png">Y-yep! Still bisexual! Not that there was any doubt!</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">Th-that's probably the size I'd wanna be at... s-small enough to not be annoying, but big enough to... s-still  be boobs.</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">&lt;i&gt;(Why am I jealous of boobs smaller than mine?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-horny.png">&lt;i&gt;Now I know how a slip-n-slide feels.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Even if I'm still a virgin when I walk out of this place... it was &lt;i&gt;so&lt;/i&gt; worth it.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Heh... what if we fucked on that one Garfield dark ride?&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;...And we were both girls?&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Th-thank &lt;i&gt;god&lt;/i&gt; that "no touching" rule isn't real... I wanna grab those things so &lt;i&gt;fucking&lt;/i&gt; bad...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">&lt;i&gt;(If I had a girlfriend, I'd be able to grab and suck on her tits whenever she'd let me... and I'd let her do the same to me...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">I-I've always loved the idea of feeling someone up while they're doing whatever it is they do in their free time... a-and yours look &lt;i&gt;p-perfectly&lt;/i&gt; grabbing-sized...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">I-I just wanna get fucked, and then rest my head in some boobs once we're done... is that really too much for a girl to ask for?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-panic.png">I-is it weird that I sometimes wish my boobs were smaller? N-not enough to want a breast reduction, more of a, &lt;i&gt;"it'd be more convenient, I guess."&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-panic.png">&lt;i&gt;(Now's a good chance to try and be more forward...)&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;...Oh, shit, the next round's starting. Fuck.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">&lt;i&gt;(It'd be nice to hold someone from behind and just... hold their titty. It'd keep my hands warm, and I'd be holding a titty.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_large_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="kora" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-horny.png">Holy-, does &lt;i&gt;every&lt;/i&gt; Xenob-, uh... does every blade have massive honkers, or is it just you, Pyra, and Mythra?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-smuggywuggyuwuwuuwu.png">If it's true that flat is justice, I want a world full of crime.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Call it &lt;i&gt;"having a preference for large breasts"&lt;/i&gt; all you like... I call it &lt;i&gt;"having fucking eyes."&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">...I-I'm so normal. I'm being so normal right now.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Is this your way of trying to make me lose? Because... it's probably gonna work.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-panic.png">It's not weird that I've... masturbated to some of my figures, right? N-not &lt;i&gt;ON&lt;/i&gt; them, obviously! And definitely not &lt;i&gt;WITH&lt;/i&gt; them, do you have any idea how expensive those things are?!</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">I don't know how I'm ever gonna masturbate &lt;i&gt;without&lt;/i&gt; thinking of those ever again...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">It'd probably make ~player~ &lt;i&gt;nuts&lt;/i&gt; if we pressed our boobs together, ~name~... wanna give it a try?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-horny.png">&lt;i&gt;Heh... tig 'ol biddies...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">&lt;i&gt;(I just wanna hold them... suck on them... bury my face in them... get suffocated within an inch of my life in them...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Do... d-do you ever get tired of carrying those, ~name~? &lt;i&gt;Because I'd be more than happy to give you a hand... or both of them.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-flustered.png">&lt;i&gt;(How am I supposed to act cool with those things in front of me?!)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">&lt;i&gt;(I shouldn't be able to look at those for free...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">S-so, um... do you... &lt;i&gt;also&lt;/i&gt; have mild scoliosis? I'm just curious.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="azami" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-wtf.png">&lt;i&gt;(SHIT. Is it impossible for me to save her or something? Is this one of those "the timeline will always correct itself" deals?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <condition filter="huge_breasts" role="target" />
                <state img="#-wtf.png">H-how has your back not snapped in half yet?! I can barely carry these things around without my back hurting!</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">I-I thought breasts that big would look weird in real life, but they're...&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;(HOT!)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7 9">
                <condition filter="huge_breasts" role="target" />
                <state img="#-horny.png">Mommy? Sorry, mommy? Sorry, mommy? Sorry, mommy? Sorry, mommy? Sorry, mommy? Sorry, mommy? Sorry, mommy? Sorry-</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">&lt;i&gt;(...What's a socially acceptable way to ask someone if they lactate?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <condition filter="huge_breasts" role="target" />
                <state img="#-horny.png">Y-you'd think that having big boobs myself would turn me off from the idea of massive anime titties... you'd also be &lt;i&gt;very&lt;/i&gt; wrong.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="sannytess" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-fear.png" marker="sannyko8">Longer and... oh. Oh fuck. I just got it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-fear.png">&lt;i&gt;Hhhhhhhhhhhhh.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">&lt;i&gt;(I'm more of a boobs person than an ass person, but still...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">&lt;i&gt;(I'm usually focused on a girl's boobs when I'm looking at porn, not...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-horny.png">I should probably be mad that you're only taking off your ~clothing~ when I've already lost, but I'm filled with too many gay thoughts to care.</state>
                <state img="#-panic.png">I mean... I-I already gave you a &lt;i&gt;very good look&lt;/i&gt; of everything I have to offer, so... c-could you do the same for me?</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">Dammit, if I was better at poker, I would've been able to think about you doing this when I inevitably lost. I blew my load too early. Literally.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-horny.png">&lt;i&gt;(What I wouldn't give to be pulling that off of her myself...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">&lt;i&gt;(I wish she was hovering over my face while she did that...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-neutral.png">Hah... n-need any help with that...?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-flustered.png">P-pretty much all vaginas look the same when you're standing up, but...</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">I... I just now realized that underwear is like a bra for your ass. </state>
                <state img="#-panic.png">I'm not used to looking at &lt;i&gt;bare&lt;/i&gt; ass... o-or any ass, for that matter! I don't stare at girls's asses! Definitely not!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="azami" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">...Nice. I've watched two people die in front of me in two years. Go me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="sannytess" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-panic.png" marker="sannyko9">...Shit. Guess I'm into girldick now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" oneShotId="1">
                <condition filter="hairy" role="target" />
                <state img="#-thinky.png">It was only a few decades ago that huge bushes were the norm... crazy, the passage of time.</state>
                <state img="#-thinky.png">I'd probably give up on shaving, but then it'd rub up against my spats and be really uncomfortable...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7" oneShotId="3">
                <condition filter="catfolk" role="target" />
                <state img="#-smuggywuggyuwuwuuwu.png">Well, this sure brings a new meaning to &lt;i&gt;What's New, Pussycat.&lt;/i&gt; Wahoo.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-horny.png">...Legalize eating ass.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">I don't get why people compare vaginas to flowers, honestly... they're more like venus flytraps. &lt;i&gt;Because... they ensnare things... and are generally way cooler than any shitty flower could ever be...&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;...This analogy isn't working.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">M-may I slap it? Once...?</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Rhythm based gacha games may have given me a mild gambling addiction... but they also gave me &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; good finger dexterity.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-horny.png">God, just, fucking... &lt;i&gt;use my face as a chair, pls.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">H-how desperate are you to get laid tonight, ~name~? Desperate enough to consider me as an option?</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Wh-when I was a kid, I used to practice and see how long I could hold my breath for fun... wanna see if it paid off...?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-flustered.png">&lt;i&gt;(Dammit! Just when I was starting to get my shit together!)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-panic.png">S-so, um... asking for no reason in particular. Is scissoring actually a thing, or is it just in porn?</state>
                <state img="#-panic.png">&lt;i&gt;(What would happen if I offered to eat someone out, but then I was really bad at it? You only get better at things if you practice, but how am I supposed to recover from the shame of eating pussy badly?!)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-wtf.png">Dammit, why'd I have to get &lt;i&gt;"pussy pussy pussy marijuana"&lt;/i&gt; stuck in my head &lt;i&gt;NOW?&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">...It's moments like these that make me realize there are &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; no sexy words for vagina. I mean, there's pussy, but that feels objectifying and also kind of stupid...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">&lt;i&gt;(I wonder what it'd look like... if she spread herself...)&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;H-huh? I'm fine!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_stripping">
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="anatoly" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-fear.png" marker="nanoko_anatoly1">Uh... hm. W-well, my main issue right &lt;i&gt;now&lt;/i&gt; is that whenever I try and boil any kind of noodles, the water always boils over no matter how many times I check on it. And boiling noodles is the &lt;i&gt;only&lt;/i&gt; cooking related thing I can do reliably.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_stripped">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="ms.fortune" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-wtf.png" marker="nadia_sonohead">&lt;i&gt;JESUS FUCKING-!&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;(I knew that was coming, and it STILL scared the shit out of me!)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="mari_setogaya" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-fear.png" marker="nanoko_mari2">Honestly... I-I probably would if I didn't have to share the same can with my parents. Otherwise, it's just unsanitary.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-panic.png">I-I mean, it feels kinda early for this, but... I-I'm not complaining, that's for sure!</state>
                <state img="#-panic.png">I-I've never had a guy masturbate for me before today... wh-which isn't that surprising, now that I think about it. Th-this is kind of a niche and obscure situation to be in...</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">Time for you to make like Shinji and... um. Yeah, I just made this a million times more awkward, didn't I?&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;(Don't assume everyone understands your shitass Evangelion jokes, Nanoko!)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-horny.png">It's a shame you didn't have to do this a few minutes earlier... a damn shame...</state>
                <state img="#-smuggywuggyuwuwuuwu.png">An eye for an eye, you know? Except one eye is your dick, and the other eye is... I dunno, my clit? Whatever, you get the idea. Get fappin', bitch boy.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-horny.png">W-we're... pretty much about to have sex, aren't we, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">I-is masturbation next to another person just... s-sex, but without touching each other? I sure hope so.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">W-we're allowed to... &lt;i&gt;help each other out&lt;/i&gt;, right...?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Should I be excited I won, or... &lt;i&gt;extremely aroused?&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;...Eh. I'll think about it another time.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">All I did was be halfway decent at poker, and this is still one of the &lt;i&gt;best&lt;/i&gt; rewards I've ever gotten... next to that iPod I won at the arcade when I was a kid. But it's close.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Have you ever played that one minigame with the soda cans from Mario Party 8, ~name~? Because... you're about to.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-flustered.png">It's okay if I watch, right? I-I mean, I'd &lt;i&gt;assume&lt;/i&gt; you're cool with people watching you masturbate if you're playing this game, but... consent is sexy, you know?</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">You... won't give yourself rug burn if you do that without lotion, right? O-or does it not work like that?</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">&lt;i&gt;(I'm used to watching this from the perspective of a guy filming his own cock... it feels way more vouyeristic this way.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-horny.png">You know, if you view time as a place instead of a concept, we're technically just masturbating in different places, but still in the same room. So it's &lt;i&gt;basically&lt;/i&gt; like we're having sex.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">I don't know why some people value their virginity so much, but... mine's still up for the taking, if you so desire.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-horny.png">I-I've got a free hand if you want it, ~name~... a free hand, and some other options...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Wh-what's the point of us masturbating at the same time if we aren't even gonna fuck? That just seems... inefficient...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">C-come on, ~name~, there's no rule against... just sticking it in and killing two birds with one stone.&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;We're the birds, by the way. And we definitely won't be dying.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-smuggywuggyuwuwuuwu.png">Fap for me, fool! Defile yourself before the girl who only &lt;i&gt;kind of&lt;/i&gt; defeated you!</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">...I will be watching your career with great interest.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">I guess &lt;i&gt;this&lt;/i&gt; is why we evolved to have two eyes. One to play poker, the other to watch ~name~ crank that metaphorical Soulja Boy.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-fear.png">&lt;i&gt;(Fuck, now if this makes me wet, everyone's gonna be able to see...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-fear.png">&lt;i&gt;(It's really hot, but also... vaguely threatening?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">&lt;i&gt;(I think I'd rather be the one defiling myself in front of&lt;/i&gt; him, &lt;i&gt;but this is still... enjoyable in its own way...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">&lt;i&gt;(Knowing my luck, I'm gonna end up like that eventually... will he bother to watch me when I do?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">&lt;i&gt;(It'd be better if we were doing this at the same time... but I'm nowhere near close to losing yet...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">U-um... try not to cum on my clothes when you finish, alright?&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;(And I don't think you have enough firepower to aim for my face instead...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">&lt;i&gt;(Maybe if I just... pulled up my skirt enough for him to see an outline of my...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">&lt;i&gt;(After the game, would ~name~ wanna...? No, I shouldn't be thinking about that before he's seen me naked... I don't even know if he's into me.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-horny.png">I-is this doing anything for you, ~name~? Watching me humiliate myself like this? </state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">You've got full permission to pin me down right here on the ground, ~name~. &lt;i&gt;To pin me down and fuck me senseless, leave me collapsed on the ground with your cum leaking out of me...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-neutral.png">W-would you rather pin me down by my wrists, or my neck? I'm fine with either...</state>
                <state img="#-neutral.png">I-I don't even have to look at you, ~name~... I could get off on the sound of your voice and nothing else...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">A-are you into marking, ~name~? Does the idea of covering me in hickies and bite marks to let everyone know I'm yours sound appealing...?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-hmm.png">&lt;i&gt;(Do guys have different sensitive spots on their dicks like girls do, or is the whole thing the sensitive spot?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">&lt;i&gt;(I wish we could offer ourselves up as volunteers... ourselves, and our mouths.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">D-do you... need any inspiration, ~name~? </state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">U-um, just in case you're nervous, I find men moaning... &lt;i&gt;really hot&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">&lt;i&gt;(I'm not allowed to cum yet, but maybe I could give him a thighjob... as long as he doesn't grind too high up.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">&lt;i&gt;(How am I supposed to go back to rule 34 and doujins when I've gotten this up close and personal?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Men... are hot...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-horny.png">&lt;i&gt;(Maybe if I just grope myself a little, no one'll notice...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">There's not much else for me to do right now aside from making direct eye contact with your dick... you're cool with that, right?</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Shit, man... I wish I could do more than just watch.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">My hands are free now, y'know. Nothing's off the table.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="megamix" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">&lt;i&gt;(Damn. As dead as the chances of Activision ever making another Crash game.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-smuggywuggyuwuwuuwu.png">Nice job, sport.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="azami" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">...?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-fear.png">Another one bites za dusto! Get it? It's a Jojo ref.. uh, forget I said that. I promise I get bitches.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="azami" />
                <state img="#-fear.png">And... there she goes. &lt;i&gt;(How the FUCK am I supposed to talk about this in therapy?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-flustered.png">It's okay if I watch, right? I mean, I'd &lt;i&gt;assume&lt;/i&gt; you're cool with people watching you masturbate if you're playing this game, but... consent is sexy, you know?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I-I'll... try not to make &lt;i&gt;direct&lt;/i&gt; eye contact with your vagina...</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">Uh... g-ganbatte?</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">T-try not to sprain your wrist while you do this, okay? Because I've done it before, and it was... &lt;i&gt;not&lt;/i&gt; fun, explaining that to the doctor with my dad in the room.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-fear.png">&lt;i&gt;(...Why did I think it'd look wildly different from how I masturbate? That's literally a perfectly normal vagina.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">&lt;i&gt;(Those noises she's making, they're so cute, but so sexy...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-panic.png">Uh... having you do that while I'm still mostly clothed feels... &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; unfair. Sorry...</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">S-so, uh... come here often? Wait, shit, no, bad choice of words...</state>
                <state img="#-panic.png">...Huh. Boobs. Bounce bounce, am I right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-panic.png">Hey, uh... wh-what would you say the healthy amount to do this is? And... is two or three times a day too much?</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">&lt;i&gt;(Fucking hell, I can't stop thinking of that Vine with the mac and cheese...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">I wonder if the other girls at school... on second thought, maybe I shouldn't imagine my classmates masturbating.</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">&lt;i&gt;(It's like she knows all of her sensitive spots... I just jackhammer with my fingers and hope for the best.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">Do you ever wish it was as easy to masturbate with a vagina as it is with a dick? I'm serious, this shit's like rocket science sometimes.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Do you need to get any work done, ~name~. D-do you need something to sit on while you do? Because my face is right here...</state>
                <state img="#-neutral.png">I-I've never eaten someone out before, so I'd probably be really bad at it... but I'll only learn with experience.</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">People back home always talk about conserving water... I don't know if this place has the same issues with water that California has, but it wouldn't hurt to shower together after this, right...?</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">I don't know if scissoring actually gets you off... but I'm willing to try anything once.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Back home doesn't have cute girls like you, ~name~...</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">Wait, you know what they should have here? A leaderboard! Time how long it takes for everyone to cum and see who can do it the fastest! Who runs this place? Where can I pitch this?</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">&lt;i&gt;(She looks so graceful compared to... eh, whatever. I'm too horny to self-deprecate at this point.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="chica" />
                <state img="#-horny.png">&lt;i&gt;(...I would fuck the shit out of that robot, man.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-smuggywuggyuwuwuuwu.png">Fuck yeah.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate_first">
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-fear.png">Um... you guys would believe me if I said I did this on purpose? No? Not even a little?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate">
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-horny.png">Eh, it's whatever. I've been wanting to do this since I lost my spats, actually.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="start_masturbating">
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-flustered.png">Just... ignore me if I start saying weird stuff, okay? I have a habit of talking out loud when I masturbate, and some of my thoughts get... weird.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="masturbating">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-neutral.png">There are a few doujins I've read so many times that I can pretty much just recite them in my head... it's coming in handy right now, that's for sure.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">U-um... I guess it's kinda nice, doing it for someone else's enjoyment... not that I'm &lt;i&gt;not&lt;/i&gt; enjoying this, obviously.</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">I-I would've brought at least one of my vibrators or dildos here with me, but the idea of carrying a rubber dick around with me felt... weird...</state>
                <state img="#-neutral.png">R-remind me... hah... to buy one of those clit sucker thingies when I have enough spending money again...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">&lt;i&gt;(I feel so exposed... like everyone's just seconds away from pouncing on me and fucking me into the ground...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">&lt;i&gt;(Maybe I should go to a class without wearing anything under my skirt... if I've learned anything from this game, it's that I'm maybe an exhibitionist.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="heavy_masturbating">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-heavy.png">&lt;i&gt;O-oh, fuck, I'm actually doing it, I thought I'd...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-heavy.png">&lt;i&gt;I-it's been so long since I last did this with my just my hands, I thought I wouldn't be able to...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-heavy.png">&lt;i&gt;F-fuck, fuck, somebody just fill me until I'm bursting already-...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finishing_masturbating">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-finish.png">&lt;i&gt;F-FUCK!~&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-fear.png">...You will not repeat or remember anything you have seen today.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="after_masturbating">
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-hmm.png">They give out towels here, right...?</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">&lt;i&gt;(Wait, shit, no, don't scratch your face with that hand! You just fucked yourself, dumbass!)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">...How am I supposed to make small talk after doing all that?</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">...I guess my job here's done. And I've just gotta stand here until the game's over now.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_victory">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-fear.png">...I didn't think of anything cool to say when I won. Fuck.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-smuggywuggyuwuwuuwu.png">Yeah, &lt;i&gt;of course&lt;/i&gt; I won. I'm a certified gamer, after all.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_defeat">
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-smuggywuggyuwuwuuwu.png">Well, I may not have conquered, but I saw, and I &lt;i&gt;definitely&lt;/i&gt; came. Nice job, everyone.&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;(And nice job not losing your shit around all these hot people, me.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="global">
            <case stage="0-9" hidden="1">
                <state img="#-calm.png">calm</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">confused</state>
                <state img="#-displeased.png">displeased</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">excited</state>
                <state img="#-fear.png">fear</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">flustered</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">happy</state>
                <state img="#-hmm.png">hmm</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">horny</state>
                <state img="#-neutral.png">neutral</state>
                <state img="#-niconii.png">niconii</state>
                <state img="#-panic.png">panic</state>
                <state img="#-pissed.png">pissed</state>
                <state img="#-pose.png">pose</state>
                <state img="#-sad.png">sad</state>
                <state img="#-shy.png">shy</state>
                <state img="#-smuggywuggyuwuwuuwu.png">smuggywuggyuwuuwuuwu</state>
                <state img="#-thinky.png">thinky</state>
                <state img="#-wtf.png">wtf</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

    </behaviour>
</opponent>
