<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>

<!--This file was machine generated using the Character Editor v6.7.9 at 1:04:41 PM on December 16, 2022. Do not edit this file directly unless you know what you're doing.-->
<opponent>
    <version>v6.7.9</version>
    <first>Adora</first>
    <last />
    <label>Adora</label>
    <gender>female</gender>
    <size>medium</size>
    <timer>15</timer>
    <intelligence>average</intelligence>



    <wardrobe>
        <clothing name="panties" generic="underwear" position="lower" type="important" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="bra" generic="bra" position="upper" type="important" />
        <clothing name="leggings" generic="leggings" position="lower" type="major" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="shirt" generic="shirt" position="upper" type="major" />
        <clothing name="jacket" generic="jacket" position="upper" type="minor" />
        <clothing name="boots" generic="shoes" position="feet" type="extra" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="belts" generic="belt" position="waist" type="extra" plural="true" />
    </wardrobe>


    <behaviour>
        <trigger id="selected">
            <case stage="0" id="49">
                <condition filter="human_female" status="crotch_visible" role="other" character="human" />
                <state img="#-scared.png">We haven't started yet! Is this some sort of mind game? Why are you already exposed?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="50">
                <condition filter="human_male" status="crotch_visible" role="other" character="human" />
                <state img="#-upset.png">You're taking the fun out of the game! Now there's no mystery or tension to it. I was supposed to be having fun.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="47">
                <condition gender="female" status="chest_visible" role="other" character="human" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">Whoa! Has the game started already? Am I late?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="48">
                <condition gender="male" status="chest_visible" role="other" character="human" />
                <state img="#-normal.png">You remind me of Bow. It's probably just the abs on display.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" priority="1">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Hello, I'm Adora. Is this seat open?</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">So, this is where the poker match is happening? I'm SO ready for some competition!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_start">
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~background~" value="haunted forest" />
                <state img="#-scared.png">WHAT IS THIS PLACE? IS THAT A GHOST? HOW IS THIS SUPPOSED TO BE FUN?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" priority="30">
                <test expr="~background.water~" value="true" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">Won't the cards get wet if we play here?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" priority="30">
                <test expr="~background.voyeur~" value="true" />
                <state img="#-mad.png">I'm not backing down just because someone is watching me. It's not a problem if I win. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="1">
                <condition count="3" status="alive" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">I think we're a bit short. Isn't this a five-person game?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition count="0" gender="male" />
                <state img="#-sparkle.png">An all-female game? Count me in!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-brag.png">Alright, time for some relaxation.</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Name's Adora, and I'm feeling good! I've prepared for any and all possible scenarios. I am so ready for this Poker thing!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" oneShotId="41" hidden="1" priority="1000">
                <state img="#-scared.png" marker="Fabulous Secret Powers">This case is supposed to be hidden! How did you find it?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="swap_cards">
            <case stage="0-7" priority="1">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Give me ~cards.text~ ~cards.ifplural(cards|card)~.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">There is a method to this, I just have to figure it out.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">That clearly isn’t going to work. Let’s try this again.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Should I keep this one? I mean, it's so close to a straight but...</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Remember the chart. Going for pairs is better than straights, however...</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Please don't make me regret this...</state>
                <state img="#-laugh.png">I should aim for pairs. Going straight is never an option!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" priority="1">
                <test expr="~cards~" value="1" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">One card, please.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" priority="1">
                <test expr="~cards~" value="2" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">I'll take two new cards.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" priority="1">
                <test expr="~cards~" value="3" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">Give me three.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" priority="1">
                <test expr="~cards~" value="4" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I need four cards. Hopefully, something to help this high card.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" priority="1">
                <test expr="~cards~" value="5" />
                <state img="#-upset.png">Give me a new hand!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" priority="1">
                <test expr="~cards~" value="0" />
                <state img="#-brag.png">Nothing for me! This hand is perfect!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="good_hand">
            <case stage="0-7" totalRounds="4-">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Looks like I just needed a warm-up.</state>
                <state img="#-brag.png">Ah, I can taste victory now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" totalRounds="0-3" priority="1">
                <state img="#-cocky.png" oneShotId="1">That's a strong way to start the game.</state>
                <state img="#-brag.png" oneShotId="2">Looks like I'm on my way to an early lead.</state>
                <state img="#-normal.png" oneShotId="3">Don't feel too bad if I beat you, it's still early in the game.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" priority="1">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Wow! These are pretty good cards. Alright, let's see what you got!</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">How do you wash a deck of cards? I think the Inventory has to after each game. I hope they do.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Horde Cards replaced all the kings, queens, and jacks. They had generals, captains, and Sargent. There are no cool pictures though.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">This'll be a piece of cake.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Glimmer's right! I have gotten really good at improvising!</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Yes!... I mean, oh no! I have such a terrible hand...</state>
                <state img="#-brag.png">I knew advanced prep would be the key to success!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="okay_hand">
            <case stage="0-7" totalRounds="0-3" priority="1">
                <state img="#-awkward.png" oneShotId="7">Everyone is more talkative than I was expecting.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" oneShotId="8">I didn't think poker would be this...social.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="9">The stakes are still low. No need to stress about luck, yet.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" priority="1">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">I can work with what I got. It's one of my many talents.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">I'm not familiar with this type of poker. I studied Brightmoon hold'em for this game.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Can no one tell Glimmer this is where I went tonight? She'd totally make fun of me for it.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">On one hand, losing means that these guys won't have to lose. But on the other... I don't want to lose either!</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Alright Adora, keep it cool. You can win with these cards. All you have to do is beat a single opponent!</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Okay, I need to relax... Is there something I can hit? Maybe someone to spar with?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" totalRounds="4-" priority="1">
                <state img="#-normal.png">Think carefully before you swap. It's going to be a close round</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">This is the best type of hand: good, but still bad enough to be risky!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="bad_hand">
            <case stage="0-7" totalRounds="4-" priority="2">
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Maybe I'm getting too comfortable around everyone.</state>
                <state img="#-scared.png">Wait! That was the wrong card!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" totalRounds="0-3" priority="2">
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="13">Not a great start.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" oneShotId="14">How can everyone talk, and play poker? I can hardly think right now.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="15">I got distracted. I can't focus if everyone is talking.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" priority="1">
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Ohhhhh no. That was a bad swap.</state>
                <state img="#-disapointed.png">That was not my best move.</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">I went for greatness and I came up short. Story of my life.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I haven't technically bet anything yet. I could just sit this round out and go to the bathroom, right?</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Here's a tip ~human~. Don't do what I just did.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">It's okay! Really! I have everything under control!</state>
                <state img="#-scared.png">Why do my plans always fall apart? Always! It’d be impressive if it wasn't terrifying!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="hand">
            <case stage="0-7" id="51" oneShotId="25">
                <condition status="alive" character="human" layers="0" />
                <condition count="2" status="finished" />
                <state img="#-cocky.png">It all comes down to this! Thanks for playing with me ~human~, but you're going down!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="53">
                <condition count="0" status="not_lost_all" />
                <condition count="1" status="alive" role="opp" var="opponent" />
                <state img="#-cocky.png">It's just you and me ~opponent~. Do your best, and may the best strip poker player win.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" totalRounds="0-3" priority="1">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">The early rounds are less interesting.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Every bit of clothing counts. You have to treat every round as a make-or-break situation. Even if it's boring this early.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">You can take your time, but it's a little early to be stalling.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">It's too early to say if someone is winning yet. Let's keep going.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">Can an ace connect to a two for a straight? It counts as a one, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" totalRounds="4-" priority="1">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Maybe the other princesses would like to come here too... But not Frosta. Oh, definitely not Frosta.</state>
                <state img="#-laugh.png">This place has a really calm atmosphere... Even Mermista could chill here... &lt;br&gt;No, wait, what am I saying, she'd probably be like &lt;i&gt;"Uuuugh, stripping in front of strangers? I already have Sea Hawk if I want to embarrass myself..."&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">You know who'd love this place? Perfuma! She's all about this relaxed, friendly vibe... And the stripping, the games, the... &lt;i&gt;Self-touching&lt;/i&gt;...</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">- So, uh... Are we gonna talk about our feelings after this, or are we gonna make fun of the losers? Just so I know whether this is a Bright Moon or a Fright Zone kind of party...</state>
                <state img="#-normal.png">We never had parties back in the Horde... But we did have small, secret meetings to play card games. So this makes me feel nostalgic. </state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">I'm keeping my sword by the way. Whenever someone else had it things went terribly wrong.</state>
                <state img="#-laugh.png">Does anyone like She-Ra here? I hear she's pretty cool.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" totalRounds="7-" priority="1">
                <state img="#-normal.png">Win or lose, just try to enjoy it.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Are you guys doing anything after the game? Do you want to hang out?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip">
            <case stage="1" id="58" oneShotId="40" priority="100">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Reason3" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" marker="Reason4">I really needed this break, to be honest. It's just hard to ask for time off when there's so much counting on me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="self" consecutiveLosses="3-" />
                <state img="#-mad.png">Come on Adora! Get your head in the game!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="54" priority="20">
                <state img="#-normal.png" marker="Reason1">I made a bad swap; it happens. I won't sweat the details.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_winning">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-aroused.png">It's more fun if there is a close game. I was told to have some fun after all.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">How about I be fair and take four things off?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Fine, you earned another layer.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-aroused.png">It's more fun if it's a close game. Beat me again next round to make it more exciting.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-brag.png">Good round! I think it'll be more fun if we're all undressed.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-aroused.png">It's only fair, I'm staring at topless people right now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-sparkle.png">Is this going to bring us to sudden death? That's so exciting!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_normal">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-calm.png">My first loss isn't anything to worry about. I wasn't expecting to be flawless in a game of chance.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-aroused.png">My last defense. Now it's win or lose. It's pretty exciting!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Let's spice up this game a little.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-normal.png">I know what I did wrong. I'll do better next round.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Me? Well, I was hoping to show off, just a little.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-brag.png">These leggings cover too much of my abs. I worked hard to have these muscles. I got to show them off!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-aroused.png">I'll take my bra off. It's unfashionable anyway.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_losing">
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I might be losing, but I still don't feel very worried. Maybe I should take off more?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-upset.png">I don't like the pattern I'm seeing. I'm losing a lot of games.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-aroused.png">This is getting bad. This is getting kind of fun!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-upset.png">This looks like I'm on my last legs. I got to make a comeback!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-aroused.png">I have to show something important, before everyone else. The embarrassment might help me play better.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-disapointed.png">My last defense has to go. I still have one more round in me, I can turn this around. I hope.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripping">
            <case stage="0" priority="100">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Reason1" />
                <state img="Strip-0.png" marker="Reason2">Last time I needed a break my friends couldn't figure out how to help me relax. So now, I get to do my own thing.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" priority="100">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Reason4" />
                <state img="Strip-1.png" marker="Reason5">Being She-Ra has so much responsibility. I have to fight battles, plan attacks, and live up to some legendary heroes. It's a lot.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="Strip-0.png">My belts are keeping me from all my good stuff. It's just how the game goes.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="Strip-1.png">It's two boots and two socks. I just don't want to ruin the socks, plus they're pretty boring for this game.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="Strip-2.png">This jacket has been with me ever since I started my adventure. It's the best jacket a girl could have.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="Strip-3.png">You beat me enough times to earn a little skin. I hope you like muscles.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="Strip-4.png">I hope you all will focus on more than just the abs though.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="Strip-5.png">I never wanted to lose this much. Well, let's see if you can still focus after I take this off!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="Strip-6.png">Why is my heart pounding so hard? I think I'm enjoying this, and not just sexually.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripped">
            <case stage="1" priority="100">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Reason2" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" marker="Reason3">I came here because I used to play poker back in the academy. I love the tension and planning, but enough about me. Back to the game!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" priority="100">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Reason5" />
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Don't get me wrong, being She-Ra has its perks. Big muscles, amazing hair, and the ladies love her.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7" id="38" oneShotId="23">
                <condition status="exposed" role="self" />
                <condition count="0" status="exposed" role="opp" />
                <state img="#-brag.png">I still have one loss left. If you want to look at my body instead of your cards, then be my guest.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-normal.png">Alright, next hand! Let's keep this game going.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">That's a bit better. Those boots are designed for combat, not comfort.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-disapointed.png">I'll get my jacket back after this game, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">I don't have an impressive bra, but it's practical for combat. You can still enjoy it; just don't get distracted.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-confused.png">I don't know what good underwear looks like. I've never been shopping for it. I've never actually been shopping for clothes, huh. Is that weird?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-aroused.png">It's so much easier to breathe without my top on. My chest was starting to feel tight.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-mad.png">No losses remaining. You have to focus Adora! Just tune everyone out and think. Alright, bring it on!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_strip">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition filter="blade" role="target" />
                <state img="#-cocky.png" oneShotId="50">Heh, I bet my sword is better ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition filter="fighter" role="target" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="52">Hey ~name~, you look good for a fight. Can we train together? I haven't had a decent sparring partner for a while.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition filter="ghost" role="target" />
                <state img="#-scared.png" oneShotId="62">NO! I'm not doing this today! I hate ghosts! Why would you even haunt me? I didn't kill anyone!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition filter="military" role="target" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="54">Finally, someone who can actually take war seriously. I know so many soldiers who don't take battle planning seriously. I mean, can you believe that?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition filter="student" role="target" />
                <state img="#-brag.png" oneShotId="69">Ah, you must go to the academy. I pretended I was a student once. Totally nailed it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition filter="undead" role="target" />
                <state img="#-scared.png">Are you dead? Is that allowed? I mean, I don't know! I hate this kind of stuff!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition filter="prince" role="target" />
                <state img="#-normal.png" oneShotId="56">A prince? I've never actually met one. I know it's technically called &lt;i&gt;"The Princess Alliance"&lt;/i&gt;,  but do you want to join?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" priority="150">
                <condition role="target" stage="2-10" />
                <alternative>
                    <condition filter="mean" role="target" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <condition filter="aggressive" role="target" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-upset.png" oneShotId="220">Hey! It's only a game. Can you try to be a bit nicer?</state>
                <state img="#-mad.png" oneShotId="244">You're ruining this poker game with your attitude. Knock it off already.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition filter="perverted" role="target" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" oneShotId="221">I should have known a creep would play a game like this.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition filter="villain" role="target" />
                <state img="#-upset.png" oneShotId="223">I've lived in the Fright Zone long enough to know when someone is bad news. You, ~target~, are definitely bad news.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" totalRounds="0-3">
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="142">Alright, you lost. Time to strip.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" oneShotId="143">Umm, you have to strip, ~target~.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="144">Hey! I won!</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="145">Umm, don't feel nervous stripping in front of a girl. I'm pretty nervous though.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" totalRounds="4-6">
                <state img="#-normal.png" oneShotId="151">Things are starting to get interesting.</state>
                <state img="#-brag.png" oneShotId="152">Look at this! I won. You already know what that means, ~target~.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="150">That was a good round! Let's see if the strip is good too.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-9" totalRounds="7-">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Well, look who has to strip. You're not going to take something small, right?</state>
                <state img="#-normal.png">You're up, ~target~. Take your time and try to be comfortable.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">~Target~ loses? Well, I think we all earned the win.</state>
                <state img="#-brag.png">Another good round of poker! Not for ~target~, but for us.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Did you learn something? I think I'm about to. Get it?</state>
                <state img="#-normal.png">It doesn't matter what you take off as long as you're still happy to be here. I sure am.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-1" totalRounds="7-">
                <state img="#-cocky.png" oneShotId="156">I am dominating this game.</state>
                <state img="#-disapointed.png" oneShotId="157">I won again? This isn't very tense.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" priority="5">
                <state img="#-confused.png">It's ~target~ that has to strip. I think. Am I right?</state>
                <state img="#-brag.png">Boom! I win! Alright ~target~, strip it.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">Hey ~target~, did you make a risky swap or just not have anything good?</state>
                <state img="#-normal.png">Someone had to lose the round. The fun part is what ~target~ is going to do next.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">That was closer than it looked. I just got lucky with the swap.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">There is a lot more small talk in this game of poker than I was prepared for. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9" priority="5">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">You might join me if you keep being reckless like that.</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">Don't get distracted! You could have stared at my body if you won!</state>
                <state img="#-brag.png">You'll lose the whole game if you keep losing hands. </state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Do you need a coach? I don't have &lt;i&gt;much&lt;/i&gt; else to do.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_strip">
            <case stage="0-9" id="71">
                <condition role="target" character="aoba" stage="3-7" consecutiveLosses="4" sayingMarker="Aoba's-pissed" />
                <state img="#-disapointed.png">Are you ok? Do you need a little break Aoba?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="61">
                <condition role="target" character="lucy" stage="4" sayingMarker="virgo" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">Gate of the what?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition filter="catfolk" role="target" />
                <state img="#-aroused.png" oneShotId="25">So, ~name~, you're cute. Like a kitten! Yea, that's what I uh, meant.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition filter="blade" role="target" />
                <state img="#-cocky.png" oneShotId="23">Heh, I bet my sword is better ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition filter="ghost" role="target" />
                <state img="#-scared.png" oneShotId="75">NO! I'm not doing this today! I hate ghosts! Why would you even haunt me? I didn't kill anyone!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition filter="undead" role="target" />
                <state img="#-scared.png" oneShotId="31">Are you dead? Is that allowed? I mean, I don't know! I hate this kind of stuff!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition filter="military" role="target" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="29">Finally, someone who can actually take war seriously. I know so many soldiers who don't take battle planning seriously. I mean, can you believe that?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition filter="fighter" role="target" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="27">Hey ~name~, you look good for a fight. Can we train train together? I haven't had a decent sparring partner for a while.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition filter="princess" role="target" />
                <state img="#-normal.png" oneShotId="78">Hey! You're a princess too? That's great! Do you have any advice? I'm terrible at basically everything royal.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition filter="witch" role="target" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="33">I know a few witches. One of them is super evil and the other is incredibly nice to me. Both are, um, eccentric.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition filter="student" role="target" />
                <state img="#-brag.png" oneShotId="80">Ah, you must go to the academy. I pretended I was a student once. Totally nailed it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition filter="lesbian" role="target" />
                <state img="#-flirt.png" oneShotId="226">I think we're going to get along. Hi, I'm Adora.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" priority="150">
                <condition role="target" stage="2-10" />
                <alternative>
                    <condition filter="aggressive" role="target" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <condition filter="mean" role="target" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-mad.png" oneShotId="228">Would it kill you to be polite? It's a game of poker. </state>
                <state img="#-mad.png" oneShotId="230">I never thought someone could be more rude than Catra, but you've exceeded my expectations.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition filter="silent" role="target" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="236">I'm a big fan of the strong silent type. You came to the right game!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" priority="20">
                <condition role="opp" hasHand="Royal Flush" />
                <state img="#-sparkle.png">A royal flush! That's amazing!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="self" hasHand="Royal Flush" />
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Look at what I got! No one was beating me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-7" totalRounds="7-">
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Well, I'm looking forward to this.</state>
                <state img="#-brag.png">~Name~ lost, so it's time to enjoy the benefits of winning!</state>
                <state img="#-very aroused.png">The cards decided that you lost ~name~. You know what that means!</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Boom! I win again!</state>
                <state img="#-very aroused.png">I was hoping you'd lose ~name~. Not because I hate you or anything! It's just, I have to play to win.</state>
                <state img="#-normal.png">That was close! I almost had nothing before that swap. That's never a fun spot to be in.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-1" totalRounds="7-">
                <state img="#-disapointed.png">This game isn't as tense as I thought it would be.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">Was I this good back in the Horde? I thought I lost a lot.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Why can't I be this lucky all the time?</state>
                <state img="#-brag.png">I'm starting to feel overdressed. Maybe I'll go for a flush next hand.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" totalRounds="0-3">
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="114">It's still anyone's game. Just relax.</state>
                <state img="#-normal.png" oneShotId="115">I think I figured out your tell, ~target~. There's no betting so it doesn't really matter.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="116">Looks like this game is getting interesting.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="117">I won? Well, it's more like ~target~ lost. </state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png" oneShotId="118">Is it rude to stare?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="119">It's just an early game loss. There's no need to panic or celebrate. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" totalRounds="4-6">
                <state img="#-brag.png" oneShotId="126">I think you underestimated how good my cards were.</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png" oneShotId="127">It's starting to get more exciting. Every hand counts, so be careful, ~target~.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="128">Remember ~target~, High cards are more likely to be in our hands than in the deck.</state>
                <state img="#-brag.png" oneShotId="129">Beating people with cards is fun, but this next part is even better.</state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png" oneShotId="130">That was close! Now to the good part.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="131">I think you'll remove something from your top.</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png" oneShotId="132">I'm rocking this game! </state>
                <state img="#-brag.png" oneShotId="133">This is going well. Things are starting to get interesting!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9" priority="10">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Did I distract you? I have that effect on people.</state>
                <state img="#-laugh.png">Care to join me?</state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png">I can't tell if I want you to win the game, or lose quickly. I guess you can be naked either way.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">I'm looking forward to this.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="tie">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-mad.png">Now fight to determine the loser! We don't do that here? That's lame!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0-9" id="65">
                <condition role="target" character="brock" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-scared.png">Take cover! Was the safety not on this whole time?!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-9" id="42">
                <condition status="crotch_visible" role="target" />
                <state img="#-scared.png">Hold on, that counts?!</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">Don't think that taking off something small while I'm naked is cool.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Little by little I'm getting you closer to masturbating.</state>
                <state img="#-normal.png">Be careful, your little items can only save you for so long.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">It's not going to save you from defeat.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-disapointed.png">That's not impressive.</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">~clothing.ifPlural(Your ~clothing~ are ruining the mood. | Your ~clothing~ is ruining the mood.)~</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Now I feel super exposed</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="0-9" id="40">
                <condition status="crotch_visible" role="target" />
                <state img="#-laugh.png">I wonder if they make ~clothing~ for penises? That would make this game much more interesting.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="18">
                <test expr="~clothing~" value="belt" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" oneShotId="35">Do you know where any cool belt buckles are? My old one was the Horde emblem and all Glimmer had was a wing.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="19">
                <test expr="~clothing~" value="boots" />
                <state img="#-normal.png" oneShotId="37">Your boots look pretty sturdy. I like a guy with a strong taste in footwear.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="20">
                <test expr="~clothing~" value="glasses" />
                <state img="#-disapointed.png" oneShotId="39">It's going to be harder to see the cards without your glasses. Are you sure you can take that chance after a loss ~name~?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="21">
                <test expr="~clothing~" value="gloves" />
                <state img="#-laugh.png" oneShotId="41">Those seem handy. Bow said that pun would be funny.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="22">
                <test expr="~clothing~" value="hat" />
                <state img="#-awkward.png" oneShotId="48">I don't understand the appeal of hats. It seems like it would always be in the way or go flying off.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="23">
                <test expr="~clothing~" value="headphones" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="43">Why would you want to listen to music by yourself? Isn't music only made for dancing?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="25">
                <test expr="~clothing~" value="necklace" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="45">Why do some people wear a necklace when they just want to show off the centerpiece? Can't they just have it on their shirt?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">I'm getting closer to beating you.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Trust me, it's the little losses that you think about later.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Let's just move on. I'll beat ~target~ again.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-upset.png">Did you enjoy taking that off? I didn't enjoy watching it.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0-9" id="72">
                <condition role="target" character="florina" stage="0" saidMarker="fled" />
                <state img="#-disapointed.png">Should we pause the game until Florina returns? Will she be back? Maybe I should check on her.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="73">
                <condition role="target" character="vriska" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-sparkle.png">You can transform too? That's amazing!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="35">
                <condition status="crotch_visible" role="target" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Wait, were you going to count that this whole time? That's, umm, okay.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" totalRounds="0-3">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Starting off small to build the tension? Well, a tactical decision can still be boring.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I was expecting something small this early, but it's still boring.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Am I supposed to know why you're wearing  ~clothing~? Is this normal?</state>
                <state img="#-normal.png">You seem to know a bit about fashion. Do you offer lessons?</state>
                <state img="#-disapointed.png">It's not very interesting when all you remove ~clothing.ifPlural(are ~clothing~| is ~clothing~)~.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="0-9" id="79">
                <condition role="target" character="ms.fortune" stage="3" sayingMarker="Fortune_Strip_2C" />
                <state img="#-scared.png">AHHHHHH! She just died!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="33">
                <condition status="crotch_visible" role="target" />
                <state img="#-disapointed.png">That's actually underwhelming, and confusing. Is this a trick to throw everyone off?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="7" oneShotId="2">
                <test expr="~clothing~" value="belt" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">Belts are pretty useful. It's the perfect mix of fashion and function.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="8" oneShotId="3">
                <test expr="~clothing~" value="glasses" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">Won't that make it harder to see everyone else get naked? Did you think that move through?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="9" oneShotId="4">
                <test expr="~clothing~" value="gloves" />
                <state img="#-laugh.png">Heh, guess you could say the gloves are coming off. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="10" oneShotId="5">
                <test expr="~clothing~" value="hat" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">Do you think I should wear a hat? I look pretty good in a tiara. Then again, that's when I have She-Ra's hair.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="11" oneShotId="7">
                <test expr="~clothing~" value="headphones" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">What are those for? They look too clunky to be practical in battle.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="12" oneShotId="6">
                <test expr="~clothing~" value="necklace" />
                <state img="#-normal.png">That's a cute little necklace. Just be aware that it can be used as a strangling device if you're ever in trouble.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="13" oneShotId="8">
                <test expr="~clothing~" value="bracelet" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">Why would you have a gauntlet that small?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="16" oneShotId="11">
                <test expr="~clothing~" value="shoes" />
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Do your shoes also have a steel toe hidden in them? Glimmer says it's not normal. Pfft, it's totally normal, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-calm.png">It's a start. Let's see if you can do better next round.</state>
                <state img="#-disapointed.png">Are you hiding anything else? I think it's fair to let us know.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0-9" id="43">
                <condition status="crotch_visible" role="target" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Wasn't there a stripping order rule we had to follow? No? Please hurry up; I'm running out of small talk.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I know three boys. I should probably bump those numbers up.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I don't know much about boys' fashion, or any fashion really.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_minor">
            <case stage="0-9" id="63">
                <condition role="target" character="ignatz" stage="3" sayingMarker="glassesstart" notSaidMarker="bernadettathrowstart" />
                <condition role="target" character="ignatz" sayingMarker="glassesstart" notSaidMarker="artpunstart" />
                <condition role="target" character="ignatz" sayingMarker="glassesstart" notSaidMarker="igfluttershy_hug" />
                <condition role="target" character="ignatz" sayingMarker="glassesstart" notSaidMarker="artpunstart" />
                <condition role="target" character="ignatz" sayingMarker="glassesstart" notSaidMarker="igpetra_stripglasses2" />
                <test expr="~target.costume~" cmp="!=" value="ignatz_drawn_brawn" />
                <state img="#-disapointed.png">Do you need us to stop the game? It's not fair if you can't read the cards.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="41">
                <condition status="crotch_visible" role="target" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">Why? I have no idea why you would do that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="24">
                <test expr="~clothing~" value="jacket" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">Are shoulder pads still fashionable? It's just that your jacket didn't have them so I'm wondering if I missed something.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Back to the game!</state>
                <state img="#-brag.png">Don't lose twice in a row, ~target~. I'm not going easy on half-naked guys.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Was that it? Alright then.</state>
                <state img="#-normal.png">Just try not to lose again.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-disapointed.png">I feel like I was really bad at the game now.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Was I eager to lose? It should have been a closer game.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0-9" id="75">
                <condition role="target" character="shantae" stage="1" sayingMarker="monkey" />
                <state img="#-sparkle.png">That's the cutest thing I've ever seen! An adorable animal transformation is the best thing I can think of!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="36">
                <condition status="crotch_visible" role="target" />
                <state img="#-upset.png">Did you forget about your ~clothing~? I definitely did.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-normal.png">I don't know if I prefer a slow removal or a quick one. Eh, both are good.</state>
                <state img="#-laugh.png" oneShotId="49">You reap what you sew. Get it? Sew? Like clothing? Never mind...</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I'll take anything if it means you'll be closer to full nudity.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">It has to come off eventually.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_minor">
            <case stage="0-9" id="34">
                <condition status="crotch_visible" role="target" />
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Wow, that's oddly arousing. I think you're into something and dragging me into it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="14" oneShotId="10">
                <test expr="~clothing~" value="jacket" />
                <state img="#-brag.png">I bet you'll agree that jackets are the coolest item someone could wear. Glimmer believes that it's a hood. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="15" oneShotId="9">
                <test expr="~clothing~" value="stockings" />
                <state img="#-normal.png">Those are some tall socks. You might as well commit to full leggings. Then you'll save money on shorts. It's pretty cost-effective.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-brag.png">Let's get back to it. I want to beat ~target~ again.</state>
                <state img="#-normal.png">Are you ready, ~target~? I don't want to move on until you are.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">It's not much, but it will do; for now.</state>
                <state img="#-disapointed.png">Aw, that's it?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_major">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-brag.png">Just act like you're going to take a bath with all of us. Totally less embarrassing.</state>
                <state img="#-laugh.png">I'm not into guys, but we can be friends. We got a few things in common already.</state>
                <state img="#-normal.png">At least your ~clothing~ served its purpose.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_major">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Make sure to treat those clothes with care and respect. Then your layers might last longer.</state>
                <state img="#-normal.png">Are you nervous yet? Just take a deep breath and only focus on your goal. That's combat advice, but it might work here.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">And now we can get back to poker!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_major">
            <case stage="0-9" id="60">
                <condition role="target" character="aimee" stage="0-2" />
                <state img="#-scared.png">That's not proper gun safety! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="76">
                <condition role="target" character="caulifla" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-sparkle.png">Did you just turn into a She-Ra? That's amazing!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-happy.png">The less I have to imagine the better!</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">Is my outfit not right for stripping? My clothes are way different from ~target~'s.</state>
                <state img="#-brag.png">Your ~clothing~ looks great. Even better now that I won it off you.</state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png">I liked your ~clothing~ before, but this is much better.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Don't worry about being exposed like this. I'll protect you if something goes wrong.</state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png">I can stand guard if you need me to. So relax and undress, I'll take care of you.</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Strip easy, nobody will try anything as long as I'm here.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_major">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Give me a second. ~Target~'s body is taking up all my thinking power.</state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png">You look even cuter than you did thirty seconds ago.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Nice~.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-9" id="59">
                <condition role="target" character="brock" />
                <state img="#-scared.png">Get down!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-normal.png">I've seen Bow's stomach plenty of times. This won't be anything new.</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Are you taking your shirt off because you're desperate or because you want to show off?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition filter="athletic" role="target" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">That is some great muscle definition! How often do you work out?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <condition filter="muscular" role="target" />
                <state img="#-brag.png">Those are some impressive muscles, but I still think She-Ra is more impressive</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Wanna arm wrestle?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition filter="muscular" role="target" />
                <state img="#-brag.png">Looking fit! What's your secret? Mine's a magic sword and working out when I'm stressed.</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Wanna arm wrestle?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="16">Is there any reason for boys not to have breasts?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">You're not looking too shabby, ~target~.</state>
                <state img="#-normal.png">There's nothing to be ashamed of there. Try to relax.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">There's some male nipples. Not my favorite kind, but still good.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-9" id="68">
                <condition role="target" character="sly_cooper" />
                <state img="#-upset.png">If you take your pants off now, why would I care about your other layers? You're taking the tension out of the game!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">It's ok Adora. It's just a penis. No need to treat ~target~ any differently.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Is this going to hurt our friendship? </state>
                <state img="#-brag.png">You lose, ~target~. The one embarrassing thing for a guy to show too.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_small_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-awkward.png" oneShotId="176">Can we please deal cards now?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_medium_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="178">Where have I seen that shape before? Somewhere in the Fright Zone, I think.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_large_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="180">That seems like it would be a burden in a fight.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-9" id="39">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Nice butt.</state>
                <state img="#-normal.png">See? It's not that embarrassing.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-9" id="78">
                <condition role="target" character="polly" saidMarker="UnfinishedBusiness" sayingMarker="Polly Fades Out" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">She's finally gone! Now I can relax!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="77">
                <condition role="target" character="kora" sayingMarker="blade_power" />
                <state img="#-flirt.png">A transformation and cute breasts? It's like my two favorite things in one fun package.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-aroused.png" oneShotId="19">This is the reward I've been waiting for.</state>
                <state img="#-brag.png" oneShotId="18">A loss for ~target~, and two soft prizes for the rest of us.</state>
                <state img="#-very aroused.png" oneShotId="20">I won't judge you, I promise. I'll stare though, like a lot.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="21">I prefer this version to regular poker. ~Target~ is about to show us why.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_small_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Those are amazing! You look so cute!</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">I hope you don't mind me saying, but I think you're really cute.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_medium_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-9" id="66">
                <condition role="target" character="mari_setogaya" saidMarker="Cat_transformation" sayingMarker="Cat_transformed" />
                <state img="#-sparkle.png">You can transform into a catgirl? It's my two favorite things in one!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-aroused.png">That's a great set you have there! If you, umm, don't mind me saying.</state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png">Those look great for cuddling. Can I give it a go?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_large_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-9" id="62">
                <condition role="target" character="polly" saidMarker="UnfinishedBusiness" sayingMarker="Polly Fades In" />
                <state img="#-scared.png">The horny ghost is back! Stay away from me, please!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition filter="muscular" role="target" />
                <state img="#-sparkle.png">Big breasts and muscles? You're the hottest girl I've met!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Those are huge! You look so hot!</state>
                <state img="#-very aroused.png">I ummm, hehehe, &lt;i&gt;wow.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-aroused.png">I used to sneak peeks at the other girls in the Horde showers. That's how I found out I was into girls. This wonderful moment reminded me.</state>
                <state img="#-sparkle.png">It's finally time! All the rounds leading up to this moment! I'm so excited!</state>
                <state img="#-brag.png">I'd like to dedicate this victory to all cute girls. Especially ~target~.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition filter="pubic_hair" role="target" />
                <state img="#-aroused.png" oneShotId="168">I like the soft feeling of some hair down there.</state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png" oneShotId="169">If you put a little perfume down there it makes, um,&lt;i&gt; being intimate&lt;/i&gt;, so much better.</state>
                <state img="#-very aroused.png" oneShotId="170">I'm going to have a hard time focusing on the rest of the game now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition count="0" filter="pubic_hair" role="target" />
                <state img="#-flirt.png" oneShotId="164">Nothing in the way. Now that's a perfect view. </state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png" oneShotId="165">It's definitely cleaner to be fully shaven. Plus there's no risk of hair getting into unwanted places. Pretty smart.</state>
                <state img="#-very aroused.png">I'm trying to look away, but it just keeps pulling me back in. It's so easy to see now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-sparkle.png">I love this game!</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">You look amazing ~target~. I hope you'll still be friends with me after the game.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_lost">
            <case stage="0-7" id="46" oneShotId="24">
                <condition status="lost_all" role="target" />
                <condition count="0" status="not_alive" />
                <state img="#-brag.png">~Target~ is the first one out, Sorry, but I'm trying to win here. At least you can still enjoy the game.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="6">
                <condition role="target" consecutiveLosses="3" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">I can't tell if you're trying to lose at this point. No one's that unlucky, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="56">
                <test expr="~target.lead~" cmp="&gt;" value="1" />
                <state img="#-normal.png">I'll chip away all the defenses you have ~target~! I've gotten pretty good at that!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-brag.png">Boom! I win!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Did I distract you? I'm not sorry.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_stripped">
            <case stage="0-9" id="5">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <test expr="~clothing.generic~" value="bra" />
                <test expr="~target.wearing(shirt)~" cmp="!=" value="~blank~" />
                <state img="#-aroused.png">That's a cool trick! Can you teach me it after the game?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="26" oneShotId="19">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <test expr="~clothing.generic~" value="shoes" />
                <test expr="~target.wearing(shoes)~" cmp="!=" value="~blank~" />
                <state img="#-scared.png">How prepared did you come to this game? How did you even manage that?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="28">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <test expr="~clothing.generic~" value="socks" />
                <test expr="~target.wearing(shoes)~" cmp="!=" value="~blank~" />
                <state img="#-upset.png">You can't put your shoes back on! They came off!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="29">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <test expr="~clothing.generic~" value="underwear" />
                <test expr="~target.wearing(pants|shorts)~" cmp="!=" value="~blank~" />
                <state img="#-scared.png">I don't want to see what you look like naked if you can do that!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="27" oneShotId="20">
                <test expr="~clothing.generic~" value="underwear" />
                <test expr="~target.wearing(underwear)~" cmp="!=" value="~blank~" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">I guess that's one way of keeping your crotch hidden, but couldn't you have just worn a normal outfit?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="37" oneShotId="22">
                <condition status="naked" role="target" />
                <state img="#-cocky.png">Careful, ~name~, you can't afford another mistake if you want to win this game.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="chihiro" />
                <state img="#-disapointed.png">Why didn't you correct me? Now I feel terrible for saying you were a girl this whole time...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-brag.png" oneShotId="87">I win! You know the rules ~target~. </state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png" oneShotId="88">Did you try your hardest? Or did you give in to the temptation of losing?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="89">I believe that's the last loss for you. That was fun while it lasted.</state>
                <state img="#-normal.png" oneShotId="86">Don't feel too bad about losing, it'll ruin the next part for you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-laugh.png" oneShotId="94">There's no shame in losing. There's a little shame in the forfeit though.</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png" oneShotId="95">Just don't make a mess. I don't know what will happen if any gets on me.</state>
                <state img="#-normal.png" oneShotId="96">Hey! Welcome to the loser's corner.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="97">You gave it your best! Don't worry about losing; it's just a game about luck.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-awkward.png">You have fun with that. I'll just ignore you for a little while and keep doing . . . this.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">I've never thought about how boys masturbate. It seems pretty straightforward.</state>
                <state img="#-laugh.png">When you grab it like that; it looks like you're holding my sword!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-confused.png">How hard are you gripping? Wouldn't it hurt?</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">This is why we need chairs! It's rude to make us do this on the floor.</state>
                <state img="#-normal.png">You look like you're getting a workout in ~target~. Make sure to use your other arm to even out.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-9" id="74">
                <condition role="target" character="twisted_fate" sayingMarker="Hat_Cheat" />
                <state img="#-mad.png">You were cheating! Oh, you better start running!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-normal.png">Thanks for keeping it over there.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">That shot out with such inaccuracy. How are you supposed to aim with that?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">That was really interesting to watch! Boys and girls both just rub it until it feels good.</state>
                <state img="#-cocky.png">That didn't seem like a large payload you fired. When was the last time you masturbated?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-aroused.png" oneShotId="102">Don't think of it as losing. It's more like stress relief.</state>
                <state img="#-sparkle.png" oneShotId="103">~Target~ lost? I was hoping she would!</state>
                <state img="#-brag.png" oneShotId="104">You don't have anything left. It was fun playing with you though.</state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png" oneShotId="105">I'll happily accept this as a prize.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="111">I get it, you want to masturbate next to me. It's more fun with friends</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png" oneShotId="112">When you think about it; only the losers of this game get a prize.</state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png" oneShotId="113">Let's see if masturbating is more fun with friends.</state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png" oneShotId="110">I can help with your forfeit if you want.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-9" id="69">
                <condition role="target" character="nico_robin" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png">That is...freaky.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-very aroused.png">This is way better than imagining things.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">If you want any pointers I'd love to help out.</state>
                <state img="#-normal.png">Try to enjoy it. If you need us to look away just ask, and I'll make sure to assist you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-brag.png">If you want my help just ask.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">You can sit in my lap if you want. It's better than the floor.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-aroused.png">That's some really good form.</state>
                <state img="#-very aroused.png">I'm definitely doing this again on my next day off.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Keep it up, ~target~. You're doing great!</state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png">You're pretty good. Can I get some tips later?</state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png">I like a girl who can take losing that seriously.</state>
                <state img="#-very aroused.png">Girls are so pretty, and hot, and pretty hot!</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">I could watch ~target~ all day.</state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png">If your wrist gets tired let me know. I'll be happy to help.</state>
                <state img="#-very aroused.png">Oh woooow. That's getting the heart rate up.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-very aroused.png">I'll be thinking about that for a while.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">I think we're past the friend stage now. </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate_first">
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-disapointed.png">No! I'm the first one? I must have been doing something wrong.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate">
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-cocky.png">You win. That was a fun game though. </state>
                <state img="#-laugh.png">I lost. It feels like I'm getting a prize though.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="start_masturbating">
            <case stage="7" priority="0">
                <state img="#-aroused.png">I wonder who is going to enjoy this more, me or you guys?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="masturbating">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-upset.png">I still have my sword. So don't start leering at me.</state>
                <state img="#-normal.png">I should do this more often. I hardly get alone time though.</state>
                <state img="#-disapointed.png">It's embarrassing if you stare too much.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">I used to do this in bunks before, but this is a little too public.</state>
                <state img="#-flirt.png">I haven't done this in a while. I forget how good it feels.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Oh! I forgot other people were here for a second.</state>
                <state img="#-disapointed.png">She-Ra might be hotter, but it feels like a waste to use her powers like this.</state>
                <state img="#-very aroused.png">I'm starting to feel it.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Do I have to talk about this? It feels weird talking about anything else.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="heavy_masturbating">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-Heavy3.png">Heh, getting really close now.</state>
                <state img="#-Heavy2.png">I should be careful or I might break something.</state>
                <state img="#-Heavy1.png">. . .</state>
                <state img="#-Heavy2.png">I might moan, so, don't judge me, please.</state>
                <state img="#-Heavy1.png">Hah, hah, yes.</state>
                <state img="#-Heavy3.png">Almost there.</state>
                <state img="#-Heavy1.png">Yes, yes, yes.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finishing_masturbating">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="Cum.png" marker="Admitted">Catra!</state>
                <state img="Cum.png">AHHHH!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="9" id="52">
                <condition count="0" status="not_lost_all" />
                <condition count="2" status="alive" var="playing" />
                <state img="#-sparkle.png">That was fun, but this is what I've been waiting for. A showdown!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9" priority="10">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Admitted==1" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Can we all forget I just said that?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Wow, I needed that.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="after_masturbating">
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-aroused.png" oneShotId="22">Wow! I think I successfully relaxed tonight. Check that off the to-do list.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">After the game can we go over some card-swapping strategies? I think I could learn a lot from you all.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Does, um, anyone have a towel?</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">I don't think I'm into exhibitionism, but standing around naked is pretty hot.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">Am I supposed to commentate on everything now?</state>
                <state img="#-disapointed.png">Can I keep playing? I just want to practice some more.</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">Sorry to interrupt the flow of things here, but can I go get a drink or something?</state>
                <state img="#-awkward.png">The post-game banter completely slipped my mind. I should have practiced this part.</state>
                <state img="#-normal.png">If this keeps up much longer I might have enough energy to go again.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_victory">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Boom! I knew I had this! Thanks for the fun time, everyone. I need to uh, go use the bathroom.</state>
                <state img="#-sparkle.png">I won? I knew I could do it! Do I get a prize? A hug, maybe?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_defeat">
            <case stage="9" id="45">
                <condition status="lost_all" role="target" />
                <test expr="~self.place~" value="2" />
                <state img="#-normal.png" collectible="Mini">I was so close! Maybe I should have kept my socks after all. Oh well, good game ~target~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9" id="44">
                <test expr="~self.place~" value="2" />
                <state img="#-cocky.png" collectible="Mini">Wow! That was a close game. I almost had it too! Let's go again. I bet I can beat you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-aroused.png" collectible="Mini">I don't feel like a loser. I feel pretty relaxed! This game is awesome! Let's go again, uh, if you want.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

    </behaviour>
</opponent>
