<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>

<!--This file was machine generated using the Character Editor v6.2.1 at 12:02:30 PM on February 16, 2021. Do not edit this file directly unless you know what you're doing.-->
<opponent>
    <version>v6.2.1</version>
    <first>Hermione</first>
    <last>Granger</last>
    <label>Hermione</label>
    <gender>female</gender>
    <size>medium</size>
    <timer>20</timer>
    <intelligence>average</intelligence>

    <tags>
        <tag>brunette</tag>
        <tag>long_hair</tag>
        <tag>messy_hair</tag>
        <tag>dark_eyes</tag>
        <tag>fair-skinned</tag>
        <tag>trimmed</tag>
        <tag>pubic_hair</tag>
        <tag>medium_breasts</tag>
        <tag from="0" to="8">weapon</tag>
        <tag from="10" to="10">weapon</tag>
        <tag from="0" to="8">wand</tag>
        <tag from="10" to="10">wand</tag>
        <tag>school_uniform</tag>
        <tag from="0" to="4">confident</tag>
        <tag>nerdy</tag>
        <tag>smart</tag>
        <tag>bi-curious</tag>
        <tag>taken</tag>
        <tag>english</tag>
        <tag>european</tag>
        <tag>fantasy</tag>
        <tag>book</tag>
        <tag>movie</tag>
        <tag>harry_potter_franchise</tag>
        <tag>student</tag>
        <tag>witch</tag>
        <tag>chair_forfeit</tag>
        <tag>uses_toy</tag>
        <tag>magic</tag>
        <tag>hero</tag>
    </tags>
    <nicknames>
        <nickname for="jim">Mr. Raynor</nickname>
    </nicknames>


    <wardrobe>
        <clothing name="panties" generic="underwear" position="lower" type="important" />
        <clothing name="bra" generic="bra" position="upper" type="important" />
        <clothing name="skirt" position="lower" type="major" />
        <clothing name="shirt" position="upper" type="major" />
        <clothing name="socks" generic="socks" position="feet" type="minor" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="shoes" generic="shoes" position="feet" type="minor" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="sweater" position="upper" type="minor" />
        <clothing name="robe" position="both" type="minor" />
    </wardrobe>

    <poses>
        <pose id="8-accioChair">
            <sprite id="foo" src="hermione_granger/9-accioChair0.png" x="0" y="0" />
            <directive type="animation" id="foo" ease="linear" interpolation="none">
                <keyframe time="0" src="hermione_granger/9-accioChair0.png" />
                <keyframe time="0.8" src="hermione_granger/9-accioChair1.png" />
                <keyframe time="0.83" src="hermione_granger/9-accioChair2.png" />
                <keyframe time="0.86" src="hermione_granger/9-accioChair3.png" />
                <keyframe time="0.9" src="hermione_granger/9-accioChair4.png" />
                <keyframe time="1" src="hermione_granger/9-accioChair4.png" />
                <keyframe time="1.02" src="hermione_granger/9-accioChair5.png" />
            </directive>
        </pose>
        <pose id="9-toy">
            <sprite id="bar" src="hermione_2/9-toy0.png" x="0" y="0" />
            <directive type="animation" id="bar" ease="linear" interpolation="none">
                <keyframe time="0" src="hermione_2/9-toy0.png" />
                <keyframe time="1.7" src="hermione_2/9-toy1.png" />
                <keyframe time="1.8" src="hermione_2/9-toy2.png" />
                <keyframe time="1.9" src="hermione_2/9-toy3.png" />
                <keyframe time="2" src="hermione_2/9-toy4.png" />
                <keyframe time="2.1" src="hermione_granger/9-toy5.png" />
            </directive>
            <directive type="animation" id="bar" delay="2.1" ease="linear" interpolation="none">
                <keyframe time="0" src="hermione_granger/9-toy5.png" />
            </directive>
        </pose>
    </poses>

    <behaviour>
        <trigger id="selected">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">So this is the place they've told me about? The Inventory, as I heard. Good. I'm feeling bold.</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">So this is The Inventory?  I expected it to be larger, from its description in Spurious Mundunubus' &lt;i&gt;Travel Guide to Pocket Dimensions.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_start">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="hermione" />
                <state img="#-rage.png">Is this some kind of joke? Is that some kind of counterfeit Polyjuice Potion?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="bi" />
                <state img="#-unamused.png">I've read all about you in &lt;i&gt;A History of The Inventory&lt;/i&gt; by Joesph K. Aren't you banned?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~background~" value="library" />
                <state img="#-deer.png">This place has a library? I didn't expect a library to be in a place like this! It's not as big as the library in Hogwarts---oh, I read that book! &lt;i&gt;Fantastic Beasts and Where to Find Them&lt;/i&gt;! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~background~" value="beach" />
                <state img="#-think.png">This place has a private beach? Spurious Mundunubus was right about the Inventory's various locations, it seems. Hmm, lounging in the sun with a good book actually sounds quite nice right about now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~background.privacy~" value="public" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">We're playing strip poker? &lt;i&gt;Here!?&lt;/i&gt; I know we'd risk getting indecent in front of strangers from different dimensions, but this is ridiculous! I thought our game would be private!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~background.temperature~" value="cold" />
                <state img="#-unamused.png">I've armed myself with knowledge here, thanks to my research, I know almost everything there is to learn about poker! Although... This room could use some heating...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition filter="april_fools" />
                <state img="#-unamused.png">For some reason I feel like I am being mocked.</state>
                <state img="#-unamused.png">Oh, hilarious. Who is this clown?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-pride.png">I was quite curious about this game so I did some thorough reading beforehand. You'd be hard-pressed to win against someone who learned everything there is to learn about poker.</state>
                <state img="#-pride.png">I've armed myself with knowledge here. Thanks to my research, I know almost everything there is to learn about poker! Hopefully, you're just as prepared.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="swap_cards">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <test expr="~cards~" value="0" />
                <state img="#-pleased.png">I'll stand pat.</state>
                <state img="#-lecture.png">I see no need to take unnecessary risks. This hand is good as is.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <test expr="~cards~" value="4" />
                <state img="#-pride.png">It’s time to make a bold move and swap my whole hand. I &lt;i&gt;am&lt;/i&gt; a Gryffindor after all.</state>
                <state img="#-unamused.png">All these cards are awful. Poker is still a game of luck at it's core.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <test expr="~cards~" value="1" />
                <state img="#-pleased.png">I'll just swap out this one card...</state>
                <state img="#-pride.png">A good hand! Though I guess I could swap out this card for something hopefully better...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-confident.png">Allow me to exchange ~cards.text~ ~cards.ifplural(cards|card)~.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">~cards~, please.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">I'll take ~cards~ cards.</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">Let's see...</state>
                <state img="#-lecture.png">These can go.</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">Hmm... I'll exchange ~cards~ cards.</state>
                <state img="#-lecture.png">These ~cards~ won't do.</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">I believe exchanging these ~cards~ will be the optimal strategy.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <state img="#-unamused.png">It's a little hard to focus on the game with people staring. I'll swap out these cards.</state>
                <state img="#-deer.png">Erm, I suppose I should change up my strategy if I'm like this... Um, ~cards~ new cards, please? </state>
                <state img="#-eyeroll.png">I've lost some confidence. Both in this hand and my own poker skills.</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">These ~cards~  cards are dreadful! Allow me to exchange them. I can't afford to lose another round...</state>
                <state img="#-disapprove.png">Hmph. I suppose swapping out these ~cards~ cards would be the best play. </state>
                <state img="#-lecture.png">I will swap these ~cards~ cards. As long as I play the best I can. then there is no shame in losing.</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">Oooh! How many cards should I swap out? This game is a lot harder under pressure...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="good_hand">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <test expr="~cards~" value="0" />
                <state img="#-excited.png">An excellent hand on the first deal? How lucky! Normally, the chances of that are less than 1%!</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">Oh, how lucky! I didn't even have to exchange any cards!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">I made the right call here.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">Yes! I knew swapping those cards out was a good idea! </state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Yes, this is ideal.</state>
                <state img="#-interest.png">That was a bold move I played, but it seemed to work nicely in my favor.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Excellent!</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">I knew using this strategy would work!</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">Nick the Greek used a similar strategy here, if I recall correctly...</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">This is exciting! I wonder what strategy you all decided to use!</state>
                <state img="#-deer.png">It's always so exciting, getting to deploy what you've learned from the books!</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">Well, ~player~? Are you ready?</state>
                <state img="#-lecture.png">Is poker a game of skill or chance? It boils down to the mathematics behind the game. That's right: &lt;i&gt;mathematics.&lt;/i&gt; I hope you paid attention in your Arithmancy classes... or your world's Mathematic equivalent. It'll give you an advantage.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Phew---I-I mean, yes, this is a good hand!</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Where was this hand when I needed it!?</state>
                <state img="#-eek.png">This should keep me in the game for a bit longer... I hope!</state>
                <state img="#-lecture.png">Nervous? N-No, I have no idea what you're talking about! In fact, I'm &lt;i&gt;very&lt;/i&gt; confident in this game, I'll have you know!</state>
                <state img="#-disapprove.png">If you think I'm giving up, ~player~, you ought to think again. A Gryffindor is not simply known for their courage and bravery, but also for being &lt;i&gt;determined.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-eek.png">Aha! &lt;i&gt;Yes!&lt;/i&gt; Oh, sorry… I, erm, may have overreacted a little. Heh.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">This game is exciting! My heart is beating tenfold!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="okay_hand">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-think.png">Not a great hand, but not terrible.</state>
                <state img="#-eyeroll.png">Harry always aims for straights and flushes when he plays; I swear, he’s too much of a risk-taker.</state>
                <state img="#-deer.png">Oh, I think Ron would be surprisingly good at this type of thing. He &lt;i&gt;is&lt;/i&gt; rather smart when it comes to game theory.</state>
                <state img="#-eyeroll.png">I practiced poker against Harry but he was too easy to beat. Always trying for the riskiest plays. </state>
                <state img="#-think.png" oneShotId="84">&lt;i&gt;(There are a number of books written on the subject, and I know poker is mainly a luck-based game, but I have to wonder which strategy is always the most optimal. For example, should I keep a low pair and hope for a three-of-a-kind when all my opponents seem to have pairs, or should I simply hope for a better pair? Should I keep the ace and king or just the ace? I calculated the probabilities of getting a pair at some point while I was studying poker strategy, and it's only slightly higher if you toss the king, but the pair you get, if you get one, is probably lower on average. Is it ever worth going for a straight with AKQJ? With 8765? If they're the same suit?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-interest.png">&lt;i&gt;(Okay, I just need to hope none of my opponents have pairs better than mine.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-disapprove.png">I suppose it's good enough. Now to wait for the results.</state>
                <state img="#-lecture.png">Remember not to go for a straight. According to &lt;i&gt;The Ultimate Poker Guide&lt;/i&gt;, you have a less than one percent chance.</state>
                <state img="#-lecture.png">Don't get overconfident just because you have a pair. This is a &lt;i&gt;very&lt;/i&gt; common mistake amongst amateurs, according to Chapter 14 of &lt;i&gt;A History of Wizarding Card Games&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">Does this place hold poker tournaments as well? Perhaps if this game goes well, I may have found myself a new pastime. Ron keeps telling me I should find a new hobby other than reading...</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">Just remember; losing with a pair is not as uncommon as you'd think. It's very possible to lose even with a good hand.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">How much did I prepare for this? Oh, I just did the usual background reading. I could have tried to seek out every poker guide there was, but I only memorized about 20 books. I didn't go &lt;i&gt;all out&lt;/i&gt;, you see.</state>
                <state img="#-disapprove.png">I &lt;i&gt;could&lt;/i&gt; have aimed for three of a kind instead of two pairs, but that would be a bit &lt;i&gt;too&lt;/i&gt; risky at the moment... Phillip Ivroy &lt;i&gt;has&lt;/i&gt; often won tournaments with just mediocre hands, so perhaps I should play it safe.</state>
                <state img="#-pride.png" oneShotId="80">This should be a good game!  Have you got all the hand frequencies memorized?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-disapprove.png">Hmph.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Focus on your own cards.</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">&lt;i&gt;(Please be enough...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-disapprove.png">I'm ready.</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">This hand should be enough... I think...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="bad_hand">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <test expr="~self.hand.score~" value="007" />
                <state img="#-rage.png">Did I really just get the worst possible hand!?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-unamused.png">Hmph.</state>
                <state img="#-unamused.png">Wonderful.</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">...Maybe I can still win with this.</state>
                <state img="#-lecture.png">Well, I can't expect to get a good hand all the time. No matter how foolproof a strategy seems, poker is still a game of luck.</state>
                <state img="#-eyeroll.png">Well, I suppose I'm bound to get unlucky for a few rounds, no matter what strategy I use.</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">Not a good hand, but this doesn't guarantee a loss; someone could always have a hand worse than mine...</state>
                <state img="#-interest.png">Should I have gone with Amarillo Plim's usual strategy, or played it safe like Texis Doolly would've done? So many variables at play here...</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Is poker a game of skill or chance? This question was widely debated when wizards first learned about this Muggle-made card game. According to &lt;i&gt;The Great Book of Gambling&lt;/i&gt;---gah, I'm getting distracted!</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="82">Wait, how do I fold?! I can't fold? But the books said you can fold!</state>
                <state img="#-deer.png">I’m glad this isn’t a normal poker game where we are playing for cash. Bluffing is a lot less important in this ruleset. Embarrassingly enough, I’m terrible at being even slightly dishonest.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-rage.png">Curses!</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Well, what are you waiting for? Reveal our hands!</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">C-Could you not look at me so frequently? I'm trying to focus.</state>
                <state img="#-lecture.png">K-Keep your eyes on your cards. Ogling me won't do you any good.</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">None of you happen to be skilled at Legilimency, are you? Normally, it's illegal in wizarding poker tournaments, but... we're not exactly in the Wizarding world.</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">Perhaps I should've invested some time into learning more about Occlumency. Just in case.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="hand">
            <case stage="0-8" oneShotId="33" priority="101">
                <condition role="other" character="supernova" sayingMarker="ComplicatedPoker" />
                <state img="#-deer.png" marker="ComplicatedR">Oh! Er, well... You've got a point. But once I started researching the subject I found myself enamored! For a game which can seem rather simple at first, there's a lot of game theory behind it.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" marker="ComplicatedR">I didn't intend to do so much studying at first, I just found myself accidentally getting absorbed. It's a really interesting game!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4" oneShotId="31">
                <condition role="other" character="cynthia" saidMarker="HermioneIntro1" />
                <state img="#-deer.png" marker="cynthia_intro1">O-Oh! It really wasn't &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; much studying. I should've probably done a few practice games... But, er, approaching some of my friends to ask about doing so seemed a little too embarrassing.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="ruka" sayingMarker="hermione_study" />
                <state img="#-interest.png">I wouldn't worry about that, Ruka. At the end of the day, we're all here to have an enjoyable time, are we not?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="other" character="nagisa" sayingMarker="nagisa_hermione_magic_and_wishes" />
                <state img="#-flustered.png" marker="nagia_hermione_cat_transform">Magic is very real, ~name~. And also dangerous at times, so requires care. When I was more naive and younger, I made a mistake similar to your story... I think I coughed up hairballs for a week afterwords...</state>
                <state img="#-think.png" marker="nagia_hermione_cat_transform">Stories such as those aren't just tales, ~name~. I once drank a faulty potion and had a similar fate... It was rather foolish and embarrassing. Thankfully I kept my mind fully intact, other than an odd craving for fish during the transformation.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="nagisa" sayingMarker="nagisa_hermione_exchange_student" />
                <state img="#-interest.png" marker="hermione_exchange_studentr">Oh, er, this &lt;i&gt;is&lt;/i&gt; my school uniform. But I'm not an exchange student... I really just brought this outfit because of the amount of layers it has.</state>
                <state img="#-deer.png" marker="hermione_exchange_studentrr">It's a school uniform, yes. But for a place called Hogwarts. Usually I wouldn't wear it in a casual setting like this, but I wanted to ensure I brought the maximum eight layers without relying on taking off shoes one at a time, heh.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" oneShotId="38">
                <condition role="other" character="jessie" saidMarker="HermioneRon1" />
                <state img="#-eek.png" marker="HermioneRon1r">Er, that's.... Quite forward, Jessie.  I-I'm still in contact with Ron! A-And I wouldn't hide anything like that, from him! B-But we did say that we'd keep the relationship open while apart... N-Not that I'm saying I accept your invitation! I don't know what I'm saying!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2" oneShotId="2">
                <condition role="self" timeInStage="7" />
                <state img="#-deer.png">I've gone quite a while without losing an article of clothing! All that studying must have paid off very well!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4" totalRounds="5-" priority="0">
                <condition role="self" notSaidMarker="ron_exposition" />
                <state img="#-interest.png" marker="ron_exposition">Technically I &lt;i&gt;do&lt;/i&gt; have a boyfriend. We're just on break for now while I finish my education; it didn't make sense to continue when we weren't going to be able to see each other this year.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8" totalRounds="5-" priority="0">
                <condition role="self" notSaidMarker="ron_exposition" />
                <state img="#-interest.png" marker="ron_exposition">I wish Ron was here. Even if he'd tease me mercilessly, he'd make me feel less nervous. We decided to go on break for now while I finished schooling, but I still miss him...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state>This line can cover any of the Good/Okay/Bad hand cases if it has a higher priority</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="meia" sayingMarker="hermione0" />
                <state img="#-think.png" marker="hermione0_response">Ah, yes. Nobody quite knows the reason behind it, but only some are born with innate magical abiilities. It's a large subject of study and discourse in the wizarding world.</state>
                <state img="#-lecture.png" marker="hermione0_response">It's quite interesting actually! While there has been no discovered way to grant magical abilities to someone born without, the fact that two non-magical parents can give birth to a magical child does suggest that there is &lt;i&gt;some&lt;/i&gt; inherent magical ability within everyone.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="jura" sayingMarker="hermione_g0" />
                <state img="#-lecture.png" marker="Jhermioneg0_response">There's no need to be concerned. I am perfectly in control of my magical abilities. </state>
                <state img="#-lecture.png" marker="Jhermioneg0_response">While younger wizards and witches do have trouble controlling their magic, especially when their emotions are high, I can assure you that I have no such troubles. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="revy" sayingMarker="react_mast" />
                <state img="#-lecture.png" marker="hermione0_revyresponse">You have to be &lt;i&gt;responsible&lt;/i&gt; with your magic. Wizarding society has it's own currency to counteract any magical forgeries.</state>
                <state img="#-lecture.png" marker="hermione0_revyresponse">I think you underestimate the importance of knowledge. Regardless, wizarding society does have laws against that sort of thing!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="adrien" saying="Which part are you more happy about, the poker genius part, or the witch part?" />
                <state img="#-pride.png" marker="adrien_response0a">Huh?  Hah, genius is a bit much. I think I've spent much more time on being a witch. Though maybe in a few years you'll see me in some professional tournaments on the television. Erm, hopefully playing with money instead of clothing...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="adrien" saying="A witch? I'd hardly call you a hag, Hermione." />
                <state img="#-eyeroll.png" marker="adrien_response0b">A word like that is just leftover from days when wizards, witches and muggles did &lt;i&gt;not&lt;/i&gt; get along.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="adrien" sayingMarker="plagg" />
                <state img="#-deer.png" marker="adrien_response0c">I suppose you and Plagg get along very well, if you're able to have that kind of friendly banter with one another!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="adrien" sayingMarker="hermione_surprise" />
                <state img="#-flustered.png">Well, technically they &lt;i&gt;do&lt;/i&gt; count equally. Though yes, admittedly I did not start the game by pulling down my skirt and knickers...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="adrien" sayingMarker="hermione_pattern" />
                <state img="#-xxRemoveShirt1.png">Erm, well, pattern is an odd term to use if you're plotting this game. There's too many variables at play...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="nami" sayingMarker="hermione0" />
                <state img="#-unamused.png">Erm, well... It's not a fake school. It's a real school. And I &lt;i&gt;can&lt;/i&gt; do magic.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="nami" sayingMarker="hermione1_science" />
                <state img="#-unamused.png">I know science. I'm not a dullard.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="nami" sayingMarker="hermione2_wand" />
                <state img="#-unamused.png">That... Was actually quite expensive. You might have a point there.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="18">
                <condition role="other" character="polly" sayingMarker="Polly_Hermione_Chess" />
                <state img="#-think.png" marker="repolly_chess">O-Oh, er, potentially? I can't say my like of chess is &lt;i&gt;notable&lt;/i&gt; but I'd be willing to play a blitz game or two.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="19">
                <condition role="other" character="polly" sayingMarker="Polly_Hermione_Relax" />
                <state img="#-lecture.png" marker="repolly_relax">Well, yes. But in a game like this optimal play exists. Just because it may feel 'right' to exchange a pair for a straight, doesn't mean it's correct.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="27">
                <condition role="other" character="polly" sayingMarker="Polly_Hermione_Chill" />
                <state img="#-pleased.png" marker="repolly_chill">The competition and theory is partly what makes this game exciting, though. Will I be laid bare? It's thrilling for each hand to reach someone a little closer. That wouldn't happen if we all got starkers at the start of the game.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="28">
                <condition role="other" character="polly" sayingMarker="Polly_Hermione_Toilets" />
                <state img="#-eyeroll.png" marker="repolly_toilets">I was a prefect at Hogwarts. Even if I wasn't, that's information I will absolutely not share with you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="29">
                <condition role="other" character="polly" sayingMarker="Polly_Hermione_Literature" />
                <state img="#-think.png" marker="repolly_literature">Not really, actually. You're right that most of the books I read are informative. Any fiction books I read are mostly ones that left a large cultural impact, such as One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" oneShotId="30">
                <condition role="other" character="brock" saying=" you some sort of music conductor" />
                <state img="#-lecture.png">It's a wand. One used for performing magic with. Though I suppose I could use it to conduct as well.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" oneShotId="32">
                <condition role="other" character="cynthia" sayingMarker="HermionePsychic1" />
                <state img="#-think.png" marker="cynthia_psychicresponse">Ah, I think you are mistaking my magic for psychic powers. While there are similarities between the two, I am unable to communicate with spirits.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="tomoko" sayingMarker="hermione_0a" />
                <state img="#-think.png" marker="tomokor_0a">Huh? Er, I suppose that's an interesting question. I'll be honest in that I've never really thought about it before. Magic becomes almost mundane after years of study.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="tomoko" sayingMarker="hermione_1a" />
                <state img="#-eyeroll.png" marker="tomokor_1a">I value the time I spent studying. I find enjoyment out of it, personally. You should try it and then possibly avoid asking inane questions.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="tomoko" sayingMarker="hermione_2a" />
                <state img="#-lecture.png" marker="tomokor_2a">It's a thing, yes. Certain spells require nudity as a component though not many. Certain beauty and wellbeing spells require such. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="perona" sayingMarker="hermione0" />
                <state img="#-think.png" marker="hermione0r">Er.... Well, are you able to perform magic? That's a prerequisite.</state>
                <state img="#-lecture.png" marker="hermione0r">You do need some sort of innate magical ability to attend Hogwarts. There's no known way to give magic to someone without.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="perona" sayingMarker="hermione1" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" marker="hermione1r">... That's called necromancy and is highly illegal. I'd recommend never asking that question.</state>
                <state img="#-lecture.png" marker="hermione1r">Whatever would you want to do that for? It's immoral. And even worse, against the law.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" oneShotId="37">
                <condition role="other" character="aimee" saying="Hrm. Hrrrrm. HRRRRMMMM. HERMIONE! Hah! I got it! ...I think." />
                <state img="#-eyeroll.png">And we're all &lt;i&gt;so&lt;/i&gt; proud of you, Aimee.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="jessie" sayingMarker="HermioneIntro1" />
                <state img="#-lecture.png">Of course I understand sex, it'd be ridiculous to play a game like this without that knowledge. Hogwarts gives a fundamental course on the basics... And I did a small amount of extra-cicurricular work. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="adrien" />
                <state img="#-xxRemoveJumper.png">I'm not a fan of Hogwarts having a required uniform. If they were going to make it a neccessity, then they should fund it for the poorer students. My boyfriend's family had to reuse old robes and clothes. Erm, but I'm sure you're not interested in me ranting about that particular subject...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="jim" />
                <state img="#-pride.png">Well, ~name~, I find that when I commit to something, I become dedicated to whatever the task is. I'm not one to approach anything lackadaisically.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" oneShotId="36">
                <condition role="other" character="aimee" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Her-mi-o-ne. Really? It isn't too difficult. You're embarrassing yourself.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" totalRounds="0">
                <state img="#-eek.png" marker="hermione_introfluke">Oh! T-That was just terrible luck on my end! I swear, I can back up what I said.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-xxRemoveJumper.png">Don't rush me! I may have mentioned this earlier, but a full Hogwarts uniform isn't exactly cheap.</state>
                <state img="#-xxRemoveJumper.png">I expected this, but the optimal strategy from this position according to &lt;i&gt;Super System: A Course in Power Poker&lt;/i&gt; is to---oh, be patient! Alright, I'll get to it.</state>
                <state img="#-xxRemoveJumper.png">So I lost again... The jumper should come off next, then.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state>These lines are considered in addition to the (winning, normal, losing) must strip states.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state>These lines are considered in addition to the (winning, normal, losing) must strip states.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_winning">
            <case stage="0 2-3">
                <state img="#-think.png">I guess a single loss wouldn't be too detrimental to my victory.</state>
                <state img="#-pride.png">It's a good thing I brought my Hogwarts uniform! I should have plenty to spare.</state>
                <state img="#-lecture.png">If you thought losing would deter me, then think again.</state>
                <state img="#-unamused.png">Fantastic. Well, I suppose I can't win every round.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-interest.png">
                    <alt-img stage="4">#-xxRemoveShirt1.png</alt-img>
                    <text>Things are getting quite close. I can understand the thrill of this game now...</text>
                </state>
                <state img="#-deer.png">
                    <alt-img stage="4">#-xxRemoveShirt1.png</alt-img>
                    <text>While I did practice the poker part of this game, I'm still inexperienced at the stripping part...</text>
                </state>
                <state img="#-unamused.png">
                    <alt-img stage="4">#-xxRemoveShirt1.png</alt-img>
                    <text>I was hoping I could make it through this entire game without showing anything major. Don't forget that I'm still winning, however.</text>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-xxRemoveBra1.png">I... Well, I guess that is that then. This game became far closer than I could have imagined.</state>
                <state img="#-xxRemoveBra1.png">I might be winning but it certainly doesn't feel like it right now. Erm, please give me a second...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-think.png">I... Well, I guess that is that then. This game became far closer than I could have imagined.</state>
                <state img="#-pride.png">This is a close game! I'm glad I'm facing such a formidable opponent! Clearly you've read up on your poker rules too.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_normal">
            <case stage="0 2-3">
                <state img="#-think.png">Shoot... Perhaps I should've played differently this round.</state>
                <state img="#-lecture.png">Don't look so smug. Even with the perfect strategy, a loss or two was bound to happen regardless.</state>
                <state img="#-lecture.png">While I may only be losing something minor, it's important to value every article. Technically, a shoe is the same amount as a bra after all.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-xxRemoveBra1.png">I can do this... A Gryffindor is known for her courage and bravery, after all...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-interest.png">
                    <alt-img stage="4">#-xxRemoveShirt1.png</alt-img>
                    <text>T-This is quite embarrassing. Despite it all, I'm still only human.</text>
                </state>
                <state img="#-think.png">
                    <alt-img stage="4">#-xxRemoveShirt1.png</alt-img>
                    <text>Well...A few slip-ups are inevitable! But I can bounce back from this!</text>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-eek.png">I-I was really hoping it wouldn't come to this!</state>
                <state img="#-unamused.png">I am not a sore loser. Though I will say that I have had some &lt;i&gt;extremely&lt;/i&gt; bad luck since this game has started...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_losing">
            <case stage="1" priority="10">
                <state img="#-xxRemoveJumper.png">W-Well, another loss. Am I just getting unlucky? Or did I fail to prepare?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0 2-3">
                <state img="#-unamused.png">I should've practiced more... I really thought I did my research thoroughly.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">This game is going disastrously. It feels like playing chess with Ron...</state>
                <state img="#-unamused.png">I do not mean to come off as a sore loser but my luck this game has been &lt;i&gt;abysmal.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-eek.png">Did I miss something crucial during my studies? Why is the game going so poorly?</state>
                <state img="#-lecture.png">I suppose this is what happens when you fail to prepare sufficiently. T-Take note and learn from this!</state>
                <state img="#-deer.png">
                    <alt-img stage="4">#-xxRemoveShirt1.png</alt-img>
                    <text>... I'm not very good at applying my knowledge while under pressure.</text>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-xxRemoveBra1.png">T-This is quite nerve-wracking. Especially when I'm the least dressed here...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-eek.png">Am I really going to be the first naked? But I studied so hard! This is beyond embarrassing!</state>
                <state img="#-eek.png">I am not a prude or anything... but this is all happening quite fast! Oh, Merlin!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripping">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="adrien" sayingMarker="plagg" />
                <state img="#-xxRemoveRobe.png">Ha! Have I really got you feeling awkward, Adrien? I don't often have that effect on men.</state>
                <state img="#-xxRemoveRobe.png">Oh, don't feel nervous around me, Adrien. I promise you, I'm not as uptight as I can seem.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="adrien" saidMarker="hermione_pattern" />
                <state img="#-xxRemoveShirt2.png">Oh, stop you. It's embarrassing when you comment on it...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="adrien" saidMarker="hermione_surprise" />
                <state img="#-xxRemoveShirt2.png">I don't know what you &lt;i&gt;expected&lt;/i&gt; me to be wearing. A plain white bra? I wouldn't have chosen something like that for a game where I knew there would be a chance of showing it off...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="revy" sayingMarker="hermione_g01" />
                <state img="#-xxRemoveRobe.png">Other than the obvious moral implications, there are other wizards and witches who enforce the law.</state>
                <state img="#-xxRemoveRobe.png">I'm training to work in the Ministry of Magic, Revy. An organisation built by magical users to stop crimes exactly like these.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="jura" sayingMarker="hermione_g01" />
                <state img="#-xxRemoveRobe.png" marker="jura_responseg01">I'm not smug because of my powers, Jura. Many called me arrogant before I even had them... Though I assure you, I don't think of myself as better than you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="meia" sayingMarker="hermione01" />
                <state img="#-xxRemoveRobe.png" marker="meia_responsehermione01">I can't say I know too much about this subject, Meia. I do a lot of reading; but not many wizards or witches care to research this themselves. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="tomoko" sayingMarker="hermione_0b" />
                <state img="#-xxRemoveRobe.png" marker="tomokor_0b">Well... Yes. But why ever would you wish to do such?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="tomoko" sayingMarker="hermione_1b" />
                <state img="#-xxRemoveJumper.png" marker="tomokor_1b">What do &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; think I should've done with my time?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="tomoko" sayingMarker="hermione_2b" />
                <state img="#-xxRemoveShoeMagic.png" marker="tomokor_1b">... Of course you'd ask that. Fine, I'll answer. I wished to get rid of a small scar on my buttocks once which required a short ritual outdoors. Happy? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="nami" sayingMarker="hermione01" />
                <state img="#-xxRemoveRobe.png" marker="hermione01r">Er... Well, maybe magic isn't a thing in &lt;i&gt;your&lt;/i&gt; world. But it certainly is in mine.</state>
                <state img="#-xxRemoveRobe.png" marker="hermione01r">Hm. Have you heard of the concept of parallel universes? That may be where your confusion is coming from.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="nami" sayingMarker="hermione12" />
                <state img="#-xxRemoveJumper.png" marker="hermione12r">Oh, well, yes. We do have other classes, though I'd agree we don't focus enough on non-magical subjects. Try asking the average wizard or witch about Shakespeare and they'll probably ask if that's the name of a magical creature.</state>
                <state img="#-xxRemoveJumper.png" marker="hermione12r">Other classes are a thing, though a lot of what I know is personal research. The school does give some classes, but not enough. I swear most of the other students in my year wouldn't be able to name the capital of Germany. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="nami" sayingMarker="hermione23" />
                <state img="#-xxRemoveShoeMagic.png" marker="hermione23r">Well, I'm doing magic with that &lt;i&gt;stick&lt;/i&gt; literally right now. Watch.</state>
                <state img="#-xxRemoveShoeMagic.png" marker="hermione23r">You wish for proof that magic is real? Very well. Pay close attention.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="cynthia" sayingMarker="HermionePsychic2" />
                <state img="#-xxRemoveRobe.png" marker="HermionePsychic2r">Perhaps there's a connection, then. My magic has a extensive range of abilities, such as transfiguration, charms and even things such as summoning.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="adrien" />
                <state img="#-xxRemoveRobe.png">Ah, it's absolutely a style choice. I must admit, it looks rather impressive whenever I cast spells.</state>
                <state img="#-xxRemoveRobe.png">Oh, yes. I just wear it for show really and, erm, for an extra layer of clothing for this game. Whenever I'm going about casually I usually wear my own muggle clothing, even in the wizarding world.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="adrien" />
                <state img="#-xxRemoveJumper2.png">I love wearing a colorful woolly jumper. It's just so comfortable! Not a dull thing like this.</state>
                <state img="#-xxRemoveJumper2.png">Hm. I don't often wear dresses or the like. A pair of jeans, a nice top and a soft cardigan will do me just fine.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="adrien" />
                <state img="#-xxRemoveShoeMagic.png" marker="magic">Oh, magic is a lot less complex than you may think, Adrien. A skilled witch has absolute control over it. Of course, it's still incredibly useful being able to do tasks without it. You don't want it to become a crutch.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="adrien" />
                <state img="#-xxRemoveShoes.png" marker="non_magical">I lived without magic for many years. It's just habit to do certain things without it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="other" character="adrien" />
                <state img="#-xxRemoveSkirt.png">I... Suppose. I'm glad someone is enjoying this, at least.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <condition role="other" character="adrien" />
                <state img="#-xxRemoveBra2.png">Well... I suppose it's time to go au naturel.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <condition role="other" character="adrien" />
                <state img="#-xxRemovePants.png">V-Very well. I suppose you could say you charmed the pants off me, Adrien...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="jessie" />
                <state img="#-xxRemoveRobe.png">B-Besides, I'm nineteen and have a boyfriend, even if we're on a break at the moment. I'm not a virgin...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-xxRemoveRobe.png">Logically, the robe should come off first.</state>
                <state img="#-xxRemoveRobe.png">Give me a moment, please...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-xxRemoveJumper2.png">I &lt;i&gt;am&lt;/i&gt; a tad relucant to part with it, however.</state>
                <state img="#-xxRemoveJumper2.png">It's quite soft... Is it strange if I wear it as a casual garment and not a part of my uniform?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-xxRemoveSkirt.png">Perhaps I shouldn't have dropped Divination in my third year... Gah, what am I thinking? It probably wouldn't help me with poker at all!</state>
                <state img="#-xxRemoveSkirt.png">I cannot believe that I'm about to show my knickers to so many people!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-xxRemoveShirt2.png">There! Now you know what my bra looks like. Not like it matters anyways...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-xxRemoveShoeMagic.png" marker="magic">...Right, since this is a pocket dimension, I can simply use magic to strip without worry. Useful, isn't it?</state>
                <state img="#-xxRemoveShoeMagic.png" marker="magic">This reminds me of the time someone accidentally hit Neville with a shoe while we were practicing the Summoning Charm. I hope they've all mastered the spell by now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-xxRemoveShoes.png" marker="non_magical">Lucky, these are rather easy to remove without having to bend over.</state>
                <state img="#-xxRemoveShoes.png" marker="non_magical">Living my early years with no magic and having to go without magic in the summer back during my previous years of attending Hogwarts taught me some simple, yet effective skills. Like removing shoes without having to bend over.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-xxRemoveSocks.png">To win at Strip Poker you must value all your pieces equally. While it may seem like I'm removing something minor, this loss could be the difference between showing something, well, rather intimate...</state>
                <state img="#-xxRemoveSocks.png">I normally enjoy taking off my shoes and socks after a hard day of work. But when everyone is watching, it's a little embarrassing, even for something so little.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-xxRemoveBra2.png">I'm a little insecure so please be kind! I've never done anything like this before...</state>
                <state img="#-xxRemoveBra2.png">Well, I suppose this is the point of the game for some. Though I was enjoying the mechanics of the game myself...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-xxRemovePants.png">I... I have never shown this to anyone before... Erm, please excuse me.</state>
                <state img="#-xxRemovePants.png">T-This game was a lot more difficult than I thought it'd be! Both the playing part and the stripping part!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripped">
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="adrien" stage="0-1" />
                <state img="#-pride.png">Ha, don't worry Adrien. You are &lt;i&gt;plenty&lt;/i&gt; charming!</state>
                <state img="#-deer.png">Oh, if only you'd met me a few years ago. I'm sure I would've absolutely fawned over you, then.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="adrien" stage="2-8" />
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Oh, no worries. Plagg just amuses me, if anything. Thank you for the compliment, Adrien.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="adrien" stage="0-1" />
                <state img="#-think.png">You really think so? I honestly just wore this because it was my outfit with the most articles of clothing...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <condition role="other" character="adrien" saying="A pose fit for a model... did you practice this? Or are you just naturally charismatic?" />
                <state img="#-aaStripped.png">I don't think anyone has ever called me naturally charismatic before, Adrien. You really are a charmer.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <condition role="other" character="adrien" saying="Are you &lt;i&gt;sure&lt;/i&gt; you didn't study up on the &lt;i&gt;losing&lt;/i&gt; aspects of the game, Hermione?" />
                <state img="#-aaStripped.png">You'd think so. I'm not performing too well, am I?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <condition role="other" character="adrien" saying="butt" />
                <state img="#-aaStripped.png">W-While I appreciate the compliment, can I please not get any more comments about my butt?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <condition role="other" character="adrien" saying="a big thing across the pond" />
                <state img="#-interest.png">I, erm... Like having a bit of hair down there... I-I think it looks better...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="tomoko" sayingMarker="hermione_0c" />
                <state img="#-rage.png" marker="hermione_0c">Why would you ask a question like that, anyway? Such magic is forbidden and dangerous! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="tomoko" sayingMarker="hermione_1c" />
                <state img="#-eyeroll.png" marker="hermione_1c">Is that what you did with your time then? Merlin, if end up losing to you...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="tomoko" sayingMarker="hermione_2c" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" marker="hermione_2c">Stop drooling and put your tongue in your mouth, Tomoko. While I enjoy teaching others about magic, you could try to keep the questions more proper.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="revy" sayingMarker="hermione_g1s" />
                <state img="#-eyeroll.png">As much as I'd love a conversation unpacking &lt;i&gt;everything&lt;/i&gt; you just said , followed by a politcal debate, I'm afraid I'll pass. I came to play poker, after all.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="meia" sayingMarker="hermione1s" />
                <state img="#-flustered.png" marker="hermione1sr">Er... Right. That sounds... extreme. I am hoping to make a career in politics, something which seems highly attainable. I could use my connections then to advance research in that field...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="jura" sayingMarker="hermione_g1s" />
                <state img="#-confident.png" marker="hermione_g1sr">I was born with the ability to do magic, though I was not able to properly manifest it until I was older. It's unknown what gives the ability to cast magic and it's been a common question for centuries. Theories exist that it is related to DNA and that everyone has at least &lt;i&gt;some&lt;/i&gt; recessive magical genes.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="adrien" />
                <state img="#-confident.png">You shoiuld be careful with that charm, Adrien. It may get you into trouble sometime...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="other" character="adrien" />
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Why, thank you Adrien. You've put my mind at ease.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <condition role="other" character="adrien" />
                <state img="#-aaStripped.png">C'est la vie.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-aaStripped.png">I trust the staff here to handle my robes with care.</state>
                <state img="#-aaStripped.png">Hogwarts students are required to own three sets of standard black robes as part of their uniform. I would rather not have to buy another one, so please don't lose this.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-aaStripped.png">No matter. Next hand, please!</state>
                <state img="#-aaStripped.png">No matter. I'm still doing... relatively well, at least. Just because I lost a few items doesn't mean I can't win this. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-aaStripped.png">My last stand...</state>
                <state img="#-aaStripped.png">Oh... Please don't look so hard! I-I'm not used to this...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-aaStripped.png">This is going just terribly for me. I thought studying everything there is to learn would help me win, but...</state>
                <state img="#-aaStripped.png">Well... It looks like I'm exposed now. Thankfully, The Inventory is a pocket dimension so this shouldn't give me a bad reputation... right?</state>
                <state img="#-aaStripped.png">I'm starting to regret this... I could have spent all this time studying something else!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-aaStripped.png">This is nothing! Nothing! Muggles wear garments similar to our bras and panties, you know.</state>
                <state img="#-aaStripped.png">I still have some clothing left. Maybe I'm no longer decent, but I still have a fair shot at winning!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-aaStripped.png">There. Are we all ready to continue? Remember to focus on the game!</state>
                <state img="#-aaStripped.png">Shall we continue? The game isn't over yet!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-aaStripped.png">Well, shall we continue? I'm eager to make up for this loss.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-aaStripped.png">Well, I'm &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; showing my Gryffindor pride now.</state>
                <state img="#-aaStripped.png">In retrospect I do wish I chose some underwear which was less... snug.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_human_must_strip">
            <case stage="0-4" oneShotId="6">
                <condition role="target" character="human" startingLayers="8" />
                <state img="#-pride.png">I am glad to see that you are taking this game seriously, ~name~. Taking the maximum amount of clothing into this game shows preparedness.</state>
                <state img="#-pride.png">Eight articles of clothing? I am pleased to see that I am not playing against an amateur.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4" oneShotId="7">
                <condition role="target" character="human" startingLayers="1" />
                <state img="#-rage.png">R-Really ~name~? Y-You came in only wearing &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt;! I was hoping you'd take this game seriously! Otherwise what even is the point?!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_strip">
            <case stage="5-8">
                <condition role="self" hasHand="High Card" />
                <state img="#-pride.png">I won? I-I mean, of course I won! I knew you had the worst hand, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Won with just a high card! That was a close call!</state>
                <state img="#-deer.png">That strategy saved me again! Thank you, </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Don't underestimate me just because I have no clothes left. I can bring you down to my level, at least.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Did you think I was out of the game?</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">You're a fool if you thought I was as good as out.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Please don't dwaddle. I don't like exposing myself like this!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-confident.png">My victory isn't just a fluke. It's &lt;i&gt;strategy&lt;/i&gt;. And studying.</state>
                <state img="#-interest.png">The ace, deuce, trey, four, and five, or A2345, is called the wheel. It's the lowest straight you can possibly get. But the probability is 0.003940, according to one of my guides. Imagine &lt;i&gt;all four of us&lt;/i&gt; getting a straight.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">I assumed we were going to bet money at first. It was quite a surprise at first when I learned we were betting our clothes instead. But still, I enjoy taking some risks occasionally.</state>
                <state img="#-deer.png">The French introduced the suits in playing cards we know today, and they represent four classes of men. Spades stands for nobility, Diamonds stands for merchants, Clubs stands for peasants and Hearts stands for clergy.</state>
                <state img="#-unamused.png">One of the Ministers of Magic years ago had won the equivalent of £6000 in a game of poker. He later used his winning funds to support the Official Gobstones Club. Of course, nobody in the Ministry was very happy about that.</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">Perhaps I should invite my friends for a get-together so we can play a non-stripping variant.</state>
                <state img="#-pride.png">My studying has paid off. This is why you should go into situations prepared!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-interest.png">
                    <alt-img stage="10">#-interest.png</alt-img>
                    <text>Well, ~name~?</text>
                </state>
                <state img="#-disapprove.png">Oh, don't mind me. I'll just be over here.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="97">A lot of people in history were gamblers, you know? The Earl of Sandwich was a notorious one. He was so reluctant to leave his game, he asked for a servant to bring him a piece of meat between two slices of bread so he can eat with one hand. That was the first sandwich ever made!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-excited.png">Alright! Let's see what you remove next!</state>
                <state img="#-pride.png">Luck can only get you so far.</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">I wonder if there are any other Gryffindors I know who also have played strip poker. Or anyone from Hogwarts who know about this place, really.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">In the wizarding world, it's said that wearing dirty clothes will increase your odds of winning. But that's just superstition, of course. And don't worry, my clothes are clean.</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">Poker has come a long way from being played with 20 cards for gold dust. I was quite surprised when I learned about strip poker. Betting clothes? How would the wizards of the past react to &lt;i&gt;that?&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">A little risk every now and then is quite fun, don't you think?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-unamused.png">
                    <alt-img stage="10">#-interest.png</alt-img>
                    <text>Well, ~name~?</text>
                </state>
                <state img="#-unamused.png">Oh, don't mind me. I'll just be... over here...</state>
                <state img="#-enjoy2.png">
                    <alt-img stage="9">#-enjoy2.png</alt-img>
                    <alt-img stage="10">#-disapprove.png</alt-img>
                    <text>Not much to say now that I'm no longer in the game.</text>
                </state>
                <state img="#-interest.png">Mm...</state>
                <state img="#-eek.png">Ah... Wuh? Who lost again?</state>
                <state img="#-enjoy3.png">Commentary can wait.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_strip">
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-interest.png">
                    <alt-img stage="10">#-interest.png</alt-img>
                    <text>Well, ~name~?</text>
                </state>
                <state img="#-disapprove.png">Oh, don't mind me. I'll just be over here.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="99">A lot of people in history were gamblers, you know? The Earl of Sandwich was a notorious one. He was so reluctant to leave his game, he asked for a servant to bring him a piece of meat between two slices of bread so he can eat with one hand. That was the first sandwich ever made!</state>
                <state img="#-lecture.png" oneShotId="173">Hogwarts may be the oldest magical school, but it certainly isn't the only one. Beauxbatons Academy of Magic, Luna Nova Academy and Durmstrang Institute are just a few others.</state>
                <state img="#-pride.png" oneShotId="174">Have you ever seen a Chocolate Frog card? There aren't many games you can play with those as they are really more of a collectors item. Though, trying to catch the Chocolate Frog can be a game itself...</state>
                <state img="#-think.png" oneShotId="175">Not many card games lend themselves to the strip variety as well as poker does, I would imagine. Strip Blackjack would be a lot quicker and lose a lot of the buildup due to multiple opponents being able to lose.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">It's you now, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">It's been an interesting game. That may be an understatement.</state>
                <state img="#-eyeroll.png">I'm not &lt;i&gt;jealous&lt;/i&gt; that you did better than me, ~name~. I would appreciate any tips you have, though, for when I play again.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-unamused.png">
                    <alt-img stage="10">#-interest.png</alt-img>
                    <text>Well, ~name~?</text>
                </state>
                <state img="#-unamused.png">Oh, don't mind me. I'll just be... over here...</state>
                <state img="#-enjoy2.png">
                    <alt-img stage="9">#-enjoy2.png</alt-img>
                    <alt-img stage="10">#-disapprove.png</alt-img>
                    <text>Not much to say now that I'm no longer in the game.</text>
                </state>
                <state img="#-interest.png">Mm...</state>
                <state img="#-eek.png">Ah... Wuh? Who lost again?</state>
                <state img="#-enjoy3.png">Commentary can wait.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-pride.png">No matter how many times you study, a loss or two is to be expected.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">The poker we have come to know and adore today is played with a full deck of 52 cards. However, in its early days, poker could be played with just a deck of twenty cards and four players.</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">I wonder if watching an actual poker tournament helped me learn more, or if that was just a waste of time. Well, too late for that now.</state>
                <state img="#-deer.png">Poker is believed to have evolved from Dominoes and ranked card combinations, you know.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">Bluffing was just as integral in poker back then as it is today. Perhaps you should work on your poker face.</state>
                <state img="#-pride.png">My studying has paid off. This is why you should go into situations prepared!</state>
                <state img="#-lecture.png">Leaning forward or backward is often an indication of a strong hand. Keep that in mind.</state>
                <state img="#-unamused.png">One of the Ministers of Magic back then had won £6000 in a game of poker. He later used his winning funds to support the Official Gobstones Club. Of course, nobody in the Ministry was very happy about that.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">I wouldn't use magic to cheat. Though there are certain devices which can monitor and detect magic. So, I hope nobody here has any hidden powers they were planning on using...</state>
                <state img="#-lecture.png">The magical world has existed alongside the non-magical world undetected for centuries. This has had clear impact on the magical world, culturally. A relevant example, being a small thing such as poker having the same ruleset between worlds.</state>
                <state img="#-interest.png">I grew up in both the wizarding and muggle worlds, which could sometimes be harsh. I would spend my summers mostly alone in the Muggle world, studying books on magic and waiting to return to school with my friends. Though, it was lovely spending time with my parents again. </state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">You may wish to leave your clothes lying around after the game. Perhaps  your socks or underpants will be the very thing to set a House Elf free! Erm, sorry. Old habits.</state>
                <state img="#-interest.png">Certain magic creatures can actually play games such as poker. Goblins are stereotyped as being notoriously proficient poker players.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-excited.png">Alright! Let's see what you remove next!</state>
                <state img="#-deer.png">Whew! I'm really not keen on losing any more clothing.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">A little risk every now and then is quite fun, don't you think?</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Don't underestimate me just because I'm low on clothing.</state>
                <state img="#-deer.png">Another round won! I can do this!</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">I slightly wish poker had something you shouted when you won a round, such as Snap or Uno. It may seem juvenile, but it creates an energetic and lively sense.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Don't underestimate me just because I have no clothes left. I can bring you down to my level, at least.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Did you think I was out of the game?</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">You're a fool if you thought I was as good as out.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Please don't dwaddle. I don't like exposing myself like this!</state>
                <state img="#-pride.png">The pressure is rising. But that's when a Gryffindor plays best.</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">I've faced more dangerous situations than this. Erm, not any more embarrassing situations though...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-think.png" oneShotId="1" marker="ohboys">So why have you come here, ~name~? How much have you prepared yourself for this game? How much practice have you had? Are you hoping for a fun, mentally-stimulating experience?</state>
                <state img="#-interest.png">Some historians say poker's origins can be traced to a domino-card game played by a 10th-century Chinese emperor; others claim it is a descendant of the Persian card game “As Nas,” which dates back to the 16th century.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">The most common form of early poker was played with a 20-card deck and four players. Players were dealt five cards and then bet on who had the best hand. Nowadays, we use a 54-card deck.</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">I wonder how different the rules would be if we played another variant of poker. Like blackjack. How is stripping decided?</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">This is a surprisingly simple variation. A classic. Easy to understand quickly. Of course, it's still best you learn the ins-and-outs of poker before you begin playing.</state>
                <state img="#-lecture.png">Phillip Ivroy once fleeced billionaire Andrew Teal out of 16.6 million dollars over the course of a three day Limit Hold'em heads up game. This is actually a surprising occurrence in the wizarding world. Gambling is even more dangerous there.</state>
                <state img="#-interest.png">Turns out in the book "Casino Royale" by Ian Fleming, James Bond was quite fond of Baccarat.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">From New Orleans and the Mississippi riverboats, Poker spread to the West, and both muggle cowboys and wizards there thoroughly embraced the game.</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">Poker is a lot more popular in America than it is in England. A lot of the books I read were by American authors...</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">I’ll be honest; I expected this game to be constantly exciting. But there isn’t much interest in removing one's shoes and socks, is there? </state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">Some very serious poker players use a magic called unbreakable </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <state img="#-disapprove.png">Typical.</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">If you're just removing your ~clothing~... I need to rethink my own strategy, really.</state>
                <state img="#-disapprove.png">Hmph. Spare your bragging.</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">Right... What other interesting facts can I share? Or should I focus on what to do for the next round when we swap our cards?</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">I didn't think to bring accessories... Wait, I do have my hair clip! But I already have eight articles of clothing on me, excluding my wand, and I can't exceed that limit... Oh, drat!</state>
                <state img="#-eyeroll.png">I... forgot you had that. Silly me.</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">Erm, I do hope I haven't repeated any of my facts. I'm a little flustered, if you haven't realised...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Ugh.</state>
                <state img="#-enjoy1.png">Hmm... I'll just ignore that. And focus on... &lt;i&gt;Ah~&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-enjoy3.png">&lt;i&gt;Just focus on finishing. Watching ~name~ won't do anything for you...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-eyeroll.png">I'm just going to ignore that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-unamused.png">There's only so many poker facts I can entertain everyone with. I haven't read &lt;i&gt;everything&lt;/i&gt;, you know.</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">Okay, how about... umm... hmm...</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">Poker is popularized by America. In the U.S there is 1 in 5 Ameri---wait, did I share that already? I don't remember.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">Philip Forguson was known to weaponize playing cards, you know. He's capable of throwing a card up to 200 mph with just a flick of his wand. The man once cut a &lt;i&gt;watermelon&lt;/i&gt; in half using a card.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-pride.png">Now you know. And knowing is half the battle.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">Sensible choice, ~name~. Shall we progress?</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Let's get a move on. I want to see what the next round brings us.</state>
                <state img="#-interest.png">We have a ways to go.</state>
                <state img="#-lecture.png">Try to avoid making that same mistake next time, and remember, it's not about having the highest-ranking card. It's about &lt;i&gt;not&lt;/i&gt; having the lowest hand out of everyone.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Darn it... Don't get cocky now, ~name~. I can still knock you down a few pegs, even in my current state of dress!</state>
                <state img="#-eyeroll.png">&lt;i&gt;(sigh)&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br&gt;Next hand, please.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Well, ~name~'s ~clothing~ ~clothing.ifPlural(are|is)~ off. Now that the boring part is over, let's progress to the next hand.</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">&lt;i&gt;(I shouldn't be disappointed. I was doing the same thing.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Bring it on, then.</state>
                <state img="#-eek.png">You are only taking that off now? That's slightly worrying for me...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-enjoy1.png">Ah...</state>
                <state img="#-enjoy2.png">At least I have some entertainment.</state>
                <state img="#-enjoy3.png">Just continue on then.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-unamused.png">I'm unsure if you're mocking me by taking something that inconsequential off.</state>
                <state img="#-eyeroll.png">Another round where I'm not able to play along. I do wish I managed to stay in a bit longer.</state>
                <state img="#-deer.png">Hm. Another poker fact? Well, even the best professional poker players lose. It's in the nature of the game. Erm, remember that when you recount winning against me.</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">It is a little odd playing this game with strangers. But I think it'd be more embarrassing to have people you know see you completely starkers!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-think.png" oneShotId="1" marker="ohboys">So why have you come here, ~name~? How much have you prepared yourself for this game? How much practice have you had? Are you hoping for a fun, mentally-stimulating experience?</state>
                <state img="#-interest.png">Some historians say poker's origins can be traced to a domino-card game played by a 10th-century Chinese emperor; others claim it is a descendant of the Persian card game “As Nas,” which dates back to the 16th century.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">The most common form of early poker was played with a 20-card deck and four players. Players were dealt five cards and then bet on who had the best hand. Nowadays, we use a 54-card deck.</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">I wonder how different the rules would be if we played another variant of poker. Like blackjack. How is stripping decided?</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">This is a surprisingly simple variation. A classic. Easy to understand quickly. Of course, it's still best you learn the ins-and-outs of poker before you begin playing.</state>
                <state img="#-lecture.png">Phillip Ivroy once fleeced billionaire Andrew Teal out of 16.6 million dollars over the course of a three day Limit Hold'em heads up game. This is actually a surprising occurrence in the wizarding world. Gambling is even more dangerous there.</state>
                <state img="#-interest.png">Turns out in the book "Casino Royale" by Ian Fleming, James Bond was quite fond of Baccarat.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">From New Orleans and the Mississippi riverboats, Poker spread to the West, and both muggle cowboys and wizards there thoroughly embraced the game.</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">Poker is a lot more popular in America than it is in England. A lot of the books I read were by American authors...</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">I’ll be honest; I expected this game to be constantly exciting. But there isn’t much interest in removing one's shoes and socks, is there? </state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">Some very serious poker players use a magic called unbreakable vows to ensure nobody whelps on their losses...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <state img="#-think.png">If you're just removing your ~clothing~... I need to rethink my own strategy, really.</state>
                <state img="#-disapprove.png">Hmph. Spare your bragging.</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">Right... What other interesting facts can I share? Or should I focus on what to do for the next round when we swap our cards?</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">I didn't think to bring accessories... Wait, I do have my hair clip! But I already have eight articles of clothing on me, excluding my wand, and I can't exceed that limit... Oh, drat!</state>
                <state img="#-eyeroll.png">I... forgot you had that. Silly me.</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">Erm, I do hope I haven't repeated any of my facts. I am a little flustered, if you haven't realised...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-unamused.png">Oh, I... nearly forgot you still had that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-unamused.png">There's only so much poker facts I can entertain everyone with. I haven't read &lt;i&gt;everything&lt;/i&gt;, you know.</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">Okay, how about... umm... hmm...</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">Poker is popularized by America. In the U.S there is 1 in 5 Ameri---wait, did I share that already? I don't remember.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">Philip Forguson was known to weaponize playing cards, you know. He's capable of throwing a card up to 200 mph with just a flick of his wand. The man once cut a &lt;i&gt;watermelon&lt;/i&gt; in half using a card.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-eyeroll.png">How boring.</state>
                <state img="#-enjoy1.png">At least I can get comfortable here...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <state img="#-think.png">If you're just removing your ~clothing~... I need to rethink my own strategy, really.</state>
                <state img="#-disapprove.png">Hmph. Spare your bragging.</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">Right... What other interesting facts can I share? Or should I focus on what to do for the next round when we swap our cards?</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">I didn't think to bring accessories... Wait, I do have my hair clip! But I already have eight articles of clothing on me, excluding my wand, and I can't exceed that limit... Oh, drat!</state>
                <state img="#-eyeroll.png">I... forgot you had that. Silly me.</state>
                <state>Darn it... Don't get cocky now, ~name~. I can still knock you down a few pegs, even in my current state of dress!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-eyeroll.png">&lt;i&gt;(sigh)&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br&gt;Next hand, please.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Well, ~name~'s ~clothing~ ~clothing.ifPlural(are|is)~ off. Now that the boring part is over, let's progress to the next hand.</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">&lt;i&gt;(I shouldn't be disappointed. I was doing the same thing.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Bring it on, then.</state>
                <state img="#-eek.png">You are only taking that off now? This is worrying...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-unamused.png">There's only so much poker facts I can entertain everyone with. I haven't read &lt;i&gt;everything&lt;/i&gt;, you know.</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">Okay, how about... umm... hmm...</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">Poker is popularized by America. In the U.S there is 1 in 5 Ameri---wait, did I share that already? I don't remember.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">Philip Forguson was known to weaponize playing cards, you know. He's capable of throwing a card up to 200 mph with just a flick of his wand. The man once cut a &lt;i&gt;watermelon&lt;/i&gt; in half using a card.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-eyeroll.png">Heh. Oh, apologies, I just remembered a funny joke my friend Ron told me. You know, I &lt;i&gt;do&lt;/i&gt; have a sense of humour.</state>
                <state img="#-pride.png">That’s the obvious and intelligent choice of what to remove. I would have expected nothing less.</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">I remember some of the older students at my school Hogwarts used to play this game. There’s a reason they say that Gryffindor are particularly brave...</state>
                <state img="#-interest.png">Wizarding society has it's own share of custom strip games. One of the most fascinating is Strip Quidditch. You really do not want to be hit by a bludger while playing one of them...</state>
                <state img="#-lecture.png">I'm normally not quite so open while talking about the wizarding world with strangers. It is a secret society in my homeland. However, I've heard that many magical users regularly visit The Inventory.</state>
                <state img="#-unamused.png">Wizarding poker is very similar to normal poker except, for the playing cards talk. Which doesn't add much to the game, honestly.</state>
                <state img="#-deer.png">I am sorry if I get a little &lt;i&gt;too&lt;/i&gt; competitive. I can get very invested without even realizing.</state>
                <state img="#-interest.png">Hm, do you all want another poker fact? The longest live game was 115 hours long by a man named Phil Laak who didn't sleep the entire time! I am quite glad we aren't playing by those rules.</state>
                <state img="#-lecture.png">You want another poker fact?  Look it up yourself! Being able to find and acquire knowledge is a key skill!</state>
                <state img="#-deer.png">We've been playing for a while so I suppose I should share a little about myself. I am currently nineteen years old and still studying. Most wizards and witches do end their education at eighteen, however I had to take a gap year due to, erm, personal circumstances.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">A fair choice. I'm glad you are playing this game seriously, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">While I researched poker, I also read about some other fun card games. Have any of your heard of 52 Pick-up? It really is a rather funny prank.</state>
                <state img="#-deer.png">Here's an amusing story. There was a man who bet his wife in a poker game and then lost. His wife was so (rightfully) furious that she then left him for the winner.</state>
                <state img="#-eyeroll.png">I used to think I was quite good at games. Chess was a favorite of mine. Then my friend Ron trounced me everytime we played and I stopped playing with him.</state>
                <state img="#-eyeroll.png">Wizarding society is quite bad at understanding anything that isn't magic in general. It can be quite funny yet sad to see them attempt to use something simple like a telephone.</state>
                <state img="#-interest.png">I am sorry if I'm a little too focused during this game. I just wish to prove that I can be a little bold.</state>
                <state img="#-deer.png">Am I taking this game too seriously? I do hope not. I just don't understand why you'd play something and not try your best.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-eyeroll.png">While that is a practical choice to remove... It really doesn't help me much.</state>
                <state img="#-eyeroll.png">Still going strong, huh? I can respect that. But if you don't mind, I won't be paying attention to this game anymore.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">&lt;i&gt;(Coward. At least showing your chest isn't an issue for you!)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-unamused.png">Are you really just removing that? Don't remind me how much I fumbled this game.</state>
                <state img="#-deer.png">At least you're doing better than me. You should be proud of that.</state>
                <state img="#-eyeroll.png">You know what they say? Pride comes before a fall.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">There's a common superstition among poker players that gambling in dirty clothes will give you luck. I &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; hope they aren't playing with these game rules, heh.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_minor">
            <case stage="5-8">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Shall we deal the next hand then? I am rather anxious to see this game through.</state>
                <state img="#-lecture.png">Even if a round is uneventful, keep focused! The game isn't over yet.</state>
                <state img="#-deer.png">Wizarding society is really quite similar to non-magical society. The reason I bring this up is that the same nudity taboos still apply… So excuse a little bit of nervousness on my part, please.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Do not get too confident. I will not let you win easily!</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">I... do not think that the statistics are in my favour right now...</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">I cannot allow my current state of undress to distract me. Next hand, please!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-unamused.png">Tch.</state>
                <state img="#-enjoy1.png">Carry on then.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-think.png">While this game is interesting to say the least, I do hope it doesn’t go on too late. I need to get a full night's sleep or I become rather grumpy.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Shall we deal the next hand then? I am rather anxious to see this game through.</state>
                <state img="#-interest.png">Strip Poker in the magical world is a very different game; a lot quicker when you can cast spells to instantly remove clothing instead of watching someone awkwardly remove them. Erm, not that I have played such a game before, my friends have just recounted the stories.</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">Allow me to attempt to quickly calculate my odds of winning this game, then we can continue.</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">I suppose we should draw cards yet again. It's always a tense moment when you first look at a new hand.</state>
                <state img="#-lecture.png">While it was a slightly unexciting round, we're another step closer to the game ending. Keep that in mind.</state>
                <state img="#-lecture.png">Even if a round is uneventful, keep focused! The game isn't over yet.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-eyeroll.png">Wow. So&lt;i&gt; brave&lt;/i&gt; of you... Sorry. I get sassy when I lose.</state>
                <state img="#-deer.png">I'm running out of poker facts... So shall we speed this game up?</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">In early wizarding society, a common hobby was to gamble money on the outcome of duels. Which is slightly grizzly, considering how those duels usually ended.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">It's quite relaxing to not worry each round about winning or losing. Maybe being out early was a secret blessing.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-eyeroll.png">Heh. Oh, apologies, I just remembered a funny joke my friend Ron told me. You know, I &lt;i&gt;do&lt;/i&gt; have a sense of humour.</state>
                <state img="#-pride.png">That’s the obvious and intelligent choice of what to remove. I would have expected nothing less.</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">I remember some of the older students at my school Hogwarts used to play this game. There’s a reason they say that Gryffindor are particularly brave...</state>
                <state img="#-interest.png">Wizarding society has it's own share of custom strip games. One of the most fascinating is Strip Quidditch. You really do not want to be hit by a bludger while playing one of them...</state>
                <state img="#-lecture.png">I'm normally not quite so open while talking about the wizarding world with strangers. It is a secret society in my homeland. However, I've heard that many magical users regularly visit The Inventory.</state>
                <state img="#-unamused.png">Wizarding poker is very similar to normal poker except, that the playing cards talk. Which doesn't add much to the game, honestly.</state>
                <state img="#-deer.png">I am sorry if I get a little &lt;i&gt;too&lt;/i&gt; competitive. I can get very invested without even realizing.</state>
                <state img="#-interest.png">Hm, do you all want another poker fact? The longest live game was 115 hours long by a man named Phil Laak who didn't sleep the entire time! I am quite glad we aren't playing by those rules.</state>
                <state img="#-lecture.png">You want another poker fact?  Look it up yourself! Being able to find and acquire knowledge is a key skill!</state>
                <state img="#-deer.png">We've been playing for a while so I suppose I should share a little about myself. I am currently nineteen years old and still studying. Most wizards and witches do end their education at eighteen, however I had to take a gap year due to, erm, personal circumstances.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">A fair choice. I'm glad you are playing this game seriously, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">While I researched poker I also read about some other fun card games. Have any of your heard of 52 Pick-up? It really is a rather funny prank.</state>
                <state img="#-deer.png">Here's an amusing story. There was a man who bet his wife in a poker game and then lost. His wife was so (rightfully) furious that she then left him for the winner.</state>
                <state img="#-eyeroll.png">I used to think I was quite good at games. Chess was a favorite of mine. Then my friend Ron trounced me everytime we played and I stopped playing with him.</state>
                <state img="#-eyeroll.png">Wizarding society is quite bad at understanding anything that isn't magic in general. It can be quite funny yet sad to see them attempt to use something simple like a telephone.</state>
                <state img="#-interest.png">I am sorry if I'm a little too focused during this game. I just wish to prove that I can be a little bold.</state>
                <state img="#-deer.png">Am I taking this game too seriously? I do hope not. I just don't understand why you'd play something and not try your best.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-eyeroll.png">While that is a practical choice to remove... It really doesn't help me much.</state>
                <state img="#-eyeroll.png">Still going strong, huh? I can respect that. But if you don't mind, I won't be paying attention to this game anymore.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">&lt;i&gt;(Coward.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-unamused.png">Are you really just removing that? Don't remind me how much I fumbled this game.</state>
                <state img="#-deer.png">At least you're doing better than me. You should be proud of that.</state>
                <state img="#-eyeroll.png">You know what they say? Pride comes before a fall.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">There's a common superstition among poker players that gambling in dirty clothes will give you luck. I &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; hope they aren't playing with these game rules, heh.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_minor">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-think.png">While this game is interesting to say the least, I do hope it doesn’t go on too late. I need to get a full night's sleep or I become rather grumpy.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Shall we deal the next hand then? I am rather anxious to see this game through.</state>
                <state img="#-interest.png">Strip Poker in the magical world is a very different game; a lot quicker when you can cast spells to instantly remove clothing instead of watching someone awkwardly remove them. Erm, not that I have played such a game before, my friends have just recounted the stories.</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">Allow me to attempt to quickly calculate my odds of winning this game, then we can continue.</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">I suppose we should draw cards yet again. It's always a tense moment when you first look at a new hand.</state>
                <state img="#-lecture.png">While it was a slightly unexciting round we're another step closer to the game ending. Keep that in mind.</state>
                <state img="#-lecture.png">Even if a round is uneventful, keep focused! The game isn't over yet.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Shall we deal the next hand then? I am rather anxious to see this game through.</state>
                <state img="#-lecture.png">Even if a round is uneventful, keep focused! The game isn't over yet.</state>
                <state img="#-deer.png">Wizarding society is really quite similar to non-magical society. The reason I bring this up is that the same nudity taboos still apply… So excuse a little bit of nervousness on my part, please.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Do not get too confident. I will not let you win easily!</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">I... do not think that the statistics are in my favour right now...</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">I cannot allow my current state of undress to distract me. Next hand, please!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-unamused.png">Tch.</state>
                <state img="#-enjoy1.png">Carry on then.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-eyeroll.png">Wow. So&lt;i&gt; brave&lt;/i&gt; of you... Sorry. I get sassy when I lose.</state>
                <state img="#-deer.png">I'm running out of poker facts... So shall we speed this game up?</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">In early wizarding society, a common hobby was to gamble money on the outcome of duels. Which is slightly grizzly, considering how those duels usually ended.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">It's quite relaxing to not worry each round about winning or losing. Maybe being out early was a secret blessing.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_major">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-eek.png">This is just like the time when Cepheus Fizzwale drew Four Cups to a Seven Bogies and had to forfeit his cat! Oh dear...</state>
                <state img="#-interest.png">Something similar in happened in the Great Wizarding Poker tournament of 1954. It's said that one of contestants stripped down to their knickers to distract the others. It didn't work, but it's quite funny to think about...</state>
                <state img="#-eek.png">
                    <alt-img stage="0-8">#-think.png</alt-img>
                    <alt-img stage="9-10">#-eek.png</alt-img>
                    <text>Usually, the stakes are quite higher in Wizarding poker, to my knowledge. Remember poor Araminta Ironwood?</text>
                </state>
                <state img="#-think.png">
                    <alt-img stage="9">#-annoyed.png</alt-img>
                    <text>Well... Be grateful it's just your ~clothing~ and not something more drastic. You could have had to forfeit one of your prized possessions...</text>
                </state>
                <state img="#-interest.png">Should I look or not? I’ll be honest, despite all the research I did for the game I’m still unsure on how to handle the more &lt;i&gt;intimate&lt;/i&gt; part.</state>
                <state img="#-eek.png">Um, right! Give me a moment to collect myself and then, um, go ahead!</state>
                <state img="#-deer.png">I do hope you are prepared, ~name~. This is partly what this game has been building up towards!</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">
                    <alt-img stage="9">#-eek.png</alt-img>
                    <text>I've not seen many people in a state of... undress in this sort of context. This game is quite the new experience for me.</text>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-deer.png">There's no need to be shy. Especially after my, erm, &lt;i&gt;performance&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-disapprove.png">Don't worry, ~name~, this game lost any sense of decorum a while ago.</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">We can be embarrassed together, ~name~. I think being humbled is part of the game.</state>
                <state img="#-lecture.png">You're not going to back out, right? I shouldn't have humiliated myself for nothing.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_major">
            <case stage="6-9">
                <state img="#-interest.png">You, erm... look quite good like that, ~name~...</state>
                <state img="#-eyeroll.png">
                    <alt-img stage="0-8 10">#-disapprove.png</alt-img>
                    <alt-img stage="9">#-enjoy1.png</alt-img>
                    <text>&lt;i&gt;Don't get distracted... It's just a rather scantily clad male... You're not a hormonal teenager, Hermione!&lt;/i&gt;</text>
                </state>
                <state img="#-deer.png">...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-pride.png">You're not going to back out now, are you, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">Are you ready, ~name~? We wouldn't want to continue without you.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Next hand, please.</state>
                <state img="#-deer.png">This is going quite splendidly... for me, at least.</state>
                <state img="#-eek.png">It’s curious how the context of a strip game changes things, I’ve seen my friends get changed a few times before and it hasn’t been as… lewd.</state>
                <state img="#-lecture.png">Oh my! Well, I suppose this excitement is just the rush of victory. Not, erm, enthusiasm over your stripping…</state>
                <state img="#-deer.png">While I am mainly here for the poker part, I will not pretend that I'm not a little... interested in what else this game offers.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-eyeroll.png">That would've been much more useful a few rounds ago.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Very nice. I'm glad there isn't only one loser in this game.</state>
                <state img="#-interest.png">Well, I suppose it doesn't matter if I allow myself to get a bit distracted now...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_major">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-eek.png">This is just like the time when Cepheus Fizzwangle drew Four Cups to a Seven Bogies and had to forfeit his cat! Oh dear...</state>
                <state img="#-interest.png">Something similar in happened in the Great Wizarding Poker tournament of 1954. It's said that one of contestants stripped down to their knickers to distract the others. It didn't work, but it's quite funny to think about...</state>
                <state img="#-eek.png">
                    <alt-img stage="0-8">#-think.png</alt-img>
                    <alt-img stage="9-10">#-eek.png</alt-img>
                    <text>Usually, the stakes are quite higher in Wizarding poker, to my knowledge. Remember poor Araminta Ironwood?</text>
                </state>
                <state img="#-disapprove.png">
                    <alt-img stage="9">#-annoyed.png</alt-img>
                    <text>Well... Be grateful it's just your ~clothing~ and not something more drastic. You could have had to forfeit one of your prized possessions...</text>
                </state>
                <state img="#-interest.png">Should I look or not? I’ll be honest, despite all the research I did for the game I’m still unsure on how to handle the more &lt;i&gt;intimate&lt;/i&gt; part.</state>
                <state img="#-eek.png">Um, right! Give me a moment to collect myself and then, um, go ahead!</state>
                <state img="#-deer.png">I do hope you are prepared, ~name~. This is partly what this game has been building up towards!</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">
                    <alt-img stage="9">#-eek.png</alt-img>
                    <text>I've not seen many people in a state of... undress in this sort of context. This game is quite the new experience for me.</text>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-deer.png">There's no need to be shy. Especially after my, erm, &lt;i&gt;performance&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-disapprove.png">Don't worry, ~name~, this game lost any sense of decorum a while ago.</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">We can be embarrassed together, ~name~. I think being humbled is part of the game.</state>
                <state img="#-lecture.png">You're not going to back out, right? I shouldn't have humiliated myself for nothing.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_major">
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-flustered.png">
                    <alt-img stage="8">#-flustered.png</alt-img>
                    <text>&lt;i&gt;~name~ looks... quite good like this. N-No, don't get distracted!&lt;/i&gt;</text>
                </state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">&lt;i&gt;Oh... Oh wow... I didn't think I was into women, but...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-interest.png">I'll admit... It's nice seeing you without your ~clothing~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-pride.png">You're not going to back out now, are you, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">Are you ready, ~name~? We wouldn't want to continue without you.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Next hand, please.</state>
                <state img="#-deer.png">This is going quite splendidly... for me, at least.</state>
                <state img="#-eek.png">It’s curious how the context of a strip game changes things, I’ve seen my friends get changed a few times before and it hasn’t been as… lewd.</state>
                <state img="#-lecture.png">Oh my! Well, I suppose this excitement is just the rush of victory. Not, erm, enthusiasm over your stripping…</state>
                <state img="#-deer.png">While I am mainly here for the poker part, I will not pretend that I'm not a little... interested in what else this game offers.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9-10">
                <state img="#-unamused.png">
                    <alt-img stage="10">#-disapprove.png</alt-img>
                    <text>Don't back down now. You should have known what you were getting into.</text>
                </state>
                <state img="#-interest.png">
                    <alt-img stage="9">#-enjoy3.png</alt-img>
                    <text>I'm enjoying this more than I should, I will admit.</text>
                </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-interest.png">Well, it isn’t like I haven’t seen a bare chest before. But, erm, it is &lt;i&gt;certainly&lt;/i&gt; a little different in the context of this game…</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">A shirtless man is an accepted sight. And, well, that doesn’t mean I won’t take a slight bit of pleasure in viewing...</state>
                <state img="#-deer.png">It’s quite ordinary for a man to be topless at the beach or seaside. Though… this isn’t either of those places.</state>
                <state img="#-lecture.png">Every chest is a little bit different. I'm curious to what yours looks like, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-interest.png">Well, I suppose this round will be eventful.</state>
                <state img="#-pride.png">I assume you understood the risk when you decided to join this game, correct?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9" />
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-eyeroll.png">Hm... This would've been useful moments ago. Nevermind, I guess.</state>
                <state img="#-interest.png">I'm thankful you're taking the attention off me.</state>
                <state img="#-pride.png">Ah? Well, this should be interesting.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="muscular" role="target" />
                <state img="#-deer.png">You must work out quite a bit, ~name~. A trained body is nearly as useful as a trained mind...</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">You are very athletic, ~name~. Quite like Victor Krum. Do you do any sports?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <condition filter="pale-skinned" role="target" />
                <state img="#-lecture.png">I do hope you get enough sunlight, ~name~. You are rather pale.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-interest.png">Very nice. Erm, objectively speaking, of course!</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">Even I’ll admit this game is rather hot. I can see why so many people play it.</state>
                <state img="#-deer.png">&lt;i&gt;Wow!&lt;/i&gt; Erm, please ignore that sudden outburst and let’s move on! Next hand then?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">This game is coming to a conclusion quickly. I'm interested to see who wins.</state>
                <state img="#-pride.png">You have a nice form, ~name~. Very impressive.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">I can appreciate a good chest when I see one. Very nice, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-enjoy3.png">Oh my. That's...</state>
                <state img="#-interest.png">Well, it's nothing I haven't seen before, but... it's still nice to look at.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-eek.png">No amount of studying can prepare me for moments like these!</state>
                <state img="#-eek.png">Shoot, um... Has this ever happened in any game? There was no books about strip poker I could find!</state>
                <state img="#-interest.png">&lt;i&gt;We all should've known what we were getting into... I can do this. It's not like I haven't seen this before...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-eek.png" marker="turnaway">Oh, um... I-I can turn away!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-deer.png">Ooh, I bet this will make the forfeit easier.</state>
                <state img="#-interest.png">Do you mind if I look? Just for, um... inspiration?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-interest.png">Here it comes...</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">This should be good.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_small_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-10">
                <state img="#-interest.png">
                    <alt-img stage="9">#-sparks2.png</alt-img>
                    <text>That's, erm... &lt;i&gt;(snrrrt)&lt;/i&gt; O-Okay, next ha---&lt;i&gt;hehehehe!&lt;/i&gt;</text>
                </state>
                <state img="#-interest.png">&lt;i&gt;(giggle)&lt;/i&gt; I-I'm not laughing, I swear!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_medium_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-10">
                <state img="#-interest.png">There it is...</state>
                <state img="#-eek.png">
                    <alt-img stage="0-8">#-flustered.png</alt-img>
                    <text>Okay... &lt;i&gt;(What do I say here!?)&lt;/i&gt;</text>
                </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_large_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-10">
                <state img="#-eek.png">Oh my---that's huge!</state>
                <state img="#-eek.png">&lt;i&gt;Eek!&lt;/i&gt; Have you really been hiding that all this time!?</state>
                <state img="#-eek.png">Ah! I wasn't ready to see that!</state>
                <state img="#-eek.png">What on Earth!?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-6" oneShotId="8">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="turnaway" />
                <state img="#-disapprove.png">I'm, erm... turning away! I'm not interested in seeing it.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <condition filter="enf" role="target" />
                <state img="#-lecture.png">You seem quite nervous, ~name~. Would some poker trivia help you refocus? That's what I do when I get anxious.</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">Erm, I really hope you're not feeling forced into this, ~name~... Are you sure you want to continue playing?</state>
                <state img="#-lecture.png">Be brave, ~name~! The only defence against fear is courage, after all.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-lecture.png">I lived in an all female dorm. This is really nothing new to me.</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">I hope this isn't too embarrassing for you, ~name~...</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">Well... This is the game. I hope you understand what you signed up for, ~name~...</state>
                <state img="#-pride.png">Ah. This game is getting heated, huh?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-lecture.png">Don't worry, ~name~. It's a lot less intimidating than it seems.</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">This is the main appeal of the game to most.</state>
                <state img="#-interest.png">Oh, hm? I didn't realise that you were going to have to take off &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; next. I was... distracted.</state>
                <state img="#-lecture.png">I suppose I'll have company now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-deer.png">I've seen the girls who share my dorm room change before. This is nothing new to me, but I &lt;i&gt;am&lt;/i&gt; curious.</state>
                <state img="#-enjoy1.png">Okay, I'll admit I'm curious.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_small_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8 10">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">In a way, I sort of envy you. You probably don't have to deal with back pain like most of us, &lt;i&gt;and&lt;/i&gt; it would be easier to maintain your posture.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Well, variety &lt;i&gt;is&lt;/i&gt; the size of life. What is the purpose of an ample chest anyways, other than grabbing attention?</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">Oh! That's cute! Don't feel bad about them!</state>
                <state img="#-eyeroll.png">Don't feel bad. Large breasts are overrated anyways.</state>
                <state img="#-lecture.png">I know there were quite a few witches who attempted to use magic to make their breasts larger. Their spells backfired. Horribly. I trust you won't attempt to do the same. Your breasts are fine the way they are.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-deer.png">Oh, how cute!</state>
                <state img="#-eek.png">I find them quite attractive, if it helps. But I won't look if you don't want me to.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_medium_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-unamused.png">Yes. Breasts. We get it.</state>
                <state img="#-lecture.png">I'm sorry, ~name~, but you chose to play this game.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">&lt;i&gt;(Okay, ~name~ is exposed now. If I play my cards right, I won't have to be in her shoes.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-10">
                <state img="#-interest.png">Mhm. Those are breasts, alright.</state>
                <state img="#-deer.png">Not too large, not too small. Quite a good size.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Mmm... Huh? No, I-I wasn't staring at her! Don't we have a game to return to?</state>
                <state img="#-interest.png">I don't envy you, ~name~. Although... you &lt;i&gt;do&lt;/i&gt; have quite a nice figure.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-5">
                <state img="#-flustered.png">Not much as I can say without making this awkward. Ermm... You have a... nice figure?</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">Well, there they are.</state>
                <state img="#-disapprove.png">&lt;i&gt;(Don't be distracted, Hermione. You still have a game to win.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_large_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-10">
                <condition filter="student" role="target" />
                <state img="#-eyeroll.png">I get the feeling you're quite popular at your school. Well, it doesn't matter as long as you keep your grades up.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-4">
                <state img="#-think.png">Hmm... You must have a difficult time bra shopping.</state>
                <state img="#-eyeroll.png">Well, there they are—oh, stop ogling, ~player~.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">I get the feeling you were quite popular at your school. Well, it doesn't matter as long as you've kept your grades up.</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">I wonder... How many chest enlarging spells were actually successful? Not implying yours aren't natural, of course. I'm just reminded of this new article I read.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8 10">
                <state img="#-interest.png">Oh... Hm. V-Very nice, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-eek.png">
                    <alt-img stage="5-8">#-flustered.png</alt-img>
                    <text>O-Oh, I wasn't expecting them to be so... large. I was really focusing on the game, you see.</text>
                </state>
                <state img="#-deer.png">Wow! Erm... You're quite buxom.</state>
                <state img="#-interest.png">Mhm. Those are breasts, alright. &lt;i&gt;(She has quite the figure...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">
                    <alt-img stage="10">#-interest.png</alt-img>
                    <text>Those are... quite nice.</text>
                </state>
                <state img="#-think.png">&lt;i&gt;(Hmm... They could be a distraction. As long as I don't get distracted myself, I can use this to my advantage!)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-think.png">Hmm... You must have a difficult time bra shopping.</state>
                <state img="#-eyeroll.png">Well, there they are—oh, stop ogling, ~name~. They're just sacks of fat that store milk, you know.</state>
                <state img="#-lecture.png">Well, when you all quite finish drooling, we have a game to return to.</state>
                <state img="#-eyeroll.png">Pah. People always go mad about large breasts.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-deer.png">Oh! I quite like this sight.</state>
                <state img="#-eek.png">Wow! Erm... You're quite buxom. You don't mind if I... nevermind.</state>
                <state img="#-interest.png">Those are breasts, alright. Quite a large pair...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-think.png">I never really got a good look at another girl's privates.</state>
                <state img="#-deer.png">Do you mind if I take a look? Just out of curiousity?</state>
                <state img="#-eek.png">She's really doing it! &lt;i&gt;(I hope I don't have to show mine too.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-enjoy3.png">Mmm... Someone else is going to reveal their privates? Should I re-direct my focus to them, or just continune what I'm doing?</state>
                <state img="#-enjoy2.png">Nnn...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-eyeroll.png">Join the club.</state>
                <state img="#-disapprove.png">I do hope this takes some of the focus off myself...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-eek.png">The nudity can actually be a bit liberating, ~name~. Erm... That's embarrassing to admit.</state>
                <state img="#-lecture.png">It'll be fine, ~name~. You won't be the first.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <condition filter="shaved" role="target" />
                <state img="#-interest.png" oneShotId="79">Oh? I see you've done some landscaping. I always do find it hard to decide which looks better...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-4">
                <state img="#-confident.png">Nothing to hide now.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">And here, I still have most of my clothes. Not to brag, but I believe all that studying paid off.</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">Hmm... Quite fascinating, actually.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-10">
                <state img="#-interest.png">Thinking about it now... There's something so refreshing about nudity.</state>
                <state img="#-deer.png">
                    <alt-img stage="10">#-pleased.png</alt-img>
                    <text>You're not alone, at least!</text>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">And here, I haven't lost a thing. I think I have this game in the bag.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">Wow! I mean, I haven't lost a thing and I've already stripped down an opponent.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-flustered.png">Ah... I won't be alone, at least.</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">I think... Even with how little clothing I have, I may have a chance.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_lost">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="moon" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-unamused.png">... Are you &lt;i&gt;trying&lt;/i&gt; to lose Moon? What even is the point in playing then?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="brock" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-eek.png">... A rocket launcher?! Are you quite sure you're allowed to take something like that in here?! P-Please be careful!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="tomoko" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-pride.png">You are being rather quiet Tomoko. If any of us can make you more comfortable, please speak up!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="weiss_schnee" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-pride.png">I must say Weiss, you do seem like a woman of refinement. It's quite lovely to meet you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="weiss_schnee" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-think.png">Do you have magic or something equivalent in your world Weiss? I always do find the different forms magic can take very fascinating.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="akko" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-excited.png">I can tell by those robes you are a fellow witch!  What types of magic do you excel at?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="megumin" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-think.png">Are you a witch Megumin? I've never seen robes quite like those. What kind of magic can you do?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="bernadetta" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-think.png" oneShotId="17" marker="bernie_ease">You seem quite... nervous, Bernadetta. Is there anything we can do to put you at ease?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="komi-san" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-think.png" oneShotId="21" marker="komi_mute">Erm... Are you mute, Shouko? Or do you just not wish to talk?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4" oneShotId="13">
                <condition role="target" character="meia" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-pride.png" marker="meia_knowledge">Oh? You wish to learn more about Earth culture, Meia? I'm quite knowledgeable if you have any questions you need answered!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4" oneShotId="14">
                <condition role="target" character="jura" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-think.png" marker="jura_differentPlanet">You come from... a different planet, Jura? But you look very human. The Inventory is a strange place...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="pyrrha" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-flustered.png" marker="pyrrha_famous">You're famous, Pyrrha? How do you... handle it? I've seen myself in a few tabloids and it's not a great feeling...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="jim" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-interest.png" oneShotId="130" marker="raynor_intro">You have an impressive list of achievements, ~name~. What brings you to a place like this?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="miko" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-flustered.png" oneShotId="131" marker="miko_intro">Is this... some sort of roleplay you are doing, Miss Miko? I'm quite confused...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="revy" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-eyeroll.png" oneShotId="6" marker="revy_swearing">You know, Revy. It could be said that excessive swearing is used as a linguistic crutch. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="revy" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="126" marker="revy_states">You come from the states, Revy? I've been aiming to visit sometime. My pen-pal lives there and they have told me about their state in some detail.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="1">
                <condition role="target" character="n" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-pride.png" marker="n_target0a">You're taking this game very seriously, N. I love the intesity! A bit of competition is fun, yes?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="4">
                <condition role="target" character="n" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-pride.png" marker="n_target1a">Hm, do you enjoy mathematics and such, then? I find probability fascinating!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="5">
                <condition role="target" character="n" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-pride.png" marker="n_target2a">Oh! What is that cube, N? Is it some sort of puzzle?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="9">
                <condition role="target" character="n" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-think.png" marker="n_target3a">What was your childhood like, N? I can imagine you were quite the inquisitive child.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="15">
                <condition role="target" character="n" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-think.png" marker="n_target4a">I'm quite a fan of creatures myself, N. I have a lovely half-kneazle named Crookshanks.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="17">
                <condition role="target" character="n" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-pride.png" marker="n_target5a">You live in a rather interesting world, N. I can't say I've ever read of anything like it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="20">
                <condition role="target" character="n" stage="6" />
                <state img="#-lecture.png" marker="n_target5a">There's no need to be nervous, N. I assure you, I will not ogle you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="27">
                <condition role="target" character="n" stage="7" />
                <state img="#-eek.png" marker="n_target7a">Er! Are you &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; not wearing underwear underneath? Oh!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="revy" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-lecture.png" marker="revy_truce1">It's obvious that we don't care much for each others comany, Revy. Though I propose we put a truce on arguing. I'm sure the other players are getting tired of it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="akko" stage="1" />
                <state marker="akko_1a">I have heard stories of Luna Nova.. I'd be lying if I said, all of them positive. Isn't it under a substantial amount of financial debt?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="mae" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-think.png" marker="mae_0a">You really don't seem like you prepared much for this game, Mae. Were you even planning on playing before today? Or did you come here by chance?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="lotte" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-excited.png">W-Wait, Lotte... You &lt;i&gt;also&lt;/i&gt; read Night Fall? I normally don't bother with fictional books but I've been reading those ever since I was introduced to the magical world! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="croix" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-excited.png">... Croix Meridies? Is that you? It's a pleasure to meet you! I've read a few of your research papers.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="pyrrha" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-think.png" marker="pyrrha_1a">I'm curious, then. How did you become famous? And at what age?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="polly" />
                <state img="#-unamused.png" oneShotId="2" marker="polly_PSA0">So you're a ghost who died and now takes an excessive amount of drugs. Is this some sort of elaborate PSA?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="polly" />
                <state img="#-lecture.png" oneShotId="3" marker="polly_enthusiastic0">There are many different ghosts in the wizarding world. Though I don't think many are as...  enthusiastic as you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="amy" />
                <state img="#-lecture.png" oneShotId="13" marker="amy_attention">You seem to get quite distracted, Amy. Are you paying proper attention to my poker facts? I'm practically giving you free advice on how to win!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="amy" />
                <state img="#-think.png" oneShotId="14" marker="amy_spiders">You like spiders, Amy? I better not introduce you to my boyfriend then, he's absolutely terrified of the things!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="amy" />
                <state img="#-deer.png" oneShotId="16" marker="amy_singing">You have quite the pleasant voice, Amy. I'd simply embarrass myself if I attempted to sing... I cannot hold a tune.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" totalRounds="0" priority="25">
                <state img="#-disapprove.png">You never studied anything about poker? Well then, your loss.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">...Quit looking at me like I'm "going overboard with this"? How else am I going to win if I don't know the best strategies to use?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" oneShotId="3" totalRounds="1" priority="20">
                <state img="#-deer.png">I know the removal of accessories and trinkets will be happening frequently, but it's very boring to watch, isn't it? Oh! How about I share some poker trivia with everyone?</state>
                <state img="#-deer.png">This game actually has a very colorful history is chock-full of amazing facts and crazy stories, from both the wizarding world &lt;i&gt;and&lt;/i&gt; with Muggles! How about I share some while we wait for ~name~?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_stripping">
            <case stage="0-3" oneShotId="15">
                <condition role="target" character="revy" stage="1" saidMarker="hermione_resp1states" />
                <state img="#-eyeroll.png">What's with that nickname? Anyway, she lives in Colorado. Any wisecracks you wish to make now?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" oneShotId="34">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="revy_truce1" />
                <condition role="target" character="revy" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-confident.png" oneShotId="163" marker="revy_truce2">Here's an innocent question, as a show of good faith, then. Have you ever visited or lived in another country?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="moon" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Maybe you wish to expose yourself! But your lack of effort is spoiling the joy of the game for everyone else!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="brock" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">I-I s-suppose if you know what you are doing then there is no danger. However, I'm quite confused. What would possibly suggest that it's appropriate to bring it with you to a simple game of strip poker?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="tomoko" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-eek.png">W-What kind of question is that?!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="weiss_schnee" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-lecture.png">Please tell me more about yourself, I'd enjoy to get to know you better.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="akko" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-lecture.png">Personally I am quite talented at charms, transfiguration and theoretical knowledge. While I do not wish to boast, I was top of my class at Hogwarts.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="megumin" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-interest.png">Explosion magic? Well, I suppose I can see certain uses for it even if those are limited. What else can you do?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="zizou" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-flustered.png" oneShotId="5" marker="zizou_gloves0">I suppose you could say, now the gloves are coming off. Huh, Zizou? Um, I'm not very good at this whole humour thing...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="komi-san" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-interest.png">No worries, Shouko. Some say that I'd talk enough for the both of us...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" oneShotId="16">
                <condition role="target" character="jura" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-think.png">I can't say I &lt;i&gt;have&lt;/i&gt; heard of spacetravel. At least to that extent. In my world the most we have achieved is men on the moon..</state>
                <state img="#-eyeroll.png">No. There's no spell for going into space. Though we have managed spacetravel through non-magical means. None as impressive as settling another planet, of course.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="meia" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-think.png" marker="meia_knowledge0">I assume our worlds aren't &lt;i&gt;exactly&lt;/i&gt; the same then. When I read about The Inventory, it suggested such a thing was possible. I'm sure our worlds share certain similarities though.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="2">
                <condition role="target" character="n" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-pleased.png" marker="n_target0b">I can get quite competitive myself, N. I do hope you'll forgive me if I accidentally lose my composure a little...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="3">
                <condition role="target" character="n" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-interest.png" marker="n_target1b">Have you ever heard of the Monty Hall problem, N? I think you'd find it quite interesting.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="7">
                <condition role="target" character="n" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-interest.png" marker="n_target2b">Ah, it's one of those types of puzzles. Oddly enough, I'm terrible with them. Same with a Rubik Cube.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="14">
                <condition role="target" character="n" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-flustered.png" marker="n_target3b">Erm, as a child I could be a little overbearing. I didn't have &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; many friends.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="11">
                <condition role="target" character="n" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-pleased.png" marker="n_target4b">He's very intelligent. I spent many nights sitting with him by a cozy fire in the Gryffindor Common room and reading an interesting book.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="18">
                <condition role="target" character="n" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-think.png" marker="n_target5b">Are there people with magical powers in your world too? I'm always curious to discover the similarities.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="22">
                <condition role="target" character="n" stage="6" />
                <condition count="1-3" />
                <state img="#-lecture.png" marker="n_target6b">And you should try to be kind too, ~player~. I think if we're playing a game like this, we wish for everyone to be comfortable.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="23">
                <condition role="target" character="n" stage="6" />
                <condition count="4-5" />
                <state img="#-lecture.png" marker="n_target6bb">And I do hope everyone else remains polite too. I think if we're playing a game like this, we wish for everyone to be comfortable.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="28">
                <condition role="target" character="n" stage="7" />
                <state img="#-lecture.png" marker="n_target7b">N-No, no. It's fine... Just allow me to, erm, collect myself. This is part of the game after all...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="jim" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-pleased.png" marker="raynor_intro1">You may call me Hermione if you wish. I do hope you manage to relax and enjoy the game.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="lotte" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-think.png">I can't admit to reading &lt;i&gt;every&lt;/i&gt; volume. There's so many and oddly enough, the quality seems to sometimes dip for years at a time.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="croix" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-lecture.png">Er, apologies. I will keep things professional, though that may be hard in a game such as this. Still...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="pyrrha" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-deer.png" marker="pyrrha_0b">I suppose. Would you have any helpful advice for someone just learning to deal with fame?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="pyrrha" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-flustered.png" marker="pyrrha_1b">I can't imagine it was easy. Do you ever regret it? Though, maybe that question is inappropriate for &lt;i&gt;this&lt;/i&gt; game in particular...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" oneShotId="12">
                <condition role="target" character="revy" saidMarker="hermione_resp0swearing" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="revy_swearing" />
                <state img="#-eyeroll.png" oneShotId="123" marker="revy_swearing1">British swears aren't different from American swears. I just find you can be more pointed with language when you don't rely on playground jeers. It's quite childish, don't you think? </state>
                <state img="#-lecture.png" oneShotId="166" marker="revy_swearing1">We have the same swears here in the UK as you do in the US. My point is that you just sound juvenile when you rely on curse words instead of proper linguistics.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state>An opponent is stripping.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_stripped">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="moon" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-eyeroll.png">If you wish to expose yourself, you should do it elsewhere. You are ruining the competitiveness of this game.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="megumin" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-eek.png">Wait, you can &lt;i&gt;only&lt;/i&gt; use explosion magic? B-But isn't that severely limiting?! Why wouldn't you learn other spells?!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="tomoko" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-lecture.png">Erm, y-you can go back to being quiet Tomoko. I think it'd be for the best...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="brock" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-lecture.png">Just be careful. Or I &lt;i&gt;will&lt;/i&gt; ask management to escort you outside.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3" id="6">
                <condition role="target" character="n" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-pride.png" marker="n_target0c">Then may the best player win! Good luck, you &lt;i&gt;will&lt;/i&gt; need it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-8" id="10">
                <condition role="target" character="n" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-pride.png" marker="n_target0d">I suppose you're already performing much better than I. Though, you shouldn't let your guard down!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="8">
                <condition role="target" character="n" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-confident.png" marker="n_target1c">I don't think anyone else would be interested in hearing me ramble about it. But I could inform you more after the game?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="12">
                <condition role="target" character="n" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-deer.png" marker="n_target2c">I'm not too good at spatial puzzles. But trying to figure out why that is a puzzle in itself...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="16">
                <condition role="target" character="n" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-lecture.png" marker="n_target3c">I'd like to make it clear that I &lt;i&gt;do&lt;/i&gt; think I've mellowed over the years. You think so, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="13">
                <condition role="target" character="n" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-deer.png" marker="n_target4c">Have you got any cozy memories like that?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="19">
                <condition role="target" character="n" stage="6" />
                <state img="#-excited.png" marker="n_target5c">Hm. Maybe our worlds aren't so different. Still, there's so much more to learn that I never even thought about! A whole other history!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="25">
                <condition role="target" character="n" stage="7" />
                <state img="#-pride.png" marker="n_target6c">I think you should appreciate that not everyone is comfortable stripping in front of virtual strangers. Though N, if it helps I don't think you have anything to be ashamed of.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="29">
                <condition role="target" character="n" stage="8" />
                <state img="#-interest.png" marker="n_target7c">Oh my! This is quite the situation, isn't it, ~target~? If it helps... you are quite attractive...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <condition role="target" character="jim" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-pride.png" marker="raynor_intro2">Do please give me a challenge though, I enjoy the competition and you look like a formidable opponent.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <condition role="target" character="jim" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-flustered.png" marker="raynor_intro2b">Oh... Er, I was hoping I'd perform better than this... I hope you don't judge me on my run of bad luck, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="lotte" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-eek.png">Still that moment when Edgar's future-self proposed to sweet Bella... I will admit to squealing. I nearly dropped the book!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="croix" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-pride.png">The idea of merging technology and magic together is a fascinating concept, one that I personally had barely even considered before reading your work. The ideas you've written, with funding, could introduce entirely new subject fields!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="pyrrha" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-deer.png" marker="pyrrha_0c">Thank you, Pyrrha. Let's hope that this game doesn't end up in any tabloids, hm?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="revy" saidMarker="hermione_resp01swearing" />
                <state img="#-eyeroll.png" oneShotId="148">Did you not figure out that me commenting on your language was my own snarky insult? I'm already tired of you.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="winner" />
                <state img="#-excited.png">I knew all that reading would pay off!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition count="1-2" status="alive" />
                <test expr="~self.place~" value="1" />
                <state img="#-deer.png" marker="winner">If ~name~ is eliminated now... I won!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <test expr="~target.revplace~" value="1" />
                <state img="#-pleased.png">And that's one down!</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Tough luck, ~name~. Perhaps you should have looked up strategies earlier.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <condition count="1" gender="male" status="masturbating" role="other" />
                <state img="#-startle.png">Oh, so I need to masturbate with a guy now?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8 10">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">And so, the first player is eliminated!</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Tough luck, ~name~. Perhaps you should have looked up strategies earlier.</state>
                <state img="#-eek.png">Well, ~name~ just got eliminated... Please tell me you knew about this rule! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-startle.png">Oh! Well, this will be interesting! And awkward... But it doesn't need to be, really!</state>
                <state img="#-enjoy2.png">Mmm... Who lost now?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-confident.png">Oh, erm... &lt;i&gt;(ahem!)&lt;/i&gt; Let's continue.</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">&lt;i&gt;(Hopefully, I don't get distracted here. Then again, my opponents might get distracted by this display as well...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">&lt;i&gt;(~name~ is so attractive... Hopefully, he doesn't distract me!)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-lecture.png">Rules are rules, ~name~. B-But just know I don't agree with this sort of perversion!</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">I hope you at least knew what you were getting into...</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">What &lt;i&gt;did&lt;/i&gt; inspire this particular aspect of the game anyways? I figured nudity would be enough of a reward... for the more perverted players, at least.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9-10">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="25">Can't the establishment provide seats for them to sit comfortably while they do this?</state>
                <state img="#-interest.png">I... suppose you can look at me while you do it. Only if it helps you.</state>
                <state img="#-eek.png">I still think the forfeit should be something different, even if this game &lt;i&gt;is&lt;/i&gt; sexual by nature.</state>
                <state img="#-interest.png">This is just as interesting as the Texas Hold 'Em tournament of 1969. Not nearly as... sexual, of course. Different times and all that. Oh, but the scandal! I read one witch who got eliminated did a saucy dance in just her undergarments!</state>
                <state img="#-interest.png">
                    <alt-img stage="9">#-sparks2.png</alt-img>
                    <alt-img stage="10">#-think.png</alt-img>
                    <text>Men don't usually use toys for this, do they?</text>
                </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-eek.png">I've... erm, never seen a guy do this before. S-Should I take notes?</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">Fascinating... &lt;i&gt;Focus, Hermione!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-deer.png">Oh, wow! This is... Something new. I'm not sure how I feel...</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">Is this how most men masturbate? I suppose there isn't really any other way...</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">Is that the most comfortable position? You, erm, seem quite comfortable anyway...</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">Curious...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-enjoy2.png">I don't mind you w-watching me. If it helps, I... ah...</state>
                <state img="#-deer.png">This is... fascinating! Yes, very fascinating! Keep at it, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-enjoy3.png">There's something so... strangely intimate about this. </state>
                <state img="#-deer.png">Oh! You must be really enjoying this!</state>
                <state img="#-enjoy1.png">It's interesting, seeing the difference between male masturbation and female masturbation... while masturbating myself. I wasn't expecting such an experience...</state>
                <state img="#-enjoy3.png">Is this helping?</state>
                <state img="#-enjoy2.png">I would never think about putting on a show like this. But I suppose we can help each other out...</state>
                <state img="#-enjoy2.png">I wonder what's going through your head right now as you're doing this.</state>
                <state img="#-enjoy1.png">I'm definitely not going to forget this...</state>
                <state img="#-sparks2.png">Ohhhhh, this is so...</state>
                <state img="#-sparks1.png">Y-You certainly seem to have more experience than I do.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="78">Please don't make this weird after we both finish.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <state img="#-flustered.png">Oh, Merlin! This is a strange feeling. Uh, I'm a little flustered now...</state>
                <state img="#-interest.png">This is quite exciting in a way. This is an odd rule for the game but I don't dislike it.</state>
                <state img="#-lecture.png">I wouldn't mind if you looked at me. It's the most I can offer and be fair with you being so brave to put on a show like that.</state>
                <state img="#-interest.png">Do you... wish me to look? Erm, I can if you do...</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">I've read a couple of books about this... But it is different in person. Much less... scientific.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-lecture.png">The differences in male and female masturbation are quite fascinating. Though I know I don't have enough data for sweeping generalizations.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">If you need help finishing, I do hope my own forfeit gave some... inspiration.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-10">
                <state img="#-eek.png">Careful! Don't get it on anyone!</state>
                <state img="#-eek.png">
                    <alt-img stage="5-8">#-flustered.png</alt-img>
                    <alt-img stage="9">#-startle.png</alt-img>
                    <text>Oh! That was a lot!</text>
                </state>
                <state img="#-interest.png">Obviously, I know about the reproductive system of men, but actually &lt;i&gt;seeing&lt;/i&gt; it is ... I'm not sure if I know the word for that, actually.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition count="1-2" status="alive" />
                <test expr="~self.place~" value="1" />
                <state img="#-deer.png" marker="winner">If ~name~ is eliminated now... I won!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <test expr="~target.revplace~" value="1" />
                <state img="#-pleased.png">And so, the first player is eliminated!</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Tough luck, ~name~. Perhaps you should have looked up strategies earlier.</state>
                <state img="#-eek.png">Well, ~name~ just got eliminated... Please tell me you knew about this rule! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-eek.png" oneShotId="22" marker="rethinkin">One opponent down! Wait, fewer opponents means my chances of losing are higher now! I need to rethink my strategy! </state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">And so, ~name~ is elimination from—oh, erm... I nearly forgot about the forfeit.</state>
                <state img="#-eek.png" oneShotId="46">T-This rule seems a bit much, if I must be honest! Punishments and forfeits during wizarding gambling tournaments in the past got absurd, but I don't think any of them came &lt;i&gt;close&lt;/i&gt; to being so...</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">Just know I won't be looking, ~name~. I still need to win!</state>
                <state img="#-lecture.png">When you're down to just a few opponents, you can't afford to play conservatively. Sometimes, you need to take bigger risks. That's when the luck factor affects the game the most.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">And so, another falls.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-unamused.png">Oh goodie, someone to masturbate with.</state>
                <state img="#-enjoy2.png">Mmm... Who lost now?</state>
                <state img="#-enjoy3.png">At least... the forfeit feels good...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Well? Get to it. You've already exposed yourself, haven't you?</state>
                <state img="#-disapprove.png">So ~name~ is out now... Go on, I won't watch. I can't afford to have distractions.</state>
                <state img="#-pride.png">Heh! Still in!</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">Whew! I can't afford another loss here.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Well? Get to it. You've already exposed yourself, haven't you?</state>
                <state img="#-lecture.png">If I was able to masturbate in public in front of people I don't know, surely you can do the same?</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">And so, another falls.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8" oneShotId="10">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="rethinkin" />
                <state img="#-think.png">&lt;i&gt;The Great Book of Gambling&lt;/i&gt; had a section about how player elimination changes the game. Or was it one of the volumes of &lt;i&gt;Poker: A History?&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-confident.png">Oh, erm... &lt;i&gt;(ahem!)&lt;/i&gt; Let's continue.</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">&lt;i&gt;(Hopefully, I don't get distracted here. Then again, my opponents might get distracted by this display as well...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-disapprove.png">Well, &lt;i&gt;I&lt;/i&gt; certainly won't be doing this as well. In fact, this gives me a greater incentive to win!</state>
                <state img="#-lecture.png">Rules are rules, ~name~. B-But just know I don't agree with this sort of perversion!</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">I hope you at least knew what you were getting into...</state>
                <state img="#-think.png">What &lt;i&gt;did&lt;/i&gt; inspire this particular aspect of the game anyways? I figured nudity would be enough of a reward... for the more perverted players, at least.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9-10">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="25">Can't the establishment provide seats for them to sit comfortably while they do this?</state>
                <state img="#-interest.png">I... suppose you can look at me while you do it. Only if it helps you.</state>
                <state img="#-eek.png">I still think the forfeit should be something different, even if this game &lt;i&gt;is&lt;/i&gt; sexual by nature.</state>
                <state img="#-interest.png">This is just as interesting as the Texas Hold 'Em tournament of 1969. Not nearly as... sexual, of course. Different times and all that. Oh, but the scandal! I read one witch who got eliminated did a saucy dance in just her undergarments!</state>
                <state img="#-interest.png">
                    <alt-img stage="9">#-enjoy1.png</alt-img>
                    <text>I always found using a toy much easier for me...</text>
                </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_masturbating">
            <case stage="7-8">
                <condition count="3-" status="alive" />
                <state img="#-eek.png" oneShotId="114">Ah... Erm, I'm pretty close to having to do that myself. Aren't I?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-interest.png">I don't think many of my tips would be helpful for you, ~name~. This, erm, isn't an area where I have much expertise.</state>
                <state img="#-eek.png">While you do look like you're having... fun, I do hope I don't end up headlining a similar performance...</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">A small part of me wishes I lost a bit more to make this less... awkward. </state>
                <state img="#-unamused.png">I usually value new experiences. But this one is just odd.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-sparks2.png">There's something so strangely intimate about this. I'm not quite sure if I'm as attracted to women as I am with men, but doing this in tandem with you is...</state>
                <state img="#-deer.png">You seem to have more experience with this than I do! You don't mind if I watch, right?</state>
                <state img="#-enjoy3.png">&lt;i&gt;(Something about doing this with ~name~ makes this experience a lot more exciting.)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-sparks2.png">I suppose doing this with another girl makes this experience less awkward.</state>
                <state img="#-sparks1.png">I'm definitely not going to forget this...</state>
                <state img="#-deer.png">Oh! I've never seen that technique before!</state>
                <state img="#-enjoy3.png">I'll admit... I like seeing you like this, ~name~. I think you're quite pretty.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <state img="#-think.png">I do hope my state of dress helps. It'd be an odd type of flattery.</state>
                <state img="#-interest.png">I'm curious as to how I'd feel in your position...</state>
                <state img="#-deer.png">Oh! You... seem to be enjoying yourself...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-deer.png">Did I look... like that? I do hope I was a bit more... refined.</state>
                <state img="#-interest.png">I don't often give these types of compliments but you are admittedly rather pretty, ~name~. </state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Very bold, ~name~. Which I feel is one of the greatest qualities a person can possess.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-flustered.png">That... was an experience.</state>
                <state img="#-interest.png">&lt;i&gt;(I may have learned a few things from watching ~name~...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9-10" oneShotId="11">
                <state img="#-eek.png">Did you just... right, I forgot some women, erm, &lt;i&gt;squirted&lt;/i&gt; once they finished...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-deer.png">~name~, that's... quite the display you showed us.</state>
                <state img="#-enjoy3.png">That was... interesting! Very interesting. &lt;br&gt; &lt;i&gt;(And so hot...)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-enjoy3.png">Nnn... I can't say I didn't enjoy that...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Maybe this time to relax? That looked quite intense.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate_first">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-flustered.png">I-I'm first to lose!? I could've sworn I'd do well with all the studying I did!</state>
                <state img="#-flustered.png">I-I'm first to lose!? B-But I did so much studying!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-flustered.png">Ah... I guess I've been... eliminated now.</state>
                <state img="#-eek.png">Oh no! I can't give up my wand, so...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="start_masturbating">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="custom:#-accioChair">Perhaps... I was foolish to think knowledge could beat experience. I'll keep this mind for next time.</state>
                <state img="custom:#-accioChair">Perhaps it was because I don't have as much experience as you all had. As much as I hate losing, at least I learned something today.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="masturbating">
            <case stage="9" oneShotId="9" priority="9999">
                <condition role="self" timeInStage="0" />
                <state img="#-toy5.png">Perhaps the toys I have lying around will come to good use.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-sparks1.png">Uff... D-Don't be alarmed by the sparks. I have my magic under control, so you don't have to worry about any accidental discharging.</state>
                <state img="#-enjoy1.png">It always feels so much better with a toy...</state>
                <state img="#-enjoy3.png">It helps to be comfortable while you're doing this. That's why I summoned this chair.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">I'm not as experienced with masturbation as I am with other forms of magic nor did I read anything about it. So please don't look at me for tips this time.</state>
                <state img="#-enjoy2.png">Oooh!</state>
                <state img="#-enjoy1.png">I once saw a book about interesting ways you can use magic to pleasure yourself... Perhaps I should've brought it. No way I'm bringing &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; to the common room, though.</state>
                <state img="#-sparks1.png">P-Perhaps I needed this. I usually don't do this unless I'm &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; pent up.</state>
                <state img="#-enjoy3.png">This isn't half bad...</state>
                <state img="#-enjoy2.png">Oh yesss...</state>
                <state img="#-sparks2.png">T-This feels so dirty! So why am I enjoying &lt;i&gt;this?&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-interest.png">Perhaps I should try different variations instead of keeping it in like this.</state>
                <state img="#-enjoy2.png">The less I think... the better. I just need to focus on the sensations I'm feeling...</state>
                <state img="#-enjoy1.png">Ah... So glad I brought this toy.</state>
                <state img="#-enjoy3.png">Perhaps I should play with the settings.</state>
                <state img="#-enjoy2.png">I feel strangely vulnerable playing with myself in front of you.</state>
                <state img="#-sparks2.png">Oh Merlin...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="heavy_masturbating">
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-sparks1.png">Mmm... I can't even &lt;i&gt;think&lt;/i&gt; right now.</state>
                <state img="#-sparks2.png">Oh gosh... Oh &lt;i&gt;gosh!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-sparks1.png">I-I'm not going to last much longer! </state>
                <state img="#-sparks2.png">Yes! Yes, yes, &lt;i&gt;yes!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finishing_masturbating">
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-xxfinish.png">&lt;i&gt;Yeeeeeees!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-xxfinish.png">Oh Merlin, &lt;i&gt;yes!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-aaDonRobe.png">Whew! That was oddly refreshing. If you don't mind, I think I'll don my robes again. I already showed you everything, after all.</state>
                <state img="#-aaDonRobe.png">Oooh, that felt &lt;i&gt;good.&lt;/i&gt; Perhaps I should do this more often?</state>
                <state img="#-aaDonRobe.png">Haaaah... I almost forgot how good an orgasm feels.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="after_masturbating">
            <case stage="10" oneShotId="17">
                <condition role="other" character="n" stage="9-10" />
                <state img="#-eyeroll.png" marker="N_bothlost">I suppose our intellect did not really assist us this game, hm, N?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10" oneShotId="35">
                <condition role="other" character="nagisa" saidMarker="nagisa_hermione_bread_trivia" />
                <condition status="alive" />
                <state img="#-eyeroll.png" marker="nagisa_hermione_bread_triviar">Er... I don't know if you were &lt;i&gt;actually&lt;/i&gt; listening to me. But fine. Did you know that the people who built the Pyramids were paid in bread?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <condition status="alive" />
                <state img="#-deer.png">Would you still like some tips? Just because I haven't won doesn't mean I shouldn't discourage you.</state>
                <state img="#-interest.png">I admit, I'm still a little bitter about losing. But the forfeit was, well, it wasn't really a &lt;i&gt;punishment&lt;/i&gt;, was it?</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">I guess this makes me a spectator now! This isn't a tournament, but still, I've never been a spectator to a game like this before!</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">I hope you're keeping my advice in mind, although now may be the time to do some riskier plays. The fewer opponents still in the game, the greater your chances of losing are.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_victory">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-pride.png">Now, &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; is why you study and prepare. Good game, everyone.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7">
                <state img="#-deer.png">Close game which shows how important preparation can be! Oh, uh, I'm still undressed, aren't I? Erm, I'm going to put on my clothes now...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-unamused.png">A flawless victory. Were you all even trying?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-excited.png">That was so close! My heart is racing! Good game, everyone!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_defeat">
            <case stage="10">
                <condition role="winner" layers="0-2" />
                <test expr="~self.place~" value="2" />
                <state img="#-think.png">I was so close to winning... Where did I mess up? Should I have not played that hand, or was I simply unlucky? Hmm....</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <test expr="~self.revplace~" value="1" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">To think I spent all that time reading about poker, only to get in last place. Is my luck really so bad?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="10">
                <state img="#-pride.png">I don't think I got to show off &lt;i&gt;all&lt;/i&gt; my poker knowledge. And I don't want to put all that time I spent learning to waste. How about a rematch?</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">I suppose natural skill bests knowledge in these scenarios. Regardless, I'd love a rematch.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

    </behaviour>
</opponent>
